-Who is it?
-Fantasia.
Hey, girl.
-I thought you were going to Star City.
-I am tonight.
You think you're bad with that camera.
Come on.
You're ruining the shot
with your lousy dancing.
Bobby, look who's here.
-How you doing?
-Fine.
-Is Ray with you?
-No.
-That's good.
-That's real good.
You know you're always welcome here.
You got here just in time.
Bobby's about to blow out
the candles on his birthday cake.
It's your birthday? How old are you, 60?
That's your IQ, woman.
This is Darren and Danielle.
I left my purse in the car. I'll be right back.
What are you guys doing?
Everybody get on the floor and be quiet.
-What the fuck?
-Get on the floor, goddamn it!
Let go, Ray.
Down.
Fantasia!
Be quiet and everything will be okay.
-Where does Marco live?
-I don't know.
-I said, where does he live?
-Where, goddamn it?
-I don't know!
How do you get your shit?
Does it fly over here?
-Ray, please.
-You don't know nothing about this.
If we tell anybody where Marco lives,
he'll kill us.
What do you think we're going to do?
Tell me or I'll slap your head off.
Leave us alone!
You don't have to hit her like that.
Tell him and everything will be okay.
Jackie don't know where Marco's staying.
I deal with him, she don't.
Leave her alone and I'll tell you.
Who is it?
It's Bobby, Marco.
I've got to get something from you.
-I told you not to come so late.
-Come on, man.
I got to get something tonight.
Come on in here, man.
This is a pretty woman you got here.
Look at those titties. I like those.
Ray, what are you doing?
-Hey, man!
-I want some of this.
What you want is on that table.
I got $200 in my wallet. Take it.
-I ain't fucking around.
-Take the money and the coke.
-This is lighter fluid.
-You're sick.
I'll fuck her up.
I don't want your little $200.
Fuck you. I don't want your $200.
Stop it!
-Then you got the money?
-Put it out!
-I'll light her up! Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Motherfucker!
Goddamn.
Got it?
They got a fucking kid.
Goddamn it, you motherfucker.
Where's your goddamn kid?
Go look for the kid.
We can't leave him here.
I've been all over the house.
I don't give a shit! Go look for him.
He might be hiding.
Mommyl Mommyl
Honey, what's wrong? What is it, baby?
It's okay, Daddy's here.
She had a bad dream.
You okay? I'll take her in our room.
Are you okay?
Dale, are you coming to bed?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Good. Come on, Dud,
let's get to the wallets.
Watch your feet.
I need a name.
Let's do this body first.
I think this is our stranger.
Who do we got?
John, meet Robert Prost.
How do you do, Robert?
Watch your feet.
We're out of here.
-Isn't that a light in Robert's window?
-Yeah. At 10:00 in the morning.
Shit!
John!
Anything on that tape?
Some background voices.
You?
Nothing.
How did you ID this Ray Malcolm?
A neighbour recognised
Ray's car parked out front.
Did they see him?
She did see a black guy with glasses
come out, get in Ray's car and split.
Didn't know Ray's last name. Said he was
staying with some dopers. We checked.
You separated it?
Not yet. Is that Ray's package?
So who's this black guy?
They call him Pluto.
He's been hanging with Ray
the last couple of weeks.
I'd say he's from out of town.
Pluto? That's it?
For now.
Who's the girl?
-Fantasia.
-Bullshit.
Good-looking. Ray's old lady.
Listen to this.
Hey, girl. I thoughtyou were going
to Star City tonight.
Bobby, look who's here.
Sounds like she said,
"I thought you're going to...." what?
It sounds like,
"I thought you were going to Star City."
Then the other girl says something.
Play it again.
Hey, girl.
-I thoughtyou were going to Star City.
-I am tonight.
It is Star City.
"I thought you were going to Star City."
Dud, check this out.
A robbery arrest from '79.
In case of emergency, notify....
"Jeremiah Malcolm. Relationship: Uncle.
"Star City, Arkansas." I'll be damned.
Jimmy, are you there?
Yeah, Dale. Come on back.
I went to the courthouse
and checked the records on Ray Malcolm.
He was born here,
but hasn't lived here in 20 years.
I'm heading to the uncle's place now.
Do me a favour. Call Charlie,
tell him to come to work early tonight.
I'm staying out there
in case those folks show up.
If they do, we're going to be
laying for them.
This could be a big one.
I'll talk to you later. 10-4.
10-4 and out.
Just give their names,
Ray Malcolm and Pluto Franklin.
Give a description of the girl.
Say the victims were stabbed to death.
How many stab wounds?
Don't mention that.
Or the hog-tying and pillowcases.
-And the other three?
-Say they were strangled.
What about the kid?
Don't mention the kid.
Just say there was a survivor.
And that we think the suspects fled
the state. We might get national coverage.
You got to give me something.
The press is all over my butt.
-Say they're as violent as we've seen.
-Really?
Thank you.
What's the story on this Star City thing?
Somebody, come on. Dud.
Would it be a wild goose chase
if you went there?
We've been lucky so far.
And we can tie Ray there.
I talked to the police chief.
He didn't know of Ray or Fantasia...
...but he's gonna check the uncle out.
I'm waiting for his call.
What about an ID on the second suspect?
Pluto. His real name is Lenny Franklin.
He's originally from Chicago.
He and Ray got busted
about six years ago...
...for another drug rip off. Same shit.
They did two years together
in San Quentin.
Prison buddies.
Pluto's a piece of work.
IQ of 150 and a college graduate.
We think he did the stabbings.
His package indicates
he's very fond of a knife.
He has three priors.
For some reason,
he left the videotape playing.
Sick son of a bitch.
There were no prints,
so he left a calling card.
He's here.
Cole here.
Put him through.
Chief Dixon, this is Dud--
I'm fine, thank--
Put him on the box.
What did you say his name was?
Chief Dale Dixon. Chief,
I'm putting you on the speaker phone.
Chief Jenkins is here.
Los Angeles Chief of Police, Jenkins?
No shit. It's a pleasure to meetyou.
Good to meet you.
-Now what we want to talk about--
-Guess you're pretty busy out there.
-Sure.
-I'll bet.
You gotsix people dead out there
at the same time.
That don't happen much here.
Sometimes we get a stabbing.
Coloured boys, generally.
Every other Saturday night...
...one of them sticks another one
over a card game.
-We should discuss the--
-Craps sometimes.
Now you wanted to know about
this boy's uncle. I think we hit thejackpot.
I went to the uncle's place.
It's the damnedest hideout I've ever seen.
It's in the woods,
about six miles northeast of town.
The only way there is over an old,
rickety bridge.
You'd never find it
if you didn't know where to look.
You city boys would be lost in ten minutes.
But I'm ready, don't worry.
Damn, Bonnie.
-Excuse me?
-Nothing.
They were out of onion rings,
so I gotyou Tasty Taters.
It's L.A., Cheryl Ann, and Chief Jenkins.
Yes, sir.
So you think this is a promising avenue
of investigation?
It's promising all right. Me and
my deputies can set up a surveillance now.
Chief Dixon, why don't we hold off on that
until we get a game plan.
Ifyou say so.
That would be best.
It's my job. We'll get the sons of bitches.
I'll be waiting on you.
What are you two doing here?
When did you get back?
-Wednesday night.
-Wednesday night?
That's no honeymoon.
You should have stayed longer.
Earl had to get back to work
and I'm starting a new job next week.
What are you going to be doing?
Bookkeeping at the Rice Mill.
Muriel retired...
...so I talked to Old Man Hosey
and he hired me.
Take it easy.
Dale?
Well, that's good. Congratulations.
-Thank you, Dale.
-We better be going.
You want some of this?
Why don't you put some clothes on?
I told you to put some clothes on.
Ray, those people are dead.
Those people are dead.
No shit.
And you were there.
Don't forget that.
Didn't I tell you
to put some goddamn clothes on?
We got enough of this shit
to last us until 1995.
We got enough to last
until we get to Houston.
We're not selling all this shit.
We're selling it to Billy in Houston.
I'm going back to Chicago.
I don't give a fuck what you do.
Riding up and down the road
don't make sense.
What do you think will happen?
Are we going to get in trouble?
I was planning to sell some to
them country sons of bitches in Arkansas.
Man, I don't like this Arkansas shit.
We'll be in and out. Don't worry.
We're not building a house.
It's not a problem.
What are you worried about?
What the fuck do you think?
I don't get you.
Why don't you loosen up
and have some fun?
Why don't you get high with Ray and me?
Don't you want to feel good?
This is the biggest thing
that ever happened to us.
And you're just sitting there
like a little brown turd.
Goddamn it!
Watch yourself, Ray.
Listen up, motherfucker. Listen up!
This is what will happen.
We will go to Houston and sell the shit...
...because this little $15,000 won't last.
Until then, I will hold onto the blow.
And Ray, I don't want to hear
any more bullshit out of you...
...or her.
You son of a bitch!
Fucking son of a bitch!
Why don't you just go to sleep, fucker?
You forgot just one fucking thing.
You forgot about the money.
I have all the goddamn money.
You keep that little $15,000, Ray.
He's right, baby.
We should sell the stuff in Houston.
Think of all the money.
We'll be okay.
Pluto knows people in Chicago.
We can live off that money for a long time.
Come on, baby, it's going to be okay.
We can buy all the blow we want
when we get there.
We'll be safe.
Pluto will take care of us.
We'll be safe, baby.
This is really beautiful.
It's as green as hell.
You know I'm a country boy.
That's crap. You were born in L.A.
Malibu.
What the fuck?
Howdy.
Welcome to Star City. We've got
a full day, so follow me to the motel...
...you can unpack
and we'll get something to eat.
When I saw you drive by,
I knew you were the boys from California.
Cops look the same everywhere, I guess.
Follow me.
Oh, shit.
You boys are in for a treat.
Fern, can we get some more biscuits?
-Sure, Hurricane.
-And more coffee.
Hurricane?
Some folks call me that.
I never figured out why.
We can wait in the woods.
When the bad folks show up...
...we'll put the stopper in the bottle.
They'll be sorry they ever heard
of Star City.
This is good.
My mother used to make food like this.
Thanks. How's Walter?
He had gallbladder surgery.
Good for him. I'll be giving you boys
my full cooperation.
Me and my two deputies...
...will take turns watching the place
around the clock.
So you boys can just relax, drink beer,
chase chicks, and whatever.
We'll help.
-We'll help you.
-Suit yourself.
Another thing. Old Man Malcolm...
...l guarantee he don't know jack-shit
about what his nephew did.
Did you talk to him?
Not yet. I just know. There aren't even
any telephone lines up there.
He's a hermit.
Hardly ever leaves his property.
I think we ought to talk to him
and let him know.
-That may be the case, but--
-Charlie! Get on in here.
This is my deputy. Retired police officer.
Charlie, this is Dud Cole.
And this is Dan Macintosh.
John. John McFeely.
Oh, right. All them Mac names
sound alike to me.
-You eaten, Charlie?
-Yeah, Jocelyn fixed me--
Charlie's a Yankee from Detroit.
Dale, if we talk to this guy
and he's involved--
-I told you he's not.
-Hurricane. I mean, Dale.
These are dangerous people.
I understand that.
You boys about ready?
Just a second.
Here, Fern.
Keep the change.
There is no change, Hurricane.
It's a $12 check...
...and you gave me a ten!
Catch you later.
Is he gone?
I haven't had a full meal
since I met the son of a bitch.
Go ahead, Jimmy.
It's Harlan Childress. Lureen called.
He's raising hell.
I'm on a case here. Unless he's trying
to kill her, I don't have time.
She said he's trying to kill her.
I'mjustletting you know.
Okay, 10-4.
Hop in. We have to make a little stop
before we go to the Malcolm place.
Open this door!
Goddamn it! Lureen!
Harlan! Goddamn it.
-Settle down, Harlan!
-Let go!
Harlan, goddamn it!
You calm down now. Calm down.
Do you want to take a ride with me?
-Settle down.
-He was out all night drinking.
Who are those men?
It's okay.
She locked me out of the kitchen.
I understand.
You were out all night drinking.
You knew she was going to do this,
didn't you?
If you apologise, she may let you in.
He knows I will.
We'll go to church, he'll feel better.
All right, Lureen.
-You won't let them take him away?
-They're with me. They're from L.A.
Get up. Pull yourself together, okay?
Come on.
Come on. Get up.
Now come here.
Do me a favour.
Put this axe back in the shed.
All right?
I don't want to have to come back
out here. Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Put that axe in the shed.
And fix this window.
-Tell Cheryl Ann and the baby I said hi.
-Tell them hi.
-Sorry about the window.
-That's okay.
It's okay, boys. I'm out here twice a week.
Motherfucker!
Goddamn it! They know me now.
Are you aware of that, bitch?
They know my face, my name,
probably how long my dick is!
A goddamn kid! Why didn't you tell me
about that fucking kid?
I swear to God, I didn't see any kid!
He must have been hiding.
Quit lying!
Don't hit me no more.
Pluto, don't let him hit me no more.
Get rid of her, Ray.
We'll be okay.
-Shut up.
-We'll dump the car. They won't find us.
They won't find you maybe!
They won't find us!
-It'll be okay.
-Get your hand off of me.
We'll be okay.
Isn't there another way, Dale?
Watch your step. The timbers are rotten.
Yeah, rotten.
I crashed my motorcycle
on this bridge when I was 14.
The volunteer fire department
had to put it out.
You can still see some of the burn marks.
Perfect hideout.
-Is the old man there?
-Yeah.
-I wonder who else is there.
-He's by himself.
Dale, wait a minute.
It's okay, boys. Come on.
How you doing?
You okay?
-I said, "You okay?"
-I'm doing okay.
That's good.
I'm Chief Dixon.
I'm fixing to do what?
I'm fixing to feed the chickens
before it gets too damn hot.
Have you heard from your nephew lately?
Have you heard from Ray Malcolm?
He's my brother's boy.
I heard of my own kin.
Has he talked to you lately?
When was the last time you talked to him?
-Talked to who?
-Ray Malcolm.
Ray is my brother's boy.
I got to finish feeding these chickens.
It gets hot around here at noontime.
I hope you and them chickens
have a goddamn heatstroke.
Can I help you boys?
"I'm fixing to feed these chickens."
I say, "Have you heard from Ray Malcolm?"
Put that on Daddy's plate, sweetheart.
He says, "Ray Malcolm is my nephew.
"My brother's boy.
I guess I heard of my own kin."
So I said, "Have you spoken to him?"
He said, "Who?"
I said, "Ray Malcolm."
He said, "Ray's my brother's boy."
Imagine the conversation
when Ray shows up.
Rolls?
Is this great or what?
This is great, Cheryl Ann.
There you go.
I hope he does show up.
'Cause I got news for you.
That white trash and
those two niggers are in for--
Cheryl Ann, you nearly broke my--
Bonnie, pass me the pickles.
I never got any beans. May I have some?
Did you think I was going to cut you?
I wouldn't hurt you
for anything in the world.
I'm glad you didn't kill that man
in the car lot.
What do you think we are?
That don't mean nothing, Dale.
What concerns me is that we left ourselves
so goddamn exposed.
So out there.
Anybody could tell
the man wasn't involved.
You can't assume anything about anybody.
That's the guy who will fuck you.
Shit. I've been police chief here for...
...hell, going on six years.
I've never even had to draw my gun.
Come kiss your favourite mommy.
Get in the bed.
Get in there.
-See you in the morning.
-Goodnight, Mommy.
Enjoying yourself?
Getting enough to eat and drink?
Just about.
Isn't that your second bottle?
Yes, it is.
I want to apologise
for that last comment before.
I bet John feels terrible.
Dale didn't mean it.
He just grew up talking that way.
I understand.
I'm sure John does, too.
These people are dangerous, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
I've never seen Dale this excited before.
This case is the biggest thing
that's ever happened to him.
He really likes you and John. I can tell.
I think he looks at you like you're heroes.
Well, we're far from that.
You might want to tell him that.
I have a little girl who needs her daddy.
Dale doesn't know any better.
He watches TV. I read non-fiction.
We better head back.
No, come on guys, the night is young.
-Who wants cookies?
-We all do.
-Very serious meal.
-They're in here.
-I got to go pee.
-Pee off the porch.
Like shit.
You know, Dale...
...this case is our problem.
What I'm saying is,
you can be as involved or...
...uninvolved in the apprehension
of these guys as we want.
Assuming they show up.
If they do, I'll be there.
You got a nice spot here.
Nice house, nice family.
You're a lucky guy.
I guess I am a lucky guy at that.
I hardly ever lose a coin toss.
I go to the horse races,
bet a long shot and it always comes in.
My mama used to say
I was born under a lucky star.
Here's an article about Julia
from Dark Memories.
That ain't Julia.
That's that damn twin sister.
No, it's not.
Ma'am, can you tell him who this is?
That's Julia on Dark Memories.
I told you. You got any maps of Houston?
We don't need no map of Houston.
Be cool.
How are you, Bill?
It's real quiet out there.
I think we got
the two most exciting jobs in town.
Your other burrito is ready.
He's watching me. He knows who I am.
-No, he doesn't.
-He does.
Baby, let's go.
Back up. Just back up.
Ray, stop it. Stop it.
Shit.
I'd never get up on a horse.
-Get your hand off me.
-Let's go.
Let's go, okay?
Don't fuck up, man.
-Will that be all?
-That's it.
Hope you don't mind
that we opened things up.
As long as you pay for it.
You going to drink that beer and drive?
No, we wouldn't do that. This is for later.
Just kidding.
$7.95, please.
-Have a nice night.
-You, too.
She's too young for you, Bill.
I like them young.
Shit! That trooper is behind us.
Don't look back.
Just be cool.
What if he pulls us over?
He won't.
Slow down, Ray. Don't panic.
He recognised me back there. I know it.
If he had, he would have arrested you
in the store.
He's just looking us over.
A white boy and a nigger girl in Texas.
That's all it is.
He's probably running our plates.
542.
Go ahead.
On your out-of-state plate, New Mexico
licence number Nora-Edward-2-4-5...
...the vehicle is recently purchased.
There are no warrants.
No current registration available.
10-4. Could you check the teletype board
for the past few days?
I seem to recall a teletype from California...
...of a male and female black...
...and a male white,
wanted for a couple of murders.
Speed up, Ray.
You'll make him suspicious.
Speed up, slow down.
Make up your fucking mind.
Did you find that teletype?
Still looking, 542.
10-4.
542.
I'm going to pull them over.
Fuck!
What do we do?
-I'll blow his goddamn head off.
-Pull over.
We're going to be cool and play it by ear.
We won't kill him unless we have to.
We're not going to be stupid.
Could I see your licence and registration?
Hi, it's you again.
You have a California licence
and New Mexico plates and registration.
We had California plates...
...but our car broke down in New Mexico
and we got a new one.
Told you we wouldn't make it.
He wouldn't listen to me.
This one will make it.
Make it where?
Philadelphia. My mother lives there.
She's sick.
Ray's my boyfriend,
so he got the job of taking me there.
Richard's our friend.
He's just along for the ride.
Were we speeding or something?
No, ma'am.
Then why the fuck did you pull us over?
I want you to get out of the car,
one at a time.
You first, ma'am.
Get your hands up!
Calm down. You said, "Get out.
You first, man," right?
Step to the rear of the car
and keep your hands visible.
You said, "Get out of the car,"
that's all I'm doing.
What's wrong with you?
Do what he says.
Stay where you are, ma'am.
Put your hands on the car.
Spread them out.
Now spread your legs.
Same thing, hands on the car.
Spread your legs.
Okay, ma'am, come back here.
-Why don't you tell us what we did--
-Keep your hands on the car!
Okay, ma'am--
Goddamn! Yes, baby! Yes!
You motherfucker!
Let's go! Get her in the car.
Come on! Now!
You motherfucker!
Pluto, we're going the wrong way.
We're going back to town. Turn around.
-Ray, did I kill that man?
-Yes, but you did a good job.
What the fuck are you doing?
You're going the wrong way!
The car's been identified.
We have to get rid of it.
Yes, you killed him, goddamn it.
Would you fucking turn the car around?
We're going the wrong way!
We'll pass the motherfuckers, got it?
-The cops will see us.
-We got no fucking choice.
If we head out of town, they'll catch us.
So shut up.
-How are you?
-I got a hangover, but--
Nothing here. Quiet as a Sunday morning.
When did you arrive?
I relieved Charlie around 4:00.
You want some coffee?
-No thanks.
-No.
I was thinking about
what you said last night.
-No wonder you were pissed off.
-I wasn't.
No, you were right.
If that old man hadn't been deaf,
I could have blown the case.
Well, I don't know.
No, I made a mistake.
You know more about this stuff than I do.
I don't want you thinking
we're incompetent.
Dale, you have the energy
and dedication of ten cops.
No shit?
Let me ask you something else.
If I'm full of shit, you just tell me.
I want to move to L.A. and join up.
Join up with what?
The police department. I've been
on the force here since I was grown.
After ten years of busting peeping Toms,
I'd like to take a crack at the big time.
I realise getting on the force
is no walk in the park, but...
...once we wrap up this case
and with your recommendation...
...well, who knows?
You, me and Macintosh
could make a great team.
That's an interesting idea.
How you doing, Hurricane?
This is Larry Gibson, our local Smokey.
Larry, this is Dud Cole. He's from L.A.
Last night, some folks killed
a Texas State Trooper.
It says here they may
be headed for Houston.
They may fit the description
of the folks you're after.
Son of a bitch.
We may even have a photograph of them
in a convenience store.
-Surveillance camera?
-Yeah.
Texas.
Looks like they're headed our way, boys.
Got another cup?
-You don't mind drinking after me?
-Not at all.
Goddamn. Texas.
Do you think our people
whacked that trooper?
We'll know when we see the photo.
Hurricane is waiting on the bad guys
the way a kid waits for Christmas.
Hurricane is a force of nature.
I like old Hurricane.
He's a tremendous guy.
-You know what he told me this morning?
-What?
He wants to come to L.A.
and join the force.
-Are you kidding?
-Honest to God.
He said he thought that me and him
and Macintosh would make a great team.
No shit.
He said he wanted a crack at the big time.
What did you say?
I told him it was an interesting idea.
That's the funniest thing I ever heard.
Can you imagine that motherfucker
roaming around Parker Centre?
He'd "put a stopper in the bottle."
That yokel would last ten minutes.
"Put a stopper in the bottle."
Hurricane, you know
no one's allowed back there.
-Just getting a candy bar.
-You plan to pay for it this time?
I saw your car parked out front.
Charlie relieved me a half hour ago.
Dud, I didn't mean to put you
on the spot this morning.
Dale, we didn't mean--
That's me.
This is 210.
Ijust got back from Little Rock
with thatpicture.
10-4. That's us.
You leave it.
Jimmy, you got it?
That's Ray.
And so that must be
our mystery girl, Fantasia.
Her name's not Fantasia.
It's Lila Walker.
Hey, Pluto.
What's happening?
How are you, Beaver?
They're cool.
Come on in.
-Come on in.
-Go ahead.
This is Fantasia. That's Ray.
That's Joey.
And the whining one on the couch is Kim.
-She had a couple teeth yanked out.
-Fuck you, Beaver.
Grab yourself a chair.
You want to sit down?
That's okay. I'm fine.
So where's this multitude of coke?
-Where's Billy?
-He ain't here.
I can see that. Where is he?
He's still in New Orleans.
New Orleans?
When will he be here?
Tomorrow night.
He didn't tell me that when we spoke.
He got hung up.
He didn't know that would happen
when he spoke to you.
We'll wait for him.
We can't wait. We have to go.
We'll wait until tomorrow.
We'll stay here.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
We don't have much room, and....
Yeah, what the fuck, man.
You can have my room.
I've slept on the couch before.
Fuck you, Beaver. I'm not moving.
Give me the phone.
Sometimes I think you haven't got
a brain in your head.
I'm going to Star City.
The only reason I got involved in this shit...
...is so we'd get some money
and I could go home and see my people.
That was before all this shit happened.
Now it's about time we got
where we're going.
So what's the problem?
All you have to do is
pick me up on the way.
You know that Pluto isn't going to do that.
You heard what the man said.
I think it's a good idea.
If she goes ahead of us,
it will be safer to travel.
We won't fit the description so easily.
No problem.
Ain't that some shit.
Can you make it a whole day without me?
I don't know.
It looks like just her brother
and mama are there.
What kind of people are they?
Good people. Christian people.
I can't believe she got mixed up
in this shit.
Hurricane, how is it
that you know this Lila Walker?
I arrested her for shoplifting once.
She was just a kid in high school.
All she took was lipstick
and that shit they put on their eyes.
Wasn't worth ten bucks.
I could tell right off she wasn't bad,
just high-spirited.
So I decided to try to help her out.
You know, talk to her.
Then one day, she just disappeared.
Somebody said...
...she took off for Hollywood
to become a movie star.
Anyway, that was about five years ago.
I didn't hear of her again till now.
She's moved up from stealing lipstick.
I don't believe she killed anyone.
That kid in the closet. She opens the door,
sees him, closes the door.
That proves she's not a killer.
Hurricane, that don't prove shit.
So, do we talk to the mother?
-What if she tips off Lila?
-She won't.
She wouldn't do that, not Lila.
Have you heard from her?
No, I haven't. Not since last summer.
Some time around June or July.
Mr. Dixon, you know Lila. She wouldn't do
what they're saying she did.
She must have been kidnapped.
Brainwashed.
Some of the best policemen in this country
are after Lila and those fellows.
They'll catch them, too.
It will help Lila if she turns herself in.
Chief Dixon is right.
We can't promise anything, but if
she cooperates, that will have weight later.
I haven't heard from her, but if I do,
I'll tell her what you said.
Ronnie, have you heard from your sister?
No, sir.
Would you tell us if you had?
Yes, sir.
Grandma...
...l'm hungry.
Byron, don't bother us now, honey.
Who's that?
That's Lila's boy.
Didn't you know Lila had a boy?
And he's a pretty boy, too.
Thanks for your time.
That's all we need for now.
They're not going to Jeremiah's at all.
No. Fantasia's coming home
to see her kid.
Hurricane, just how well
do you know this gal?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
That's real fucking funny.
Fuck!
Goddamn her.
Look at you. You've gone Hollywood.
Look at you, all grown up.
Stand back. Let me have a look at you.
Yeah, you still ugly.
I'm just playing. You look fine.
I'm feeling fine.
I'm going to see my baby. I'm going home.
You can't go home. The cops are after you.
-What did they say?
-Get in the car.
-I didn't do the things they said.
-I know that.
Being on the run makes you look guilty.
I already look guilty.
Looking guilty is being guilty
for black people.
You know that. I won't get a fair trial...
...and I won't go to prison.
Chief Dixon said that--
-Dale Dixon?
-He's the one who came to the house.
Didn't you used to know him?
Yeah, I used to know him.
Ron, I didn't come all this way
not to see my baby.
They'll be watching our house...
...so you have to take me someplace
outside of town.
Then tonight you bring my baby
out to see me.
Then tomorrow I'll be gone.
Ronnie, please.
I'm your sister. I need your help.
Okay, Lila.
A friend of mine's grandma died
a couple of months ago.
She had a house off the highway
past the bait shop.
No one's living there now.
I'll be out there all night, so don't wait up.
Are Dud and John going to be with you?
No, they're not.
We don't need 19 goddamn people
to watch a house.
I know you're capable of--
Just because I'm not from L.A.,
don't mean I can't watch a house.
Okay?
I love you. You know that, don't you?
I know that.
And I love our little girl
more than anything.
I know that, too.
I would give you every dime
we talked about if I had the money.
The problem is, I don't have it.
Your partner's making me nervous.
Sit your ass down, ponytail.
I know you guys are on the run.
You need everything you can get.
It's better than nothing, right?
Let's lighten up.
This town is hot, and so are you.
You're on every goddamn channel.
You got no one else you can trust but me.
I'm going to let you walk with one.
You can take it or leave it.
Fucker.
Eight fucking dollars. Who cares?
He has to have more money than that.
Let's go.
Pull over. We're splitting up.
What are you talking about?
Pull over. Everything's fucked up.
We'll split the money and the coke,
then I'm gone.
I ain't doing that.
Don't fuck with me.
Just give me my money.
I can't do that. I don't have any money.
Say what?
I don't have any money.
Where's my money?
I ain't got it. She took the fucking money.
I got $56. She took it.
Now let go before I have a wreck.
You're a pussy-whipped fucker.
Don't give me that shit. It was your
fucking buddies who had no money.
Your good friend, Billy.
What the fuck am I doing with you?
You're a pussy-whipped motherfucker!
If you want any money,
you'll have to go to Arkansas.
Lila, we got to go.
Just give me a few minutes with him.
It's almost 4:00 in the morning.
It's time for you to go home, go to bed
and get up and see your grandma.
I love you, honey. Will you be a good boy?
Give me a kiss good-bye.
Come on, Lila.
Take care of my baby, okay?
Will you be all right?
Ronnie, put the money in the bank, okay?
-How you doing?
-Stop right there.
Turn around.
Put your hands on the counter.
Spread your legs.
Simon says.
Can I turn around now?
Just stay like that.
Where are your two pals?
Ray and Pluto?
They'll be here soon.
How soon is that?
I don't know.
They have to call first.
How do I know you're not lying?
They might show up here any minute.
I'm not lying to you, Dale.
What will you do with me?
Get in the other room. Go on.
Go into the living room.
-What are you doing?
-Sit down.
What are you doing?
Two fellows from L.A. want to meet you.
-Put the phone down.
-Why?
Ray and Pluto will call here
to see if everything is cool.
I won't answer the phone
if you call those cops.
Yes, you are.
Goddamn it!
Lila, even if I wanted to, I can't help you.
I don't have the legal authority.
You didn't have the authority
to fuck me when I was 17...
...but that didn't stop you.
That's right.
Instead of spying on me, why didn't
you come in and say hello to your son?
He's not my kid.
Not your kid?
He's nearly as white as you are.
That proves nothing.
Are you calling me a whore?
I was a virgin when we met
and you know it.
Hear the whippoorwill?
Remember what you said
about hearing a whippoorwill?
It means someone's going to die.
Why do we have to sit here in the dark?
I don't want to be a sitting duck
if they show up.
I told you,
they won't be here until they call.
Where you going?
-My cigarettes are in my purse.
-Get one of mine.
-I smoke menthol.
-I'll get them.
I forgot that thing was even in there.
Ray gave it to me for protection.
-I don't even know how it works.
-You pull the damn trigger.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Did you think I would shoot you?
That's crazy.
Now can I have my cigarettes, please?
You have a light, baby?
Does your wife treat you right?
Yes, Lila, she does.
That's good.
What's her name again? Thelma Lou?
Cheryl Ann.
That's right.
And you and Cheryl Ann have a little girl.
What's her name?
Bonnie.
How old is she?
Eight.
You don't like telling me
about your family, do you?
No, I guess I don't.
I don't blame you.
-I got something for you.
-Where are you going?
Don't shoot me, officer.
What the hell are you doing now?
-Can I turn on the light?
-No.
I put it in here to keep it fresh.
Can we leave this open to get some light?
This is our baby's birthday cake.
I don't want any.
Suit yourself.
It's good.
You should try some.
Today's his birthday?
No. It was in September.
I missed it.
I left him with Mama
before he was two years old.
That means I've missed four birthdays...
...so we celebrated all four of them
last night.
Does your mama know about....
Know what?
No, I never told her.
I never meant you any trouble, Dale.
I still don't.
Wouldn't Bonnie be surprised to know
she had a half-brother in Nigger Town?
You should have some of our baby's cake--
Quit calling him that.
Why? That's what he is.
Damn it, I told you I didn't want any.
-Do you want this?
-What are you doing?
-This is what you want.
-Cut it out.
Cut it out, goddamn it!
Why did you ever fuck with me?
Me and my brother's daddy was white,
did you know that?
Of course, we never knew him.
He had another family.
That's why I kind of look white.
Because my daddy was white.
You figured since I kind of look white,
you could fuck me, what the hell.
Because I was kind of black...
...you could dump me, what the hell.
211 to 210.
Dale, where are you at?
Hey, June.
Juney! How are you doing?
You got something for me?
Hi, Mr. Charlie.
Is this Ronnie? Ronnie, this is Ray.
Is Fantasia there?
Yeah, Lila.
Where is she?
Have you got a number out there for her?
Give it to me, all right?
Ronnie! Ronnie, come here.
-Come here.
-I got to go.
If you know something about
Lila being here, you tell these gentlemen.
I don't want you being in trouble.
No, ma'am.
I don't know nothing about that.
June Hawkins told me
he was out last night digging frogs.
Driving back, he saw you driving
in front of him with Byron in the car.
Where had you and Byron been
at 4:00 a.m.?
We've been here all night.
June's mixed up. He's old.
He don't see so well.
-I'll make the bastard talk!
-He won't talk. It's his sister.
Can I speak to the boy?
-How are you this morning?
-Fine.
-Pretty sleepy?
-I guess so.
-You go out with Uncle Ronnie last night?
-No.
You sure?
-You didn't see a pretty lady?
-No.
You sure?
-Did Uncle Ronnie tell you to say that?
-Yeah.
So this has just been pretend?
What do you say we stop playing pretend
and play really?
And you really should spend a night in jail.
So you can tell your sister.
You got to let me go.
I can't do that, Lila.
You can't let them put me in jail.
What's going to happen
to our baby with me in jail?
Your mom will keep taking care of him.
I'll give her money for him.
Why won't you give him the money?
Why don't you just say,
"Byron, I'm your daddy"?
I don't see how that would....
I guess it wouldn't be a good idea.
I guess it would be better
just to put me in jail...
...and forget about your five-year-old son.
Hi, baby.
Yeah, everything's cool.
Everything's real cool.
Ray, where are you calling from?
What's the name of the gas station?
Ray, you missed the turnoff.
It's about half a mile back up the highway.
You turn right at this place
called Cothern's Bait Shop.
There's a little road there.
You're not far, baby.
Just about ten minutes away. Hurry.
Yeah, I miss you.
Is that the road, Byron?
-I don't think so.
-You don't think so?
When they arrive, get them in the house
and away from the car.
Open the door, talk to them.
Let them see everything is okay.
Then stay in the kitchen
until I say to come out.
Then if they get trigger-happy,
you'll be out of the line of fire.
Then you'll let me go?
I'll let you go.
Is that the road you took?
Don't go in there fucking around.
In and out. You got me?
What do you think I'd do? Don't worry.
You sure this is it?
Yeah.
You got it straight?
Hi, baby.
Come on, Fantasia, let's go.
It'll be a few minutes.
I have to pack my stuff.
What stuff? All you had was your purse.
It won't be long. Come on in.
Shit!
I'll be back.
That's bullshit. I'm sticking on your ass.
She better not have bought any clothes.
What does she have to pack?
-Come on.
-Be careful. I love you.
Did you spend any of my money?
Fantasia? Where did she go?
Police officers, freeze!
Hands up or I'll blow you to fucking hell!
-What the fuck?
-Get on the floor! Now!
Who the fuck are you?
-You bitch!
-Shut up! Shut up!
-Why the fuck did you do this?
-I'm sorry.
Stay back!
210.
210, A-1 channel 1. Come in, goddamn it.
Hurry up.
Hurricane, where the hell have you been?
I need help out here.
What's your 10-20?
Oh, God.
Dale, what's your 20? Where are you?
I'm off the highway,
two miles down Sulphur Springs road.
There's a house.
In the woods, there's this house--
Is there an address?
I don't know the goddamn address.
Just send some help. And an ambulance.
I got three suspects down
and I'm hurtpretty bad.
-Three suspects down.
-You know Sulphur Springs Road?
Hold on, Byron.
Charlie, do something.
Dud, come on! Charlie's taking care of it.
Come on!
That son of a bitch nailed them.
Hey, man.
The ambulance is on the way.
I'll get you some blankets, okay?
Are you dead, mister?
-No, not quite.
-Where's the lady at?
She's over there.
Don't go away. Come back.
Come stay with me.
-Stay here with me.
-How did you get blood on yourself?
I got in a fight.
What do you do with your keys?
I lock things up.
Come here. I can't see your face.
Come a little closer.
Your name...
...is Byron.
You're five years old.
Four or five?
Five.
Just come sit with me.