They may fit the description
of the folks you're after.
Son of a bitch.
They got a photograph of them
in a convenience store.
- Surveillance camera?
- Yeah.
Texas.
Looks like they're headed
our way, boys. Let's go.
Got another cup?
- You don't mind drinking after me?
- Not at all.
Goddamn. Texas.
Think our people whacked that trooper?
We'll know when we see the photo.
Hurricane is waiting on the bad guys
the way a kid waits for Christmas.
Hurricane is a force of nature.
I like old Hurricane.
He's a tremendous guy.
Guess what he told me?
He wants to come to L.A.
And join the force.
- You're kidding.
- Honest to God.
He said he thought
that me and him and...
"Macintosh" would make a great team.
No shit.
He said he wanted a crack
at the big time.
What did you say?
I told him
it was an interesting idea.
That's the funniest thing
I ever heard.
Can you imagine that motherfucker
roaming around Parker Center?
He'll put a stopper in the bottle.
That yokel won't last ten minutes.
Put a stopper in the bottle.
Hurricane, you know
no one's allowed back there.
- Just getting a candy bar.
- You gonna pay for it this time?
I saw your car parked out front.
Charlie relieved me a half hour ago.
Sorry I put you on the spot, Dud.
Dale, we didn't mean...
Oh, that's me.
This is 210.
I just got back from Little Rock
with that picture.
10-4. That's us.
You leave it.
Jimmy, you got it?
That's Ray.
And so that must be
our mystery girl, Fantasia.
Her name's not Fantasia.
It's Lila Walker.
Hey, Pluto.
What's happening?
How are you, Beaver?
They're cool.
Come on in.
- Come on in.
- Go ahead.
This is Fantasia. That's Ray.
That's Joey.
And the whining one on the couch is Kim.
She had a tooth yanked out.
Fuck you, Beaver.
Grab yourself a chair.
You want to sit down?
That's okay. I'm fine.
So where's this multitude of coke?
- Where's Billy?
- He ain't here.
I can see that. Where is he?
He's still in New Orleans.
New Orleans?
When will he be here?
Tomorrow night.
He didn't tell me that
when we spoke.
He got hung up.
He didn't know that would happen
when he spoke to you.
We'll wait for him.
We can't wait. We have to go.
We'll wait until tomorrow.
We'll stay here.
I don't think
that's such a good idea.
We don't have much room, and...
Yeah, what the fuck, man.
You can have my room.
I've slept on the couch before.
Fuck you, Beaver.
I'm not moving.
Give me the phone.
Sometimes I think you haven't got
a brain in your head.
I'm going to Star City. The only reason
I got involved in this shit...
is so we'd get some money and I
could go home and see my people.
That was before
all this shit happened.
Now we have to get where we're going.
So what's the problem?
All you have to do is...
pick me up on the way.
You know that Pluto isn't going to
do that. You heard what the man said.
I think it's a good idea.
If she goes ahead of us,
it will be safer to travel.
We won't fit the description so easily.
No problem.
Ain't that some shit.
Can you make it a whole day
without me?
I don't know.
It looks like just
her brother and mama are there.
What kind of people are they?
Good people. Christian people.
I can't believe she got mixed up
in this shit.
Hurricane, how is it that
you know this Lila Walker.
I arrested her for shoplifting once.
She was just a kid in high school.
All she took was lipstick
and shit to put on her eyes.
Wasn't worth ten bucks.
I could tell right off she wasn't bad,
just high-spirited.
So I decided to try to help her out.
You know, talk to her.
Then one day, she just disappeared.
Somebody said...
she took off for Hollywood
to become a movie star.
Anyway, that was about five years ago.
I didn't hear of her again till now.
She's moved up from stealing lipstick.
I don't believe she killed anybody.
That kid in the closet. She opens
the door, sees him, closes the door.
That proves she's not a killer.
Hurricane, that don't prove shit.
So, do we talk to the mother?
- What if she tips off Lila?
- She won't.
She wouldn't do that, not Lila.
Have you heard from her?
No, I haven't.
Not since last summer.
Some time around June or July.
Mr. Dixon, you know Lila.
She wouldn't do
what they're saying she did.
She must have been kidnapped.
Brainwashed.
Some of the best policemen
in this country...
are after Lila and those fellows.
They'll catch them, too.
It will help Lila
if she turns herself in.
Chief Dixon is right.
We can't promise anything,
but if she cooperates...
that will be
taken into account later.
I haven't heard from her, but if I do,
I'll tell her what you said.
Ronnie, have you heard
from your sister?
No, sir.
Would you tell us if you had?
Yes, sir.
Grandma...
I'm hungry.
Byron, don't bother us now, honey.
Who's that?
That's Lila's boy.
Didn't you know Lila had a boy?
And he's a pretty boy, too.
Thanks for your time.
That's all we need for now.
They're not going to Jeremiah's at all.
No. Fantasia's coming home
to see her kid.
Hurricane, just how well
do you know this gal?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Ha-ha. That's real fucking funny.
Fuck!
Goddamn her.
Ronnie.
Look at you.
You done gone Hollywood.
Look at you, all grown up.
Stand back.
Let me have a look at you.
Yeah, you still ugly.
I'm just playing. You look fine.
I'm feeling fine.
I'm going to see my baby.
I'm going home.
You can't go home.
The cops are after you.
- What did they say?
- Get in the car.
I didn't do the things
they said I did.
I know that.
Being on the run
makes you look guilty.
I already look guilty.
Looking guilty is being guilty
for black people.
You know that.
I won't get a fair trial...
and I won't go to prison.
Chief Dixon said that...
- Dale Dixon?
- Yeah.
He was the one
who came to the house.
Didn't you used to know him?
Yeah, I used to know him.
Ronnie, I didn't come
all this way not to see my baby.
They'll be watching our house...
so you have to take me someplace
outside of town.
Then tonight you bring my baby
out to see me.
Then tomorrow I'll be gone.
Ronnie, please.
I'm your sister.
I need your help.
Okay, Lila.
A friend of mine's grandma died
a few months ago.
She had a house off the highway
past the bait shop.
No one's living there now.
I'll be out there all night,
so don't wait up.
Are Dud and John
going to be with you?
No, they're not.
We don't need 19 goddamn people
to watch a house.
I know you're capable of...
Just because I'm not from L.A.
Don't mean I can't watch a house.
Okay?
I love you.
You know that, don't you?
I know that.
And I love our little girl
more than anything.
I know that, too.
I would give you every dime
we talked about if I had the money.
The problem is, I don't have it.
Your partner's making me nervous.
Sit your ass down, ponytail.
I know you guys are on the run.
You need everything you can get.
It's better than nothing, right?
Let's lighten up.
This town is hot, and so are you.
You're on every goddamn channel.
You got no on else
you can trust but me.
I'm going to let you walk with one.
You can take it or leave it.
Fucker.
Eight fucking dollars. Who cares?
He has to have more money than that.
Let's go.
Pull over. We're splitting up.
What are you talking about?
Pull over. Everything's fucked up.
We'll split the money and the coke,
then I'm gone.
I ain't doing that.
Don't fuck with me.
Just give me my money.
I can't do that.
I don't have any money.
- Say what?
- I said I don't have any money.
Where's my money?
I ain't got it.
She took the fucking money.
I got $56. She took it.
Now let me go before I have a wreck.
You're a pussy-whipped fucker.
Don't give me that shit.
It was your fucking buddies
who had no money.
Your good friend, Billy.
What the fuck am I doing with you?
You're a pussy-whipped motherfucker!
If you want any money,
you'll have to go to Arkansas.
Lila, we got to go.
Just give me a few minutes with him.
It's almost four in the morning.
I know.
It's time for you to go home, go to bed
and get up and see your grandma.
I love you, honey.
Will you be a good boy?
Give me a kiss good-bye.
Come on, Lila.
Take care of my baby, okay?
Will you be all right?
Ronnie, put the money
in the bank, okay?
Dale.
- How you doing?
- Stop right there.
Turn around.
Put your hands on the counter.
Spread your legs.
Simon says.
Can I turn around now?
Just stay like that.
Where are your two pals?
Ray and Pluto?
They'll be here soon.
How soon is that?
I don't know.
They have to call first.
How do I know you're not lying?
They might show up here any minute.
I'm not lying to you, Dale.
What will you do with me?
Get in the other room.
Go on.
Go into the living room.
- What are you doing?
- Sit down.
What are you doing?
Two fellows from L.A.
Want to meet you.
- Put the phone down.
- Why?
Ray and Pluto will call here
to see if everything is cool.
I won't answer the phone
if you call those cops.
Yes, you will.
Goddamn it!
Lila, even if I wanted to,
I can't help you.
I don't have the legal authority.
You didn't have the authority
to fuck me when I was 17...
but that didn't stop you.
That's right.
Instead of spying on me...
why didn't you come in
and say hello to your son?
He's not my kid.
Not your kid?
He's nearly as white as you are.
That proves nothing.
Are you calling me a whore?
I was a virgin when we met,
and you know it.
Hear the whippoorwill?
Remember what you said
about hearing a whippoorwill?
It means somebody's going to die.
Why do we have to
sit here in the dark?
I don't want to be a sitting duck
if they show up.
I told you,
they won't be here until they call.
- Where you going?
- My cigarettes are in my purse.
- Get one of mine.
- I smoke menthol.
I'll get them.
I forgot that thing
was even in there.
Ray gave it to me for protection.
I don't know how it works.
You pull the damn trigger.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Did you think I would shoot you?
That's crazy.
Now can I have
my cigarettes, please?
You have a light, baby?
Does your wife treat you right?
Yes, Lila, she does.
That's good.
What's her name again?
Thelma Lou?
Cheryl Ann.
That's right.
And you and Cheryl Ann have
a little girl.
What's her name?
Bonnie.
How old is she?
Eight.
You don't like telling me
about your family, do you?
No, I guess I don't.
I don't blame you.
- I got something for you.
- Where are you going?
Don't shoot me, Officer.
What the hell are you doing now?
- Can I turn on the light?
- No.
I put it in here to keep it fresh.
Can we leave this open
to get some light?
This is our baby's birthday cake.
I don't want any.
Suit yourself.
It's good.
You should try some.
Today's his birthday?
No. It was in September.
I missed it.
I left him with Mama
before he was two years old.
That means
I've missed four birthdays...
so we celebrated all four of them
last night.
Does your mama know about...
Know what?
No, I never told her.
I never meant you any trouble, Dale.
I still don't.
Wouldn't Bonnie be surprised to know
she had a half-brother in Nigger Town.
You should have some
of our baby's cake...
Quit calling him that.
Why? That's what he is.
Damn it.
I told you I didn't want any.
- Do you want this?
- What are you doing?
- This is what you want.
- Cut it out.
Cut it out, goddamn it!
Why did you ever fuck with me?
Me and Ronnie's daddy was white,
did you know that?
Of course, we never knew him.
He had another family.
That's why I kind of look white.
Because my daddy was white.
And you figured
since I kind of look white...
you could fuck me,
what the hell.
Because I was kind of black...
you could dump me, what the hell.
211 to 210.
Dale, where are you at?
Hey, June.
Juney! How are you doing?
You got something for me?
Hi, Mr. Charlie.
Is this Ronnie? Ronnie, this is Ray.
Is Fantasia there?
Yeah, Lila.
Where is she?
Have you got a number
out there for her?
Give it to me, all right?
Ronnie! Ronnie, come here.
- Come here.
- I got to go.
If you know something
about Lila being here...
you tell these gentlemen.
I don't want you
being in trouble, too.
No, ma'am. I don't know
nothing about that.
June Hawkins told me he was
out last night digging frogs.
Driving back, he saw you driving
in front of him with Byron in the car.
Why were you out with Byron
at 4 A. M?
We've been here all night.
June's mixed up. He's old.
He don't see so well.
I'll make the bastard talk!
He won't talk.
It's his sister.
Can I speak to the boy?
- How are you this morning?
- Fine.
- Pretty sleepy?
- I guess so.
- Did you go out with Ronnie last night?
- No.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- You didn't see a pretty lady?
- No.
You sure?
- Did Uncle Ronnie tell you to say that?
- Yeah.
So this has just been pretend?
What do you say we stop
playing pretend and play really?
And you really should spend a night
in jail.
So you don't tell your sister.
You got to let me go.
I can't do that, Lila.
You can't let them put me in jail.
What's going to happen to our baby
with me in jail?
Your mom
will keep taking care of him.
I'll give her money for him.
Why won't you give him the money?
Why don't you just say,
"Byron, I'm your daddy?"
I don't see how that would...
I guess it wouldn't be
a good idea, huh?
I guess it would be better
just to put me in jail...
and forget about
your 5-year-old son.
Hi, baby.
Yeah, everything's cool.
Everything's real cool.
Ray, where are you calling from?
What's the name
of the gas station?
Ray, you missed the turnoff.
It's about half a mile back
up the highway.
You turn right at this place
called Cothern's Bait Shop.
There's a little road there.
You're not far, baby.
Just about ten minutes away. Hurry.
Yeah, I miss you.
Is that the road, Byron?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
When they arrive, get them
in the house and away from the car.
Open the door, talk to them.
Let them see everything is okay.
Then stay in the kitchen
until I say to come out.
Then if they get trigger-happy,
you'll be out of the line of fire.
Then you'll let me go?
I'll let you go.
Is that the road you went down?
Don't fuck around in there.
In and out. Got me?
What do you think I'd do?
Don't worry.
You sure this is it?
Yeah.
You got it straight? Do you?
Hi, baby.
Come on, Fantasia. Let's go.
It'll be a few minutes.
I have to pack my stuff.
What stuff?
All you had was your purse.
It won't be long.
Come on in.
Shit!
I'll be back.
That's bullshit.
I'm sticking on your ass.
She better not have bought
any clothes.
What does she have to pack?
- Come on.
- Be careful. I love you.
Did you spend any of my money?
Fantasia.
Where did she go?
Police officer, freeze! Hands up,
or I'll blow you to fucking hell!
- What the fuck?
- Get on the floor! Now!
Who the fuck are you?
- You bitch!
- Shut up!
- Why the fuck did you do this?
- I'm sorry.
- Stay back!
210.
210, A-1 channel 1.
Come in, goddamn it. Hurry up.
Hurricane, where the hell
have you been?
I need help out here.
What's your 10-20?
Oh, God.
Dale, what's your twenty?
Where are you?
I'm off the highway,
two miles down Sulphur Springs Road.
There's a house, and there's woods...
there's this house...
Is there an address?
I don't know the goddamn address.
Just send some help.
And an ambulance.
I got three suspects down,
and I'm hurt pretty bad.
Three suspects down.
You know Sulphur Springs Road?
Hold on, Byron.
Charlie, do something.
Dud, come on!
Charlie'll taking care of it. Come on!
This is 211 to base.
Send an ambulance
to Sulphur Springs Road right away.
That son of a bitch nailed them.
Hey, man.
The ambulance is on the way.
I'll get you some blankets, okay?
Are you dead, mister?
No, not quite.
Where's the lady at?
She's over there.
Don't go away. Come back.
Come stay with me.
Stay here with me.
How did you get blood on yourself?
I got in a fight.
What do you do with your keys?
I lock things up.
Come here.
I can't see your face.
Come a little closer.
Your name...
is Byron.
You're five years old?
Four or five?
Five.
Just come sit with me.