[Book Title - The Interpretation of Dreams by Freud Sigmund]
[Chapter 3 - The Dream as a Wish-Fulfillment]
The gentle breeze that blew past my shoulder
Hiding behind the clouds is the sunlight
Take me along with you
Holding my hand
This warmth
The gentle breeze that blew past my shoulder
Hiding behind the clouds is the sunlight
Take me along with you
Holding my hand
This warmth
Hmmm
The flowing sea above your head
Resting behind the clouds is the sunlight
Turning and turning
I have fallen into your arms
This warmth
The gentle breeze that blew past your shoulder
Hiding behind the clouds is the sunlight
Oppa, wake up!
Hurry up and wake up!
Mother...
Mother has disappeared.
What are you talking about.
[To my son, Minsoo]
Where did she suddenly go?
I asked the nurses.
They say she was discharged.
I don't know!
I hate Mother!
So bad!
Minsoo.
Yes?
Come over here.
It's just nice!
Minsoo has the same broad shoulders as my son.
I too think my shoulders aren't bad.
So much bragging! Just like Yoomi.
But...
Your son will definitely like it.
Why?
Nowadays, which mother in the world will knit a sweater for their son?
Shall I knit one for you?
I love you, Mother! How do I repay you?
You must be Ihealthy ancMive to a ripe old age!v
What should I do? Shouldil give you a piggyback?
Get well soon.
What should I do? Should I give you a piggyback?
What should I do? ShouldiUgive you a piggyback?
What should I do? Shouldikgive you a piggyback?
Stand up.
Let me carry you, Mother.
Oh my...
It's alright if you don't want a piggyback...
Alright, I'll have one.
[Hey Oppa!!!]
Excuse me...
Ward 313's Patient Kim Yoomi has disappeared.
What number?
Ward 313 s Kim Yoomi.
12 years old.
Unnie
We are an adult ward here.
This patient...
For children to high school patients
They are assigned to the pediatric ward.
No, that can't be the case.
Please verify it for me.
Search for it.
You said 'Kim Yoomi' right?
Yes.
In our hospital, there's no patient young or old named Kim Yoomi.
That can't be the case...
Mr. Minsoo.
Oh, Ms. Nurse!
That...Yoomi has disappeared.
Our Yoomi has disappeared!
Yoomi?
Why? Ward 313's Kim Yoomi.
Ms. Nurse liked Yoomi the most!
What are you talking about now?
If anything comes up, call me straight away.
[Avens Rehabilitation Hospital]
Mr Minsoo, are you alright?
Mr Minsoo, Mr Minsoo!
No one knew about the girls existence.
The girl called Yoomi
Never existed in the world in the first place.
Although I knew it was a beautiful dream
But I didn't want to sleep anymore.
To wake up once again
It felt like another person by my side will disappear.
Wake up.
Quickly wake up.
Wake up. Please!
Excuse me!
Aren’t you the one who visited Ward 313 the last time?
Together with our ward's Mother.
No, I mean Park Wonju-ahjumma
What relation do you have with her?
The day after the both of you met
Park Wonju-ahjumma suddenly disappeared.
Are the two of you really unrelated?
Minsoo...
How do you know that name?
Ahjumma.