Over here...
Is Ms. Leejiwon here?
Ms. Leejiwon?
What is it?
l-m from the insurance company.
Ms. Lee Jiwon
Let me go straight to the point.
You are currently staying in the hospital without injuries.
I specially did some investigation.
In the past year, you have been hospitalized 18 times for traffic accidents.
The average hospital stay is 3 weeks.
A total of 168 days.
Basically you are staying at the hospital every month.
If I were to pursue this according to the law
Ms. Lee Jiwon, you will be in trouble!
Faking a hospital stay, and insurance fraud.
This is an offense tenable of up to 10 years jail and 20 million won fine.
Ms. Leejiwon
You are faking it, right?
Then why is there not a single symptom? Putting on a show?
I'm really treating you as a younger sister, that's why I'm telling you this.
Before I call the police
Quickly pack up and discharge yourself from the hospital.
Pack up.
What?
You are currently staying in the hospital without injuries.
How dare you malign me as a fraud?
Insurance company employee?
From which insurance company are you from?
Let's go the legal route!
I've recorded it all.
You!
With your threats and defamation
I can report you to the police and consumer protection center.
Also, your company. I can sue you till your pants drop.
Let's see what you will become. We shall see.
Let me show you what s craziness.
Do you want to die?
I didn't mean that.
You.
Younger sister?
How old are you to call me younger sister?
Take out your identification card.
I'm really sorry.
I didn’t mean that.
If you don't give me
Urn calling 112.
Born in !94?
21 years old?
Life is hard.
In the future, avoid me when you see me.
I'm really sorry. I will definitely avoid.
Alright.
While Noona is still in a good mood, get out.
Please...
On the company's side...
I'm just an intern.
I'm really...
How can there be such crazy pebple?
Seripusly.
I'm really going crazy.
Unnie!
Do you want an apple?
Your name is Yoomi, right?
I hank you.
I will eat well!
What are you doing in broad daylight!?
Oh my...
Minsoo, are you alright?
Im fine.
You haven't recovered. Why are yo Tdancing some weird dance?
That's not right.
What?
Weird dance?
Seriously.
Please, get yourself together.
Please act your age as a senior.
Oh my...
Oh my!
Senior?
What's the point of talking...
I shall just keep my mouth shut.
That...
It seems...
I haven't officially announced it yet.
Tonight, I
Will be treating everyone!
Still alive.
Indeed!
I want fried chicken and beer!
What do you mean fried chicken and beer?
Oh, right.
Then, I want fried chicken and cola.
I want orange juice.
First chicken, then...
You are going to riot again.
Dcryou wan time to punch you?
No, I don't.
I had too many of that already.
I don't eat stuff like fried chicken.
Don't count me in.
Ms. Jiwon.
Are you saying you don't eat chicken?
Chicken!
Alright, alright!
I'll join in.
From where does she belong?
The company alcohol ritual.
She's so serious making poktanju.
It's really nice.
Older brother.
Please say a word.
Ever since staying in the hospital
Each and every day.
It feels like a dream.
Of course, not every thing is a good dream.
I'm really happy to have known everyone.
In the future
I hope we will be able to maintain this fate.
Everyone.
Cheers.
Oh my!
One shot, one shot!
How long are you doing to make me dance?
Look at my shoulders.
They're out of sockets!
Lover shot!
These days...
I'm sorry for what I've said.
My husband danced with others.
He abandoned me and the children.
I'm in the same situation.
My husband had an affair.
And then he ran off.
Leaving 3 children behind.
One day, that man
brought a woman with child
to appear before me.
They are all children
But my children...
became children who were not loved.
Because I couldn't take it
I took the children and ran away.
Now that the children are all married.
I feel how dumb my life has been.
So I made a decision
To Uve a new life, I began dancing.
It's not to seduce men.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know about this.
Actually...
I want to seduce men too.
Speaking of which...
Your burns seem pretty serious.
What was the reason?
It happened while I was working at the hotel.
That day was especially busy.
As I was so busy
A group of customers came to eat.
Because I was in a hurry to serve the group
While moving the tables
The gas hose was plucked out.
Even now when I see lighted candles
My heart will pound really quickly
Even my hands tremble.
She almost got into big trouble.
Ms. Jiwon.
No, I'm older than you, so I will speak comfortably.
Is that alright?
Honestly
I'm very envious and jealous of you.
You are pretty, and your body is great. Your qualities are excellent.
Conversely, I only know how to work hard.
Day by day, I wait to become an old virgin.
I also wish to be like you, to be able to dress up nicely.
And date someone.
But I only know how to work hard.
So much time has already passed.
Pretty face and good body?
Naturally?
That's such a joke.
When I was still a student
I was so fat, like a pig.
I didn’t have a single friend.
I was always ostracized.
I weakly lived till now.
It was like I was dead every day.
Actually, I previously had
thoughts that dying would be better off.
Why is the atmosphere like this?
Who died?
I have a body that will make noses bleed.
That's Leejiwon!
Swore that
I would make a single female pictorial shoot.
You don't believe?
I will film it for you.
- I will really film it.
- ﻿I will really film it.
You are drunk.
Stop talking.
So noisy. So noisy.
Eat this.
Drink this.
Rise and shine
Come over.
You come over.
This rascal.
You rascal, come over
Are you not coming?
Hurry up over here.
One.
Two.
Three!
It's mealtime!
It's mealtime.
Did you sleep well?
It's morning!
It's so funny!
Oh my!
Hold on.
It's so pretty!
Unnie, put some here too.