Are the two of you really unrelated?
Minsoo...
How do you know that name?
Ahjumma.
That's not right.
This...How can it be?
Why are you here?
O﻿ppa!
Were you frightened?
Where did you go?
Why are you acting like an idiot?
How can a man cry like that?
What is the meaning of this?
Did you plan this together to scare me?
Something like a hidden camera?
O﻿ppa.
You have slept too long.
Minsoo
Although it s hard for you to believe it.
But whatever happened and whomever you met here
Are all your imagination.
What are you talking about..
How can this be an imagination?
What are you talking about.
You are having such thoughts, right?
Is this a dream?
This isn't a dream.
Please, stop it1
Stop it1
Now, open your eyes and see the reality.
Please! Stop saying it!
Welbome to heaven
Welcome
My dad died too.
Mmsoo has the same broad shoulders as my son.
[Chapter 3 - The Dream as a Wish-Pulfillment]
He's messed up
Did he turn into a vegetable?
You woke up
You woke up!
Yoomi
How does Oppa know my name?
For coming back to my side
Thank you
Why is this Oppa like that?
Does your head hurt?
Something badLhas happened.
Everyone, wake up!
Hurry up!
Excuse me
Are you alright?
Yes
That's a relief.
It s good to hear you saying you are fine.
I’m really fine
Since everyone is gathered
Let me introduce you to everyone in the ward.
That's not necessary.
I know everything.
Look...
I said this Oppa is messed up
Like me?
Now
I know...
The reason for beingihere.
And also...
The reason why everyone is here.
Noona.
Thank you for teaching me such a cool dance,
Mother
Thank you for taking care of me.
Also .
Although I haven't worn it
I'm very thankful for the sweater.
Haesun-noona
Although we didn't share much together
But to help me in the background
I'm really thankful
And...
Also
Jiwon
Actually
I really like you.
Also
Lastly, it’s our Yoomi.
I missed you‘the most.
Now.
It's time for me to leave
It seems I've left my original state for too long...
Everyone
Thanks to everyone
I'm really...
Very happy.
It was really... really..
Bitter-sweet
I will definitely not forget.
Bye
Oh my!
Driving me nuts
That.
Nurse!
Son!
Son, it's mom!
It's mom!
Look at mom!
Son!
What's the matter?
My son!
My son finally opened his eyes after 3 years!
Quickly get the doctor-on-call
Madam!
Did you do it right?
Before injecting a patient, you haverfo verify it. Do you not know!?
I'm very sorry.
The fluid was wrong, so I'm changing it for him.
Mr Minsoo
How's your body now?
Do you have any stomaches or headaches?
I m fine, really.
My stomach is fine, and my head doesn't hurt.
In fact, I'm full of energy. My condition is perfect.
That's a relief.
Quickly fix it, and change it to glucose fluid.
This kind of thing should have been done by yourself
How can.you blame others.
I'm so unlucky.
Return to that moment multiple times a day, every day.
Returning to the split moment I made a decision mistake.
The moment which caused everything to go up in flames.
Actually
I haven't woken up from my deep coma.
I am having a happy dream again today.
Drinks are going down the throat.
Alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol, ﻿alcohol.
For my son.
For my son...
Seeing everyone
I'm so happy
In the future
I hope we will be able to maintain this fate.
Everyone.
Cheers.