Excuse me.
Can we talk without pinching?
Do you want
Me to give you a kiss?
No, it's alright.
Don't be modest!
Book Title - The Interpretation of Dreams
Yes!
Yes.
Elder brother.
Why are you not playing the game seriously? What are you thinking about?
Even the dog shit is coming out!
Aigoo- Is it my turn?
You are a bit weird today.
Why do you keep looking in Jiwon-unnie's direction?
What are you talking about?
When was I looking over there?
Seriously...
Could it be...
You are interested in Jiwon-unnie?
What...
What...what the heck are you saying.
Hey! Why would I have any liking for her?
I...
like...
the pure and innocent style.
Compared to the sexy style
I prefer girls who are pure and innocent.
That's the type of style I like.
Darling, are you saying that you like the innocent type like me?
Jerk.
Ajura handing it out
Let me win!
Let me and the Hwatu cards
Become one.
Let me catch a good card.
Seriously...
Mother, why did you hit me!?
This is very frail.
Thankfully, this is a hospital
I can lie down here immediately.
What should I eat?
Crazy bit...
It's a bit weird.
She's...Ms. Jiwon, right?
Yes, Crazy bitch.
Yes, Lee Jiwon.
But, why?
From what I see, she’s...
A bit stiff and introverted.
But I don't think she's a bad person.
Why do you call her...
Crazy bitch?
I don't really know how to say...
Dong is Dong.
Crazy bitch is Crazy bitch.
Why do you need any explanation?
Mr. Minsoo?
You are asking us why we call her by that nickname?
About 3 weeks back
Began the legend of the Crazy bitch.
[3 weeks ago]
Are you looking for someone?
Is this ward 313?
Yes, that's right.
This is such a mess.
Patient...
I took a while to find you.
This is your bag.
Currently, this is the only available bed.
I didn’t intend to have a single-person room.
But find me one that is a 2 or 3 persons room.
For a patient like you that has light injuries, we can't do that...
What!?
For a patient like you that hasUight injuries, we can’t do that...
For a patient like you that has light injuries, we can t do that...
A patient needs to stay in a hospital.
What do you mean by light injuries?
Are you a doctor?
No.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, Patient.
Patients have to change into the patient outfit.
Oh by the way, Unnie.
I'm not going to wear the hospital's clothes.
Wearing what others,have worn before is the most irritating.
Also
I will not eat the food the hospital provides.
Don't leave any for me.
But, patient...
It's not that, but the hospital has clear rules...
Why is this person so inflexible?
I said it's not necessary.
This isn't something for me to decide.
How many times must I tell you?
Emotional labor is so tiring...
If that's the case...
If you don't get abused, it would be weird.
Why did a crazy bitch come here?
Unnìes
Shouldn't we put a stop to the crazy bitch?
This isn't some penitentiary center.
If there's a problem
Just give it to the Ahjummas here.
What!?
- Ahjumma!?
On the second day
Something happened.
Are the patients alright?
Yes sir.
You didn't put on make up today?
How s your injury?
Yes...
Thanks to you, I'm much better.
For someone of your age
It's not suitable to dance such vigorous dances.
What treatment do you think this patient should get?
From the current state
The skin hasn't deteriorated.
With another month of continuous treatment
And with the patient s agreement on doing cosmetic surgery
The scars can all be removed.
Did she explain it clearly?
Yes.
Good.
Thank you doctor.
For such a patient
Due to improper posture
Which results in turtle neck
Lumbar disc protrusion
And carpal tunnel syndrome.
You can say this is a common illness of the modern person.
You.
Yes?
Do you know the treatment for turtle nec <.
Yes. It s...
First, you need plenty of rest.
And you need to fix your posture.
So in short...
For neck protrusion resulting in scoliosis
The basic treatment is correction treatment or physiotherapy.
For this missus, to improve without surgery is a rare occurence.
In such a situation, we can have cervical spine surgery
That is to sak that in the event her nerves are not being compressed
There is no need for surgery.
And compared to having too much rest, having suitable amounts of exercise
Will be very helpful for treatment.
That is all.
Applause.
So you know that your posture is important, right?
You need to frequently maintain a straight back.
And do more yoga stretching exercises.
The region around the bone fracture when the accident happened
Is in the midst of recovery after supportive physiotherapy.
If it's early stage bone fracture
Through repeated compression support
It will usually be diagnosed as fully recovered.
So clever.
I don't have anything to say.
But as a doctor
I need to say something.
So, Patient Kim Yoomi
Eat well
Sleep well and do well.
So cute.
Patient.
We are doing our rounds.
I'm opening the curtain.
So sorry.
Because of the change in place where I sleep
I can't sleep well.
This patient was involved in a minor traffic accident.
According to CT and X-ray scans
There's nothing serious.
Then shouldn't she be in a normal ward?
Oh, doctor.
Yes.
My heart seems to beat very fast.
I'm not sure if it's a consequence of the accident.
Even if it's a tiny sound
I will be really shocked.
My body is also feverish.
If I do not strip to sleep at night
I can't sleep at all.
Also...
Here, at my hip.
It's really pain too.
Here too...
So man tricks.
Send this patient for psychotherapy and physiotherapy.
Have the treatment fo [ 1 month. Let it be so.
From then onwards
We thought of ways to put down Jiwon.
We were always researching.
Over here...
Is Ms. Lee Jiwon here?
Ms. Lee Jiwon?
What is it?