Director!
What happened?
Welcome to heaven.
Welcome.
Who are you!?
Where am I?!
Are you alright?
This time...
In my opinion...
He's messed up.
By any chance...
Did he turn into a vegetable?
Don't say such things.
What?
I only spoke out of concern.
She's a hottie.
Don't be late.
It's all your fault!
You'll be sorry if he can't recover!
Why do you always say this to me?
Crazy bitch!
Yoomi.
Yes?
Come here.
Come and watch over this guy for a while.
If anything comes up, call me straight away.
OK!
You woke up.
You woke up!
Be quiet.
You'll wake people up.
Thank goodness.
I was so worried.
Looks like you were looking after me?
I'm just here because theinurse-unnie asked me to, for your information!
You got up so I'm going back to my spot.
Hey, wait a moment.
Let me ask you for a favor.
That Unnie...
She got in for an injury while dancing
Huh? Unnie?
You don't mean...
She's 68
But she thinks she's still in 20's
Like before
put on makeup
She has a flower on her head
Like she's in her 20's
Her no make up face isn't bad.
That was grandma.
Okay?
Park Wonju. 58 years old.
But we still call her mother.
While she was working
She got burned.
She has a son and a daughter.
Says her son lives somewhere distant.
Can't get a hold of him.
Do you see the sweater?
She's making it for her son.
You should call her mother as well
It's for the best.
Mom, mom
Okay?
The Unnie over there
38, past her marriage age.
Choi Haesun.
She’s always working late.
Even at home.
So
She has turtle neck
Lumbar disc
And carpal tunnel syndrome.
She still works like that.
And
That crazy Unnie from earlier
Lee Jiwon.
27 years old.
Nylon patient.
Nylon?
In her own words
She got in a car accident.
But she's jogging everyday-
the morning-
In my opinion
She's fine.
Nickname is Crazy bitch.
She seems rather abnormal.
You too.
What was that just now?
Wipe that smile off your face.
I will introduce myself now.
I'm Kim Yoomi.
12 years old.
I was hurt during school PE.
I am rather smart.
I am one of the top in school.
My dream is to become a doctor.
My hobby is dancing.
As you can plainly see, I'm rather good looking.
So popular too.
By the way, what have you been writing?
Oh, it’s nothing.
Names and ages. Those slDrt of things.
Youre weird.
Anyway, nice to meet you, guy.
Aigoo
Yes, I am in your hands.
Oppa, you are kind of stupid
And cute.
It's your turn now.
Family?
My mother and my younger sister.
What about your father?
My father died when I was 16.
It's been just us 3 since then.
Really?
My dad died too.
Before I was born.
Dinner
What's up with eating stinky food every day?
Crazy bitch!
Hey.
Hey
If you tell anyone that you saw me.
Understand?
I'll beat you.
Yes, yes.
I understand.
OK!
Alright.
Want some'beer?
Beer?
Why?
You can't drin 4.
I can drink, but...
We re not supposed to...
You drink well!
Cheers!
Che...cheers.
Drink it in one shot!
One shot?
Alright, alright.
I will cheer for you.
Drinks are going down the throat.
Alcohol, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol, alcohol!
How long are you going to make me dance?
Look at my shoulders.
They're out'df their sockets!
Do you want your shoulders out of their sockets?
Actually
I don't give out drinks
I’m being generous.
Yes.
You are so cute.
Th...thank you.
By the way
You are...
What?
Younger than I am, if I'm not mistaken...
Are you a 87 rabbit?
That's right.
I’m a 88 dragon!
Roar- We re friends!
A year difference doesn't mean anything once out in society.
That's a little...
Even with my parents who are 30 years older than I am
I don’t use honorifics.
Everyone
Does that.
Why?
You got a problem?
Who asked you to be born a year earlier?
She's insane while sober.
Even worse drunk.
Time to get out of here!
Hey!
Oh my
You'd better behave!
- Wait, hold on!
- You’d better behave!
Stop it, please.
Aish !
I really want to
Beat her.
What's that?
You're gonna hit me, huh?
You...
What did you think of my body line, when you got a peek?
Amazing, right?
How about it?
You want to touch the "real" thing?
Yes.
I mean, no.
You are so cute
Pain...
Ah...it's pain...
It really hunts.
Let go already!
I oughtta!
You are being ostracized
Because you are acting like this!
Sigh...
Let me tell you something.
I went to a prestigious school
And work for a big corporation!
l'm an elite, got it?!
I'm not someone you can look down on. You...!
You... rascal.
So~ cute~ !
Excuse me.
Can we talk without pinching?
Do you want
me to give you a kiss?
No, it's alright.
Don't be modest!