- 340.
- Yes.
Can I see
the director?
You can see him tomorrow.
Do you want to make an appointment?
- Yes, at 12:30, if possible.
- The reason?
A loan,
we have already spoken.
I am about to obtain Belgian nationality,
Now, I can do so.
14,000
In a month,
if all goes as planned.
When will I see you?
I am hanging up now.
I love you.
Me too. Bye.
50 Euros, please.
What do you want?
I know... and it is the
third time you called.
- Thanks.
- Thank You.
- How much do I owe you?
- 10 Euros.
I am going to sleep.
- Do not you fancy a game of cards?
- No.
Close the curtains.
Are you coming?
No... I said no!
Have you heard? I said no.
Yes, I heard. Goodnight.
Are we going to play then?
Lower the music!
The music, a little lower!
- What do you want?
- I have to talk to you. Open.
Tomorrow I have
to get up at six.
Tonight I will not go out.
It is over.
No, this time is serious,
but you have to help me.
- Promise me that you will.
- Let me sleep, Claudy!
I must know
so I set a target.
- I do not know when I will return.
- Tell me a time, any time.
Five?... Six?...
At nine?...
What time then?
At seven? Ok?
- Whatever.
- If you are late, call me.
Do not forget
to return the mattress.
- What are you doing?
- Lock me inside.
- And if you want to leave?
- I have to resist!
No, I will not do it.
You will want to go out
and I will have to come back.
No, I swear no! Lorna!
If I am late, tell her
that I will stay here tonight.
I will tell her.
He told them
I would return during my break.
- Only at nights.
- I said so. But did not understand.
It is bad. He is stopping.
Terminal 4.
Can you do the pick up, Fabio?
I will.
He says he wants to quit this time.
He has asked me to help him.
Tomorrow he will be the same
If he quits though,
what shall we do?
As we said, we overdose him.
- And will the police believe it?
- Of course.
It will not be the first time that someone
lies dying from overdoses.
The cops! Six months, nothing!
But now you are becoming a Belgian!
- Will you wait?
- No, I have to go to the airport.
Show them the photo
of the wedding.
Where are the police?
- I do not feel well, I wanted to see you.
- Get out of my bed.
- I thought I could.
- Get out! Go!
- Look what you have done! Shit!
- Sorry.
Bring a towel.
It was not the police
He wanted me to come back.
- Do not do that again.
- I was not feeling well.
I do not care!
I arrived late,
it gives me no time to eat.
- Do you want me to prepare a sandwich?
- No.
- Who is it?
- You need something?
Go away!
This is the second time
this morning.
Will you go to buy Buscopan?
I have cramps.
- Here, it costs 18 or 19 Euros.
- Why do I need to do something for you?
- If I see the others, I will be in trouble!
- And? It is not my business.
You got married for money,
you will get twice to divorce!
I do not mind the money! Help me!
Buy the Buscopan!
You go!
- Help me, Lorna!
- Get up!
Get up!
Write the name of medicine
on a piece of paper.
Give it.
- What is the name?
- Buscopan.
Loc me inside.
My key!
It fell into the truck!
Go to the cabin 3, please.
It is me.
I wanted to talk to you.
Bye...
I will call you on Sunday...
Good evening...
A Buscopan, please.
Do you have a prescription?
- Is it really bad?
- It is not for me...
For my husband...
He has cramps...
Ok I will give you,
but usually you need a prescription.
What?
What do you want? Water?
- Let me.
- Help me get up.
Let me, Claudy!
- Help me, I have cramps, I am hurting!
- Take the Buscopan!
I have taken it,
but I am still hurting.
Wait...
- Call my doctor.
- Why do not you call him?
Lorna, help me! Help me!
In D, Dr. Mayr.
Tell him I want to go
to the hospital.
Good evening...
I am the wife of Claudy Moreau
He quit drugs...
He is in pain
for two days now...
He wants to go to the hospital...
Yes, I am giving him to you...
- Already registered.
- Does it cost anything?
No, but tomorrow will bring
healthcare card.
Your money.
- Claudy, your money!
- I do not need them here.
Let me just 20 Euros
to snuff.
Tomorrow I have to bring your health card,
where is it?
Put it into my pocket.
- Is there someone to look after me?
- The admissions officer said that they will
Tomorrow, will you bring
the CD player and CDs?
- Do not leave me alone.
- A nurse is coming now.
Stay until he comes.
Please.
Yes, I am coming down.
I will be
in the taxi parking.
- Claudy Moreau?
- Room 110.
- I brought his health card.
- Go to admissions, ground floor.
Can you give him these things?
Are you his wife?
- Yes!
- Go, but do not stay too much.
The last door on the left.
Room 110.
- What shall we do?
- Ask for divorce, as he believes.
Why not?
We have chosen a junkie to prevent divorce.
And it would take too long.
What if the Russian
is in agreement?
I have set for June.
I gave my word.
Put on the window wipers.
The button on the left.
I will find a faster way
to obtain a divorce.
And who pays 5,000 Euros
to a junkie?
Take 5,000 from the 10,000
Euros of the Russian.
- Are you engaged with him or what?
- Fuck it. I am with Sokol.
- And why are you backing off?
- I am not backing off.
To die from overdose
will look strange.
Almost everyone leaves
and then come back again.
Divorce has many risks,
it is best to become a widow.
Sokol!
I was afraid you were gone.
The minibus to Germany
has not arrived yet.
I like you more
without the beard.
You are now Belgian.
Near Colonia.
At the reactor core.
- One minute into the reactor, 1,000 Euros.
- It is not dangerous?
- Only if you do it every month.
- You will go back?
No, we will return
directly to Italy.
Take... 1,200 Euros.
- How much we have in mind?
- Nearly 20,000 Euros.
Let me see your card again.
What a joy to live with you.
We must still have to wait
for the Russian.
- Did you find any space for the bar?
- Next week.
The bank will give me
some addresses.
Tell me you love me!
- I love you. What's wrong?
- Nothing
The minibus. I got to go.
Claudy is trying to quit.
He believes it this time.
- I would prefer a divorce...
- Have you spoken to Fabio?
He is afraid of the Russian.
But the divorce will be quicker if
I say that my husband beats me.
- Wont they investigate?
- I think it always works.
If it falls,
all will be shit!
- Let Fabio decide.
- I do not want him to die.
It is too late.
We have an agreement, is only a drug addict.
Lorna, you can not leave now.
We are near the end...
If something does not work,
call me.
Come.
That's it. The other arm.
You can now dress.
17 Ferreire Street
Marital Home
abstinence of heroin.
Wednesday,
November 14, 2007  21:00.
He is now in the hospital?
Yes, since that
Wednesday night.
You should have come
that very evening.
Present the complaint before the judge,
but I do not think that is sufficient
Why not?
Given the position of the hematoma,
they could argue that you did it.
It was him, he wanted drugs.
If at least you had one witness...
but you do not.
Sign here, please.
I need money,
The sooner I get to remarry,
the sooner I will get them.
- A real marriage?
- No. Like ours.
A foreigner who pays
to be Belgian
I have helped you quit.
And that was not the deal.
Now you can help me, right?
Do you agree?
I do not want me
characterised as abusive.
- You are already booked for drugs and theft.
- It is not the same.
I have never struck a woman.
And 5,000 Euros for the divorce,
you do not you care?
I can wait.
I am collecting allowance
and I could find a job.
If you accept,
I will help you to stay clean.
Even after the divorce.
Someone is coming.
Come on, Hit me.
Hit me, Claudy!
Come on!
You should have played your
king before your dame.
It is 10 to 3.
- One last game?
- We said until 3.
It is there.
Come on.
Get up.
You said you would hit me
if I stayed!
Come on!
With the fist!
I can not.
Are you okay?
I was struck and
I hit my head against the wall.
You should complain
to the police.
I will.
Do you agree to testify
if the police asks?
He did not seem a violent person.
Do not always trust appearances.
- What is your name, madam?
- Monique Sobel.
Can you write your name on a piece
of paper and your phone number?
Fabio wants to see you.
He is at the parking.
All fine with
the girl from the laundry.
- I am afraid, Lorna.
- Why? I have not done anything.
Do not do it.
Do not go to the police.
- And if it works?
- Do not do it!
You are his wife, take care of him.
The rest leave them to me.
Do not trust me?
Mandatory. I need you.
Okay, go now.
Lorna! Do not forget,
you need me too.
Do not want the job to get ruined.
It is my first one with the Russians.
Nor do I. I want my money.
Now you admit it.
Who was that guy the other
night at the station?
- Sokol.
- But Sokol has a beard.
Yes, but he shaved it.
Lorna, someone asked about you.
Excuse me,
back in two minutes.
I left,
I wanted to surprise you.
- You mean you are cured?
- Yes
If I am bad,
I can call the hospital.
You must resist.
- Can you give me the house keys?
- Let me get them.
And my money.
I just want 10 Euros
for cigarettes.
- Shall we eat together to celebrate?
- I can not, I have a lot of work.
Shall I prepare dinner for tonight.
It will do me good.
I need some more money
for shopping.
- When will you be back?
- I do not know, about seven.
Okay, bye.
Yes. Who is it?
Almost ready.
I made the pasta carbonara.
A letter came for you.
I have left it on the bed.
It is a letter from the judge,
he has granted the divorce.
- Back in an hour.
- I have cooked, and it is almost ready.
You can wait an hour, right?
- I thought we were going to celebrate!
- In an hour, okay?
Roberto, have you seen Fabio?
Fabio waits in the taxi
at the plaza.
I have not done anything more,
I swear.
It is a consequence
of the complaint.
Too late for the Russian,
he can not wait.
Ask!
It is only one month more!
And you get to marry for one week
and after divorce... it sucks!
Why?
I have a husband who attacked me.
I will make the race.
And you will give him 5000 Euros
the day of the divorce?
Yes, from the lame 10,000
of the Russian.
Okay, I'll call him,
just to see if he accept the month.
- Will you call me when you have talked?
- Yes
I spoke with the Russian,
he agrees.
Get out of here
with all your shit!
- Go!
- Shut up, my money!
I want to talk first!
Wait here.
- 10 minutes, no more.
- Alright.
- Give me my money!
- You started again?
- Call the hospital.
- My money!
Wait, calm down!
- I do not want you to start again.
- You got your divorce, what do you care?
- Give me my money!
- I will!
- I have left them at the laundry.
- Liar! Give them to me!
Give me the envelope!
- Give me the key!
- No!
- Is this bike alright?
- Which?
The blue one.
Yes, 50 Euros.
I will take it.
60 Euros to open the door
and 10 by two keys.
50-50?
- No, it is my fault, the door.
- It is also my fault.
- 35 per head?
- Alright.
I will ride all day.
It is something to do.
- Can I come at noon?
- I will be alone in the shop.
Not to have lunch. I need a target
in the middle of the day.
I will come by
and then leave.
I have the need to see you.
I am off now.
Here, it is better than what you have them.
See you later...
The family was here.
They will pay the funeral.
- I said I will pay.
- I told them but they said no.
- Can I see him for the last time?
- You already recognised him.
- The officer is gone.
- I am his wife.
Are you sure
you do not want to stay here?
The police will think
that you are fleeing.
Have you heard what I said?
They might suspect something.
The police has my phone number.
Give it back.
- The CD player.
- He does not need it anymore.
Give it to her.
You can stay one more week.
It will seem normal.
Where are you going to go?
- Where I was before.
- But the rent.
I have already made an agreement
with the girl.
- Won't you take his razor blade and things?
- No.
Spirou, come and collect things
of the junkie from the bathroom.
Are you going to continue
with the long face?
Would you tell him if you knew
the Russian would not wait?
I have helped you.
Say thanks instead of the long face.
For the unexpected work
another 1,000.
That you took care of him when
he wanted to quit. It was a job.
If you deny it
then it means you are not with us.
Still with us, right?
You were always alright!
You did not talk,
so we were able to overdose him.
I have the 1,000 Euros,
I will give them to you whenever you want.
Take the photo.
Spirou. Take the bag.
Ms. Moreau is at home?
We had still some questions pending.
It is for the autopsy report.
I will take your bag.
We will wait in the car.
Come in.
The autopsy confirms that he dies
of a drug overdose.
Do you know of any enemy
that wanted him dead?
Would anybody earn anything
by killing him with an overdose?
- He just quit them.
- He was depressed?
- Have he ever talked of suicide?
- No.
You asked for divorce
because he beat you...
Did he know you will get it?
Since when?
Since you received the letter from
the judge, four days ago.
- When did the dealer tell us?
- Friday, 4 days ago.
You husband called him
to buy heroin.
Perhaps the news
of the divorce?
According to the dealer,
you prevented him to buy it.
Alone and depressed
he could have taken the dose...
...which killed him on purpose or by mistake?
Possibly.
Well. We are going now.
- Good evening, Mrs. Moreau.
- Good evening.
Excuse me, are you the
mother of Claudy?
No, it is the lady
who is in the car behind you.
I am Lorna,
the wife of Claudy...
I wanted to give you this.
It is the money he left me.
Has he talked about me?
It is my son, his brother.
This is the wife of Claudy.
- What is that?
- The money that was left by Claudy.
You are his wife,
they are yours.
- For the girl...
- We do not want your money specially of Claudy.
Take them.
Good... I feel better...
Call me and I come...
1000 kilometers...
I am leaving again tonight.
What do we do?
- Are you asleep?
- No.
You should not worry.
A junkie prefers drugs
instead of life.
Sooner or later he would start again...
and who knows... he would die.
Shall we see sites
you have found for the bar?
Agreed.
Here, the number 36...
It is too small.
There is no room
for tables...
Come and see.
You see?
Only three rooms...
- And a garden?
- Is it big?
Yes, in summer
we could put tables outside.
I like it.
- You really have to go tonight?
- Yes.
Well, the minibus
will leave at six.
Shall we dance?
Lorna, this is
Andrei Aslikov.
Kosti, the interpreter.
Sit down.
- Want something to drink?
- A beer.
Something for you?
No, he does not take anything,
me neither.
Roberto, a beer!
Do you like your
Belgian identity card.
- Do you have the document?
- Yes.
The official document that says
that she is a widow and can marry again.
They paid in advance.
Take your share.
Three bundles.
In twenties.
This is the price of a pack of
cigarettes in Moscow.
Want the 1,000 Euros
you rejected?
Like I said,
I would save them for you.
See you soon.
What?
Yes, I signed this morning.
I am so happy, Sokol!
Our bar!
Let me count...
One, two, three, four...
Roughly four meters.
The counter can be put
in this location.
Width is the same...
Length... wait...
One, two, three, four, five...
Fits five or six tables.
The third...
Tables also fit here.
There is a door...
We can make
a small kitchen there.
The door to the garden.
How nice...
It has even trees.
Perfect for summer.
Yes, yes.
Now I am
on the first floor...
Up the stairs there is a bathroom...
with a tub...
Very big...
Beside there is a room...
We could put the living room.
In this one
we can do the kitchen.
The second floor.
For sure that it is for the bedroom.
Wait...
Yes, I'm fine...
I was so excited...
I had nothing to eat...
I loaded my mobile
and I came straight here...
Yes, I am better...
I must have
low blood pressure...
I will call you later.
Come with me...
Take off your clothes, put this robe on
and wait until I call you.
Any operations?
Any chronic disease?
- Do you take any medication?
- No.
- Your last period?
- Seven weeks ago.
Are you here for a reason?
I want an abortion.
Voluntary interruption of pregnancy.
Alright...
We will do an ultrasound to establish
the exact date of pregnancy and set the date.
By law, we must give you
8 days to think.
Come and lie down.
Lie down.
What, madam?
Anything wrong?
You do not want
the ultrasound?
I do not want the abortion!
- In your name?
- In the name of the child I will give birth.
We can not open an account in that name,
a person that does not exist.
- It will be born in eight months.
- It is not born yet though.
I can only Book
an account number.
Yes, but I want
to pay the money quickly.
Into your account, and transfer
to the new one when it is born.
Alright.
First I will come to the reservation
account number of the child.
- Still has no name. Surname?
- Moreau. M-O-R-E-A-U.
Have you forgotten the appointment
with the Russian?
You did not hear the bell?
Luckily someone came out.
Fabio here...
Tell Andrei we are coming...
Yes, I know, I had a problem
with the taxi. I am sorry.
Quickly, the Russians
have already arrived!
Are you coming like that?
I am pregnant.
What? Are you sure?
- Have you seen a doctor?
- Yes.
What about the Russian?
Why you were not careful?
You and the idiot Sokol?
Next week we will go for abortion.
Be quick now...
- What if I want to have it?
- Forget it.
- The Russian does not want you like that.
- I would ask him to recognize it.
Never mind,
it was not planed like that!
Micky will be one
of the wedding witnesses.
Have something from me.
He circulates papers.
We have worked for him.
Totally trustworthy.
Sometimes the police
interrogate witnesses.
They have to see
you dancing together.
Andrei, you should dance
with her.
If they say they met here,
they need witnesses.
All right for you if I have a child?
Me, a child?
- A child, not with you.
- Marriage yes, child no!
You the wedding,
me the child!
- No, no. We talk later.
- Never mind.
No trouble. It is nothing.
No child, only wedding.
I just asked,
If I was pregnant
Would he marry me?
That was the question.
He would not pay for the child.
We did not agree that.
- Anything wrong?
- All fine.
She asked if he would take her
if she was pregnant.
- Why did you ask him?
- I have my own life, it could happen.
If it happens,
you will have an abortion.
No problem.
There is no child.
If he wants,
a doctor can exam her.
He agrees.
He has a doctor as a friend.
We will let you dance now.
I told you not to mention it.
I just wanted to know
what he is thinking.
Do not do that again.
Never! Do you understand?
We will go
for the abortion tomorrow.
What is wrong?
The doctor who examined her
is coming.
You asked for abortion?
- No!
- Why not?
You have the number of Sokol?
In my mobile, in my bag.
Sokol is not the father,
Claudy is.
The junkie?
- You fucked with the junkie?
- His name is Claudy.
- Are you her partner?
- Friend. I brought her here.
Does the sedative
begin to take effect?
As I have shown on ultrasound,
you are not pregnant.
You are too disturbed
to accept it.
It is better to stay in 2 days
for observation.
- Do you agree?
- Yes
They will prepare your room.
- Individual, if possible.
- I think so.
Why did you tell me you were pregnant?
- I am.
The doctor said you are not.
- Mrs. Sobel?
- Ah, good evening, ma'am.
- Do you remember me? And Claudy?
- Your husband? Of course.
- I have to go.
- Will you come and see me?
One moment, I will look at the
room you were given.
- Can I stay in your room?
- Yes, there is a sofa bed.
- I do not want to return to Albania.
- This is the best solution.
- Tell him to let me stay.
- He will say no.
He does not trust you.
You talk too much.
- You would tell it to the nurse...
- She knew Claudy...
If you love me, understand
why I wanted the child.
There are no child,
do not get crazy.
- I did not want to betray you.
- Shut up!
You must complete this and this, but unsigned.
You must sign in the bank.
Cancel the loan. The bank only keeps
part of the money.
- That amount?
- The bastards!
Call me
when the doctor arrives.
7,000 are gone!
You are like him.
You just want your money back.
He lost his money with the Russians.
It is natural to want them back.
I am talking about you.
You will take as much as you gave
and then I will not see you again.
I will come at Gramsh.
You will not.
Your certificate
for the annulment of the loan...
and the receipt to sign.
Here is your money.
I take back
and the 1,000 I gave you.
5600 is what they had spent?
5600 I paid in?
You know better.
The first track.
I will be in a month in Milan.
Then I'm going
to see you at Gramsh.
What do you want?
See you.
Give me the phone.
- Why?
- For your card.
- What if I call you?
- Aske Spirou.
Why do not you get the highway?
I have to make refuel.
There is a gas station,
I will go while refueling.
Not here,
there is another cheaper.
I have to pee. Stop.
- Can't you wait?
- No
You do not need the bag
to urinate.
They want to kill us.
Do not be afraid,
I will protect you.
We will continue running...
It is safer...
We will start a fire...
I am going to get
some firewood.
Do you hear?
I will not let you die.
Never.
I left your father to die.
You will live.
Sleep now.
We will leave
tomorrow morning.
We will find
something to eat and drink...
We will ask from a house.
Do not worry.
Somebody will help us.
Goodnight
To our friend Henry Ingberg
A film written and directed by
Jean-Pierre and Luc Dardenne