I always preferred to stay at home
It wasn't the best thing for the success
of my music, but too bad
Success counts for little
compared to a clear conscience
I know that my friends and the Führer
have the greatest and most noble ideas
But I also know that they would tear off
mosquitoes' legs, one by one
That always happens to Germans
when they are lonely
It always comes back
Who is lonelier than the men in the Party
when they rule?
Fortunately they're not alone now.
They are in France
France will cure them
And they know it
They know France will teach them
to be truly great and pure-hearted
But for that, they need love
A shared love
I bid you good night
The long spring days arrived
The officer now returned
with the last of the sun's rays
The Fuhrer announces far-reaching
historic decisions will be made
One evening he came down,
a book closed over his finger
He wore the suppressed half smile
of one who knows...
...he is about to make others happy...
He said
I'm sorry to disturb you so early
but I have this for you
It's from 'Macbeth'
Such greatness
It's at the end
Macbeth's power is slipping away
and with it the loyalty of those...
...who finally realise
the depths of his ambition
The noblemen who defend Scotland's
honour waiting for his imminent downfall
One of them describes
the dramatic symptoms of this downfall
Angus: now does he feel
his secret murders sticking on his hands
He is upbraided by a revolt each minute
for his breach of faith
Those he commands
move only in command
Nothing in love
Now does he feel his title
hang loose about him...
...like a giant's robe
upon a dwarfish thief
That's what must give your president
some sleepless nights
I pity this man, despite the contempt
he inspires in me and in you
Those he commands
move only in command, nothing in love
A leader who does not have the love
of his people is a miserable puppet
But can we hope for anything else?
Who but a dreary climber
would have taken on this role?
There needed to be someone
who would sell his country...
...because today France
cannot willingly fall into our open arms...
...without losing her dignity
in her own eyes
Often the most sordid go-between
is responsible for the happiest union
The go-between is no less contemptible
for it, nor the union less happy
The Paris train
I must inform my hosts
I shall be away for two weeks
I'm delighted about going to Paris
I have my leave and I'm going to spend it
in Paris, for the first time
It's a big day for me
The biggest, while I wait for another
which I hope for with all my soul
It will be an even bigger day
I can wait. For years, if need be
My heart is very patient
In Paris I'll see my friends
Many are party to the negotiations
being conducted with your politicians...
...in preparation for the wonderful union
of our two nations
In a way I'll witness this marriage
I want to tell you that I'm happy for France
whose wounds will quickly heal
But I'm even happier for Germany
and for myself
No one will ever have benefited more
from a good deed than Germany will...
...by restoring France's greatness
and freedom
I bid you good night
The French army
threatened to invade England
The Third Coalition took up arms
on the continent
Napoleon entered Vienna,
he triumphed at Austerlitz
In less than 100 days
the Coalition was dissolved
I was sent here by God, King of Heaven,
to drive you out of France
We didn't see him when he returned
We knew he was there, there are
many signs of a guest in the house...
...even if he remains invisible
But for a number of days,
more than a week, we didn't see him
Should I admit to it?
This absence troubled me
I thought about him
I think I felt regret and concern
Neither my niece nor I spoke of it
But when in the evening,
we heard his uneven tread...
...I saw from the way she suddenly and
stubbornly applied herself to her work...
...and from the faint lines
on her face...
...giving her an expression that was
both determined and expectant...
...that her thoughts were similar to mine
I had to go to the German headquarters
to make some declaration about tyres
Come in
For a free Europe
What do you want?
Lieutenant
- Make five copies and send them one.
- Yes, Lieutenant
I didn't say anything about it to my niece,
but women have a feline intuition
All evening she kept looking up
from her work...
...and looking at me
trying to discern something in my face...
...which I forced into an expressionless
blank by diligently drawing on my pipe
She finally dropped her hands
as if she was tired...
...and folding the material asked for
my permission to go to bed early
She kissed me and I think I saw
in her beautiful grey eyes...
...a reproach and a heavy sadness
Once she had left
I felt an absurd anger rise in me
Anger at being absurd
and having an absurd niece
What was this stupidity?
I couldn't answer that
If it was stupidity
it seemed to be deeply ingrained
Three days later,
just as we were finishing our coffee...
...we heard the familiar footsteps
with their irregular tread...
...coming in our direction
I suddenly remembered that winter evening
when we had first heard his footsteps...
...six months earlier
I thought, it's raining today too
My niece had put a square of printed silk
around her shoulders
I was warming my hands on the bowl
of my pipe and it was summer!
I thought I could see a man
behind the door...
...his forefinger raised, ready to knock...
...and delaying the moment...
...for by the very act of knocking,
he would set in motion the future
Finally he knocked
Not with the lightness of one hesitating
nor the brusqueness of shyness overcome
They were three full and long knocks
Calm, assured knocks of a decision
on which there was no going back
I was expecting to see the door open
immediately as usual
But it remained shut and I was overcome
by an uncontrollable uneasiness
He's going to leave
What should I do to behave with dignity
on this evening?
Come in, sir
I learned then that the hands,
if you observe them well...
...can be as expressive as the face
Even better than the face...
...as they more easily escape
the control of the will
I have something serious to tell you
Everything I have said
these past six months
Everything the walls of this room
have heard...
...you have to...
...you have to forget
Such a light!
I saw these victorious men
I spoke to them
They laughed at me
I had been so happy to go there
Treblinka?
- Yes, what about it?
- What's the significance of Treblinka?
- Nothing, nothing now.
- Why "not any more"?
Let's not talk about that.
It's not for the faint-hearted
The mass executions take place
in the gas chambers constructed here...
...with carbon monoxide
and in the cremation ovens
There is currently
a throughput of 500 people a day...
...but improvements are underway...
...so that within two months...
...this figure can be increased
to 2, 000 people a day
Treblinka, 21 March, 1941
The start of spring!
So these gas chambers
are currently in use
No, Treblinka has already
served its purpose. It's done with
There's no one left to execute
Chemical examination post
Medical centre
I'm surprised by your opinion on this
Haven't you realised
that we're duping them?
Do you think we're foolish enough
to let France rise up again?
We're not musicians
Politics isn't the stuff of fantasy.
Why do you think we went to war?
- For the sake of their old Marshal?
- We're not mad
We have the opportunity to destroy
France and that's what we will do
Not just its power, but its spirit as well
That's where the greatest danger lies.
That's our duty
Make no mistake,
we'll do it with smiles and with care...
...but we'll make France crawl on its belly
You've been too influenced by France
in your youth, that's the danger...
...but we'll cure Europe of this disease,
we'll root out this poison
We'll flatter the writers of course...
...but we've already taken
the necessary measures
In Belgium and Holland
and in every country we occupy
French books will be allowed
except technical publications
There will be no literary works.
None!
We'll rip the venom from the beast
Getting frightened
Now they fear for their pockets,
their stomachs, their industry and trade
That's all they're worried about
There are exceptions, of course,
but we'll flatter them to death
- Nothing could be easier.
- Just for a plate of lentils
Do you realise what you're doing?
- Do you realise?
- Do you think we'll falter?
We're made of stronger stuff
You will seal France's downfall
forever
It's a matter of life and death
Violence can conquer but it cannot rule
We know that.
It takes more than an army to rule
Not at the price of the spirit
Not at that price
The spirit? It has already seen a lot
The spirit is immortal.
We're building a thousand year Reich
First we have to destroy
That's our right and our duty
On September 19, 1941
another German soldier was murdered
To atone for this cowardly crime
the following were shot
Wait a moment
A box of matches, please
There is no hope
No hope
Nothing
No one
Not just the modern authors.
Not just Péguy, Proust, Bergson
But all the others, all of these.
All of them
They will extinguish the light
Completely
That light will never shine again on Europe
One of these men was my friend
He was like a brother
We studied together.
We shared a room in Stuttgart
We spent three months together
in Nuremberg
I played him my music
He read me his poems
He was sensitive and romantic
But he left me
He went to read his poems in München,
in Munich
To new friends
He was always writing
asking me to join him
It was he I saw in Paris with his friends
I saw what they had done to him
He was the angriest of them all
He combined anger and laughter
He shouted "It's venomous, we have
to extract the venom from the beast"
I said,
"Do you realise what you're doing?"
I looked at him,
I looked into his bright eyes
He meant what he said,
that's the worst part
They will do what they say...
...methodically and resolutely
I know these stubborn devils
His lips opened and I thought he was
going to launch into some exhortation
I thought he was going to encourage us
to rebel
But no word passed his lips
They said to me,
"It's our right and our duty"
"Our duty"
Lucky the man
who so easily finds the path to his duty
At the crossroads, you're told,
take that route
This route does not take you
towards the shining heights...
...it descends into a gloomy valley...
...deep into the dark, dank forest
Oh God, show me where my duty lies
Can duty ever mean accepting the crime?
I've exercised my rights.
I've asked to join a fighting division
They've finally agreed to it
I'm authorised to leave tomorrow
and return to battle
Towards Hell
I bid you good night
Goodbye
You'd have to have been waiting
to have heard this word
But finally I heard it.
Von Ebrennac heard it, too
Take my things downstairs
It is a fine thing when a soldier disobeys
criminal orders
All set, Lieutenant
Yes, I'm coming
My niece had made me breakfast
as usual
She served me in silence
We drank our coffee in silence
Outside a pale sun was shining
through the mist
It felt very cold to me
October 1941
The publication of this book
was funded by a patriot
The printing was completed under
Nazi Occupation on 20 February 1942