-340.
- Yes
- Can you see the director?
- You can see him tomorrow.
- Make an appointment?.
- Yes, at 12:30, if possible.
The reason?.
A loan, we had already spoken.
I am about to obtain Belgian nationality,
I can now do so.
Please.
Yes.
14,000
In a month, if all goes as planned.
When will we see?.
Agreed.
I hang up now.
I love you.
Me too. Bye.
- A 50 euro, please.
- Sorry.
What do you want?.
I know, and it is the
third time I call.
- Thanks.
- You.
Thank you. How much do I owe you?.
A ten euro.
I go to sleep.
- A game?.
- No.
Close the curtain.
Are you coming?.
Yes
Hello?.
No.
It is not no!.
You've heard?. He said no.
Yes, I have heard.
- Good evening.
- Do not you fancy a game of cards?.
No.
Lower the music!
The music, a little lower!
Lorna?.
What do you want?.
- I have to talk to, open.
- No.
Tomorrow I get up at six.
Tonight I will not leave is over.
You say that every week,
Let me sleep.
No, this time is serious,
but you have to help me.
Swear that I will, Just
because you...
Let me sleep, Claudy!
I ask this because what you need,
to give a goal to my day.
Because I told you I do not
know when he returns.
I do not tell me one time.
Do five, six?.
Are the nine?.
What time then?.
For the seven?. You do well at seven?.
- Whatever.
- If you later You can call me.
Do not forget to return the mattress.
- What are you doing?.
- I must not get out, shut out.
- And if you want to leave?.
- No, if I see others fall. Here.
- No, I will not do it.
- Why?.
In half an hour and want to leave
I'll have to re-open.
No, I swear no! Lorna!
If I then tell the boss that recover
the hours this afternoon.
- Agreed.
- Thanks.
I told him he had half an hour
free at 12 and could return.
- Have told him that back in the afternoon!
- I have done, but do not
understand anything.
It is wrong, is not able to stop.
4 is the ltEn terminai Mr Ventura.t;
&lt;Did you pick, Fabio&gt;
Yes
He says he wants to leave this time.
He has asked me to help you.
Said that and the next
day again be equal.
And if you do not ever get
to leave, What do we do?.
As we expected, an overdose.
- And what the police believe?.
- Of course.
Is not the first time that someone
lies dying from overdoses.
What the fuck these cops.
During six months and then nothing...
,Paf!
About to be Belgian you throw up.
- Can I wait?.
- No, I have to go to the airport.
See the photo of the wedding.
Claudy?.
Where are the police?.
It is not.
I did not feel well, wanted to see.
- Get out of my bed.
- I thought I could.
Get out! Go!
- Look what you've done! Shit!
- Sorry.
Bring a towel.
Not the police.
It was only to return.
Yes
- I do not do it again.
- I do not feel well.
Me da igual.
I arrive late, it gives
me time to eat.
- Do you prepare a sandwich?.
- No.
Who is it?.
- Are you over clothes?.
- Go away!
This is the second time this morning.
Will you go to buy Buscopan?.
I have cramps.
Here, it costs 18 or 19 euros.
Why do I need to do something for you?.
You know, if I find out and falls.
And?. It is not my business.
Get married for money, you will
have twice the divorce!
- I will not give you more!
- I do not mind the money!
You'll ask you to help me!
Buy the Buscopan,!
- C-mpratelo you!
- No!
- Help me, Lorna!
- Get up!
Help me.
Get up!
Enter the name of medicine
on a piece of paper.
Dame.
- What is your name?.
- Buscopan.
- Close out.
- No.
,Lorna!
The key!
You've fallen into the truck!
Go to the cabin 3.
I am.
I have to talk.
Bye. I call you on Sunday.
Good night.
- Buscopan me, please.
- Do you have a prescription?.
No.
- Is it really bad?.
- Not for me, is...
For my husband, had cramps.
They give, but for the night
you need a prescription.
Thank you.
,Lorna!
What?.
What do you want?. Water?.
- Let me.
- Help me get up.
Let me, Claudy!
Help me, I have cramps, I'm bad!
- Take the Buscopan!
- I've taken it,
but I'm wrong.
I beg you.
Wait.
- Here, the doctor called.
- Why do not you call?.
,Lorna, help me! Help me!
Help me!
Takes calls. In D, Dr. Mayr.
- How?.
- In the D, Mayr doctor!
Tell him I want to go to hospital,
that makes me hospitalicen.
Good night.
I am the wife of Claudy Moreau
has left drugs...
- Tell him to take two days longer.
- Want to go to hospital.
Yes, rioja step.
Come on!
- Already registered.
- Does it cost anything?.
No, but tomorrow will bring
healthcare card.
Okay, thanks.
Your money.
- Claudy, your money!
- Save yourself, you do not need it.
Let me just 20 euros to snuff.
Tomorrow I have to bring your
card health, where is it?.
- Above the cabinet, among my things.
- Here.
Put it into my pocket.
Is there someone to look after me?.
The admissions officer said that you send a nurse.
I'm going.
Tomorrow I bring the
CD reader and CDs?.
- Do not leave me alone.
- It is a nurse.
Expects me.
Please.
Yes, low.
- I'm waiting in the taxi.
- Okay.
- Claudy Moreau?.
- Room 110.
The visiting hours are from 16 to 19.
Do not come to visit,
bring a health card.
- Go to admissions, ground floor.
- Okay.
- Can you give these things personal?.
- Is your wife?.
- Yes
- Go you.
- Never mind.
- Well, but is not much.
The last door on the left Room 110.
What do you do?.
Ask for divorce, as he
had led to believe.
No.
Why?.
We had chosen a junkie
to prevent divorce.
And it would take too much.
What if the Russian is in agreement
delaying marriage?.
I have set for June I gave my word.
Dale andalusia wipers.
The button on the left.
Basta.
Now I find myself on a faster
to obtain a divorce.
And who pays 5,000 euros
andalusia drogata?.
I have 5000 of 10,000 euros
I was given the Russian.
- Are you engaged with him or what?.
- I was sweating. I am with Sokol.
- And why did you miss the back?.
- I do not echo back.
But to stop the drug and then
die overdose is strange.
I told you no.
Almost everyone left and
then back again.
Divorce has many risks, it
is best to stay widow.
Sokol,!
I was afraid you'd gone.
The minibus to Germany
has not reached yet.
- Okay without a beard.
- Really?.
- Look...
- What?.
Watch...
I am now Belgian.
Near Colonia in the reactor core.
One minute into the reactor,
1,000 euros.
- Is not it dangerous?.
- I will not do it every month.
- Back here?.
- No, we return directly to Italy.
Takes...
1200 euros.
- How much we have in mind?.
- Nearly 20,000 euros.
Vuelveme to teach the document.
What a joy to live with you.
- We must still wait for the Russian.
- Yes
- Did you see any room for the bar?.
- I deal with it next week.
The bank will give me some direction.
Tell me you love me!
- I love you. What's wrong?.
- None.
The minibus. I gotta go.
The drogata is in the hospital,
wants to leave.
- Again?.
- This time is serious.
- I would prefer instead of divorce...
- Have you spoken to Fabio?.
Do not want to wait for the Russian,
but the divorce will be quicker if
I say that my husband beats me.
- Do not you investigate?.
- I think it always works.
If fails, send all the shit!
- To decide what Fabio.
- I'd rather not die.
It is too late.
Were agreement is only a drug addict.
Lorna, you can not leave now.
We are near the end...
If something does not work, call me.
Come.
That's it. The other arm.
Ya, you can now dress.
2007, 21 hours...
In"17 Street Ferreire,
domicilio marriage.
Circumstances: abstinence heroin.
Wednesday November 14 2007 21:00.
- He said he is now in the hospital.
- Yes, since that Wednesday night.
Okay.
Should have been that very evening.
Present the complaint
before the judge,
but I do not think that is sufficient
to expedite a divorce.
Why?.
Given the position of the hematoma,
could argue that they made you.
It was he wanted drugs.
If at least one witness had...
but we do not have.
Sign here, please.
Because I need money,
and may soon to remarry, I will soon.
- A real marriage?.
- No.
Like ours.
A foreigner who pays to be Belgian.
I've helped you leave
and was not expected.
Now you can help me, right?.
Do you agree?.
I do not want me fiche as abusive.
- Already booked for drugs and theft.
- It is not the same.
I've never stuck to one woman.
And 5000 euros dei divorce, which
could get before, do not you care?.
I can wait.
Collection allowance and
could find work.
If you accept, you will help
avoid back on drugs.
Even after the divorce.
People come.
Come on, Hit me. Hit me!, Claudy!
Come on!
I should have eaten before the king
that I will eat the horse.
Are three and ten.
- Is the last one?.
- We said to all three.
Already.
Come on.
Get up.
Get up!
You said that if I was
you pegaras me!
Come on!
With the fist!
I can not.
You okay?.
Lorna?.
No!
Okay?.
I was stuck and I have beaten
head against the wall.
You should complain to the police.
I want to do.
Do you agree to testify
if the police needed?.
Sure.
Seems not a violent person.
As to trust appearances.
What is your name, madam?.
Monique Sobel.
Can you sign your name on a piece
of paper and phone number?.
Yes, of course.
Fabio wants to see, is
Park behind there.
The girl has done the laundry
and it worked.
I'm afraid, Lorna.
Why?. I have not done anything.
Do not do it.
Do not go to the police.
- And if it works?.
- Do not do it!
You are his wife, thinks of him.
I got it from the rest.
Do not trust me?.
Mandatory.
Okay, go.
,Lorna!
You are also required.
I hope not to send the shit the
matter with the Russians.
It is the best with them
and I can not fail.
Nor do I want. I want my money.
Now you admit it.
Who was that of the other
night at the station?.
- Sokol.
- But Sokol brings beard.
Yes, but it has been shaved.
Someone asked about you.
- Excuse me, back in two minutes.
- Okay.
I left, I wanted to give
you a surprise.
- You mean you're cured?.
- Yes
If I am wrong, can I call
a number of the hospital.
You must resist.
- Can you tell me the house keys?.
- I am by them.
And on the money.
Here.
I return to you, I just want
10 euros for cigarettes.
- We eat together to celebrate?.
- I can not, there are a lot of work.
Prepare dinner for tonight, well I'm busy.
Are you doing well?.
- If you want...
- Then I pick more money
for the purchase.
- What time again?.
- Non know, about seven.
- Okay, bye.
- Yes
- Who is it?.
- Lorna.
Since almost everything is.
I made the pasta carbonara.
A letter has come for you
I have left on their bed.
It is a letter from the judge,
has granted a divorce.
Back in an hour.
I have cooked, and almost is.
You can wait an hour, right?.
- I thought we were going to celebrate!
- I had in an hour, okay?.
Roberto, have you seen Fabio?.
No.
Fabio waits in the taxi at the plaza.
I have not done anything
more, I swear.
It is a consequence of the complaint.
Too late for Russian, can not wait.
,Ask, is only one month!
And you get to marry one weeks after divorce...
They suck!
Why?.
I have a husband who attacked me.
I could hear another man waiting
for the divorce, why not?.
I make the race.
And you give him 5000 andalusia
drogata the day of the divorce?.
Yes, the lame of the 10,000 Russian.
Okay, I'll call it, just
accept expected this month.
- Will you call me when you've talked about?.
- Yes
I spoke with Russian, agrees.
- Get out of here with all your shit!
- Money.
- Let go first! Go!
- Shut up, my money!
I want to talk first!
- Wait here.
- 10 minutes, no more.
And back.
- Give me my money.
- Want to start over?.
- My money!
- Call the hospital.
Give it to me!
Wait, calm down!
- I do not want to start again.
- You got your divorce,
what do you care?.
- Give me my money!
- Now I give you.
- I've forgotten in the laundry.
- Liar! Give it to me!
Give it to me!
Give me the envelope!
- Give me the key!
- No!
Give it!
- Does this bike?.
- What?.
- The blue.
- Yes 50.
I take.
60 euros to open the door and 10 by two keys.
Son 70.
- Average pay?.
- No, it's my fault, the door.
And also my fault.
Agreed.
- 35 per head?.
- Yes
Tome.
- Thanks.
- To you.
Biking all day, so I do not have
time wondering what I can do.
Step to get you at noon?.
I have too much work, I am alone.
Unable to eat with you, just by
having an appointment at noon.
I salute you and me.
Agreed.
I gotta see you, helps
me not to fall.
Now I'm going.
Here, it is better than what you have.
- Bye.
After you came to the family.
They will pay the funeral.
- I had said it would pay me.
- I have rejected.
Can I see him last?.
I have already made the
recognition I can not.
- The agent service is out.
- I'm your wife!
Okay, okay.
Sure you do not want to stay here?.
The polica think they're fleeing.
I've heard?.
The police think you've escaped.
The police have my phone number.
Give it back.
What?.
- The reader of CDs.
- It is not helpful.
Devuelveselo.
You can stay one more week.
- All seem more normal.
- No.
Where do you go?.
Where it was before.
But the rent.
I have already made an agreement
with the girl.
- Do not you take the razor blade and things?.
- No.
Spirou, come and collect things
drogata the bathroom.
Are you going to continue long nose?.
Had I known that the Russian did not expect,
I would have said all andalusia drogata.
I have helped you.
You should agradecermelo,
instead of the muzzle.
Here.
For the work schedule. 1000 euros.
What job?.
Locked up while trying to quit quit.
Lost time, right?.
I do not like to reject it, it seems
that you are no longer with us.
Still with us, right?.
Yes
You are with us since the beginning,
do not forget.
Is it street for six months we
could have gotten an overdose.
- Agreed?.
- Yes
I have 1,000 euros, I give
you the when you want.
Take the photo.
Spirou.
Take the bag.
Does Ms. Moreau is at home?.
Good night.
- Good evening.
- Hey, lady.
We had still some pending.
Is the autopsy report.
Sorry. Under your bag.
- I hope in the car.
- Agreed.
Good night.
Pasen.
Yes?.
The autopsy confirms that
of a drug overdose.
Do you know of any enemy
I wanted dead?.
No.
Anybody interested in doing
disappear with an overdose?.
No.
Just leave the drugs.
Was he depressed?.
No.
Have you ever talked of suicide?.
Had asked for divorce
because he beat.
- Yes
- Did you know that what he had?.
- Since when?.
Since I received the letter from
the judge, four days ago.
What day talking camel?.
Friday, 4 days ago.
That night her husband called
a camel to buy heroin.
Perhaps the news of the divorce?.
According to the camel, prevented
you to buy it.
Yes
Being alone in a moment of depression,
Do you think could have fallen...
and get an overdose volontaria
or accidentally?.
Possibly.
Well. We're going.
- Bye.
- Good evening, Mrs. Moreau.
- Good evening.
Excuse me, are you the
mother of Claudy?.
No, it is the lady who is
in the car behind you.
Thank you.
Good morning, ma'am.
I'm Lorna, the wife of Claudy.
Good morning.
I wanted to restore it.
It is the money he had left.
You had talked about me?.
No.
- Good morning.
- It's my son, his brother.
Is the wife of Claudy.
- What is that?.
- The money that was left to Claudy.
You are his wife, is his.
For the girl...
We do not want your money
and less of Claudy.
Took him.
- All right?.
- Yes
No, I want to be so, near you.
Call me and I come...
1000 kilometers.
I turn to go tonight.
What do we do?.
- Do you sleep?.
- No.
Non haunts you.
Prefer a drug addict Drugs to life.
Sooner or later known to lie.
And who knows die.
So...
we'll see sites you've
found for the bar?.
Agreed.
Here, the number 36.
Is too small.
You're right.
Or not enter a table in
front the counter.
Watch yourself.
Do you see anything?.
Three local...
and a small garden.
Is it big?.
Yes, in summer could
put tables outside.
I like it.
You really have to go tonight?.
Well, the minibus will be six.
Shall we dance?.
Lorna, this is Andrei Aslikov.
- Hello.
- Kosti, the interpreter.
Hello.
Sit down.
- Want something?.
- A beer.
Something for you?.
No, I do not take anything either.
Roberto, a beer.
Do you like your Belgian
identity card.
Please.
Thank you.
Is this real?.
- Do you have the document?.
- Yes
The official document that says
it is widow can marry again.
- All right?.
- It seems so.
I have a breakthrough.
You can take your hand three bundles.
At 20 tickets.
Is the price of a pack of
cigarettes in Moscow.
Want to 1,000 euros to be rejected?.
Like I said, you save.
- See you soon.
What?. Yes, I signed this morning.
I'm so happy, Sokol! Our bar!
Expected to measure.
One, two, three, four...
Roughly four meters.
The counter can be put
in this location.
The second...
Width is the same...
Long... wait...
One, two, three, four, five...
Plus or minus five meters.
Fit five or six tables.
The third...
Tables also fit here.
There is a door...
We can make a kitchen here small.
The door to the garden.
,Que bonito!
You have until trees.
Perfect for summer.
Yes, yes.
Now I am on the first floor.
Up the stairs is a bathroom...
With the tub!
It's great!
Beside there is a room.
We could put the living room.
In this one can do the kitchen.
Climb to the second floor.
Sure that it is the bedroom.
I go up...
Sokol?.
Yes, I'm fine.
I was too excited...
I skipped breakfast and play and eat.
I loaded mobile me I
came directly here.
I'm better.
It will be a lowering of tension.
I call you later.
'Am?.
Can happen.
Thank you.
It was entirely naked, please
the couch and wait.
No.
- Any opreaci-n?.
- No.
- Chronic Disease?.
- Do you take any medication?.
- No.
Last?.
A month ago and three weeks.
What comes for a visit or for
a particular control?.
I want to abort.
Voluntary interruption of pregnancy.
Well.
We will do an ultrasound to establish
The exact date of pregnancy
after the date set the intervention.
By law, we must give
8 days to reflect.
Come on.
Come and lie down.
'Am?.
Lie down.
What, madam?. Do you something?.
'Am?.
Do not want to get the ultrasound?.
I do not abortion!
- What your name?.
- No, a child's name that I have.
We can not open an account in the name
a person that does not exist.
Born in seven months and
a half eight months.
But was not born yet!
I can only Book an account number.
Yes, but I want to pay money quickly.
Log into your account, and transfer
to you when born.
Agreed.
First come to the reservation
account number of the child.
Still has no name. Surname?.
Moreau. M-O-R-E-A-U.
Yes?.
Have you forgotten the appointment
in Russian?.
I fell asleep.
I have been calling me and jumping
the answering machine.
Yes, I'm Fabio.
Can you tell Andrei that got away?.
Yes, I know, I had a problem
with the taxi.
I ask a thousand apologies.
Quickly, the Russians
have already arrived!
Do not have anything else to get?.
I am pregnant.
What?.
Are you sure?.
- Have you seen a doctor?.
- Yes
What about Russian?.
,Could be careful! What the fuck Sokol.
Same to you! Damn!
Abort coming weeks qu,
I borrow money.
Now.
- What if I have it?.
- Forget it.
The agreement with Russia
is not expected.
- I would ask you to recognize it.
- Never mind, not in the pact.
Come on.
Micky introduces you to one of
the wedding of two witnesses.
- Good evening.
- Nice.
Hello.
- Pdete something.
- Yes, thank you.
Circulated newspapers.
I have worked for him and Lorna.
Of confidence.
Sometimes the police
interrogate witnesses.
Cheers!
You should dance together,
that you see.
Andrei, you should dance with her.
The waiter can confirm conocais you.
All right for you if I have a child?.
Me, a child?.
- A boy Andrei?.
- No, mine, not you.
Marriage itself, not children.
No, you just married,
I'm the child!
No, no. We talk, never mind.
No trouble is nothing.
No child wants you, just married.
Only to be told that if pregnant
As we married.
Just a question.
No, do not agree, then would
to pay child support.
- You do not want unexpected.
- What?.
Nothing.
Andrei asked if he married
be pregnant.
- Why have you asked?.
- Nothing...
- In my life, it could happen.
- If true, abort.
Say you're quiet no children.
You can make a medical examination.
He says he agrees with the
doctor, has a friend.
I left dancing.
I asked you not to say.
I just wanted to know
what you thought.
Never again! Never again, right?.
,Do what I tell you and stop!
Tomorrow morning abortions,
I go with you.
What happens?.
The doctor who visited arrives away.
Thank you.
.Ask about abortion?.
Do you claim abortion?.
No.
Why?.
Got the number of Sokol?.
On the phone, inside the bag.
Sokol is not the father, Claudy is.
Is the drug addict?.
- Fucking with the drug addict?.
- It's called Claudy.
Let her!
- Good evening.
- Is your husband, your partner?.
- A friend, I brought the car.
Does the sedative begins
to take effect?.
As I have shown on ultrasound,
you are not pregnant.
Refuses to admit it is disturbed.
It is better to stay in 3 days observation
to make some consideration.
Do you agree?.
- Yes
- Okay.
Prepare the room Come and get it.
- Individual, if possible.
- I think so.
Thank you.
Why tell me you were Pregnant?.
- I am.
- You said you're not.
I know better than you!
No.
Mrs Sobel?.
- Ah, good evening, ma'am.
- Do you remember me?.
- Yes, yes.
- Also from Claudy?.
Does your husband?. True.
Sorry, Now I gotta go.
- Come to see me?.
- Yes
One moment, I look at the
room you have given.
- Can I stay in your room?.
- Yes, there is a sofa bed.
- I do not want to return to Albania.
- This is the best solution.
- Tell him to let me stay.
- He will say no.
You talk too much, no
longer trusts you.
- All wanted to nurse.
- Claudy knew y...
Shut up!
If you love me, understand
why wanted the child.
There are no children, 're crazy.
- I did not want to betray.
- Do not want to talk more.
You must complete this and
this, but unsigned.
You must sign in front of the bank.
,7000 euros less, bravo!
You are like him.
You just want to recover your money.
I've done to lose money
of the Russians.
- It is normal to want it back.
- I meant you.
Stay with what I lost
and will not see you.
I will go to Gramsh.
Not going.
Your certificate of
annulment Loan...
and the receipt to sign.
Here's your money.
Bye.
Cojo also 1,000 euros you had more.
Had spent 5600 euros?.
5600.s what they had spent?.
You know better than me.
A month in Milan.
Then I'm going to
get you to Gramsh.
Sokol?.
What?.
See you.
- Give me the phone.
- Why?.
SIM card.
- What if I call you?.
- We asked Spirou.
- Why do not you get the highway?.
- I have to make gasoline.
There is a gas station,
go to while refueling.
Not here, there is another cheaper.
For, I have to pee.
- Can not wait?.
- No.
You do not need the bag to urinate.
They want to kill you.
Do not be afraid, I protect you.
Run a little more.
It is safer.
If we could fire.
I'm going to get some firewood.
Do you hear?.
Do not let die.
Never.
I left your father dying.
You will live.
Sleep now.
We will continue tomorrow morning.
Looking for something
to eat and drink.
Ask in any home.
Do not worry.
Somebody help us.
To rest.
Our friend Henry Ingberg