- 340.
- Yes.
Can I see the manager?
I can give you an appointment
tomorrow.
Yes, at 12:30 if possible.
What's it about?
A loan I talked about to him.
I'll be Belgian soon,
so I can do it.
Yes.
Fourteen thousand.
In a month, if it all goes smoothly.
When do I see you?
All right...
I'll hang up now.
I love you.
Me too.
Bye.
One euro fifty, please.
Excuse me.
What is it?
I know.
You called me three times already.
Thank you.
Thanks.
What do I owe you?
One euro ten.
I'm going to bed.
Want to play cards?
No.
Close the curtains.
Coming?
No.
I said no!
You heard? I told him no.
Yes, I heard.
Good night.
No cards then?
No.
Turn the music down!
The music... Not so loud!
Lorna...
Lorna!
What?
I want to talk. Let me in.
No.
I have to be up at six tomorrow.
I'm not going out tonight. I quit.
Like every week. Let me sleep.
I can stick it out this time
if you help me.
Promise me you'll help.
On my own, I...
Let me sleep, Claudy!
I need to know,
to set myself a goal for the day.
I don't knowwhen I'll be back.
Just give me a time.
Any time.
Five? Six?
Nine?
What time? Seven? Seven, ok?
If you want.
If you're late, you can call me.
Don't forget
to put your mattress back.
- What are you doing?
- I mustn't go out. Lock me in.
- You won't go out?
- I have to resist.
Lock me in.
I'm not doing that.
Why not?
You'll want to go out
and I'll have to come back.
No, I promise. Lorna!
If I get back late,
tell the boss I'll stay tonight.
I'll tell her.
Thanks.
He told them I could come back
during my break.
So say evenings only.
I said that. He didn't understand.
He's a mess. He's quitting.
Terminal 4.
Mr Ventura.
Can you take it, Fabio?
I'll take it.
He wants to quit this time.
He asked me to help.
He'll be high again tomorrow.
If he does manage to quit,
what do we do?
As planned, we give him an OD.
Will the police believe it?
Of course they will.
Junkies quit, use again
and OD all the time.
Damn cops!
Nothing for six months till now.
Just when you become Belgian.
Wait for me?
I have to go to the airport.
Showthem the wedding photo.
Claudy?
Where's the police?
Not here.
I felt bad, I wanted to see you.
Get out of my bed.
- I thought I could.
- On it, not in it!
Look what you've done!
Sorry.
Get a cloth.
The police weren't here.
He just wanted me to come back.
Don't ever do this again.
I didn't feel good.
I don't care.
I'll be late.
I won't have time to eat.
Shall I make a sandwich?
Who is it?
- Want anything?
- Get lost!
He's been twice already.
Can you get Buscopan for my cramps?
It costs 18 or 19 euros.
Why should I go for you?
If I see the others, I won't resist.
That's not my problem.
You got paid to marry.
You'll get double that to divorce.
- Don't ask me nothing!
- Screwthe money!
Just help me. Get some Buscopan!
Get it yourself!
Help me, Lorna!
- Get up.
- Help me...
Get up.
Write the name down for me.
Give me that.
- What's it called?
- Buscopan.
Lock me in.
No.
Lorna!
My key!
It fell in the truck!
Good evening. Number 3.
It's me.
I wanted to talk to you.
Goodbye. I'll call on Sunday.
Good evening.
I'd like some Buscopan, please.
Do you have a prescription?
No.
Are you in pain?
No, it's not me, it's...
It's my husband. He's having cramps.
All right,
but usually I need a prescription.
Thank you.
Lorna!
What's wrong?
What?
Water?
Let go.
Help me up.
Let go of me, Claudy.
Let go!
Help me up, the cramps hurt!
Take the Buscopan.
I already did but it hurts.
Please...
Wait...
Here, call my doctor.
Why don't you call him?
Lorna! Help me! Help me!
Help me...
Under D. Call Doctor Mayro.
- What?
- Under D. Doctor Mayro.
Tell him he has to get me
into hospital.
Good evening.
This is Claudy Moreau's wife.
He says he's coming off drugs...
It's been two days.
He wants to go to hospital.
Yes, I put him on.
Come on.
There, he's registered.
I don't have to pay?
No, but bring his health card
tomorrow.
All right. Thank you.
Your money.
Claudy, your money.
Keep it. I don't need it here.
Just leave me 20 for cigarettes.
I have to bring your health card.
Where is it?
On my shelfwith my stuff.
Put it in my pocket. The inside one.
Will someone take care of me?
The receptionist said
a nurse would come.
I'm going.
Can you bring me
my CD player and discs?
Lorna!
Don't leave me.
The nurse will be here soon.
Wait for him with me.
Please.
Yes, I'm coming down.
I'll be at the taxi park.
- Claudy Moreau?
- Room 110.
But visiting hours are from 4 to 7.
I'm not visiting.
I've brought his health card.
Admissions is on level zero.
All right. Could you give him this?
It's his stuff.
Are you his wife?
- You can take it to him.
- No, it's ok.
Go on, but don't stay long.
The last door but one on the left.
Room 110.
Claudy?
What should we do?
Divorce, like he thinks we will.
No.
Why not?
We picked a junkie
to avoid a divorce.
It would take too long.
What if the Russian's ready
to delay the wedding?
We agreed on June.
I'll keep my word.
Press the windshield washer.
The left-hand lever.
Ok!
I'll try to find out
if we can get a quicker divorce.
Who'll give the junkie his 5,000?
Take it out of my 10,000
from the Russian.
You fucking the junkie?
Screwhim. I'm with Sokol.
Why back down then?
I'm not backing down.
But if he ODs now, it'll look weird.
I told you it won't.
Nearly all junkies who quit
start using again.
The cops look into divorces.
You need to be a widow.
Sokol!
I was worried you'd left.
The van for Germany isn't here yet.
I like you without the beard.
Look!
You're Belgian now.
Near Cologne, in the main reactor.
One minute inside: 1,000 euros.
Isn't it dangerous?
Only if you do it every month.
Will you come back?
No, we go straight to Italy.
Here's 1,200.
- What's on the account?
- Almost 20,000.
Let me see your card again.
I'm so glad I'm with you.
We must wait for the Russian.
Yes.
Seen places for the snack bar?
I'll go next week.
The banker will give me
a couple of addresses.
Tell me you love me.
I love you. What's wrong?
Nothing.
That's the van. I have to go.
The junkie's in hospital,
trying to quit.
Again?
He's serious this time.
Maybe we should get divorced, not...
You talked to Fabio?
He won't make the Russian wait
but a divorce is quick
if my husband beats me.
Will they investigate?
Yes, but I hear it always works.
If it doesn't,
you'll wreck everything.
Let Fabio decide.
I'd rather he didn't die.
It's too late. We agreed.
He's just a junkie.
Listen, Lorna.
You can't give in
this close to our goal.
If anything's wrong, call me.
Come closer.
Nowyour other arm.
All right, you can get dressed.
17, Rue Ferreire,
at the marital home.
Circumstances:
Drug withdrawal. Heroin.
Wednesday, November 14th, 2007,
at 9 pm.
You say he's in hospital now?
Yes, since Wednesday, that evening.
All right.
You should have come then.
We'll file the complaint
but I don't think it's enough
for a fast-track divorce.
Why not?
The bruising
could easily be self-inflicted.
It was him. He wanted his fix.
It would help if you had a witness,
but you don't.
Sign here, please.
I need money.
The sooner I can remarry,
the sooner I'll get it.
A real marriage?
No.
Like us.
With a foreigner
who'll pay to be Belgian.
I'm helping you quit!
That wasn't planned.
Can't you help me too?
You'll do it?
I won't go on file as violent.
You're a junkie and a thief.
It's not the same.
I've never hit a woman.
The 5,000 euros for the divorce,
that doesn't interest you?
I can wait.
I'm on minimum benefit.
Maybe I'll find a job.
If you agree,
I'll help you stay clean,
even after we divorce.
Someone's coming.
Go on, hit me. Hit me, Claudy!
Do it!
You should have played your king
before my queen.
It's ten past three.
One last hand?
We said three o'clock.
She's there.
Come on.
Get up.
Get up!
You said you'd hit me if I stayed.
Do it.
With your fist!
I can't.
Are you ok?
Lorna?
Ok?
He hit me
and my head struck on the wall.
You should go to the police.
I'll do that.
Will you be my witness
if the police ask?
Yes, of course.
He didn't seem violent.
But you never can tell.
What's your name?
Monique Sobel.
Can you put your name and number
on a bit of paper?
Of course.
Fabio wants you.
He's on the parking lot.
It worked for a girl
at the dry-cleaner's.
You scare me, Lorna.
Why? I've done nothing against you.
You don't do this.
You don't go to the cops.
- What if it worked?
- You don't do it!
You're his wife. Look after him.
The rest's up to me.
You don't trust me anymore?
I have to. I need you.
Ok, you can go.
Remember, you need me too.
Don't make me screwup on this deal.
It's my first with the Russians.
I don't want that either.
I want my money.
That's the Lorna I know.
Who was the guy at the station?
Sokol.
Sokol has a beard.
Yes, but he shaved it off.
Lorna!
Someone to see you in the shop!
Sorry, I'll only be a minute.
I'm out. I wanted to surprise you.
You're cured then?
Yes.
If ever I feel bad,
I can call a number at the hospital.
You have to resist.
I need the apartment keys.
I'll get them.
And my money too.
Here.
I just want 10 euros for cigarettes.
Want lunch to celebrate?
I can't, I have too much work.
I'll make dinner tonight.
It'll keep me busy. Ok?
If you want.
I'll need more money then,
to buy food.
When'll you be back?
I don't know. Around seven.
See you later.
Who is it?
It's nearly ready.
Cheese and ham macaroni.
There was a letter for you.
It's on your bed.
It's from the judge.
I'm getting the divorce.
I'll be back in an hour.
Dinner's nearly ready.
Can't you wait?
We're celebrating me getting out.
We'll do it in an hour, ok?
Roberto, have you seen Fabio?
Fabio's waiting on the square.
I didn't do anything else, I swear.
It's that complaint I filed.
The Russian won't wait any longer.
Ask him. It's only another month.
A wedding two weeks
after the divorce? That stinks.
Why?
My husband beats me.
Can't I meet someone
before the divorce is final?
Ok, I'll take it.
You'll pay the junkie's 5,000
when you divorce?
Yes, out of the Russian's 10,000.
Ok. I'll see if he can wait a month.
You'll call me after?
I spoke to the Russian. He agrees.
Take your shit away!
- My money!
- He goes first!
Just get out!
I want my money!
I need to talk to you.
Wait downstairs.
- Ten minutes, no more.
- I'll be there.
Give it to me!
- You're using again?
- My money!
Let's call the hospital...
Give me my money!
Wait. Calm down.
I don't want you
to get hooked again.
You got your divorce. Hand it over!
I'll give it to you.
It's at the shop.
You're lying! Hand it over!
Give me the envelope!
Give me the key!
Give it to me!
Do the bikes work?
Which one?
- The blue one.
- Yeah.
50 euros.
I'll take the bike.
60 euros to open your door,
10 for two keys, that makes 70.
Half and half?
No, the door's my fault.
It's my fault too.
All right.
35 each.
I'll ride all day.
It'll give me something to do.
Can I come by at midday?
I'll be alone at the shop.
Not to have lunch.
It gives me a goal
in the middle of the day.
I'll stop by and leave again.
All right.
I need to see you. It helps me.
I'm going now.
Here, I'd rather you keep it.
See you later.
The family was here.
They'll handle the funeral costs.
I said I would.
I told them but they refused.
Can I see him one last time?
You already identified him.
I can't...
The duty officer has left.
I'm his wife.
All right.
Sure you won't stay here?
It looks like you're running away.
Did you hear me?
The police may get suspicious.
They have my phone number.
Give that back.
What?
The player.
He won't need it now.
Give it to her.
You could stay another week.
It would look more normal.
No.
Where will you go?
Where I was before.
You sublet that place.
I worked it out with the girl.
Not taking his razor and stuff?
No.
Spirou! Get the junkie's stuff
from the bathroom.
Going to sulk much longer?
You'd have told the junkie
if you knew
the Russian wouldn't wait.
I helped you keep going.
Thank me instead of sulking.
Here...
For the extra work, another 1,000.
What extra work?
Taking care of him when he tried
to quit was work, right?
Refusing means you're not with us.
Are you still with us?
Yes.
You always have been, ok.
Because you kept quiet,
we were able to make him OD.
Ok?
Yes.
The 1,000 is yours when you want it.
Take the photo.
Spirou...
Take a bag.
Good evening, is Mrs Moreau in?
Good evening.
Mrs Moreau,
we have a fewmore questions,
following the autopsy.
I'll take your bag.
- We'll wait in the car.
- Ok.
Come in.
The autopsy
confirms it was an overdose.
Do you know
if anyone wanted him dead?
No.
Someone who'd gain from killing him
with an overdose?
No.
He'd just come off drugs.
Was he depressed?
No.
Did he mention suicide?
You filed for divorce
because he beat you...
Yes.
He knewyou were going to get it?
Since when?
Since I got the judge's letter.
Four days ago.
What day did the dealer say?
Friday. Four days ago.
That evening, your husband
called a dealer to buy heroin.
Maybe after hearing
about the divorce?
The dealer says
you stopped him from buying it.
Yes.
Alone and depressed,
could he have taken a fix
and deliberately
or accidentally overdosed?
Possibly.
All right.
We'll be going now.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Mrs Moreau.
Excuse me.
Are you Claudy's mother?
No, the lady in that car there.
I'm Lorna, Claudy's wife.
I wanted you to have this.
It's the money he had left.
Did he talk about me?
No.
My son. His brother.
This is Claudy's wife.
What's that?
Claudy's money. What he had left.
You're his wife. It's yours.
For the little girl.
We don't need your money, or his.
Take it.
No...
Just like that. That feels good.
You call me, I come.
1,000 kilometres.
I leave again tonight.
What shall we do?
Lorna...
Are you asleep?
No.
You shouldn't worry about it.
Ajunkie prefers drugs to life.
He'd have started using again
and died one day.
Shall we take a look at the places
for the snack bar?
All right.
It's here. Number 36.
It's tiny.
Yes.
There won't be any room for tables.
Come on, take a look.
Can you see?
There are three rooms.
And a garden.
Is it big?
Yes, we can serve outdoors
in summer.
I like it here.
You have to go tonight?
Yes, the truck leaves at six.
Want to dance?
Lorna, meet Andrei Aslikov.
Kostia, the interpreter.
Sit down.
Want a drink?
A beer.
You want another?
Nothing for him. Me neither.
Roberto, a beer!
He wants to see her Belgian ID card.
- You have the paper?
- Yes.
This certifies she's a widow
and free to marry.
They paid a deposit.
Take your share. Three wads.
20-euro notes.
What they sell a carton
of cigarettes for in Moscow.
Want the 1,000 you turned down?
I said I'd keep it for you.
See you.
What?
Yes, I signed this morning.
I'm so happy, Sokol!
It's our snack bar.
Wait, let me measure it.
Four metres, more or less.
That's the room for the counter.
The second...
Same width. The length...
Just a second...
Almost five metres long.
We could have five or six tables.
And the third room...
We can have more tables.
And there's a door...
We can make a small kitchen.
I'm going out into the garden.
It's beautiful.
It even has trees.
Ideal for serving outdoors
in summer.
I'm on the first floor.
Opposite the stairs,
there's a bathroom with a tub.
Pretty big.
Another room...
It can be our living room.
And another room
where we can have a kitchen.
The second floor now.
There have to be bedrooms.
Hold on...
Yes, I'm fine.
I was so excited...
I haven't eaten all day.
I got a phone card
and came straight here.
Yes, I'm fine.
It must be lowblood pressure.
I'll call you later.
Mrs Deda?
Come with me.
Undress, put the smock on
and I'll call you.
No.
Any surgical operations?
Any chronic illness?
No.
Are you on any medication?
Your last period?
A month and three weeks ago.
Are you here for a specific reason?
I want an abortion.
A termination of pregnancy.
All right...
We'll do a scan
to date the pregnancy,
then set a date for the operation.
There's a legal wait of 8 days
for you to think it over.
Come and lie down.
Lie down.
What is it? Is something wrong?
You don't want the scan?
I'm not aborting.
In your name?
In the name of the baby I'm having.
Only people who really exist
can have accounts.
He'll be born in about eight months.
But he hasn't been born yet.
What I can do is reserve
an account number for him.
I'd like to put money on it now.
Put it on your account
and we'll transfer it
after he's born.
All right.
First I'll reserve
the account number.
First name, not yet. Surname?
Moreau.
M-O-R-E-A-U.
We're meeting the Russian!
I fell asleep.
I called and tried the buzzer.
I'm lucky someone came out.
It's Fabio.
Tell Andrei we're on our way.
I know, trouble with my taxi.
I'm sorry.
Move it. They're waiting.
You're going like that?
I'm expecting a baby.
What?
Are you sure?
You saw a doctor?
And the Russian?
Couldn't you have been careful?
Sokol's dumb! You too, damn it!
We'll get you an abortion next week.
Hurry it up.
- What if I want to keep it?
- No way!
The Russian
doesn't want you pregnant.
He won't have to recognize it.
I don't care. It wasn't planned.
Come on.
Meet Micky, one of your witnesses.
Have a drink on me.
He delivers papers.
I've worked for him, Lorna too.
Totally trustworthy.
The police
may try questioning witnesses.
Cheers.
People should see you
dance together.
Andrei should dance with her.
If they say they met here,
they'll have witnesses.
You ok if I have child?
Me, baby?
Baby Andrei?
No, me baby, not with you.
Marriage yes, baby no.
You just marriage, me baby.
No, we'll talk some other time.
Forget it.
No problem, it's nothing.
No child with you, just marriage.
It's not that.
I asked if I was pregnant,
would he marry me anyway?
I was just asking.
No. He won't pay the child's upkeep.
He wants it to go as planned.
What's up?
Nothing.
She asked if Andrei would marry her
if she was pregnant.
Why ask him that?
No reason. I have my life.
It can happen.
If it does, you'll abort.
No problem, there's no child.
If he wants,
a doctor can examine her.
He agrees. A doctor friend of his.
We'll let you dance now.
I told you not to mention it.
I wanted to knowwhat he thought.
Never do that again! Ever!
Understand?
You do as I say and that's it!
I'll take you to abort tomorrow.
What's wrong?
The doctor
who examined her is coming.
You asked about an abortion?
No.
Why not?
Got Sokol's number?
On my phone, in my bag...
Sokol's not the father. Claudy is.
The junkie?
- You fucked the junkie?
- His name's Claudy.
Shut up!
Are you her husband?
A friend. I drove her here.
Is the sedative helping?
As I showed you on the scan,
you're not pregnant.
You're too upset to accept it.
It's best to stay a few days
so we can run tests.
Do you agree?
Yes.
Good.
Someone will take you to your room.
Can it be a single room?
Yes, I think so.
Why did you say you were pregnant?
I am.
The doctor says you aren't.
She should know.
No.
Mrs Sobel?
Good evening.
- Do you remember me?
- Yes.
- And Claudy too?
- Your husband? Of course.
I have to go.
- You'll come to see me?
- Yes.
I'll check which room you're in.
Can I stay the night?
If you want.
There's a foldaway bed.
- I'm not going back to Albania.
- It's for the best.
- Ask him to let me stay.
- He won't agree.
He doesn't trust you.
You talk too much.
You'd have told that nurse.
- She knew Claudy. I...
- Shut up!
If you loved me, you'd know
why I want the child.
There is no child.
Stop this craziness.
- I didn't want to cheat on you...
- Stop it.
Fill it out here and here.
But don't sign it
until you meet the banker.
She cancelled the loan, so the bank
takes part of the deposit.
This sum here.
Bastards.
Call me once the doctor's been.
All right.
7,000 euros wasted. Bravo.
You're like him.
You just want
to get your money back.
You lost him money
with the Russians.
He wants it back. It's normal.
I'm talking about you.
You'll take what you put in
and I'll never see you again.
I'll come to Gramsh.
No, you won't.
Your copy confirming
the cancellation of the loan...
The receipt to sign...
And your money.
Goodbye.
I'm taking back
that extra 1,000 I gave you too.
I paid in 5,600?
5,600 was what I paid in?
You knowbetter than I do.
The first truck.
I'll be in Milan a month.
Then I'll come to see you in Gramsh.
What?
See you soon.
Give me your phone.
Why?
Your SIM card.
What if I need to call?
Ask Spirou.
Not taking the motorway?
I need to get petrol.
There's a place.
I'll pee while you get petrol.
Not this one.
I know a cheaper place.
I need to pee. Stop.
Can't you wait?
No.
You don't need your bag to piss.
They want to kill us.
Don't be scared. I'll protect you.
We'll keep running.
It's safer.
We can make ourselves a fire.
I'll get us firewood.
You hear that?
I won't let you die.
Ever.
I let your father die.
You'll live.
We'll sleep now.
We'll leave tomorrow morning.
We'll find something
to drink and eat.
We'll go and ask at a house.
Don't worry.
Someone's bound
to give us something.
Sleep tight.
Subtitles: Lan Burley
Subtitling: C.M.C. - Paris