Tokuma Japan Corporation presents:
Over there!
Damn, they're going at it!
Man, even Hontani got knocked out cold!
Baba's the only one left now.
The Club's rep is history!
Damn! The entire Karate
Club is dead meat!
Captain Baba's the only one left!
Hey, that's Hyoudo, right?
He's kicking ass!
He's such a talented fighter,
number one in the club.
It's not surprising you've got
the hots for him, Megumi.
Hey, over there! There's
your rival!
Takayanagi is not just in Hyoudo's
class, but also in his clubs...
Ohh... I'm so jealous! She gets
to be with him all the time...
And, on top of that, she's charming...
...and she's got a
positive attitude.
On the other hand, look at you!
At this rate, she's gonna beat you
out. Is that what you want?
But... when I meet
Riki face to face...
...I never know
what to say...
...so all I can do is to watch
him from a distance.
Captain Baba, if you please...!
Sure... But it's not too late
to change your mind...
Think about it. If you quit
Karate, what will you do?
After defeating you, Baba,
I'll fight the masters...
...of all the schools, until I'm the
best in the world. That's all.
My, how glorious! The world's
best, huh? Cocky, aren't we!
You never know until you try, Baba.
Not bad, Hyoudo! Try
this on for size!
You dodged my Seikenzuki punch!
They don't call you "Captain" for nothing.
You're trying to regain your
mental balance...
...by maintaining a space between
us to observe my movements.
But, Captain Baba, I've made up my mind...
...and after I've finished
with you...
...my study of unconventional
techniques will continue.
Then I'll be the best damn fighter
in the entire world!
Gotcha!
Baba!
C... Captain! Captain!
Oh? Ryou, what's up?
Watcha doin' here?
Look who's talking! What's
up with you, Riki?
Huh? Oh, you mean
about today...?
I just wanted to test my limits,
you know, not just Karate...
You never told me anything
like that! Why so sudden?
Hey, wait!
I don't know why myself, but
I just felt like fighting!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Riki, do you know what you're doing?
Oh, leave me alone!
No I won't! Baba said he's gonna
resign because you beat him.
What will happen to our Club then?
Who knows.
What're you talking about?!
It's all your fault!
Baba said that in order for me to quit, I had
to knock out the entire club... So I did.
Besides, I had to quit the club in order to
compete with guys from other clubs.
Figures. You're only thinking
about yourself.
And what about the meet next month?!
Without you, we're screwed.
Hey, wait!
I haven't been doing karate
for the good of the club...
...and I wasn't competing for the
good of the school either!
You bastard! Don't you
run away from me!
I haven't finished talking
to you! Riki!
Well, see ya tomorrow!
Bye now!
You stubborn fool!
Legend of the True Demons
Battle Royal High School.
Lord Byoudo, the Dimensional
Gate has been opened...
As the legend foretells, when
the Gate is opened...
...the Leopard-headed warrior will appear
and face a being of the Dark Realm...
At that time, the legendary
warrior shall be born...
Your Majesty, thy power is
flowing into the Gate...
"Flowing?" You mean, my powers are
flowing into another dimension?
A dimension into which a passage is open?
Aye. Perhaps, it is being transmuted
into the power of Fate...
...the power that will produce
the legendary warrior.
Or perhaps it is already taking some
form in the other dimension...
If that is not the case, then perhaps
it is a trap laid by someone...
Perhaps it is the work of the heavens,
a plot to limit your Majesty's power...
...but why would anyone
wish such a thing...?
I care not...
The Dimensional Gate has been opened!
Your Highness!
The time has come to fight!
OK, so what I had just pointed
out to you was...
Hmm...? What's wrong,
Hyoudo?
Oh! Riki, you're
drooling!
The time has come to fight!
Yo, Riki! Wake up! You're
still in class!
That numbskull! What's
he thinking?!
Wake up, Hyoudo!
Yowch!
Damn, was I dreaming?!
Dreaming what?!
Stand!
Hey, Hyoudo! I'm not
done with you!
Bow!
Lunch, dudes!
I'm gonna go buy some baked
goodies. Want anything?
Could you get me my usual?
No problemo!
There's a faculty meeting this afternoon to
discuss the mess you caused yesterday...
...and now you fall asleep in my class,
and even mumble while you're at it!
You're a real whiz!
You see, the Karate Club Captain, Baba,
is resigning to take responsibility.
The Club advisor, Mr. Ishiguro,
is not very happy.
It's possible you might get
left back, Hyoudo!
So, you did that?!
Everybody in school is talking about
the "Leopardmask Man!"
Riki thinks about nothing but putting
himself in the spotlight!
You beat the entire Karate Club?
Yup...
Didn't know you were that strong!
What are you guys talking about?
You don't know?!
Nope...
He fought the entire Karate Club, and
beat them all, just so he could quit!
No shit! Really? Wow!
But, why did you have to
wear a Leopard mask?
To get attention.
Besides, I found it in my house.
And I thought it was cool, so...
With this on, I'll be the #1 fighter
in the world, in all schools!
Captain Baba! Please reconsider,
for the sake of the Club!
Thanks...
...but I won't change
my mind.
I just handed in my resignation. You
see, I wasn't strong enough.
But, it was all Riki's fault...
No, it was all mine.
Captain Baba!
I'm sorry if I sound selfish...
Here ya go! They didn't have
meat-pies today...
...so I brought cutlets and
egg sandwiches instead.
Twelve of 'em, as usual!
Thanks!
And so, I'll wear my mask like
a guerilla soldier...
...and I'll beat the hell out
of the other schools.
Eventually, the media is gonna flip over me!
And then I'll be in the papers
and on TV everywhere...
...and I'll get to mouth off
about everything!
And then? And then?
Then what?
Listen. Then, I'll get on the nerves of
those pro fighters with big egos...
...and when they accept my challenge,
the rest is history.
I'll just keep on kicking their butts,
and I'll be a major celebrity!
A World-Class celebrity from our
class?! That's awesome, man!
Say, if you'd like, you can have this.
Huh...? Are you sure?
I mean, if a future celebrity
has my lunch now...
...when you become real celebrity, I can
brag about it in my neighborhood!
Oh yeah? Thanks, man!
Here, it's for you!
Then, if you don't mind!
Us country guys, we're so square!
You can have mine too!
Gee, thanks!
Have mine too! Please!
Thanks!
Mine too!
And mine, please!
Why, everybody, thank you very much!
Huh...?! Ryou, you too?
You got a lunch for me?
Oh, you want my autograph!
What're you so happy about?! Baba
resigned from the Club, you know!
Master Byoudo... Pray, caution...
Do not underestimate them...
Naive fools...
Hmm...?
Two...
Three...
I see...
Why'd you do that...?!
Hey...? Guys?!
Uh-oh... Did I hit my head
too hard or...
She's cold...
It's hard! Huh...?
A... A classroom?!
What happened to the hallway?!
I DID hit my head hard!
Lemme see what's there.
That's weird... I didn't know we
had a classroom like this!
Lend me your ears...
Among my world's many legends,
one foretells this tale...
...that when the Gate of Light opens, a
Leopard-headed warrior will appear.
It is in his Otherworld that a fierce
battle will be fought...
But before the victor can conquer
the two worlds...
...he becomes the Leopard-headed
warrior, whom I must face.
The time that has been foretold has come!
Oh, fuck that shit! I'll kick your
ass! Come out and fight!
"I am Byoudo, Master of the Dark Realm..."
Byoudo, the Master of the Dark Realm?!
Damn! There's a few
too many of them!
I am Byoudo, the Master of the Dark Realm...
You're the Harem-King that
I saw in my dream!
I had imagined that it was merely
a matter of defeating you...
However, there is one thing
I must confirm...
W... What the...?
Got anything else you wanna show me?
Just as I had expected...
This was all a diabolical
trap, sprung on me...
...by someone who could not tolerate
my relentless increase in power.
Whatever you say, you fruitcake!
Stop mumbling and get on with it.
What's next...? Get a move on!
As you wish.
Raise your left arm...
And then what?
Ah...! Shit!
You think you're funny...
You asshole...
Don't be foolish...
You paralyzed me!
I've realized, by coming here,
what the legend is saying.
By making me defeat you, it is warning
against extravagance on my part.
Huh...?
Don't you realize that you are another part
of me, a part that exists in this world...
You are my counterpart.
Oh shit... this guy's
a total nutcase!
Thanks, but I already have a father...
...besides, it's almost time for class, so
we'll have to continue this chat later...
You think I'm a "nutcase."
You want to run away.
Oh my counterpart, what
a pitiful soul you are.
You can read my mind too?!
Come where I can see you!
My powers... Return to
where you belong...
What do you think you're
doing?! Stop it!
STOP!
You made me hit my head!
What's the matter, Hyoudo?!
What the... I guess I was
dreaming after all.
And you think you're gonna be
the World Champion?! Ha!
You've got a long way to go, pal!
The hallway...
What's wrong?
Oh? It's Baba...
What...?! It is!
Captain Baba! Hyoudo's gonna
apologize about the match...
...so please
reconsider!
What're you talking about!
Don't you see, it's all your fault!
Oh? Didn't he
hear me?
Captain Baba!
X- 0... 201-0... Echo 4513...
The subject has shifted around point Alpha by
amount Delta, location relatively unchanged.
Have you completed calculating
the total energy level?
It's being redone since the previously
computed value was infinite...
My guess is that a space-time continuum
distortion has affected our computers...
An infinite energy reading...
and an anti-matter node...
Without a doubt, the data clearly
indicates that it's...
...more than enough to change
the future of this planet.
It's been a while since we've
dealt with a major case.
Zankan! There's a body of energy
approaching point X-0!
It's appeared out of nowhere, and is
unlike the one we detected earlier!
It's a hyper-psycho-kinetic-wave!
What...?! What's the location?
Sir! It's at X-0!
That's dangerous! I'd better
go check it out!
Which one?
The anti-matter node...
Please be careful...
Yeah...
In there?
Is that him? But, he's not
an anti-matter being...
The other one's here already?
That must be him...
The psycho-kinetic wave
activity... it's amazing!
You really can't tell a book
by it's cover, after all...
He couldn't have... not
from that far away!
There's no way he could spot me when
the Anti-ESPer Jammer's activated!
Have they started?
Starting today, I am the master
of the gangs in this territory...
Sez who...?!
What is this, a fuckin' joke?
Don't make us laugh! Fighting and
wussy sports ain't the same!
So, what're you gonna do
about it? C'mon, man!
Eat this!
You're a dead man, you asshole!
I thought you wanted to fight,
not show me your toys!
How do you like my toy now, asshole?
Like I said, a toy...
You can't finish me with toys...
W... What're you... a
fuckin' monster?!
Die, you bastard!
Women... should
be cuddled!
Bastard! Leggo!
Stop! Stop!
Who the fuck are you?
One, who by exterminating
creatures such as you...
...strives to perfect his humble
skills. That is who I am.
Exterminate me?
What're you... a Demon Master
or something?
"A Demon Master?" Do
they even exist?
You don't know, I see.
You gonna hurt me with that little stick?
L... L... Let go of me!
I can feel the demon inside him...
His aura is totally inhuman!
You are all mine to devour! And
there is nowhere to run!
That's an unusual chunk of wood.
But it's of no use, and now
you can't even move.
Behold, this is your fate!
What's the matter?
This way, the girl may die...
But I have no choice!
I never dreamed that creatures existed
that could transform people like this...
So, I didn't dispatch it completely!
Oh no you don't!
It's no use!
You can't run away from me!
There you are!
A fairy?
So, the man and the cat...
...were both controlled
by you!
That school has to be it... Now,
this is getting interesting...
Sound off! Loud!
Fight!
Again!
OK... see ya tomorrow!
Catch you tomorrow!
...and, get this, guess what
Yamauchi is up to...
Hey, guys, wait up! Don't
leave me behind!
That must be him.
Either he's very inexperienced,
or his power is so great...
...that he's barely able
to contain it.
Hmm...? He's come... Just as I
expected, he's come for me...
Wanna do it?
Are you the Demon Master of
this world? Wanna try me?
Oops! Wrong one!
Damn!
Hey, what's going on?
Weird!
Think you've gotten away from me?
The primary subject has teleported.
Can you tell me its new location?
Roger. The subject has moved
to... grid-ref 2031...
It's the park, above a small
hill, 2 km to the east.
Got it. Keep him under
surveillance.
I'll switch over to our secondary subject.
Roger.
Incredible!
He's clearly following the primary subject.
This is no trivial matter.
I'll keep on monitoring their activities.
Analyze the data for me.
He must be in there.
So, you've come.
You monster! There's no
escape for you now!
Reveal yourself!
H... Hold on! I was only trying
to kick a pebble...
...but then I missed it and
kicked the car instead!
Don't try to fool me!
How's this possible?! Can
he read my mind?!
No!
Do not mock me!
None of your impudence!
His powers are several magnitudes
greater than the first creature's!
Your attempts at intimidation
are most entertaining.
The world is full of all kinds of people...
Th... This can't be
happening...
Popping out of the wound...
Now, that's impressive!
That was a unique maneuver you used.
Your powers are nothing
like the first creature's.
Now, listen to what I have to say!
I'm not interested in carrying out
a conversation with a monster!
Damn!
Listen to me before you attack!
You took away my sword...
We can still fight after I'm
done talking to you!
I am Byoudo, the Ruler of the Dark Realm...
I have arrived to this world in hopes
of making a prophecy come true...
However, I fell into a trap laid
by one of my followers.
Is that your justification for implanting
yourself inside people...
...transforming them
into monsters?!
Wait! This body is that
of Riki Hyoudo.
He is my counterpart in this world, in
whom all my powers are contained...
...all because
of the trap.
We have merged into one body, but
my own will is being suppressed...
...by your counterpart?
Exactly!
You see, the monsters you fought were
the Fairy Master and her minions.
And, the reason I am here is to
destroy their breeding nests.
They are a nuisance, if left alone...
Take a look at this...
They have characteristics very
similar to those of wasps...
They first invade other living organisms...
...then hunt for new prey,
to feed their offspring...
They breed like roaches, you see... If left
alone, there'll be no end...
In the time that it took me to destroy
one, 30 more have appeared...
There'll be no end to it, that's for sure...
They are the true demons, who prey
on peoples' weaknesses...
You gruesome maggots!
Their master... once
my follower...
...plotted to revolt
against me.
This world teems with prey that'll
become food for the Fairies...
If we don't put an end to them
now, before they spread...
...this world will become theirs.
You won't enjoy it, I'm sure.
Indeed...
Therefore, I'd like to postpone
our duel until a later date...
Are we agreed?
Fine. Until we defeat those fairies, or whatever
they are, our duel will be a matter for the future.
I'm Toshimitsu Yuuki, people
call me a "Demon Slayer."
A Demon Master from another
universe, and the fairies...
This doesn't sound too simple...
What's up?
Zankan? The second of those anti-
matter bodies has started moving.
It's at a location 3km from
your current position.
Roger!
Toshimitsu Yuuki...
Hyoudo...
Riki...
Oh! A shooting star!
My dear shooting star, please
hear my wish...
Yeah, right!
If wishes really did come true, then
everything would be so easy...
Besides, I've got a major rival
in Megumi Takayanagi...
Oh, this isn't easy, is it, Teddy?
But... I'm still in love
with Riki Hyoudo...
Huh...?
Oh! A fairy?
Let me make your wishes come true...
Let me lend a helping hand...
Someone's following me...
from behind...
Behind the trees, eh? I wonder
if it's some kinda pervert...
Well wouldn't that be interesting...
Who's there?! Show yourself!
Whaaat?! A teddy bear?!
This is unbearably weird!
Don't scare me like
that! Geez!
First you're a leopard, now you're a bear?!
It's you, isn't it, Riki!
Ladies have to be careful when
walking alone at night.
You're much too fluffy to
be a serious opponent!
Such strength! Not bad
for a stuffed animal!
Stay out of this!
What... the hell...?!
Huh? The bear is only
a virtual image...
The real object is that
little stuffed animal...
What...?! It's energy is derived from
emotional stress?! Impossible!
This can't be!
I don't believe it!
How can emotional stress
take on tangible form?!
What's going on around here?!
I'm sorry if I've frightened
you. Are you OK?
Wh...? Y... Yeah...
I see. I'm glad.
Allow me...
Thank you very much...
Er... if I may ask...
Oh, me?
My name is Zankan. I'm a Space-
Time Continuum Inspector.
Since yesterday afternoon,
we've been monitoring...
...a rash of spatial distortions
near your school.
The stuffed bear we just saw may be
a side-effect of the distortions.
There are a few questions I'd like to
ask you regarding that, if I may.
Huh...?!
Oh, I know! Allow me
to escort you home.
That way, I can ask you the
questions while we walk.
O... OK!
Oh? Where did
you go?
Hey, Teddy!
Have you become jealous
of Hyoudo or something?
You failed?
What's that all about?
I'm going to bed!
Good night, Hyoudo.
A 2-meter high
teddybear...
...and a detective from
outer-space, you say?
That space-detective
person... er...
...inspector So-and-so... was
asking things about you.
Have you done something that would
make them investigate you?
Do you have a fever or something? Or, you
had a nightmare or something, I bet.
Erase her memory of last night...
Huh...? What was
I just saying?
Wow! Takayanagi is at it already,
in the middle of the day! Cool!
Uh-huh...
Oh...? Megumi, you
don't look good.
I'm alright...
Yo, Hyoudo!
Someone from another school is here to chal-
lenge you in anything-goes Martial Arts!
Huh...?
I would wager that the space-detective
has come to investigate.
So where is he?
He's already in the
Karate Dojo, waiting for you!
Gotcha! I'll be
right there!
Alright!
Riki...
You must be Hyoudo.
And you are?
I'm Zankan.
As a person, and as a warrior, will
you accept this challenge?
You're here "as a person, and as
a warrior," eh? Interesting.
Fine. I'll accept anyone's
challenge.
Yo, Hyoudo! Man, what's up with you?!
This is the Karate Dojo, of all places!
Take your shoes off!
Your shoes!
Oops, forgot about that!
And, put these on too.
I know.
You forgot your Leopard Mask too.
Oh, I don't need that anymore.
Huh? You're not gonna use it?
That's right.
How come?
Quiet, man! Just shut up and watch!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Just what brings you here?
I am here to see whether or not
we can have a little talk.
Not bad.
Huh...? My arms
and legs!
He made it look as if he was merely
dodging your strikes...
...but he got to your
pressure points.
Well?
What's up?!
Huh...? I feel like I've met
that guy somewhere...
Next, he'll probably finish you off.
Don't tell me like it's happening
to someone else!
If I can't move, you're gonna
be feeling the pain too!
If you fail to dodge my next strike...
...you're going
to die!
Is that what you want?
Oh, FUCK!
Alright!
Looks like a draw.
Well... something like
that, I suppose.
If there's something you wanted to
discuss, talk to the Man Himself.
Looks like there's still a chance to talk.
Wanna go up to the roof or some place?
Sure. I'd like that,
if you don't mind.
I knew you'd come...
I've been waiting here, confessing my
uncertainties. The wait has paid off.
You are surely a demon that seeks
out people's weaknesses...
Why are you uncertain? You're the
mighty destroyer of demons!
Let me lend a helping hand...
A aura barricade!
You've made your move, I see.
You think you've fooled me?
Only one remains...
I shall say this unto thee...
Art thou so afraid of my powers that you
must cower within your barriers?
What?!
Fool! Byoudo took your sword,
and now you know fear!
Silence!
I'm not so naive as to fall for your tricks.
Reveal yourself, Fairy Master!
Whatever you do, you can't
break these barriers.
I am Kayn, the Demon Master of the fairies.
"The Demon Master
of the fairies...?"
I am here in this world to
assassinate Byoudo.
Behold this...
Byoudo, not satisfied with
ruling the Dark Realm...
...has come to this world intending
to rule it as well.
There's nobody on this planet strong enough to interfere
with whatever you are really capable of doing.
If you refrain from using your powers,
and merely observe, I will permit it...
...but if you intend to include yourself
in this planet's history...
...then I am officially obligated
to do something about that.
I shall become the ruler of this world regardless of your obligations.
If you must interfere... then you may challenge me at any time.
But, you want to delay our duel
at a later time, correct?
As soon as you've defeated this
Fairy Master, or whatever it is...
...I advise you to go
back to your world.
If you don't return freely, then
I will have to use force.
I do not take orders from anyone.
I suggest you learn how.
What is it that you want to say?
If Byoudo should become
the ruler of this world...
...then all living souls will be forced to
follow his orders, upon pain of death.
That is undesirable.
Well...? I propose
we join forces.
If we do, then this world...
and the Dark Realm...
...will once again
be at peace.
I refuse!
If you can't defeat me, how can
you possibly defeat Byoudo?
How did you break the barriers?!
They were useless from the very beginning.
Even though your conscious
will refuses me...
...your true desire is
to defeat Byoudo.
Your body betrays you...
Allow me make your dreams come true...
W... What are
you doing?!
Let us merge together...
...and become a being...
...transcending any mere
Demon Master...
B... Begone!
Begone!
There will be a school meeting
during the 3rd and 4th periods.
All 1st-year and 2nd-year students
must report to the gym.
All student council members from
each class, and class officers...
...report to the council room at once.
Megumi, how are you feeling?
To repeat... There will be a school...
Maybe you should skip the meeting.
It's OK, I'm fine.
Say, Riki? Have I been acting
weird at all lately?
Yup. You're a pervert.
That's not what I meant!
It's just that... I've been very forgetful
these past few days.
Really?
Oh... Sandy...
Zankan?
What is it?
I've just detected strong psycho-
kinetic-wave activity.
The location is S-205... N-50... Z-124...
just 200 meters from your location!
That must be him.
Psycho-kinetic-wave activity
is very unstable.
That's very disturbing. I'd
better go check it out.
Sandy, I'll have to interrupt
my stakeout of Hyoudo.
Will you take over for me?
OK. Be careful.
And... I feel like my false memories
are more real...
Oh! Takayanagi! Is Hyoudo
playing hooky again?
Huh...?!
If he doesn't go to the meeting,
he'll be in big trouble.
Takayanagi, could you do me a
favor and go look for him...
I'll go talk to the committee
in the meantime.
What's the rush? Where
are you going?
I see that your psycho-kinetic-
wave activity is unstable...
Is there an emergency you have to take
care of while school's in session?
I'd be very interested in knowing.
Would you mind telling me?
So, you're the one who's been following
me around these last few days.
I'm sorry... but I have
to get going.
Hold it right there! I have to verify
something right now!
Just as I thought!
You intend to stop me?
I see that your "business"
must be very important...
In which case...
...there's even more
reason...
...why I cannot
let you go!
Even if it means a duel to the death!
Are you sure about that? Because
it is you who will die.
We'll see about that!
Now they're going at it?!
"Chemistry Lab."
Hmm...?
Who's there?!
My, my... What an
awful sight.
Your folks are gonna weep when they
see you lookin' like this, guys.
Seems like you have surely
stopped being human.
In which case, it's time for you
to stop being alive.
It's no use. You can't
break those bonds.
Bye.
Do you understand now? Return
to where you came from.
Not bad. You've obviously been
possessed by the Fairy Master!
You fool!
You could've lived if you
hadn't bothered me...
That's just what I wanted to hear.
What?
Without solid evidence, I cannot
simply destroy a suspect.
But thanks to your confession...
I need not restrain myself!
I see. Very interesting.
In that case... without restraint...
I'll destroy you!
You're the one who will die!
I don't know what your motives are...
...but your powers threaten
this world's stability.
As the Space-Time Continuum Inspector,
I cannot allow you to proceed.
Behold my true powers!
Take your best shot.
Oh... Hyoudo...
You're awake.
It's all right now. Nothing
to worry about, OK?
Hyoudo! Hyoudo!
Hyoudo!
Uh... Ah... It's OK. I wasted those
assholes, so don't worry.
I've always loved you!
I've always been watching you...
Er...? Huh?
Hyoudo... Help me...
What a fool...
It thought that we wouldn't notice.
This must be the mother of the
ones we just destroyed.
So, this is the 3rd Fairy...
It would've been cool if that little
act had lasted a little longer.
Bummer!
I'll end up killing you...
Help me!
Yo, Mr. Narrator!
Her consciousness hasn't been devoured yet.
I take it that she loves me a great deal.
Not YOU! The one
she loves is ME!
I can't hold on any longer...
Come on... Hyoudo...
Quickly... finish me...
Yeah. I'll kill you...
Such an inferior demon, trying
to pull off such a lame stunt!
Even though you're just lumps of meat,
I'm not finished with you yet!
Eat this!
You fool! Things like that are
of no use against me.
What?!
Gotcha!
As I said, it is of no use against me.
So I'll send it back to you!
You eat it!
OH SHIT!
C'mon, C'mon, get me if you can!
I'll make minced-meat
out of you!
Fuck! This guy won't even
obey the Laws of Physics!
What's the matter? Was this it? Was
that all of your "true powers?"
Our duel is not over yet.
Fine. Time to get
serious!
Let me see... Now the
real work begins.
Forget her. Why bother?
You stay quiet!
You've got some interesting moves.
Don't worry... just one blow from
this, and you're history.
Why, thank you for your consideration.
Prepare yourself!
You think I'll fall for the same
trick over and over again?!
Most Excellent!
It's obvious that you are exhausted.
Even in my Dark Realm, the
reconstruction of Life...
...takes more energy
than anything else.
Those guys must be finished.
What a fool...
Such naivet.
A spiritual forcefield!
Seems I'm a mite too late.
Looks like you will no longer
bother the Fairy Master.
Yuuki... A coup de gr? E?
That ain't like you.
You look pretty exhausted.
Even so, why don't we pick up where
we left off, and resume our duel.
Sure. Let's!
Don't attempt to block his attacks
directly... or you'll surely die!
I'd appreciate it if you tell me
these things in advance!
What with everything I did
earlier, I'm pooped!
Then flee!
You make it sound like he's already won!
You didn't tell me it would be like this!
The Lord of the Dark Realm, fleeing?
I won't permit it!
In coming to this world, you've acquired all manner of
human weaknesses. How could anyone fear you now, Byoudo?
Now I get it...
He's one of them...
You ought to be ashamed of yourself!
Silence! I did it
to defeat you!
Just think, those punks in the laboratory
were almost enough to destroy you...
So much for the "Lord
of the Dark Realm..."
If we get hit again, we're dead meat!
What the fuck do we do now...?
Badly wounded, I see...
He's coming for me!
Now it's merely a matter of time.
Byoudo... Fleeing
in terror...
What?!
Yuuki!
You asshole! How
could you?!
How could you let the Fairy
Master take you over?!
You've lost your soul...
...and you've defeated yourself...
You, who were once a Master!
Now look at you!
Take your own advice!
That horn will continue to slowly
bore into you, until you die!
Savor the pain!
As subjects of the Dark Realm, we had
to endure the torment you inflicted...
Now the anguish is yours to enjoy!
This is Byoudo? The Lord
of the Dark Realm?!
Now the time of our sweet
vengeance is at hand!
Face the truth!
You came to this world...
...only to be beaten to a pulp, thanks
to your foolish counterpart.
You're history...
Have you lost your mind, Byoudo...?
I owe you my thanks...
The pain from this horn has rendered
my counterpart unconscious...
...and now I am
in control.
Now I can use my powers in any way I desire!
Don't make me laugh!
Witness my powers!
Byoudo, you bastard!
Uh-oh!
Shit!
No, he's not on the 3rd Floor
either! Oooh, that idiot...!
Where is he?!
Oh, there you are! I was
looking all over for you!
NO! Stay away!
This... This ain't what
it looks like, OK?
Riki...
This is all a big mistake!
Wait! Will you wait?!
Look, I'm tired, OK!
Knock it off! Listen
to what I...
Just what'cha got to say, you jerk?!
Eyaah! Stop that! Stop!
I abhor violence!
Jerk! Bastard! Rat! You stop
right there, you pervert!
Zankan? How long do you plan
to hang around down there?
Oh, yeah... Er, why WAS I here in the
first place? I can't remember.
Beam me up, Sandy!
Roger!
As if you'll be turning everything
to cold stone...
...you gaze with bated
breath... Medusa!
When you've finished sifting through
all the lines men always feed you...
What do you want? What
do you want to do?
Using the passion inside you, you make
yourself amazingly seductive...
English Voice Cast Using the passion inside
you, you make yourself amazingly seductive...
Using the passion inside you, you make
yourself amazingly seductive...
You transform into one cool
babe... Medusa!
Your fingertips glisten at the moment
you're ready to cast your spell...
What do you want? What
do you want to do?
I'll let you see my sinful dreams, deep
inside my eyes you'll see...
For the perfect life, I've got
to put on the magic!
For the perfect life, I've got.
For the perfect life, I've got
to put on the magic!
to put on the spell!
Shining, Shining, Shining Girl!