[birds chirping]
Mr. Andrews,
Mr. Kudo, Mr. Fairchild.
Morning.
Ah, Mr. Jenson, didn't see you
at the History Club meeting.
That was the idea.
Mr. Edwards, how did the
castration go on that polo pony?
Yeah, you're next, pal.
(boy #1)
Nice tie, teach. Clip-on?
Daddy's boy.
Bite me!
[phone ringing]
(receptionist) Wellington Academy.
Are you white?
Hold, please.
I'll put you right through.
Wellington Academy.
Are you white?
Hold, please.
I'll put you through.
[reading under his breath]
Mr. Clark, your
father's waiting for you.
How are you doing, Mr. Clark?
Looking good.
Thank you, thank you,
Mr. Kuntzler, I'm fine.
Good.
There he is,
the man of the hour.
Well, Son, don't just stand there.
Come join us.
For a moment, I didn't think
you were gonna make it.
Father,
I really need to talk to you.
Plenty of time for that, Son.
Sit down.
I have something to tell you.
Sit down, Richard, and smoke.
But, Father--
Now, now,
everyone smokes a pipe here.
I do it.
Your grandfather did it.
Even the Indians
smoked on this land
before they traded it away for some
chickens and a pound ofjewellery.
But, Father, I hate--
Suck.
Son,
it gives me great pleasure
to announce that
we're promoting you
to Assistant Vice Chairman
of the History Department.
[Spits]
Father,
that's why we have to talk.
Yes, yes,
there's lots to talk about.
You'll need a telephone, and we'll
move you from the basement--
Father, for once in your life,
will you just listen to me?
Oh, my-
(man #1)
lmpudence.
(man #2)
My word.
Look, I-I've taken a job
at Barry High School.
[all gasping]
For the moment,
I will assume that you've
found a sense of
humour and are joking.
L-- I-- I'm not joking.
Richard, if you do this,
you will fail.
You will fail.
And mark my words,
you'll come crawling
back here with your
tail between your legs.
You're wrong, Father.
I'm going to succeed
at Barry High School.
And I have no
intention of ever crawling
back here with
anything between my legs.
N[Top of the world
by The Carpenters playing]
♪ Such a feeling':
coming over me I
♪ There is wonder
in most everything I see I
♪ Not a cloud in the sky,
got the sun in my eyes I
♪ And I won't be surprised
if it's a dream I
♪ I'm on the top of the world
looking down on creation I
♪ And the only explanation
I can find I
♪ ls the love that I-- II
[hip-hop music blaring]
[radio transmission buzz]
♪ 350 bringing on
in the weeks news I
♪ And no I don't shoot,
[swoop in my Coupe I
♪ Skriffa for reaffa, my
Mega, so whatcha wanna do? ♪
♪ Do you want to
fuck around with my crew? II
(Richard)
Barry High.
[eXplosion]
♪ To make money, money, money,
make money, money, money I
♪ Here go fat stacks if you
can't take money nigga I
♪ Take money, money, money,
take money, money, money I
♪ So can you please make the
cheque out to the Facemob? II
[people chattering]
Hey, could you point me
to the faculty parking lot?
Thanks a lot.
[tires deflating]
N[Why you wanna funk by The Click
featuring Spice 1 playing]
♪ Why you wanna funk
when you ain't gotta chance I
♪ Don't make me have to
make that call II
♪ Ain't no more pilin' up your faeces,
cos niggas be actin' like bitches I
♪ Pull a strap and don't use
it, nigga that ain't smart a'
♪ I know some niggas that'll take
that kind ofshit to heart like me ♪
♪ bring it back, e'rybody die Spread fireworks
make it look just like the 4th July ♪
♪ Have a sit, leave it
laminated on the shelf
♪ Even though I'd rather do
the shit by myself I
♪ Flow-a-matic automatic nigga to my
9, paperchasin', I'm heavy on the mine
♪ Every now and then a nut
feels a bit dainty I
♪ Hoes by the dozens,
they really can't stand me I
♪ Swing my way
you get your dome sprayed I
♪ you the one who tried to ran
and you became my best friend
♪ Every now and then I yell
"Get the urge to floggy!" I
"Call my daddy 'Boss'!" I
♪ Why you wanna funk
when you ain't got a chance? I
♪ Don't make me have to
make that call I
Where?
♪ Why you wanna go and pull
a strap up oufcha pants I
♪ when you know you ain't goin'
to shoot at all, no, no A'
[motorbike roaring]
♪ Go on a rampage, beanie,
smokes and clothes I
♪ Drunk as a funk,
Wild Irish Rose I
♪ Graveyard don't track,
nigga might as well I
(Richard)
Beautiful morning.
♪ Late night, greedy gut,
major clientele I
♪ Money-hungry, same draw,
same rapper will II
Come on, give me a break.
All right.
Oh, man.
Hold it. What is this?
No, wait a minute.
What the heck is this?
Get on in there.
(guard)
Come here.
(girl)
You had them last week.
I know what you mean.
All right, give me $3.
My brother, 24 carats, $24.
No, thank you.
I already have a--
[exclaiming]
Oh.
(voice on speaker) Falik Abdul,
please come to the office.
One of your fathers is here.
You watch it, OK. Okay?
Who's that?
How the hell should I know?
[stick clicking]
Well, what have we got here?
Griff, welcome back, bro.
So you finally
got what you wanted, huh?
It's a nice little business.
Keeps us in pocket change.
I knew it was you
that set me up, bro.
Well, if it bothers you that
much, go ahead, make your move.
Or did that year in
juvie soften your cheese?
This is my turf now.
You show me respect. Me.
Paco de la Vega-El Camino-Cordova-Jose
Cuervo- Sanchez-Rodriguez
[gasping for breath]
Junior.
Are we not forgetting a name?
What's that?
Skid mark.
[all shouting]
All right, you toughs.
Break it up.
Now, cut it out.
You boys ought to be ashamed
of yourselves.
School is no
place for fighting.
What are you looking for?
I'm looking for
the rest your posse
that's going to keep me from
ripping you a new asshole.
I will pretend for the moment that
you meant that in a nice way.
But I am warning you,
I'm about to lose my temper.
Now, I want you
boys to shake hands.
Go on.
There. See?
Now,
that wasn't so bad, was it?
It's always best
to shake hands,
unless someone
just sneezed into it
or if they have a stump.
That could be a little weird.
All right, now go on, everybody.
Get back to class.
Cross me again, Griffy-boy
and even Mr. Rogers here won't
be able to save your ass.
(Richard)
Go on. Bye.
Let's go, dogs.
Gentlemen, I believe
classes are this way.
(Griff) They're not at
school here anymore.
Are you in school here?
Yeah.
First day, huh?
No, not really. I was--
Mine, too. I'm a new teacher, Mr.
Clark. What's your name?
Griff. Griff McReynolds.
Oh, nice to meet you, Griff.
You know, son, I remember
my first day at school.
Hope you live
through this one, chump.
(woman on speaker)
Your attention, please.
Today begins
Sexual Awareness Week.
Please contact Nurse
Johnson in the hall.
Here you go, you little slut.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Room 134.
Thank you.
Keep moving.
I repeat, keep moving.
Pick up that can.
Where are you going? The little
girls' room is that way.
Hey, take off those colours.
Yeah, you.
Lose the cigarette.
Take a hike, Gumby.
Get rid of the sunglasses.
Excuse me.
But this kind of behaviour...
Well, I'd bet the principal would
frown on this sort of thing.
Evelyn Doyle, Principal.
Look, pinhead, I don't know what
nursery school you come from,
but, here,
you screw up, you die.
Every bad kid in the city
is dumped into our laps.
Excuse me, Ms. Doyle,
with all due respect,
I don't think there is
such a thing as a bad kid.
At least, they don't
start off that way.
They just need
someone they can relate to
and I can reach them. I know
what's def, what's wack,
what's jam,
what's straight-up booty.
Mr. Clark, how long have
you been teaching here?
20 minutes!
I've been here over 20 years.
Don't you question
my authority on this.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Are you having a hard time
finding your way around?
Yes. I'm looking
for Room 134.
Hi. Victoria Chapell.
Richard Clark.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Clark.
It's down this way.
What do you teach,
Ms. Chapell?
I'm Principal Doyle's
administrative assistant.
Drama coach.
You did say Room 134?
Yep.
(Victoria)
Well, this is it.
All of our classrooms
are in dire need of repair.
Ever since
the legislature passed
that "three F's and
you're out" law
a lot of schools have closed.
The school board decided
it just wasn't worth it.
I guess they just
gave up on these kids.
So we've been squeezed
for money ever since.
We've been forced to--
[crashing]
Ooh.
Guess I'll get that later.
Mr. Clark, are you by any chance
related to Thaddeus Clark,
Headmaster at
the Wellington School?
Yeah. Yeah, he's my father.
Every school in the district uses
his book as a faculty primer.
You know, I don't see
the family resemblance.
Most people think I
take after my mum.
(Richard)
Look at this place.
[gasping]
Boy, it has great character.
Sure, it needs
a little paint and plaster...
and floorboards...
[groaning]
[rats squeaking]
And pest control.
But a little elbow grease...
[electric buzzing]
[whimpering]
[gasping]
Yow!
Jesus!
...and some new wiring, and she'll
be back to shape in no time.
Smell those seats.
It says, "Teach me.
I want to learn."
You must think I'm
a silly idealist.
No. No.
I really admire
your dedication.
Your wife must be
very proud of you.
Actually, I'm not married.
I find that surprising.
It's pretty
hard to be married,
if you've never had
a steady girlfriend.
I'm much too busy with work to think
about much else other than work.
That's very admirable.
The last time I heard someone
talk like that was old Mr. Riley.
He was head of the History
Department until last semester.
Retired?
If you can call being
beaten to death retiring.
Coffee?
[school bell ringing]
(Victoria)
The lounge.
(boy #1)
I'm going in. Cover me.
(boy #2)
Good luck in Home Ec., Lou.
It's a little early to start
drinking, don't you think?
Who stops?
Hi, I'm Richard Clark. I'm a
new history teacher here.
What department
do you teach in?
I don't know.
Something on the third floor.
Richard, I'd like
you to meet somebody.
This is Bernie Raveling,
our athletic director, and...
It's a pleasure to
meet you, Mr. Raveling.
Letting
the moustache grow in, I see.
Richard--
From the looks
of the stubble,
I'd say it's
going to be a beaut.
I had one in college myself.
Richard, that's Ms. Wells,
the girls' gym teacher.
Did I mention how attractive
you look, Ms. Wells?
That blue sweat suit really brings
out the colour of your eyes.
You coming on to me,
pickle dick?
No. I'd never dream of it.
Oh. Not good enough for you?
Well,
it's been a real pleasure.
[bell ringing]
They should really fix
the lighting in here.
(Evelyn) All right,
settle down, you people.
Knock it off. Quiet!
I want quiet.
[horn blaring]
It's a new semester.
That means new I.D. cards
[interpreters speaking
in different languages]
Strip searches and
fresh fingerprints.
Shut up!
Now, as you know, Mr. Amott,
our Assistant Principal,
is still missing.
If you know of his whereabouts,
or if you have him,
contact me immediately.
And also don't forget,
in less than 2 months
the state will administer
the Academic Proficiency Test.
Anyone planning
on going to college
is required to
take these exams.
Don't forget
Career Day on Fridays.
The United States Marines
and the Michigan Militia
will have recruiters
here on campus.
AH right, listen up!
We have a new teacher.
His name is Richard Clark.
It's his first day.
Give him at least a week before
you do something terrible to him.
Mr. Clark,
do you have anything to say?
Now, you all should know--
A-a-actually, yes.
[groaning]
I was asked a while back,
what teaching meant to me.
My reward, is being
able to shape and mould
agile young minds like yours.
Someday you will be
the world's leaders.
But the important
thing is, I see in you
the future of America.
(woman)
You suck!
(Evelyn)
That's enough, miss!
She's the school's librarian.
Jeez, talk about low morale.
[all shouting]
All right,
please settle down.
[screeching]
[all screaming]
There. That's more like it.
I know.
I'm the enemy.
I'm the "grown-up."
But, darn it,
I was a kid once, too.
And I haven't led
a choirboy's life.
I've got my share of
parking tickets. Whoa.
At a baseball game once,
I moved down to
the expensive seats.
Yeah. I'm not proud of it.
Now, in order to get
to know you,
I've devised a little system.
When I call your name,
I would like you to stand up
and then you tell me a little
something about yourself.
[sighing]
Natalie Thompson.
Is there
a Natalie Thompson here?
I'm here, here.
What's up, gin?
Why are you late?
Because the bell
rang before I got here.
Well--
[students chuckling]
All right. Before you
came in,
we were just talking about
sharing personal information.
Perhaps you can tell us
something about yourself.
For the last week, I've had a yeast
infection that's extremely--
Not that personal.
Something about
what you enjoy doing.
I like writing poetry.
(Richard)
A poet. I love poetry.
Perhaps you have a nice one
you'd like to share with us.
Okay.
Here's one I wrote yesterday.
"Oh, hopelessness,
"unrelenting, blood-drenched,
"intestine-twisting
hopelessness.
"So thick and mucous-like in a
stinking, vomit-filled void.
"I am but a rancid
carcass on the highway.
"Road kill for the maggots.
"Floating in shark-filled bile,
like wildebeest entrails."
That's as far as I got.
I would have finished but
I couldn't find anything to rhyme
with "festering drippage."
Well, thank you, Natalie.
Is it Anthony Jefferson?
(boy)
Anferny.
(Richard)
I beg your pardon?
An - fer - ny.
Aniemy'?
Anferny, I thought I
wrote it down wrong.
All right. Tell us a little
something about yourself, Anferny.
Well, you know,
I like chilling with my boys,
blazing up a fat blunt,
rizzeezing my mizzonkey,
hitting skins
with my old lady,
hanging my ass over the line,
tagging freeway bridges.
Oh, and I'm down with that poetry
shit, too. You want to hear?
Sure.
All right.
"My benevolence is upset
and so is my pride.
"That's why I took my bitch
"for a ride.
"I'm down with the bros
and I'm up on my shiznit
"because I love it when I'm just
laid back chilling with my bitch."
[students muttering]
Whichever one of
them hoes I'm with.
I call it, Love Can
Be A Wonderful Thing.
Thank you, Anferny.
That was quite romantic.
Julie Rubels. Miss Rubels?
That's Mrs. Rubels.
See, right after I got out
of prison, I met Tito,
and that's when little
Juan and Maria came along.
[baby crying]
I certainly hope you
learned a valuable lesson.
(Julie)
Oh, yes.
Basically, as far as vasectomies
go, never use the home kit.
[all groaning]
Thank you, Julie.
Griff McReynolds?
Where's Griff? Oh, Griff.
We had the pleasure
of meeting earlier today.
Hey, Griff,
let me ask you something.
Where do you see
yourself in, say, 20 years?
Living in your house, homes,
with your cracker ass buried
under the front porch.
[all rooting]
[bell ringing]
Hi.
Excuse me.
[swooshing]
Hi.
Oh, hi.
How was your first day?
Not bad. Not bad at all.
I think I may
be reaching them.
Say, Victoria?
Do you think you could
give me a ride home?
I seem to have
misplaced my car.
Don't worry about it.
All the teachers lose
their cars the first day.
Of course, I'll
give you a ride.
That is, if you promise
to help me chaperone
the Welcome Back
dance tonight.
Really?
Oh, I'd love to.
Great.
Um, so I'll meet you out in the
parking lot in five minutes?
Okay.
[groaning]
Tripping, right?
Right.
[people chattering]
N[music blaring]
All right,
peep this out, y'all.
We going to pump it up
a little bit like this.
Yeah.
Listen, I have
a record I want you to play.
Don't you think the kids would
enjoy a nice song with a melody?
What you got, homes?
It is a rare, one-of-a-kind,
original pressing.
Yeah? All right, man.
I'm going to put
it on here for you.
Thanks.
No problem.
IJYRhinestone Cowboy
by Glen Campbell playing]
♪ Like a rhinestone cowboy I
♪ Riding out on a horse
in a star-spangled rodeo II
[scratching]
(D.J.) Yo, man, these
jams be kicking, man.
You got any more of this funky
fresh shit lying around the crib?
Hey.
Hi.
You're in my
history class, right?
I'm Griff McReynolds.
Natalie Thompson.
That was a pretty nice poem you
read in class today, Natalie.
Thanks.
How do you think
of all that stuff?
I try not to, you know?
Is it true you used to run
the gang before Paco?
Yeah, but I'm through
with gangs. Word up.
I mean,
in juvie I had time to do
some thinking
and some reading.
You know, you're different
from everybody else here.
Most of the boys I know, they're
all crude and immature.
Most of the time, they just want
to stare at girls' breasts.
You know what I mean?
Sorry. What?
Ooh, this is my song.
You want to bust one?
I don't know. We just met.
Come on. It's just
an innocent little dance.
Okay.
♪ I'm in my room
thinking about you I
♪ Comin' from behind,
ready for the 1-2 I
♪ Feeling kinda kinky,
down near the thing there I
♪ Want to give it to you I
♪ I just want to rock you
all night long II
Yeah.
(Paco)
All right, boys, let's party.
Yo, Mr. DeMarco in the house.
Beat it.
P ace .
What up?
What's the 411
on my shipment?
(Paco)
Same as always.
Mr. A's Restaurant,
Friday nights.
You bring the cash.
We bring the boot.
You know the drill.
You tell Mr. A to expect me.
I'll do that.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I got
to go mingle with my customers.
See, real money talks.
Let's see if yours does.
(Richard)
I mean, there was a time
when I tried all the self-help
groups like Outward Bound
and that other one where a bunch
of men sit around a campfire naked
beating drums and
abusing themselves.
Then I tried drugs.
[boy choking]
Prozac, Zantac, Monoxodil.
But in the end, you know
what I found worked for me?
Dim sum.
Whenever I'm feeling
overwhelmed by life,
I just head to Chinatown.
Yo, Mr. Clark, Paco and
his boys heading up in here.
You want us
to serve them fools?
Look. Anferny,
instead of using your fists
try using this.
Head-butting?
Never mind.
Just pick
a window and guard it.
Richard, you're not really
going to try and stop
Paco and his gang
from coming in, are you?
They come to all the dances.
Not anymore.
What if they got guns and
knives and everything?
Who'd bring guns
and knives to a dance?
[guns clicking]
In that case, maybe we'd
better call the police.
No, wait. The last
time they tried that,
4 people ended up
in the hospital.
I can see your point.
W-we can't have kids
going to the hospital.
Who said anything about kids?
The cops were beaten senseless.
[all chuckling]
All right.
You take care of the music.
Anferny,
you and your guys,
you come with me.
Let's go.
Say, nice leather jacket.
Men's Warehouse?
Shut up, teach. We're
coming in, so stand aside.
Not this time, gentlemen.
This dance is for
Barry students only.
We're not gonna have any
gangs inside our school.
Who's gonna stop us?
My gang-
We already up
inside the school.
You call them bunch
of pussies a gang?
Look, Paco, if you're interested
in coming back to school
and working towards a career.
Shut up!
(Paco)
Are you gonna move aside
or am I gonna have to turn your
eyebrows into a moustache?
(Griff)
Paco,
why don't you chill out, man?
Stay out of this, Griff.
Since when you
been down with O.P.P?
What you tripping about?
You with my girl.
I'm not your girl, Paco.
Since when?
We went on one date.
If I had known you were gonna
rob that liquor store,
trust me,
I never would have gone.
No one got hurt, did they?
Only 'cause the clerk was
wearing a bulletproof turban.
All right, that's enough.
Fine. I don't want you
anyway, you super freak.
You're a real jack-off,
you know that?
[all shouting]
That's enough. I mean it.
Look, we're all civilised
human beings here.
Certainly we can come up
with a compromise.
All right.
I just got some fresh wheels.
How about a chickee run?
You're a real idiot,
you know?
That's good. Chickee run.
Isn't that
better than fighting?
Okay, everybody, let's go.
Back to dancing.
And we'll see you in, what?
10 minutes. Beck's Bluff.
[all chanting]
See you at the Bluff.
Thanks, pal.
[all chanting]
Chickee run.
See? There's always an intelligent
way to solve our differences.
My God, Richard, do you have any
idea what you've just done?
Get lost, punk.
[whimpering]
[crowd chanting]
Chickee run!
All right.
First one to
jump out of the car
before the edge
of the cliff loses.
(Natalie) Now remember,
no ramming, no swerving,
and absolutely no use
of brakes at any time.
All right, listen up, guys.
Here's the deal.
When I drop this scarf
you boys are gonna go.
N°jumping the gun.
Ready...
[moaning]
Set...
[panting]
[hissing]
Se!
[zooming]
[engines revving]
(Victoria) Richard, just
promise me you'll be careful.
Remember some
things are irreplaceable.
Irreplaceable?
Nothing's gonna happen to me.
I was talking about my car!
Hey.
[honking]
Griff. Paco.
Listen to me, boys.
Going fast never
solved anything.
This is no way to
resolve a dispute.
We can work this mess out.
I want you both to get out
of your cars right now
and we'll settle
this in an adult manner,
like a fistfight.
There. That's better.
[crashing]
[groaning]
Nobody panic.
I'm okay.
Here's the tip.
Nobody has to
know about this.
It's our little secret.
[loud explosion]
(female newsreader) Firefighters
from all over Southern California
are still trying to
contain the flames
that have
blackened over 200 acres
and caused several blocks
of homes to be evacuated.
The charred remains of three
cars were found in the rubble.
One, a classic Corvette,
has been described by experts
as being irreplaceable.
I think we've heard enough
bad news for one day.
What we've been
hearing are rumours
that some of our students may
have been involved in this fire.
And very possibly, a teacher.
[gasping]
Now, you wouldn't know anything
about that, would you, Mr. Clark?
No.
You know, Clark,
I've been thinking that maybe
we got off on the wrong foot.
I happen to be a woman
who has strong opinions
about how this
place should be run.
It's just possible that you
and I don't see eye-to-eye
on our
philosophies of education.
I've always been
a woman of few words.
No miracles.
Dumping ground.
I'll need more
words than that, ma'am.
[sighing]
All right.
I'll spell it out for you.
Our primary job here
is to warehouse
these delinquents,
until such time as
they can be released
into the general population
or sent to a real jail.
Look, although I may admire and
even appreciate your ideals,
I know what works, Mr. Clark.
I know what to
expect from these kids
and they know what
to expect from me.
My hope is that you can fit
into the pattern here at Barry.
I guess I should get to class.
Well, I've certainly
enjoyed our chat
and I'll take everything
you've said to heart.
Clark!
Mr. Clark...
Chickee run, man. Yeah.
Mr. Clark,
you were smoking last night.
Thanks, Anferny.
My man!
For you, Mr. Clark.
Richard,
you forgot your briefcase.
How sweet. Is that for me?
Sorry about your car.
[can opening]
[bell ringing]
All right.
I want everyone to take their
seats.
Today,
I'd like to talk about...
All right. I guess I
won't need this anymore.
Well, let's begin, shall we?
Yesterday, I was about to
start with the Bill of Rights
and what they
mean to all of us.
Who can tell me about the Founding
Fathers and their doctrine?
(boy)
Let me go, man.
That's not funny. Let go.
(Evelyn)
Your attention, please.
This is Principal Doyle
welcoming you once again
to Barry High':
weekly Career Day.
All the companies represented
here have been handpicked
by me in order to give you a full
spectrum of safe and legal ways...
What's up, man?
I see you got
a bright future ahead of you.
You wouldn't understand,
Paco.
I'm trying to help my family.
See now, this is the shit that's
going to feed your family,
not some rinky-dink job.
Go ahead, man.
I'm sure you could use it.
I got a big deal
going down, all right,
with DeMarco
at Mr. A's Restaurant.
You remember
the zip code, right?
Yeah.
I need a good mule.
Are you up for it?
Man, I can't even think
about that right now.
Who's asking you to think?
Ask Alonzo here.
Thinking hurts.
[blower revving]
Richard?
Hello?
[door creaking]
You tell your boyfriend
this is only the beginning.
He better back off.
Get your hands off of me!
Come on, I know you want this.
I read Mike Tyson's book.
[groaning]
[spraying]
[screaming]
Javier, come quick
and bring your tools.
[firing staple gun]
Don't worry,
Victoria, I'm here.
Let me handle this.
Here, put this on.
Animal.
Get off of her.
[groaning]
Here, sit down.
[both grunting]
[water gurgling]
[screaming]
Victoria.
No. Stay away from me.
It's okay. It's me.
I know.
What the hell's
going on here?
I was attacked.
Dressed like that,
what do you expect?
And alone with him.
It wasn't just me.
there were three of us.
That makes it all better.
No, no. I was wrestling
with the other guy.
He was trying to
have sex with her.
I don't care what your arrangement
was, or how it went wrong.
Now you listen to me, Clark.
Either you shape up,
or I'll bounce you out of here
faster than a homo
at Fort Dix.
[crickets chirping]
(Richard)
Does it hurt here?
(Victoria)
A little.
And here?
[groaning]
How about here?
I can't feel your hand.
That's because
I'm touching myself.
I better get you
something to wear.
You have a T-shirt
around here anywhere?
Top drawer.
Oh.
[groaning]
Here we are.
Poor thing.
You must be exhausted.
Let me loosen that bra
and get you some air.
[meowing]
Richard...
Victoria,
I'm sorry about all this.
It's all my fault.
But if they think
by attacking you
they can scare me off,
they're nuts.
They can attack you
all they want.
I'm gonna get through
to these kids.
Oh, sure, getting them
to come to class,
it's a small victory,
but it isn't enough.
Richard, they have to
want to learn.
That's exactly my point.
And I think Griff is the key.
He seems to be a leader.
Now, if I could just
reach him,
I could get through
to the others and--
You have to be careful.
If you raise
their expectations,
their hopes, and their
dreams, and then you fail?
It's worth the risk.
These are all
basically good kids.
They deserve
the same experiences
that we all had
in high school.
Dating, going to proms,
and begging for sex.
Richard, you have to
trust me on this one.
I'm your friend.
I'm more than a friend.
To me?
Yes. Why not?
Well, no one who's ever looked
like you has ever looked at me.
That's their loss.
You know, I--l-- I have never
been very good at relationships.
In fact, most of mine
always ended with, you know:
"Hey, what are you doin' in
bed with that other woman?"
And that was me talkin'.
Victoria, I do find you
very attractive.
[breathing heavily]
What's wrong?
L-- I'm scared.
It's okay,
you can be on top.
No, no, it isn't that.
Uh...
Trouble just seems
to follow me around.
Everywhere I go, there's always
someone lookin' to bust my balls.
Oh, don't worry, Richard.
Your balls are safe
with me.
[clapping]
(Richard)
My God, you're a virgin.
(Victoria) No, no, I still
have my panties on.
[Victoria breathing heavily]
I still can't...
Richard, I'm over here.
[cat meowing]
N[music playing]
Driver, I'm the next stop.
Forget it, pal.
We don't stop
in this neighbourhood.
[grunting]
[groaning]
(Richard)
Griff?
N[music playing]
Here you go, darling.
(woman #1) Thanks, Sam.
(woman #2)
Watch your back.
[people chattering]
Here's your cola, Griff.
(Richard)
Griff.
Mr. Clark.
What-- what are you
doing here?
I live here.
Well, I realise a lot
of these men do,
but you can get help
for this, son.
No. I mean my mom and I live
in an apartment upstairs.
Oh. Well, listen, Griff.
The reason I came here
is because I--
[sighing]
I sense that you want to
make something of yourself
and if you help me, we can
turn the school around.
[Richard gurgling]
Why me, man? You'll have
to get somebody else.
Who do you think is watching
my little brothers and sisters
while my moms is working?
I'm all they got.
You remind me a lot of
myself when I was your age,
except I was white and had both
parents and lived in the suburbs
and I didn't have
any brothers or sisters.
Maybe you remind me
of somebody else.
Hey, Griff,
don't you have a dream?
You wouldn't
be interested, man.
Sure I would. Tell me.
Promise you won't tell anyone.
You have my word.
[inaudible]
[shouting]
College? You gotta be...
[music stops playing]
N[music playing] I-|-I'm sorry.
Listen, Griff, I'll make you a deal.
You help me
get these kids to learn
and I promise you,
I will do everything
in my power
to get you into college.
Don't try to play me,
Mr. Clark.
I've been
promised stuff before
that hasn't come true.
I'm safm',
where would I get the money
for college from?
You ever hear
of scholarships?
Yeah!
Well,
you probably won't
get any of those.
But there are plenty
of other ways.
I promise you.
Don't just take
my word for it, all right?
You go home, you talk it over
with your mother.
I'm sure
she'll agree with me.
Here.
Listen, Griff.
You don't have to live
in a community
infested with crimes,
and drugs, and gangs.
You don't have to end up
in some sleazy bar
[shouting] with a bunch
of washed-up bums
watchin' some over-the-hill
stripper expose herself
for a few measly dollars
in her G-string.
[grunting]
[glasses clinking]
[people cheering]
[bell ringing]
Okay. Now,
in the next six weeks,
lam gonna try and cram
as much knowledge
into your brains
as is humanly possible.
Uh, or as space will allow.
Now, this is your textbook
for the semester.
Uh, they open like this.
(all)
Oh.
Now all of you try it.
[sniffing]
Good.
All right. Let's get to work.
Maybe we should start
with some basic English.
Now, who can give me
a complete sentence?
Yo, you wack punk,
you be goin' down
the hard way.
All right, that's a good sentence.
Let's examine it.
"Yo" is a common
colloquial greeting,
comma,
"you wack punk,
"you be goin'...
This is just bad syntax.
All right, who can give me
another sentence?
Julie.
I think my water broke.
Good.
"I think..."
♪ Way deep down south I
♪ where we play this game I
♪ It's them Quad City DJs
and you I
♪ We call it the train I
♪ So if you wanna
ride your thing I
(Richard) What's the
capital of Nebraska?
Lincoln.
Right. Who freed the slaves?
Right.
Charles Keating cooked
the books of what S and L?
Lincoln.
Yes.
Who makes the best town car?
Cadillac.
[all booing]
No.
(all)
Lincoln!
[laughing]
Amazing.
Now we're getting somewhere.
♪ I can smell them tranquil
breezes from a mile away I
♪ Graduated from Booze,
up to aHazay I
♪ Baby, you looking tough
to death I
♪ Got your weave done right I
You and three of your G's
are on someone else's turf.
You're cruisin' along
in your fly ride
about 20 miles per.
There's a posse of 8 homies
just sittin' in front
of their crib,
they're just chillin' on the
porch playin' some fresh jams.
Who they got
on the box?
I think they're riffing
with Tag Team,
maybe some Ice, Snoop, Biggie,
Junior MAFIA, whatever.
They decide that
they want to throw down.
So, you and your boys,
you pile out of your hooptie
for the face-off.
Now, they have 6 baseball
bats and 2 chains.
You have
three brass knuckles...
and two sawed-off pool cues,
you know, jimmy sticks.
Now, what I want to know is,
what is the ratio
of metal weapons
to wooden ones?
(girl) Over here, over here, Mr.
Clark, Julie knows.
♪ Girl, I wanna Waller I
♪ in the back of my Impala ♪
♪ Don't need no tickets
for this thing I
♪ Justjump on in, let me hit
them switches on the train a'
♪ And it ain't no thing,
it's all the same I
[all chattering]
[all clamouring]
Okay, pop quiz. Who was the first
president to use the telephone?
Anferny.
Nixon.
No. Griff.
Garfield.
Yes.
First president to be
on television? Anferny.
Johnny Carson.
No, he was never president.
Natalie.
Eisenhower.
Yes.
Who was the last president to blow
chunks on a Japanese head of state?
Aniemy .
Bush?
Yes!
[all cheering]
[bell ringing]
Good day, Ms. Doyle.
♪ Graduated from Booze,
up to aHazay I
♪ Baby, you looking tough
to death I
(girl)
Good morning, Ms. Doyle.
♪ It's on so tight I
♪ Now it's on tonight,
yeah, yeah I
(boy) You looking fine, Ms.
Doyle.
♪ And, boo, you need to stop
faking, and come on with me I
♪ I wanna take you home
with me I
♪ to be alone with me I
♪ And I can see
you wanna hide it I
[honking]
[all clamouring]
♪ So to all of you girls,
you know I
♪ I'm calling your name I
♪ Michelle, Tamika
and Tanya II
Mr. Arnott?
Where have you been?
They released me.
[groaning]
[bell ringing]
(Victoria)
Everyone,
state law prohibits Mr. Clark
from being here today,
so he's at home,
probably a little nervous,
but I'm sure
rooting for all of you.
All right, here we go.
The Academic
Proficiency Test.
You have 8 hours in which
to complete this exam.
Good luck to all of you.
Begin work now.
(man on TV) Every day
people are discovering
just how fun and easy it is
to get a precision-layered
haircut with the incredible
Flowbee Precision
Haircutting System.
Don't be fooled by imitators.
♪ I'm less then impressive
for beyond stressin' I
♪ Embattled as
a revolutionary adolescent I
♪ But now we in the present
with fake masters I
Flowbee cuts from a half-inch
to six inches long.
[groaning]
♪ Examinin' the compact disc
to start rammin' I
[chuckling] ♪ To put the diagram
in effect and get fly ♪
♪ On immature MC': who try I
♪ Wake 'em up outta
they High School High I
Can't do it wrong. Get a
close-up on this. Squeeze.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Show your abs.
[glass shattering]
♪ The Roots crew man
is running back again I
♪ Where crabs get
knocked-out respect from I
♪ Brought back to the lab where
the scientist will dissect 'em I
♪ The old heads sniffin' start
bitchin' when we testin' a'
♪ Interrupting my class
when my class is in session I
♪ 'Cause when I manifestin'
or come to teach a lesson I
♪ What's inside of my dome, I'll
have all you clones guessin' a'
Oh, shit.
♪ Lyricaiiyi shot
with radioactive waves I
Huh?
♪ Your styles older than dolo,
we on the top of the pagoda ♪
♪ Claim to gettin' over
but you ain't makin' quota II
[buzzing]
All right, time's up.
Come on. Time's up.
Close your booklets.
I'm sure
you all did very well.
Scores will be posted
at the end of this week.
(Natalie) So, how do you
think you did on the test?
I don't know.
For the first time in my life,
I feel like I did
something right.
Me, too.
Oh, check this out.
What is it?
It's my future.
Remember that college
I was telling you about?
Yeah.
They wrote me back
yesterday.
Yeah.
Now I feel like I got
a real chance to get in.
Guess I owe a lot
to Mr. Clark, huh?
Yeah, you know,
I think all the kids
pretty much
feel the same way.
I mean, think about it.
We could both end up
at the same school together.
Oh, Griff,
this is the happiest
lever remember being.
It's the first time in my life
I haven't prayed
for a gas line to rupture
under my building
while I was smoking.
Natalie, I'm glad
you're happy.
Come on. There's somethin'
I want you to see.
Okay.
(Griff) Mr. Clark has taken this
place on as a special project.
(woman)
"Fie, my lord, fie!
"Out, damned spot.
Out, I say."
Um, line!
(man) "Who would have
thought the old man
to have so much blood?"
"Who would have
thought the old man
to have so much blood
in him?"
[all cheering]
(man)
Take it off!
Hustle up, man.
Come on, hurry up.
Yeah, sweet.
This ought to take care
of our little problem.
Let's get
out of here, Paco.
(choir)
I Which nobody can deny I
[bell ringing] ♪ For she's
a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ for she's
a jolly good fellow N
Hey, give it a rest.
(Richard) Hey, everyone,
I just want to say
before the test scores arrive
that I am so proud
of all of you.
Well?
As I expected,
every student
in this class failed.
[all murmuring]
The lowest scores
in the country.
But there must be
some mistake.
(Evelyn)
That's right.
And you're it.
See for yourself.
Figures don't lie.
We're not dealing
with Rhodes scholars here.
It's time
I just accepted what I am
and get on with my life.
No, G riff, wait.
(Evelyn)
See what you've done?
I told you to leave them
at the bottom of the barrel,
where they belong.
Griff, wait.
Consider yourself terminated
as of right now.
(Chuckie)
Natalie, wait.
Chuckie, wait.
Wait, Ms. Doyle, you're
making a huge mistake.
Mr. Clark has helped
this school.
He's a good teacher.
And I'm not just saying that
because we slept together.
[all murmuring]
Clean out your desk
by the end of the day.
Richard, wait.
No.
You were right all along.
I didn't know
what I was getting into
with these kids.
Oh, Richard.
I'm out of here.
What's wrong with all of you?
Have you forgotten how much
Mr. Clark has helped us?
You. You had a D average
before Mr. Clark
started tutoring you.
Now you're on the honour roll.
And this boy.
Everyone thought
he had Tourette's syndrome
until Mr. Clark discovered
he was a Hindu
exchange student.
[speaking Hindi]
[students shouting]
[thunder rumbling]
[all protesting]
You suck!
You can come back.
Look at me.
I'm living proof.
Call me.
[people continue shouting]
Richard! Richard, wait!
Richard.
I'm telling you, I'm really
worried about Richard.
I've been calling his house
for the past three days
and I keep getting
the same message:
"Hi. I'm not here,
and I may never be again."
Julie?
Buddy up with a mangy dog
or a small child.
Hey, Nat, are you okay?
I'm afraid Griff's
gonna join Pacca-'s gang.
Oh, come on.
Yo, hey, yo, check this out.
Word on the street is
Paco and his little punk dogs
slipped those mentals
we took.
(both)
Huh?
What I'm saying is,
they switched the tests.
That's why everybody flunked.
Well, you know, you guys.
I probably didn't need
no help.
Oh, my God,
this is awful.
Then we just
got to find Mr. Clark.
(Victoria)
Yeah, but where?
Where do you find
a man that depressed?
Wait a minute.
Dim sum.
Chinatown. Come on.
Okay, this is it.
Julie, Natalie
Uh-huh.
Why don't you two head
down that way? Okay.
Anferny, go down
to the south end of the block,
and I'll go down
this way.
All right.
[birds chirping]
Oh, please,
let this be the one.
[people chattering]
[speaking Chinese]
Richard, what are you
trying to do to yourself?
Richard, snap out of it.
Don't you recognise me?
Mum?
No, it's me.
Father O' Flannery?
[grunting]
[groaning]
Mister? Mister?
You okay?
Mister, you okay?
This girl over there,
she asked about you.
Come. Now, now, now.
Oh, Richard, thank God.
Victoria?
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
I didn't know you drank.
I drank?
I thought it was just
my pet gorilla here.
[giggling]
Richard,
how many fingers?
[Richard groaning]
(Anferny) Come on, Mr.
Clark, snap out of it.
We got to get Griff
out of that drug deal.
Maybe we should just
let the cops handle this.
That would be fine
if I didn't mind waiting
20 years to see Griff again.
All right. Now, don't worry.
I'll just go in and get him.
Mr. Clark, you can't
just go in there and be like:
"Okay, Griff,
we're going home,"
else you gonna be
going home in a box.
The only way we're going
to get Griff out of there
is you got to show up in the
back room with the cash.
You got the cash,
you the man.
Where am I gonna
get the cash?
Man, DeMarco gonna be there.
What you think
he carry in his briefcase?
Food stamps?
Your job is to make
his cash your cash.
Did you get it?
It's all in there.
Good. We just got time to eat.
All right, everybody,
wait here.
[grunting]
I'll handle this.
You're not out in 20 minutes,
me and my G's is coming in
after you, straight up.
Go in there
and represent, Mr. Clark.
You can do it.
I can do this.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help you.
Richard, if anything happens,
I want to be here with you.
Thanks.
How are we gonna know
which one is DeMarco?
We'll just
take a wild guess.
Where?
Come on.
(Richard) Someday you will
be the world's leaders.
(librarian)
You suck!
Where you going?
It's a mistake, man.
I can't do this.
[guns cocking]
I thought
we settled this, Gritty-boy.
You better decide right now.
You in or out?
I ain't asking again.
Define "in or out."
In, you're with us,
and out, you're dead.
Works for me.
Where the hell's our waiter?
(Richard)
Good evening, gentlemen,
and welcome to Mr. A's
fine dining establishment.
I'm Zack. I'll be
your waiter this evening,
and this is my trainee,
Paula.
Uh, I'm an Aries.
I enjoy watersports
and dancing.
And my hobbies
are origami--
Enough small talk.
Just bring us
two thick T-bones.
Yes, sir. Uh, yes, sir.
And, uh, would you like those
with or without the bones?
And a couple
of glasses of water.
All right.
Well, let me tell you
about our water then.
It comes from
the Los Angeles aqueduct
where it flows down
a lovely cement channel
on a bed of--
I don't care
where it came from.
Just bring it to us.
I'll take that.
It's his birthday.
Would anyone care for some
desserts this evening?
Look, you little weasel.
Just bring us
what we asked for.
Unless you want me to stick
this bread stick up your ass.
It sure would taste
better if you didn't.
[banging]
[grunting]
(Richard) You might want
to try buttering it first.
♪ It's your birthday,
it's your birthday ♪
♪ Another year older,
another year gone ♪
♪ Better live now
and have lots of fun ♪
♪ It's your birthday,
it's your birthday ♪
♪ There's no use pretending,
your life will be ending N'
Hey, stand back.
Come on. We've got
to change disguises.
[Victoria sighing]
[cloth ripping]
You ready?
Yeah, but unfortunately we've got
this other thing to do first.
Let's see
what's in this thing.
Oh, Jesus!
(Victoria)
Hurry.
(man) Manny, zap that
sauce for me, will you?
(Manny)
Got it.
Ho.
Now, what do you want?
I'm here to see Mr. A.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Mr. B.
Mr. D couldn't make it.
He's out with Mr. C.
You're early.
N[music playing]
DeMarco's early.
Say what? You?
Mr. Clark, Miss Chapell,
what are you doin' here?
Hey, no need
to be so formal, boys.
We're not in school anymore.
2 seconds you gonna be
one dead teacher.
How's that for formal?
Now, we work for DeMarco,
buyin' and sellin' drugs.
We're-- We're lowlife scumbags.
Just like you.
What are you talkin' about?
Well, what better cover than
a teacher and a secretary?
Administrative assistant.
Yes, all right.
All right,
enough of this small talk.
I've got business with Mr. A.
Where is he? Where is he?
(woman)
I'm right here.
Clark?
(both)
Ms- Doyle?
Around here
they call me Mr. A.
Mister?
I inherited the business
from my late husband.
Well, I'm shocked.
(Evelyn)
What?
That a woman
can run a business?
No. That you were
ever married.
[hissing]
All right.
Let's do it.
What exactly
is she doing here?
She's my bitch.
Ahem.
Well, my significant other.
We've been slappin' skins
for quite some time now.
Hmm.
You say you work for DeMarco.
Why should I believe you?
Uh, why would I
have his briefcase
unless I was workin' for him?
That doesn't prove anything.
You could have seen him
down in the restaurant,
dressed up like a waiter,
created some kind of
diversion,
while she snatched it
from under the table.
[gasping]
That's a little far-fetched,
don't you think?
(Victoria) Wait--Wait a minute.
Think about it.
You think he's capable
of all that?
Hey, all right.
All right.
Hey, what's the big idea?
You work out?
(Paco)
All right. Knock it off.
I say we off him now,
and then do what we want
with their bodies.
(Evelyn)
Easy, Paco, easy.
So, you like
getting high, Clark?
Who doesn't?
Then perhaps
you'd like to sample
the finest crank in town.
Sure. Sure.
Load me up a spike.
Let's get this party
into gear.
Look man, he's clean.
No tracks.
I--I take mine
in the ass.
Got used to it as a kid.
Shots.
You're startin'
to piss me off, man.
Maybe you don't have enough
holes in your head already.
(Victoria)
Excuse me.
Something seems to be
riding up here.
Hmm?
(Evelyn)
What's going on there?
Nothing I know
rides up that high.
Here.
Tie off.
[groaning]
[sighing]
Oh, you really should have
someone look at that.
It could be malignant.
(Evelyn)
Quit stalling.
We don't want to be here
all night.
Well,
here's looking at you, kid.
[Richard groaning]
[sighing]
[groaning]
Oh, wow.
Oh, this shit be kickin'.
Oh, man, I'm wasted off my ass
and you're still ugly.
[gun firing]
False alarm.
Some idiot put a gun
in the microwave.
[man muttering in Spanish]
Good stuff, huh?
So what have you got
to say for yourself?
Nothing, really.
Except it's going
to be an interesting
morning tomorrow,
after my coffee.
I'll need at least
2 magazines.
So it's all here?
As far as you know.
Half a million?
Really?
Oh, uh, yes,
down to the penny.
Now, I'll just take my stuff
and be on my way.
Wait here.
Griff, you got
to get out of here.
You're throwin'
your life away,
messing around with these drug dealers.
Look who's talking.
No, he's not
a real drug dealer.
He's just pretending.
He's here to save you.
You risked your life
to come here for me?
Yeah, of course I did.
Well, not the
risking-my-life part.
Anyway, look,
Paco switched the tests,
and the police are probably
already on their way.
We got to get out
before--
It's the waiter
and his trainee.
Yeah. Where the hell's
our dinner?
You jughead.
They're the ones
who stole our briefcase.
DeMarco, what's going on?
Is this your idea
of a straight deal?
We thought
Clark was your guy.
I never seen him
before tonight.
Hey. Another one of these,
one of us is gonna
have an orgasm.
Clark, you never
should have messed with me.
I don't want him found.
No problem.
[revving loudly]
(Victoria)
No.
(Anferny) Come on, G's.
They're down this way.
You guys.
In the house.
[students chattering]
Doyle is getting away.
Stop her.
Seems to me we've got
some unfinished business.
You're forgetting
a couple things, aren't you?
Oh, yeah, what's that?
Richard's not here
to help you this time.
And?
I have a frozen pig's foot.
[whirring]
[cackling]
(woman)
♪ I am invincible ♪
♪  I am woman ♪
♪ I am woman,
hear me roar ♪
♪ In numbers too big
to ignore ♪
[Richard grunting] ♪ And I know too
much to go back and pretend N'
[both grunting]
What's he doing?
[all chattering]
(woman)
What's going on?
Come on! Come on!
Look! There's a bigger man,
and he's got a gun!
[women clamouring]
[woman grunting]
[gasping]
[sighing]
(woman)
Oh, Christ!
Sorry.
This was a new suit,
pickle dick.
[gasping]
[gmpins]
Get back.
What are you fossils
staring at?
Eat your vegetables.
Mmm.
Get back!
I'm gonna walk out of here.
You punks get out of the way.
I'm gonna count to three,
and if you're not moving,
I'm gonna start shooting.
Do what she says, kids.
Chill, Mr. Clark.
She ain't shootin' nothin'
but the breeze.
You kids are even bigger
boneheads than I thought.
And everybody knows it, too,
except for this fool.
You know, Ms. Doyle,
that's just what you
and people like you, want
everyone to think, isn't it?
That somehow,
no matter what goes down,
we just can't cut it.
You use that as an excuse
to hold us back,
but Mr. Clark,
Mr. Clark showed us
that there is another way.
Another way to flunk.
Think we failed that test?
Yo, yo, yo, listen up.
If x is 1?,
plus the square root of 4,
minus 6, what's X?
13.
[all agreeing]
Famous Russian author of
The Brothers Karamazov?
Who is Dostoyevsky.
The Gadsden Purchase formed
parts of what two states?
(all)
Arizona and New Mexico.
All right, I'll shoot him.
What's the capital of Ecuador?
Quito!
Back off! I mean it.
NASA's Apollo Program
ended what year?
1975!
Stay away from me.
Who was responsible
for the first moonwalk?
Michael Jackson!
Huh?
What did he say?
No, I'm just playin', man.
It was Louis Armstrong's
brother, Neil.
What group is responsible
for the consumption
of the most doughnuts
in Los Angeles?
(man) Police! Right.
Nobody move.
Get your hands up.
This isn't
what it looks like.
Say hello to Mr. A.
So this is Mr. A.
We've been looking
for him for years.
You're under arrest, fellow.
Hey, partner, there's about
5 more gangster-pops
in the freezer.
It was her, man.
She masterminded
the whole thing.
I'll testify in court.
She's Mr. A.
(officer) We know. Oh.
Could I borrow your coat?
I can't feel my legs.
Come on, let me go, man.
I'll give you $50,000.
Well, Ms. Doyle,
I guess we just got off
on the wrong foot.
No hard feelings.
Wonderbra?
[grunting]
I swear to God, Clark,
when I get out,
I'm gonna hunt you down
and beat you
like a circus monkey.
Oh, by the way,
happy birthday.
(waiters) ♪ It's your birthday,
it's your birthday ♪
♪ Another year older,
another year gone N'
[all cheering]
Yeah.
Oh, this shit be kicking.
[cackling]
(Victoria) And now, to
present the diplomas
principal pro tem,
Richard C. Clark.
Will the graduates
please rise and begin...
Richard, I never thought
I'd say this,
but I was wrong
about you, son.
I can't believe
what you've accomplished here.
Thanks, Dad.
[all applauding]
When I call your name, please step
forward to receive your diploma.
An fem y Jefferson.
[all cheering]
Julie Rubels.
[baby crying]
[whooping]
There's Mommy.
Achmed Duvded.
Natalie Thompson.
And the Valedictorian
of our class,
with a 2.35 GPA,
Griff McReynolds.
You did it, buddy.
Way to go, GM“.
That's my boy!
That's my boy.
(woman)
Good for you, Griff!
(Richard) For all of you who
did not make the journey
to this stage today,
I say to you,
work as hard as you can,
do a couple hours
of homework each night
and nothing can stop you.
[all translating]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the graduating class of 1996.
Graduates, graduate!
[all cheering]
♪ Come on ride the train
And ride it I
and ride it I
♪ Come on ride the train
♪ Here we go now I
♪ Quad City Train
comin' down the street I
♪ Stereo loud got you
bumpin' to the beat I
♪ So put on your pumps
and your Daisy Dukes I
♪ Pick up the phone and go
gather your whole crew I
♪ Like Renee, Monique,
Tina, Michelle I
♪ And them big booty girls
with the weave on the tail ♪
(announcer)
Coming up on the 11:00 report,
Sparky the rottweiler
is still missing
on that Korean airliner,
day 32.
A deadly strain of bacteria
found in movie popcorn
striking its victims exactly
one-and-a-half hours
after being consumed.
And in sports,
Steve's gonna tell us
about Marge Schott's
purchase of
the Harlem Globetrotters.
That's all coming up next.
♪ Quad City DJ I
♪ Daddy, Daddy, can I go?
I wanna ride the train I
♪ Yeah, baby, you can go, if there
ain't no shame in your game I
♪ But you better watch your back,
'cause I heard people say a'
♪ That you can't walk when you ride
the train with the Quad City DJ's I
♪ Come on ride the train
and ride it I
♪ You wanna ride with me?
Okay, go pack your bags I
♪ Get ready,
and when I call your town I
♪ Move your arms up and down I
♪ and make that
choo-choo sound, like this I
♪ Jacksonville go Woo-woo I
♪ 0-Town wanna Woo-woo I
♪ Tampa wanna Woo-woo I
♪ Hotlanta wanna Woo-woo I
♪ Chi-town wanna Woo-woo I
♪ The Carolina's
wanna Woo-woo I
♪ LA wanna Woo-woo II
♪ The things you do to me I
♪ Boy! love you I
♪ The time has come
for me to show I
♪ Show that
I care for your soul I
♪ No one makes me feel
the way you do I
♪ And I'll never let you go I
♪ I just can't help
feeling the way I feel I
♪ The things you do to me I
♪ Boy, I love you I
♪ You know my love for you
is strong I
♪ I loved you for too long I
♪ Now it's time for you
to realize I
♪ That you'll always
be in my heart I
♪ And I love the things
you do for me I
♪ You give me so much joy I
♪ Boy, you know
all I need is you I
♪ You mean the world to me I
♪ And it's plain to see I
♪ That, boy, I love you I
♪ I just can't help feeling
the way I feel ♪
♪ I can't help I
♪ Just let me show you
this love is real I
♪ Let me show you I
♪ I just can't help feeling
the way I feel II
♪ That's right I
♪ Here it comes I
♪ It's off the scale I
♪ Oh, check it, check it I
♪ Yo, yo I
♪ Mama, just killed a man I
♪ Put a gun against his head I
♪ Pulled my trigger,
now he's dead I
♪ Mama, life has just begun I
♪ But now I've gone
and thrown it all away I
♪ Mama, ooh I
♪ I didn't mean
to make you cry I
♪ If I'm not back again
this time tomorrow II
[whirring]
[welding]
If Ielectric guitar soloing,
Chuck Berry-style]