"you are here."
I'm where?
(girls scream)
(boy) freshman!
(boy #2) let's get him!
(freshman)
help! Help!
Seniors!
(girl) freshman.
(girl #2)
hey, freshie!
(girl #3)
we got another freshman!
Please, put me down! Help!
Please, I'll be late
for my first class.
What do we do with him?
Stuff him in a locker.
No, not the locker.
Anything but the locker!
(%% "did we meet
somewhere before?"
by Paul McCartney and wings)
Hey.
Nice game, Tom,
even though we lost.
Oh, yeah. Ha-ha.
Hey.
How you doin'?
How's the old arm?
Well, it's pretty sore.
%% ...That's happening
%% to both of us
%% happening time
%% and time again
%% happening over and over...
Hi, Tom.
%% will the king's horses
%% and all the king's men
%% ever find out
%% what it's about? %%
(bell ringing)
"never before
has the school board
"seen a student body
such as this.
"but starting today,
things will be different.
"may I present to you
an administrator
"who has promised
to carry out her duties
"with an iron hand -
"the new principal
of Vince Lombardi high -
Miss Evelyn Togar."
Thank you.
Thank you. (clears throat)
"members of the board,
"as we stand on the threshold
of a new decade,
"we must face harsh reality.
"our educational system
has become far too permissive.
"as that famous scholar
once said...
"'my darling Evelyn,
How I long for the feel
of your luscious thighs
wrapped ar--'"
"as you all know, I am here
to replace Professor Webb,
"who is unable
to continue his duties
As the chief administrator
of this school."
And now I would like us
all to rise and salute
professor Webb
For his wonderful,
gallant effort.
Ludwig van Beethoven,
Whom you will be
interested to learn,
Wrote his greatest symphony
At a time
when he was completely deaf,
A feat which was
practically unheard of
At the time.
(wheezy laugh)
I know that most of you
are used to listening
To a very different kind
of music,
But I hope
that when you hear
The immortal strains
of Beethoven’s fifth symphony,
You will realize
what a work of genius
it really is.
I seem to have misplaced
the turntable.
Hi, everybody.
I'm Riff Randell, and this is
rock-'n'-roll high school!
(%% "Sheena is a punk rocker"
by the Ramones)
%% well, the kids
are all hopped up
and ready to go
%% they're ready to go now,
they got their surfboards
%% and they're goin'
to the discotheque à go-go...
(all screaming)
What are you doing?
Have you gone crazy?
Stop that! Sit down.
%% ...Really has it all
%% oh, yeah, oh, yeah
%% Sheena is
%% a punk rocker, Sheena is
%% a punk rocker,
Sheena is...
Please, these are
very dangerous chemicals.
Don't dance near the chemicals.
In fact, don't dance at all.
%% Sheena is
%% a punk rocker...
Asseyez vous.
(girl) whoo!
%% well, she's a punk, punk...
Please stop-- what?
Get down off my desk.
Get down off my desk!
Get in your seats.
%% a punk rocker
%% punk, punk
Aah!
%% ...Kids are all hopped up
and ready to go
%% they're ready to go now,
they got their surfboards
%% and they're goin'
to the discotheque à go-go
%% but she just couldn't stay
%% she had to break away
%% well, new York city
really has it all
%% oh, yeah, oh, yeah
%% Sheena is
%% a punk rocker, Sheena is
%% a punk rocker now
%% Sheena is
%% a punk rocker, Sheena is
%% a punk rocker now
%% well, she's a...
%% punk, punk
%% a punk rocker
Riff.
%% punk, punk
Riff!
%% a punk rocker
(music stops)
Hey, Kate,
I'm getting some static.
Not as much
as you're going to get.
So, this is
the type of behavior
that I can expect.
The minute there's not
a teacher in the room,
The entire school erupts
Into a shameless display
of adolescent abandon.
If it's discipline
that you students need,
I am the one
who can provide it for you.
Well, now,
I'm not interested
in punishing anyone,
But I think for the good
of the whole school,
The person responsible
for this deviation
from the schedule
Should step forward.
Kate, what are you doing?
What is your name?
Kate Rambeau.
And who are you?
I'm Riff Randell,
rock-'n'-roller.
(students laugh)
Obviously you do not know
who I am.
I am Miss Togar,
And I am the new principal
of this school.
(whoop over pa)
I want you to go
to your classes... Now.
This incident is going down
on your permanent record,
A record
that's going to follow you
Throughout
your entire life.
You have managed
to upset the entire school
With this godforsaken noise.
Noise? That's the Ramones'
best album.
Number one with a bullet.
Randell, I want
to see both of you
in detention center
Before the next bell,
or else.
Oh, Riff,
detention center?
I've never served
a detention before.
Oh, don't worry.
I've done more detentions than
anyone in the school's history.
(%% "teenage depression"
by Eddie and the hot rods)
Whoo-hoo! Come on, Kate.
Loosen up.
Oh, Riff, not that stuff.
Oh, come on. It's not
the end of the world.
Yahoo! Detention.
I can't believe you.
(laughs)
oh, boy, detention
with my best friend.
I don't understand it.
I mean, I'm captain
of the football team...
(bell ringing)
...My complexion
has cleared up,
And soon, I'm gonna be going
to the college of my choice.
Why don't girls go for me?
Hi, Tom.
Hey, Cheryl,
how ya doin'? Ah.
(sighs)
Nice weather
we been havin', huh?
Little dry lately, though,
But I hear it's raining
cats and dogs in Idaho.
Sure, Tom. Be seeing you?
All right.
What went wrong?
Maybe I'm too forward.
Hi, Tom.
Hey, Shawn, baby,
how you doin'?
¿qué pasa?
Nice weather we been havin''
lately, huh?
It's been a little dry,
though.
I hear it's been raining
cats and dogs in Idaho.
Yes!
See ya later, Tom.
Yes. What happened?
What went wrong?
O caring football type,
captain of the team--
I gotta
get myself together.
I need to improve
my self-image.
I need to broaden
my horizons!
(%% "I wanna be sedated"
by the Ramones)
%% I wanna be sedated
%% ba ba bamp-ba,
ba-ba ba bamp-ba...
Riff Randell.
%% ba ba bamp-ba,
ba-ba ba bamp-ba %%
(%% "smoking in the boys' room"
by brownsville station)
%% a-checkin' out the halls,
makin' sure the coast is clear
%% lookin' in the stalls,
no, there ain't nobody here
%% my buddy fang
and me and Paul
%% gettin' caught would surely
be the death of us all
%% smokin' in the boys' room
%% yeah
%% now, teacher...
No, not the urinal!
This one.
Anything but the urinal!
No! Please!
Watch it! Watch it!
%% ...Smokin' ain't allowed
in school
%% all right... %%
Hey, man,
where you goin'?
End of the line!
(boy) ...Just like
everybody else.
Hi. Uh, I need
to see Eaglebauer.
Oh, I'm sorry,
but he's tied up
at the moment.
Why don't you
just take a number
and have a seat?
Miss, you don't understand.
See, this is an emergency.
Animal, vegetable
or mineral?
Um... Sexual.
(boys) whoo!
It's a code nine!
(electronic siren wailing)
He'll see you immediately.
Ah, my man,
it's good to see ya.
Good to see ya.
How are ya doin'?
Good.
Well, have a seat.
Have a seat.
So what'll it be
for the star quarterback
of Vince Lombardi high?
Fake id? Get you liquor
in any state.
Uh, no.
Hall pass? Test answers?
No, no, that's not
gonna solve my problem.
Shoot. It's been like this
all morning,
Ever since Togar took office.
The whole school's
in turmoil! Well, look.
Look at this.
Fake ids down 50%.
Test answers down 60%.
Hall passes are fallin''
off the board.
Let's get back to you.
Tell me exactly what you want
out of life.
I want someone
with huge breasts.
The sweet stirring
of passionate youth.
I wanna get laid
before I'm 30.
Are you a virgin?
Uh, do you mean technically?
You've come
to the right place.
Eaglebauer enterprises
is a name that stands
for quality.
I'm gonna get you a date
with the most primo lady
in this school -
Kate Rambeau.
(%% fanfare)
(mouths)
Johnny, why don't you
tell Tom how happy
he'll be with Kate?
(Johnny over pa)
right you are, Mr. Bauer.
Kate Rambeau, age 17,
attends Vince Lombardi high,
Where she majors
in nuclear physics.
This perky
gal-on-the-go's hobbies
Include splitting protons
and checkers.
Included
in your night to remember
Is a matched set
of travelways luggage.
(girls' voices) ooh!
That's travelways luggage,
the first name in travel
for over five years.
And now back to you,
Mr. E.
(applause)
(%% flourish)
Thank you, Johnny.
There she is, Tom.
I had somebody else in mind.
Oh, Tom, my files indicate
she's perfect for you.
I know, I know,
but I was kinda hopin'
That you'd set me up
with Riff Randell.
Riff Randell?
How about a cheerleader?
Nice set of pompoms.
No! The only girl I ever
dream about at night is Riff,
But I always keep waking up
just before the good part.
Well, how are you set
for large amounts
of hard cash?
(snaps fingers)
I have a major credit card.
Uh, Norma, dear?
Yes, Mr. Eaglebauer.
Yes, would you
draw up a contract
for Tom Roberts
And Riff Randell?
(toilet flushes
in background)
(%% "rock and roll"
by the velvet underground)
%% you know her life is saved
by rock 'n' roll
%% yeah, rock 'n' roll... %%
What's that thing
in your ear, Randell?
Um, it's a...
A hearing aid.
Be careful, Miss Steroid.
She's very sensitive
about it.
Oh, I'm sorry
to hear that, Randell.
What?
Sorry to hear that,
Randell!
Fine. How are you?
Oh, I'm fine, thank you!
Oh, I'd say
about a quarter to two.
Come on, Riff,
let's go.
But I just had lunch.
So young.
(giggles)
That was close.
We just got out of trouble.
You wanna put us back in?
Are you kidding?
"what's that thing
in your ear?"
She doesn't even know
the Beatles broke up.
I know something is going on
behind my back.
(chuckles)
You two are not
doing your jobs.
Look at me
when I'm talking to you.
You're supposed to be my eyes,
my ears, my nose.
(both) ahchoo!
Thank you.
If this school
is going to get back
on the winning track,
We have to start cracking down
immediately...
And I know
just where to begin.
Ok, you take a note
to Mr. Mcgree,
And I want you
to take the same note
to coach steroid.
Tell them
to meet me immediately
In the science lab.
The most famous notes in all
of the musical literature.
Now...
(laughter)
"earmail."
Ha-ha-ha.
(class groans)
Class, I have to go
to Miss Togar’s office.
I'd like you
to look over the chapter
on Beethoven’s Fifth Symphony
While I'm gone.
Oh, and, class,
as soon as I get back,
There's going to be
a surprise quiz
on this material.
(all) aww!
Come on.
Nice work, Rambeau.
I knew you could do it.
Ok, now come on down.
I'm stuck.
Nonsense.
There's nothing to it.
Just go hand over hand,
But above all,
do not slide.
(squealing noise)
(all gasp)
Kate,
are you all right?
All right, girls, she's ok.
You're ok, Rambeau.
Get up and walk it off.
Come on.
Come on, girls.
Let's move it.
Hey!
You fat creep.
Yes?
Note.
"darling Evelyn,
how I long for the feel
your luscious thighs--"
Oh, wrong note.
All right, class...
(blows whistle)
...Listen up.
Are you ok?
I'm going to be gone
for a few minutes.
While I'm away,
I want you to continue
With your exercises
for the day.
(girls) aww!
Ah, none of that.
(%% piano)
let's have
a little enthusiasm.
And a... (blows)
...A-one and a-two
and a-jumping up and down.
Come on, girls.
That's right.
Peppy!
Keep that up
till I get back.
Well, you're probably wondering
why I called you here.
Me.
I know, I know.
I know.
Me.
Go and monitor
the halls.
Since assuming office
this morning,
I've noticed a number
of peculiar incidents
Among the members
of the student body,
All having to do
with rock-'n'-roll music.
Miss Togar, I have
no particular love
for rock-'n'-roll,
But it doesn't seem to me
that listening to it
Actually hurts
the students.
(laughs) but that's
where you're wrong,
Mr. Mcgree.
Recently,
I have been doing a study
Of mice subjected
to rock-'n'-roll music.
Here we have a picture
of this mouse,
A typical member
of the genus rattus rodenti,
As he appeared
before the start
of my investigation -
Clean, good-natured,
Content to scamper playfully
about his cage.
This is a picture
of the same mouse...
One week after the introduction
of rock-'n'-roll music.
I never dreamed.
Oh, the results
were dramatic.
He lost all interest
In keeping
his cage tidy.
How scientific.
He played
his electric guitar
far into the night,
Keeping the other
test animals awake.
He did?
And he met
this female mouse,
And they have been sharing
a cage together
Out of wedlock.
That's fascinating,
Miss Togar.
Yes, it is.
Is she crazy?
She's a principal.
Monitor the hall,
monitor the hall.
I am sick
of monitoring the hall.
Yep.
Let's go monitor
the freshman.
Good idea.
Get him.
All right,
up against the wall.
Spread 'em.
All right, what the hell
do you think you're doing
out here?
I was just getting
my books.
Listen,
you have a hall pass?
Well, no.
(both) no hall pass?
Hit him, hit him.
Guys, I'm allergic to violence.
I break out in blood.
Hit him anyway.
Calm down.
Let me see some id.
I haven't got all day.
I need it
for the sock hop tonight.
The sock hop.
Who'd dance with you?
All you have is a buck?
I'll have that.
Is this you?
Well, I take
a bad picture.
Tell me about it.
(both) ugh.
Listen, I'm gonna give you
a demerit.
What's a demerit?
If you get enough of 'em,
you wind up in Miss Togar's
office.
(both) %% demerit, demerit
well, what for?
Because...
(both) ...You're ugly.
Hit him now.
Hit him. Hit him.
I have a great idea.
Let's go monitor
the girls' gym.
All right.
Ok?
(muffled speech)
(%% piano)
(turns music off)
what are you doing, Riff?
Gym class called
on account of boredom.
Got some of my homework
instead.
Homework?
Yeah, for Mr. Mcgree's
songwriting class.
I've written a song
for the Ramones.
(%% rock)
wait till you hear this.
(girls) whoo!
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% well, I don't care
about history
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% 'cause that's not
where I wanna be
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% I just wanna have some kicks
%% I just wanna
get some chicks
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
(girls) whoo!
%% well, the girls out there
knock me out, you know
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% cruisin' around in my GTO
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% well, I don't like
the teachers and the principal
%% don't wanna be taught
to be no fool
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% fun, fun,
rock 'n' roll high school...
(both giggle)
%% fun, fun,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% fun, fun
%% oh, baby
%% fun, fun,
fun, fun
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
rock 'n' roll high school...
Next I investigated reports
of loss of hearing
by individuals
Due to the high decibel level
involved
In playing
rock-'n'-roll music.
Put on these
ear protective devices,
As I am going to -
Mr. Mcgree -
Play a song by the Ramones
At the decibel level
consistent with that used
In your average concert.
Your standard mouse
And your standard speakers.
Now, back, back.
This is
the rock-o-meter.
Gee.
It is used to measure
comparative rock-'n'-roll
intensity levels.
Watch the mouse
while I turn it on.
(%% "teenage lobotomy"
by the Ramones)
(squeaking)
%% lobotomy
%% DDT did a job on me
%% now I am a real sickie
%% I guess I'll have to
break the news
%% that I got no mind to lose
%% all the girls
are in love with me-- %%
Notice the loss of hearing.
The gym!
Girls!
Music!
Legs!
Dancing!
Boobs!
Randell...
Sex...
I think they're trying
to tell us something.
Ok.
(panting) come on,
come on, come on, come on.
%% well, I don't care
about history
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% 'cause that's not
where I wanna be
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% I just wanna have some kicks
%% I just wanna
get some chicks
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% fun, fun
%% rock 'n' roll
high school
%% fun, fun
%% rock 'n' roll
high school
%% fun, fun
%% rock 'n' roll
high school
%% fun, fun
%% oh, baby
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
rock 'n' roll high school %%
(%% piano)
(Kate) ...3, 4.
(Riff) 1, 2...
3, 4.
1, 2...
They're dancing.
Oh, no, Miss Togar,
it's calisthenics.
Where are their books?
This is a gym class.
They're exercising
their bodies.
1, 2...
What these girls need
is to exercise their minds.
1, 2...
3, 4.
I told you -
she's crazy.
...3, 4.
(blows whistle)
All right, girls,
hit the showers!
1, 2...
3, 4.
(blows)
1, 2...
3, 4.
All right, girls.
Come on, let's go.
(all) whoo!
(blowing weakly)
Uh, Cheryl, do you think
Tom Roberts is cute?
Yeah,
but he's such a dork.
No, he's not.
I think he's a fox.
A fox?
Tom Roberts is so boring,
his brother is an only child.
He's not half as hot
as Joey Ramone.
Who's Joey Ramone?
Where have you been -
Mars?
Earth calling Kate.
He just happens
to be the lead singer
of the Ramones.
I wish we could
see them this Thursday
at their concert.
So what's stopping you?
We can't cut classes
to stand in line
for tickets.
That's right.
Oh, please.
Ten years from now,
no one will care
If you've ever been
to high school, much less
skipped a few classes.
You all act
as if everything's
so important around here.
Just because Togar
is stuck in the '50s
Doesn't mean
there isn't life
after high school.
I've got my own future
to think about.
I know I can write
for the Ramones.
All I've gotta do
is get my songs to them.
They won't be in town
for another year,
So I've got to
see them now.
Hey, we wanna go
as much as you,
But we can't all
cut classes.
Well, I guess
it's up to me, then,
But you'll have to
cover for me, Kate.
I'm gonna take
a three-day leave
from Camp Lombardi
And be first in line.
If anyone wants to join me
at front-row center,
Why, you just let me know.
(girl) ok.
(girl #2) yeah.
All right!
(%% "school days"
by chuck berry)
%% drop the coin
right into the slot
%% you've gotta hear something
that's really hot
%% with the one you love,
you're makin' romance
%% all day long
you been wantin' to dance
%% feelin' the music
from head to toe
%% round and round
and round you go
%% hail, hail,
rock 'n' roll
%% deliver me
from the days of old
%% long live rock 'n' roll
%% the beat of the drum
is loud and bold
%% rock, rock, rock 'n' roll
%% the feelin' is there,
body and soul %%
(buzzes)
(yawns)
(%% "c'mon let's go"
by the Paley Brothers)
(man imitating war chant)
%% come on,
we'll always be together...
Hey, keep away
with that thing.
I don't want any.
Scalper.
%% come on, come on,
little darlin'
%% and again and again
and again
%% and again and again %%
(Miss Togar over pa)
Miss Kissel,
Please report
to the principal's office.
All your classes
have been canceled.
(boy) a girl!
(boy #2) everyone, hide!
Don't forget the sock hop
this evening.
Tonight's guest speaker
will be Dr. Schulz.
(typewriter clacking)
Ooh.
Red alert.
(bell clanging/
electronic siren wailing)
(knocks)
(Eaglebauer) who is it?
Kate Rambeau.
Kate, yeah.
Come on in.
Hello, Mr. Eaglebauer.
How are you doing?
Great, thank you.
Please, sit down,
sit down.
What can I do
for you, Kate?
Well, I wanna go out
on a date.
Say no more.
Eaglebauer enterprises
has a man for you.
Tell me, have you had
much experience with boys?
Well... Once I played nurse
with a boy next door
And got sued
for malpractice.
I wish part of Riff
would rub off on me.
Everything's so easy for her.
Did you have
any one particular person
in mind?
Well, I was kind of hoping
That you might fix me up
with...
With Tom Roberts.
Tom Roberts?
Yeah.
I love him.
He's a great guy.
Well, can you do it?
This will never work.
Tom will never like me.
I don't know who I'm kidding.
What possible reason
could there be
To put myself
through all this?
Sex.
I must admit,
as far as reasons go,
It must be one of the best.
Kate, I've known Tom
ever since he was a freshman,
When I sold him
his first touchdown.
Believe me, you're just
the type of girl he goes for.
(%% "did we meet
somewhere before?")
Tom, my man.
How's my would-be Romeo?
Eaglebauer, what are we
doing up here?
I thought we were gonna
start training today.
This is the perfect spot
for it.
Most romantic setting
in the city.
Just you, the skyline
and your training partner.
Training partner?
Hi, Tom.
I was kind of expecting
Riff Randell.
Eaglebauer, I don't know
whether I can go through
with this.
Couldn't I just practice
with myself?
You done too much of that
already.
Yeah.
Now, for the next three days,
You two are gonna have
nothing but fun.
Now, the first lesson -
necking.
The place - lovers' Lane.
(turns on tape deck/
crickets chirping)
The reason -
Well, you're young.
Now, what's the first thing
you guys do?
Aw, no, no, no, no.
(yawns)
Now, this next step
can either make or break
a successful date.
One-handed approach
to strap unfastening
Is a basic skill
that must be mastered.
Now watch closely
as I demonstrate.
There's the hook.
The snap.
There is the double hook.
There is
the dreaded minihooks.
And, if you play
your cards right,
The easy-open frontal assault.
Isn't it sad when a family
has to suffer so much?
Isn't it.
(buzzes)
Good morning, Joey.
Excuse me,
but I think it's obvious
I'm first in line.
Not anymore.
Hey, look,
I been waiting here
for two days.
I'm first in line.
So you wanna be
ahead of me, huh?
I don't wanna be. I am.
Apparently you don't know
who I am.
No.
I'm Angel.
Angel dust, the Ramones'
number one fan?
I followed 'em
on every stop of their tour
from Cleveland to Pittsburgh
To Tucson to Charlotte...
Ohh, you're a groupie.
Yeah, well, I happen
to be a songwriter--
Honey, you're not
a songwriter,
You're a cheerleader.
I am first in line.
I'm first in line.
Hey, what do you think
I am - filth?
You think I'm just spit
on the sidewalk for you
to walk on,
Scum under your feet?
I don't know what you are,
but I am first in line.
I am first in line.
I'm first in line,
and if you don't like it,
You can put it
where the monkey puts the nuts.
(mouths/writing)
By the way,
who do you like?
Oh, I think Joey's
kinda cute.
(%% "I just wanna have something
to do" by the Ramones)
%% hangin' out
on second avenue
%% eatin' chicken vindaloo
%% I just want to be with you
%% I just wanna have something
to do tonight
%% tonight, tonight
(man) hey,
it's the Ramonemobile!
%% tonight, tonight
%% well, all right
(screaming)
%% tonight
come on! Come on!
%% wait
%% now
%% now...
I love you!
It's me!
%% ...Myself
%% I don't wanna be
with anybody else
%% I just want to be with you
%% I just wanna have something
to do tonight
%% tonight
%% well, all right
(man) all right!
%% tonight
(man) all night!
All night!
%% tonight
%% wait
%% now
%% hangin' out all by myself
%% I don't wanna be
with anybody else
%% I just want to be with you
%% I just wanna have something
to do tonight
%% tonight
%% tonight...
Joey! Cut it out.
%% tonight
%% well, all right...
Joey! Joey!
Here's songs!
%% ...Night, tonight
%% tonight
%% tonight %%
(cheering)
I love you.
Angel, baby,
good to see ya.
I got a little surprise
for you.
The boys would love
to see ya. Come on.
This way.
Yeah, this way.
Come on, let's go.
Goodbye, cheerleader.
(man) Ramones forever!
Quit shoving, you guys.
Come on.
(man #2) stop cutting
in line!
Well, you know
what they say.
These things always happen
in threes.
Oh, really?
I want 100 of your best
Ramone tickets, please.
$1,000.
(%% "you're the best"
by the Paley brothers)
Here they are -
the Ramones tickets.
There's many more of them.
You'll get one.
There you go.
All right,
I know you want one, too.
What's all
this commotion?
There you go.
Excuse me.
What's going on here?
Here you go.
I'm giving out tickets
to the concert.
The concert?
Yeah.
I had no idea the students
were so interested in music.
Wanna go?
Complimentary ticket?
Why, thank you.
I love concerts.
But, uh, who are
the "Ramoneys"?
(freshman wheezing)
The Ramones.
They're the best group
in the world...
...Oxygen.
So, three members
of your family are dead?
Oh, we know for a fact
that you are lying.
Go and show her the proof.
What do you have
to say for yourself?
Hey, got better.
Got better nothing.
I suppose that her parents
are still alive, too.
Should I check on it,
ma'am?
No talking.
Kate, I am really surprised
at you.
I thought
you would serve as a model
for the rest of the school,
Not as an accomplice
to delinquency.
Well, she's my friend.
A friend that will lead you
down the road to expulsion.
I'm a teenage lobotomy.
I have made a full report.
Oh, Mr. Monitor, sir,
it's the breathing.
It's the...
"you two girls
have done nothing but defy me,
You have turned
the entire student body
against me..."
(gasps)
Miss Randell, just what is
your problem?
(gulps)
All right, who else has tickets
to this concert?
Uh, just us.
We're the only ones.
Miss Togar, perhaps we're
taking this a bit too far.
After all, the concert is on
their own time, and it's--
Nonsense! They should
be made an example
for the whole school.
All right,
give me your tickets.
I will give them to Charity.
No way!
Very well.
I'll have my hall monitors
take them from you.
(both) body search!
Hey, Riff,
thank you.
Thanks for the tickets,
Riff.
Hey, Riff,
thanks for the ticket.
Yeah, we couldn't
have gone without you,
And everybody's
gonna be there.
Yeah, we'll see you
there. Goodbye.
Thanks.
Have a good time.
We won't.
%% yeah, rock, rock, rock %%
(mumbles/sighs)
Can't go to the concert...
Oh, great...
Great day.
(%% "I want you around
by the Ramones")
%% I want you around
%% they're tellin' us
%% they're gonna
make a fuss
%% about the two of us
%% I want you around
%% I know what
you're thinkin' about
%% that you
have some doubts
%% I know
what you're thinkin''
%% when ya find out
I want you around
%% you know if it comes true
%% I'll be so good to you
%% I'll never treat you cruel
%% as long as
I've got you around
%% I want you around
%% you heard
that I'm no good
%% yeah, yeah, I'm no good
%% but I'll treat you
like I should
%% I want you around
%% you know if it comes true
%% I'll be so good to you
%% I'll never treat you cruel
%% as long as I've got you
around
%% I want you around
%% they're tellin' us
%% they're gonna make a fuss
%% about the two of us
%% I want you around
%% I want you around %%
(sighs)
It may have taken me
two million lawns to mow,
But it was worth it.
(knocks)
Hoo-hoo-hoo.
Look at all this stuff!
Color TV, stereo,
wet bar, waterbed!
I'll tell ya,
I never knew gettin' laid
was so expensive.
Ok, I hope I can remember
everything you taught me,
though.
Tom, you're nervous.
Here, have a drink.
It'll calm you down.
Thanks.
Hey, and whatever you do,
don't worry.
Since Riff lost her tickets
to the concert,
You can move right in.
She'll be a pushover.
Besides, look how far
you've come in three days.
Yeah, but the question is
how far will she go tonight?
"if the unknown is 'y'
and the binomial is 'x,'
What is the function
of the equation 'z'?"
Riff.
Riff!
Huh? Uh...
Oh, uh, the, uh,
The, uh, major export
of Ecuador is kapok.
Very good, but that's geography,
and this is calculus.
Ooh, sorry.
Look at your math book.
It looks brand new.
I bet you've never
even opened it.
I only use it
on special equations.
(giggles)
Oh, I don't feel like
studying tonight.
Yeah, I've gotta
get home, anyway.
I'm expecting Tom
to call me tonight.
You really like him,
don't you?
Mm-hmm. I've been seeing
a lot of him lately.
You have?
Mm-hmm.
Eaglebauer says we were made
for one another.
Oh, he did?
I think tonight
could be pretty special.
(phone rings)
Hello.
She's on the line.
Great. Just remember
what I told you.
Yeah. Hello. Hello, Riff?
Hi. It's Tom.
Tom?
Yeah, Tom Roberts.
Football player?
No.
I talk about
the weather a lot.
Oh, yeah. Hey, Kate,
it's Tom Roberts on the phone.
Tom? Why would he
call me here?
So how's it been?
Oh.
Little dry lately.
Yeah,
but I hear it's raining
cats and dogs in Idaho.
Yes. Yes! Oh, man,
it's goin' great.
Great. (mutters)
Listen, I'm just lying here
in my new van,
On my beautiful waterbed,
Listening to the Ramones'
brand-new album
On this fantastically
expensive stereo
Wondering if you'd like to maybe
go out tonight and get drunk?
All right.
Listen, I really wish
you'd reconsider-- what?
Sure, I'll go out
with you tonight.
You can't do that.
He's mine.
You will?
Just find a date
for Kate, ok?
Great, I will. Listen,
I'll pick you both up
in about an hour.
We got it!
Riff, how can you
go out with him?
I never thought about Tom
until you mentioned him.
What?!
It'd be a change for me,
don't you think?
I never went in much
for the jock type.
Oh, cut it out.
What about me?
What about tonight?
Don't worry. You'll
be in the back seat
with Eaglebauer.
He's lots of fun.
(gags)
I don't wanna have fun.
I wanna be with Tom.
(chuckles) hey,
I'm only kidding, Kate.
I wouldn't do that
to you, huh?
I'll take care of Eaglebauer.
You can have Tom
all to yourself.
Hmm?
Shouldn't kid like that,
Riff.
(mocks) shouldn't
kid like that.
You know how hot I am
for him.
Hot?
Yes, hot.
Whoa.
"hot," off the lips of Kate.
My goodness. Ha-ha.
Ha-ha, we did it!
We did it.
I got you a date
with Kate. Whoo-hoo.
Hot equals Joey Ramone.
No, hot equals Tom.
Ehh.
Aw, I can't believe it.
I can't believe it was
that easy.
He looks like a little cherub
or something. Looks like
he's gonna fly away to Heaven.
He's so sweet-looking,
kinda like a cream puff.
That's why I like him.
I like Joey Ramone 'cause
he's tall and handsome.
He looks like a poem to me.
A poem?
We get them drunk,
we go in the back,
we hit the waterbed...
We gotta take turns
in the back.
All he eats is pizza.
I just love the way
he holds the pizza
dripping above his mouth.
He slithers and slides it
into his mouth.
It's so sexy the way it...
(slurps)
Gross.
(car radio) %% questioningly
%% her eyes looked at me...
This is
screamin' Steve again,
And I've got two free tickets
to tonight's Ramones concert
For the person
who can call and tell me
What album
this song is on...
"questioningly."
"questioningingly."
What album?
Oh, what album?
Oh, what is it?
Is it road to ruin?
Yes, that's it!
Oh, Kate, how'd you know?
It says it right here
on the cassette.
Quick, where's a phone?
Where's a phone?
We've gotta get to a phone!
Right over there.
Aah!
...Very special. What I'm
trying to say is, dear,
I'd like to ask--
This is very difficult.
Please don't hang up.
I'd like to ask you
to-to-to be my wife.
Sorry, but you're
not my type.
(dials phone)
Oh, please, God,
don't let it be busy.
(rings)
it's ringing.
Hello? Yes, the answer
is "road to ruin."
Aah! We won! We won!
What? Yes, it's Riff Randell
and Kate Rambeau.
Of course we'll be there.
Yes, thank you. Oh, thank you.
Oh, we're going.
Oh, Kate, we're going,
we're going. Oh, we're going.
Aah!
What about Tom?
Oh, come on. How often do you
get to see the Ramones?
Oh, but tonight we were gonna be
meant for each other.
This is my big Chance
to get my songs to them.
We have to go.
You'll have
a great time.
(screamin' Steve)
and the super-lucky winners
of the two free tickets
For tonight's
Ramones concert
Are Riff Randell
and Kate Rambeau.
(rings)
("questioningly" continues
playing over radio)
(ring)
Hello?
Hello? Tom?
Kate and I can't
make it tonight. We've been in
a horrible seven-car accident.
We've gotta go to
the hospital for immediate
blood transfusions.
We'll see you tomorrow
in school. Bye.
Aah!
I think he took it well.
Let's go get dressed.
But I am dressed.
Yeah, but not for the Ramones.
I got clothes that'll
make you fit right in.
Come on, sexy.
The only thing I'll ever lay
is a carpet.
You can't take this
lying down.
You gotta crash that concert,
grab her up into your arms.
Love conquers all.
Besides, I'd have to
give ya a refund.
(groans)
Oh, I think I'm gonna puke.
(%% rock)
Oh, sorry, Mantovani's
down the block.
I'm hep, daddy-o.
I'm into the Ramones.
Sure you are.
Got any drugs?
Bottles? Cans? Cameras?
Let me check ya out here.
(laughs)
(man) anybody got any glue?
(man #2) who's the geek
in the beret?
(man #3) how old's that guy?
Look at the way he's dressed.
Oh, I'm sorry, we don't let
any more mice in here.
They've been exploding
all over the place.
Oh, you got headphones?
Great, great.
Just don't get
too close to the pa.
Wait, here's your stub.
Ok, go on in.
Enjoy the show.
(woman) get this guy.
Is he chic, or what?
Really, have you ever
seen anyone...
(man) who's got the carbonas?
(Riff) that's my songs.
Bottles, cans,
cameras on ya?
No, nothing. Nothing.
Ok, you're in.
Let's see what you got.
Oh, this is nice.
That won't hurt anyone,
will it?
Excuse me.
(man) nice ass.
Pinched me.
(woman) I'm lookin''
for 'ludes.
Feel good?
Yeah.
Let me see your pupils.
You're stoned. This guy
doesn't get in.
%% what a wife,
she is mine, she is his
%% and so it goes,
and so it goes,
and so it goes
%% and so it goes...
Kate, do you realize
they're all really brothers?
Imagine being the only sister
in the Ramones' family.
(man) we want the Ramones!
(man #2)
I'm so lovin' it!
(woman) come out,
please, Joey!
(woman #2)
we want the Ramones.
(cheering/applause)
Hi, gang!
This is
screamin' Steve Stevens
Steamin' your way
over station 666
With
the screamin' Steve show.
(man) oh, wow!
(gunshot sound effect)
We're comin' at ya,
alive and kickin',
With the hottest band this side
of the iron curtain -
The Ramones!
(man) you know it, Steve.
(woman)
we love you, Ramones!
Dig it.
But first, I'd like to
introduce the two winners
Of the Charity ticket raffle
Donated by the principal
of Vince Lombardi high!
(man) Togar eats it!
(woman yells)
Sister Maria Teresa
and sister Teresa Maria.
(concert over radio)
Now, that's a step
in the right direction.
And to keep this administration
moving forward,
I've made a list
of new school policy,
Which I would like
instituted immediately.
Take this down.
Girls - skirts
below their knees
And boys' hair
above their collar.
And I think it would be tidy
if they wore neckties.
And lunch is to be cut down
To half an hour
Because I am doubling up
on silent study hall.
Well, I think that
should teach them a lesson
in deportment.
How do you spell that?
D-e-portment.
Now I want you to meet
the two winners
Of the screamin' Steve
ticket contest -
Riff Randell
and Kate Rambeau!
(cheering)
(all) yay, Riff!
You're live
on the air, girls.
Why don't you say a few words
to the folks at home? Go.
On behalf of the students
from Vince Lombardi high
who are here tonight,
I'd just like to say
one thing -
Screw you, principal Togar.
We made it to the concert,
anyway! Yeah!
Who says today's youth
has nothin' to say, huh?
(inaudible yelling)
Those girls have turned
the whole school against me.
Hansel, Gretel.
I want you to crash
that concert.
I want Randell and Rambeau
brought back here immediately.
So you're Kate Rambeau, huh?
Yeah.
I just loved your latest
scientific American.
Thanks.
Hey, would you two
lovely ladies
Like to see
screamin' Steve in action
As he interviews
the Ramones?
Oh, great. I know
just the questions to ask.
That's beautiful, 'cause
I can't think of a thing.
I've waited so long
to see them. I know
they're gonna love my songs.
I can believe it.
Ya ready? Here we go.
Hey, you wanna keep it down
out here?
They're tuning up.
How'd you get in there?
Professional secret.
What's this stuff?
Stuff is gonna prove
to the Ramones that I can
write songs for them,
So out of my way, dew drop.
I'm sorry, but
the Ramones' manager,
A personal
friend of mine,
Put me in charge
of keeping everyone out.
What's all the trouble,
Angel, baby, huh?
Screamin'.
Well...
Good to see ya.
Long time, right?
Uh, who are these two?
These are screamin' Steve's
contest winners.
Oh, uh, sorry, girls,
you'll have to wait outside.
Oh, man...
Can't we just watch?
Angel dearest, why don't you
see these sweet young things
to their seats?
We'll go ourselves,
thanks.
It's gonna be ok. Yeah.
Screamin', I was wondering
if you could give us
a little more airtime.
I'm hittin' it
once an hour.
You can do
a little better.
Hey-ho, let's go!
Hey-ho--
(screamin' Steve)
here they are - the Ramones!
(Riff) Joey!
Dee dee!
1, 2, 3, 4.
%% hey-ho, let's go
%% they're forming
in a straight line
%% they're going through
a tight wind
%% the kids
are losing their minds
%% blitzkrieg bop
%% they're pilin'
in the backseat
%% they're generatin'
steam heat
%% pulsating to the back beat
%% blitzkrieg bop
%% hey-ho, let's go,
shoot 'em in the back now
%% what they want,
I don't know
%% they're all revved up
and ready to go
%% they're formin'
in a straight line
%% they're going through
a tight wind
%% the kids are losing
their minds
%% blitzkrieg bop
%% they're piling
in the backseat
%% generatin' steam heat
%% pulsating to the back beat
%% blitzkrieg bop
%% hey-ho, let's go,
shoot 'em in the back now
%% what they want,
I don't know
%% they're all revved up
and ready to go
%% they're forming
in a straight line
%% they're going through
a tight wind
%% the kids
are losing their minds
%% blitzkrieg bop
%% they're piling
in the backseat
%% generatin' steam heat
%% pulsating to the back beat
%% blitzkrieg bop
%% hey-ho, let's go
%% hey-ho, let's go! %%
%% lobotomy
%% DDT did a job on me
%% now I am a real sickie
%% guess I'll have to
spread the news
%% that I got no mind to lose
%% all the girls
are in love with me
%% I'm a teenage lobotomy
(cheering)
That, Mrs. Rambeau,
is where your daughter is.
My daughter Kate?
I thought she was
in the basement
splitting protons.
Oh, just as I thought,
Which is why I called
a special assembly
together tomorrow
To deal with this crisis.
I'm going to need
every parent's help, so...
Listen carefully.
1, 2, 3, 4.
%% well, I'm going out west
where I belong
%% where the days are short
and the nights are long
%% and I'll walk,
and they'll walk
%% and I'll twist,
and they'll twist
%% and I'll shimmy,
and they'll shimmy...
Kate, she stole
my songs.
%% we're out there having fun
in the warm California sun
%% well, I'm going out west,
out on the coast...
Gimme those back!
%% and I'll walk
%% yeah, and I'll twist...
Excuse me.
%% and I'll shimmy
%% and I'll fly,
and they'll fly
%% we're out there having fun
in the warm California sun
Hey, Riff!
She's got my songs.
(both) tackle her!
Tackle?
%% well, the girls are frisky
in old 'Frisco
%% a pretty little chick
wherever you go
%% oh, and I'll walk
%% yeah, and I'll twist...
You can catch her, Tom!
%% and I'll fly,
and they'll fly
%% we're out there having fun
in the warm California sun
%% well, we're out there
having fun
%% in the warm
California sun %%
%% gabba gabba, we accept you,
we accept you, one of us
(mutters)
Oh, shit.
%% I don't wanna be
a pinhead no more
%% I just met a nurse
that I could go for
%% I don't wanna be
a pinhead no more
%% I just met a nurse
that I could go for
Whoa.
%% I don't wanna be
a pinhead no more
%% I met a nurse
that I could go for
%% I don't wanna be
a pinhead no more
%% I met a nurse
that I could go for
%% oh
Thank you, Tom. Oh, thank you
for saving my songs.
I always knew you were
a terrific football player.
%% everyone's accusin' me
Yay!
%% I don't wanna be
a pinhead no more
%% I met a nurse
that I could go for
%% I don't wanna be
a pinhead no more
%% I met a nurse
that I could go for
%% yeah
%% gabba gabba, hey
%% gabba gabba, yay
%% gabba gabba, hey,
gabba gabba, hey
%% gabba gabba, hey
%% gabba gabba, hey,
gabba gabba, hey
%% gabba gabba, yay! %%
Joey, Joey, Joey!
Tom? Tom. Tom,
are you all right?
Speak to me.
Riff, my head.
Riff?
I've just been handed this note.
It says, "dear Ramones,
"all my friends
from Vince Lombardi high
are here tonight.
"even though our principal
Miss Togar thinks you make
nothin' but noise,
I think you're the greatest."
Do you mean you
signed up with Eaglebauer
to be with me?
Yes.
Listen, I'm glad
you're not Riff.
What do you say we become
friends, anyway?
"please dedicate your next song
to my friends Tom and Kate.
Love, your number one fan,
Riff Randell."
Ok, this is for Tom and Kate,
from our number one fan.
Yay!
1, 2, 3, 4.
%% yeah, yeah, she's the one
%% when I see her on the street
%% you know she makes
my life complete
%% and you know I told you so
aren't they great?
%% she's the one,
she's the one
%% yeah, yeah, she's my girl
That's me.
%% and when I see her
on the street
%% you know she makes
my life complete
%% and you know I told you so,
she's the one, she's the one
%% she's the one
%% know I'll never find
a girl like you
%% but in my heart,
I'll always love you
%% yeah, yeah, she's the one
%% when I see her on the street
%% you know she makes
my life complete
%% and you know I told her so,
she's the one, she's the one
%% she's the one
%% I'll never find
a girl like you
%% but in my heart,
I'll always be true
%% yeah, yeah, she's my girl
%% the best girl
in the whole wide world
Back, back.
%% when I see her
on the streets
%% you know she makes
my life complete
%% and you know I told you so,
she's the one, she's the one
%% the one
%% she's the one,
she's the one
%% she's the one
%% she's the one,
she's the one
%% she's the one
%% she's the one,
she's the one
%% she's the one %%
Joey.
Yay, Joey!
I told you
you'd have a great time.
I am.
Maybe that's them
in there.
Oh, boy, we got 'em now.
Have you seen two young
high school girls around?
Yeah, I got 'em on me.
(both) body search!
Aah!
Is he all right?
Hey, pizza!
Great.
What are you doing here?
These are my songs.
I've been trying to get them
to you for the longest time.
Hey, it's Riff Randell,
our number one fan.
Oh, wow,
you remembered my name.
This is the big time, girlie.
This is rock-'n'-roll.
Yeah, well, this is
"rock 'n' roll high school."
"rock 'n' roll high school"?
Yeah, I wrote it for
Mr. Mcgree's music class,
But I really wrote it
for you, Joey.
Hey, pizza! It's great.
Let's dig in.
Yeah, I want some.
Oh, thanks.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
No pizza for you, Joey.
More wheat germ
and riboflavin.
Yeah, come on, Joey.
Eat. Good.
I'm gonna eat some myself.
Mmm. Mmm.
Organic alfalfa sprouts.
Come on, Joey.
Good. Mmm. Come on, eat, Joey.
Good boy. Yeah.
Mama'll love ya. You like it,
huh? Huh? Good, yeah.
Iron, niacin, b12.
Grown from the earth.
Good...
I'll cherish this moment
forever.
This is how I like
to see you, my son.
Ok. Ok, girlie, the boys'll
take a look at 'em
And get back to you
tomorrow, huh?
Yeah, we're gonna be in town
one more day,
And if we like 'em,
we'll come pay you
and Mr. Mcglibb a visit.
Say hi to Vince
for us.
Oh, wow.
This is the happiest day
of my life.
Gabba gabba, hey.
(birds chirping)
And I say to you parents,
This high school
is a failure.
The past semester
has been a black Mark
On the proud tradition
of Vince Lombardi high.
Student Riff Randell alone
has disrupted classes...
They can't say I haven't
contributed anything.
...And banded the students
against me
To attend a concert
of the Ramones.
Hey, yeah!
That's right.
...That awful
rock and roll music.
You see before you
my first major step
In putting this school
back on the winning track.
I give you...
The final solution.
(students gasp)
Those are our records.
Hey, gimme those.
(all complain)
And this is what we think
of the Ramones...
(boy) we've gotta stop her!
Somebody stop her!
She can't do that!
(boy #2) hey!
Miss Togar,
I cannot stand by
and allow you to do this.
Then stand aside,
Mr. Mcgree.
Let me through.
(Eaglebauer) she's
burning our records!
We gotta stop her!
(Tom) I'll get the hose.
Togar!
That's the last straw, Randell.
Detention... For life!
(%% "school's out"
by Alice Cooper)
%% school's out for Summer
(all yelling)
(Riff) let's take the school.
My darling Evelyn,
how I long for the feel
of your luscious thighs.
See you later, Togar.
It's already fifth period.
(boy) she's gonna
call the cops.
%% no more pencils
%% no more books... %%
Hey, come on, you guys.
Follow me into the school.
I regret that I have
only one life to give
for rock-'n'-roll.
You belong in school with us,
Mr. Mcgree. Come on.
Things sure have changed
since we got kicked out
of high school.
Oh. Where are you going?
To Mr. Mcgree's class.
Well, I'm happy
to see some students
still are interested
In their studies.
We're not students.
We're the Ramones.
Ramones? You're responsible
for making that horrible
rock-'n'-roll music?
You turned the whole school
against me.
(cheering)
Do your parents know
that you're Ramones?
(cheering)
Come on in.
(girl) yay, Ramones!
(boy) kill the principal!
Rock-'n'-roll high school
is on the air again.
(%% "high school" by mc5)
%% well, come on
%% kids want a little action
%% kids want a little fun
More exciting
than study hall.
%% ...Have to get their kicks
%% before the evening's done
%% 'cause they're
goin' to high school...
Hoy, hoy, hoy,
hey, hey hey.
I'm really groovin', baby.
%% high school,
hey, hey, hey
%% you better
get out of the way
They're going to destroy
the school.
I can't believe it.
Whoo!
Ooh...
%% they only wanna
shake it up, baby
%% dance to the rockin' bands
%% they only want
a little excitement
%% they like to get
a little out of hand...
(both) oh, students...
Oh, students.
What the hell...?
(girl) we've got ya now.
Get down, Mcgree.
Whoo! Whoo-hoo!
(both) surf's up.
Call the national guard.
They're causing a riot.
These kids are--
The national guard?
But my children
are inside that school.
Oh, dear.
%% the kids know what
the deal is
%% they're gettin'
farther out every day
%% we're gonna be taking over...
Get off, you little...
God, you weigh...
%% high school, rah, rah, rah
%% high school...
(static/feedback)
%% high school,
rah, rah, rah
sis, boom, bah
%% high school...
(Hansel and Gretel) whoa!
Hey! Wait!
We're in here!
Wait, wait.
You're gonna
get it now, fat boys!
Whoo!
Nice garters.
(screams)
Whoo, sexy legs.
Whoo, Mcgree.
(all laughing)
Firing line...
Apple brown betty.
We were only following
the recipes!
Firing line...
The Tuesday surprise!
No, no, not
the Tuesday surprise.
(girl) taste treat.
(girl #2) it's delish.
Go get 'em, guys!
%% well, come on, let's go,
let's go, little darlin'...
(boy) eat it, Vince!
%% come on, come on,
let's go, and again
%% and again and again
and again
%% well... %%
No, no.
Oh, what the hell...?
Oh, my God...
(students) yeah!
Demerit! Demerit!
(boy) come on up,
and we'll bang your erasers.
So what do you think
of my school, guys?
Boy, when you have recess,
you really go all out.
Consider yourselves
officially enrolled in
rock-'n'-roll high school.
The facilities are yours.
Do whatever you want.
%% do you wanna dance
and hold my hand?
%% tell me, baby,
I'm your lover man
%% baby, do you wanna dance?
%% do you wanna dance
under the moonlight?
%% squeeze me, baby,
all through the night
%% oh, baby,
do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you,
%% do you, do you, do you?
%% do you wanna dance?
%% do you wanna dance
under the moonlight?
%% squeeze me, baby,
all through the night
%% oh, baby,
do you wanna dance?
%% do you wanna dance
under the moonlight?
%% squeeze me, baby,
all through the night
%% oh, baby,
do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you,
%% do you, do you, do you?
%% do you wanna dance?
Go on, get out there!
Yeah!
%% do you, do you, do you,
do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you?
%% do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you,
do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you?
%% do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you,
do you wanna dance?
%% do you, do you, do you?
%% do you wanna dance? %%
(cheering)
Attention!
Give it to me.
Attention, students.
(Togar) attention, students.
Hey, quiet!
Quiet, everybody! Listen!
This is your principal -
Miss Evelyn Togar!
I wanna speak
to Riff Randell.
Quiet! Come on.
Into my office.
I don't think
it's working.
I know how to...
You don't think it's working?
Start talking, Togar.
It's your dime.
Ok, Randell. I know we've had
our differences in the past,
But I think it's time we tried
to understand one another.
I think the problem is clear.
I am a reasonable,
well-educated, mature
adult member of society,
And you are a spoiled
heathen punk who has
taken over my school.
(applause)
So let's make a deal.
I can have you expelled
and turned over to the police.
But I'm gonna
forget about that
And just put one black Mark
on your permanent record
That will follow you throughout
the rest of your life...
(all murmur)
...If you'll just
come out of there right now.
(all protest)
I don't think one more
black Mark is gonna make
too much of a difference.
Eaglebauer, your partner,
comes through again.
All right.
(screams)
Here's what I think about
your school records, Togar!
You handled that very well,
Miss Togar.
What's that?
I don't know. I...
Miss Togar!
(both yelling)
Well, now they've done it.
Destroying government property.
I think ya failed,
Miss Togar. I think we're
gonna have to do it my way.
I think you're right.
Randell, I just talked
to the chief of police.
You're not out in five minutes,
he's going to Storm
the building.
Well, you heard it, folks.
Miss Togar has just
given the students
of rock-'n'-roll high
An ultimatum.
A classic confrontation
between mindless authority
And the rebellious
nature of youth.
The moment of truth
is at hand. What will
these kids do next?
Boy, this sure is
rock-'n'-roll high school.
Yeah, we liked it so much,
we're gonna play it
on our next album.
To show our appreciation,
we're gonna make you
an honorary Ramone.
(students cheering)
(girl yells)
Hey, guys, people say
that your music is loud
And destructive
and lethal to mice,
But I think you're
the Beethovens of our time.
That was a good one,
Mr. Mcgree.
(timer ticking)
Kate, is it a go?
It's a go.
All right!
Everybody follow me.
We're gonna evacuate.
I guess we should
rush the building.
Not so fast. Look.
They're coming out.
It's over.
We won.
Ladies and gentlemen,
school is out.
It appears as if the final bell
has rung for these students.
Has Riff Randell given up?
Has she and her
fellow classmates
Failed Miss Togar’s
final exam?
Is this the end
of rock-'n'-roll high?
Just what do you
have to say for yourself,
young lady?
I have seen the errors
of my ways.
I'd just like to say
to all students everywhere
That you may think the school
is yours for a while,
But it's always
run by the principal
and her administration.
That's nice.
Vince Lombardi high is...
Is your school, Miss Togar,
So you can have it.
Well, I'm very happy to see
that you've come to your senses.
And what would you have done
with the school, anyway?
Rock the roof off it.
Hit it, Marky!
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% well, I don't care
about history
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% 'cause that's not where
I wanna be...
It's so loud.
%% I just wanna have some kicks
%% I just wanna
get some chicks
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% well, the girls out there
knock me out, you know
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% cruisin' around in my GTO
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% I hate the teachers
and the principal
%% don't wanna be taught
to be no fool...
Those Ramones
are peculiar.
They're ugly...
Ugly, ugly people.
%% fun, fun,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% fun, fun, oh, baby
%% fun, fun, fun, fun
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% well, I don't care
about history
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% 'cause that's not where
I wanna be
%% rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% I just wanna have some kicks
%% I just wanna
get some chicks
this is wrong.
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
%% fun, fun,
hey, my man.
What can I do for ya?
%% fun, fun, oh, baby
%% fun, fun, fun, fun
%% rock, rock, rock, rock,
rock 'n' roll high school
rock 'n' roll high school %%
(students cheering)
Yay!
Detention. Detention.
Well, that about wraps it up
here at rock-'n'-roll high.
Remember, if your principal
ever gives you trouble
And you want this to happen
at your school,
You just give old
screamin' Steve a call.
I'm in the book
under "screamin'"!