Take this pink ribbon
off my eyes
I'm exposed
and it's no big surprise
Don't ya think I know
exactly where I stand
This world is forcing me
to hold your hand
'Cause I'm just a girl
Well, little old me
Well don't let me
out of your sight
Oh, I'm just a girl
All pretty and petite
So don't let me
have any rights
Oh I've had it
up to here
The moment that
I step outside
So many reasons
for me to run and hide
I can't do the little things
I hold so dear
'Cause it's all those
little things that I fear
'Cause I'm just a girl
I'd rather not be
'Cause they won't let me
drive late at night
Oh, I'm just a girl
Guess I'm some kind of freak
'Cause they all sit
and stare with their eyes
Oh, am I making myself clear
I'm just a girl
I'm just a girl in the world
- How much is this, Lori?
- It's very expensive.
It's very expensive.
Look, I got money
to spend in here.
I don't think we have anything for you.
You're obviously in the wrong place.
Please leave.
You know, even though we've watched
"Pretty Woman" like 36 times...
- I never get tired of making fun of it.
- Oh, I know.
Aww, poor thing. Look!
They won't let her shop.
Yeah, like those salesgirls in Beverly
Hills aren't bigger whores than she is.
I know!
Oh, my God, listen to that
sad, sad music as she leaves.
It's like, boo-hoo. Uhh.
But it is actually
kind of sad.
Anything you see here we can do, by the
way. Get ready to have some fun, okay?
- Okay.
- Mary Pat, Mary Kate,
Mary Frances, Tovah.
- Let's see it, come on!
Let's see the outfit.
- How divine!
Exactly how obscene--
I just get really happy
when they finally let her shop.
Okay, so I have
nothing to wear.
We don't even have time to make
anything new before we go out.
Well, what about this?
- Did you lose weight?
- Actually, I have been trying
this new fat-free diet I invented.
All I've had to eat for the past
six days are Gummi Bears,
jelly beans, and candy corns.
God, I wish I had
your discipline.
- This is it
- Work this
- Diddy-bum diddy-bum pow
- Here it is
I can't believe
how cute I look!
I know! You know what? This is like
the cutest we've ever looked.
Oh, it's definitely the cutest.
Don't you love how we can just
say that to each other...
- and we know that we're
not being conceited?
- Oh, I know.
No, we're just
being honest.
- Be my lover, Wanna be my lover
- Lover
Go ahead and take your time
Boy you gotta feel secure
Before I make you mine
Baby you have to be sure
You wanna be my lover
Wanna be my lover
God. I hope some cute guys get here
tonight. They were cute last night.
- Oh, they were cute.
- Really cute!
- Oh!
- Hey, Michele! Romy!
- We'll take two Diet Cokes?
Right, with extra cherries.
Don't move. I'll be right back.
Okay. I have the yuckiest taste
in my mouth from those taquitos.
- Eeew.
- I hope I don't get indigestion.
Hey, remember that time I barfed
from bad Mexican food? It was so gross.
- Oh, my God, I hate
throwing up in public.
- Me too! Ooh.
I can't believe it. There are
absolutely no guys here tonight.
I know. None.
Come on, Michele, let's just
go dance with ourselves.
Okay.
Put your hands in the air
'Cause there's a party over here
So grab yourself a beer
And we could
get on with the world
Swear to God.
Sometimes I wish I were a lesbian.
You wanna try and have sex sometime?
Just to see if we are?
What? Yeah, right, Michele.
Just the thought of having sex
with another woman creeps me out.
But if we're not married by
the time we're 30, ask me again.
- Okay.
- Tell me can you feel the
Masked girls comin'
with the fever, fever, fever
Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
Stayin' alive, stayin' alive
Ahh-ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
Stayin' alive, stayin' alive
- Ahh-ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh
- Two-four-three.
- Stayin' alive
Two-four-three.
Two, four, three.
Service.
Number 243.
It's beautiful.
Is that real wood?
During this century, boys.
Come on, Ramon. Quit jerking off
and bring the car around.
- It's about time.
- Mm. Romy!
You are looking hot today.
Yeah. That's because
I'm sweating like a pig in here.
Well, the air conditioning is
working in the service office.
You might wanna come by
and, uh, cool off later?
Yeah, Ramon.
That'll happen.
Sorry, ma'am.
He is such an asshole.
Mm.
- I'm in a hurry.
- Well--
I'm going as fast as I can,
Ms Mooney. Heather.
Heather Mooney?
From Sagebrush High
in Tucson?
- Yeah?
- It's Romy!
- Romy White!
- You're shittin' me.
No, this is so weird. I didn't
know you were living in L.A.
Well, now that you know, will
we be getting together a lot?
So, God!
You're driving a new Jaguar?
- What do you do?
- Ever hear of Lady Fair cigarettes?
- The ones that burn down real fast?
- "Twice the taste, in half the
time, for the gal on the go"?
I invented the
quick-burning paper.
Wow!
- You goin' to the reunion?
- What reunion?
Our ten-year high school
reunion in Tucson?
You're kidding me. It's been
ten years since high school?
- God. Where have I been?
- I'm stumped. Where?
- Anyway, are you going?
- I'd rather put this out in my ass.
I wonder why we didn't
get an invitation.
I mean, I'm sure Michele would
have told me if she got one.
- Michele Weinberger?
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you live with Michele Weinberger?
- Yeah.
I just thought maybe she'd
be married to Sandy by now.
- Sandy Frink?
- Yes, Sandy Frink.
He could barely contain his erection
every time she was around.
Why do you think he always
carried that huge notebook?
The Frink-a-zoid
and Michele, I am sure.
Besides, didn't you have a thing
for Sandy in high school?
I did not have a "thing." I did not have
a "thing." I did not have a "thing."
I was very much
in love with him.
Very much in love,
and there's a difference.
There's a difference.
I have to go now.
Well! I guess I won't be
seeing you at the reunion.
- But I'll tell everyone you said "hi."
- Why don't you tell everyone...
I said to go fuck themselves, for making
my teen years a living hell?
Oh, yeah, right!
Finally--
Michele. You will never guess
who I just ran into.
- God, I cannot believe
it's already been ten years.
- I know.
- Oh.
- You know...
- There she is.
Oh! God,
she was so weird.
- She still is.
- Why was she, like, always
going behind that building?
It was long ago
Seems like yesterday
Saw you standin' in the rain
- Then I heard you say
- Got a light?
- I want your love
But it comes out wrong
- Thank you.
- I want to live, but I don't belong
- Thank you! Thank you,
I really appreciate that...
because I'm not a human being
or anything, you pathetic turd!
Blood and roses
- Roses, roses
- There should be a cigarette
you could smoke all the way
through between classes.
What a waste.
- Okay.
- Find us.
- Oh. Okay.
Oh, my God, do you remember
what a big controversy it was...
for us to have our
picture taken together?
Yeah, well, Danny Weller, like,
"lodged the complaint," and, you know--
'Cause, "alphabetically,
he's supposed to be between us."
And then we said, "Okay, Danny.
If you want to be between us...
you can come to Michele's house on
Friday night, and we'll be waiting."
That's right. He came over and
we're like, "Danny, it was a joke."
I know! And then we turned
the sprinklers on him!
Oh, my God.
Didn't he die?
- I think so.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God. Michele.
Look at the "A" group.
- Mm-hmm.
Christie Masters,
Kelly Possenger...
Lisa Luder
and Cheryl Quick.
So, who would you say
was in the "B" group?
Oh. The drama crowd. You know,
like Casey Degan and Mark Black.
- Uh-huh. God, I had the hugest
crush on Casey. 'Member?
- Oh, yeah.
God, I wonder why
he never liked me.
Young man, there's
no need to feel down
I said, young man--
So, what group would
you say we were in?
Well, we definitely
weren't in the "A" group.
But you know what? We weren't
really in the "B" group, either.
Okay, we weren't in
the "C" group, were we?
What? Oh, no. Michele, come on.
I mean, that was like,
all the honour students and like...
the rejects; you know, like
Sandy Frink and Heather Mooney.
- Eeew, look at them.
- We were definitely not in that group.
- Ecch.
- She blinded me with Science
Michele! Oh, Michele.
Over here!
Want me to get your
huge notebook for you?
Oh! Heather! I wanna
take another picture of you and
Sandy for the yearbook and--
Oh! I wanna
interview you too...
because I think it would make a really
interesting article for the "Roundup."
Ohh, Toby! Fuck off.
Okay. But can I take
a picture of you first?
So, Romy, what group
were we in?
Well, you know, I'm not sure that
we were really in any group.
I think maybe we were
more like loners.
- Oh, my God! There we are!
- Yeah, and alone. Look.
You know, even though I had
to wear that stupid back brace,
and you were kinda fat...
we were still totally
cutting edge.
- I love it when it's hamburger day.
- Uh-huh.
Okay, smile! Great!
Thanks a lot!
- Can I take your picture?
- Oh, please.
- Hello, girls.
Don't forget, you have
detention after school today.
- Oh, we won't, Mr Lish.
- Yeah, we're really
looking forward to it.
- God!
- Can you believe he just got married?
- Like, how desperate is she?
- I know, it's like:
"Hi. This is my husband.
He dissects crayfish, but he
has a really good personality."
He's the kind of man
that I desire
Sets the summer sun
on fire
- I want candy
- Oh, my God.
- Michele. Billy Christianson.
- Oh, he's so cute.
- He is cute.
- Really cute.
- Hey
- Hi, Billy.
Hey
- Hey
- Ow! Billy!
Oh, Billy, gosh,
you're so slimy.
I cannot believe he's
with Christie Masters.
I know. She is, like,
so transparent.
Did you hear her report
in Miss Weigatt's class?
She actually thinks she's gonna be a
TV anchorwoman. What a "deludanoid."
Those weirdos are
staring at us again.
- They're obsessed with us.
- Look at what they're wearing.
Where do you even get
outfits that hideous?
They made them in Home Ec
from their own patterns.
Actually, I think
they're semi-interesting.
In a freakish, off-putting
sort of way. Never mind.
- Christie.
- Uh.
- Come on, I'm hungry.
No, Billy. Wait.
I wanna have some fun.
Lisa, gimme the bag.
Here you go.
You are so bad.
- What? What?
- She is out of control.
Michele? Christie Masters
is coming over here.
- Wow. She never comes over.
- Okay, just act cool.
- Hi.
- Hi, Christie.
- So. You girls gonna try out
for the spring musical?
- Us?
Yeah, you should.
It'll be fun.
- Okay. Why not?
- Yeah. So, um, what
musical are they doing?
- "The Music Man."
- You're kidding!
Oh, the Wells Fargo wagon
ls a-comin' down the street
I love "The Music Man."
Okay. Can I have
the rest of this?
Um, w--
Mm. It's good.
See ya!
She can be really nice
when she wants to be.
Michele!
- Uh-oh. Don't look now.
Here come the Frink-a-zoid.
- Oh, God! He is such a geek!
Hi, Michele. Gee, Michele,
you're looking really lovely today.
Okay. See you in Biology.
I-l-l thought I ought
to tell you, Michele, that...
Christie Masters stuck
magnets on your back.
- What?
- She stuck--
Michele, you do have
magnets on your back!
Oh, my God.
Help me.
Oh, don't let them see you get upset.
That's what they want.
Oh, my God.
- Hey!
- I'm pretending you just
did something hilarious.
Now, you laugh at me.
Come on, do it.
God, that was so rude. I mean, you
couldn't help it if you had scoliosis.
I know. And what a bitch, taking
your hamburger. I mean, what was that?
God, remember the prom?
You got so thin by then.
Oh, I know. I was so lucky,
getting mono. That was, like,
the best diet ever.
I wonder, if I had gotten
my brace off sooner, if
somebody would have invited me.
I mean, other
than Sandy Frink.
Well, nobody
invited me either.
Well, at least we looked fantastic,
and that is the most important thing.
- We were cool on craze
- Oh, gee. Nice outfits. Really.
- When l, you
- Oh, look, it's the Madonna twins.
- And everyone we knew
Could believe, do, and share
in what was true, Oh, I said
Okay, this is so typical.
Of course, we're like the only ones...
who don't look like
we're going to a hoedown.
-Oh, I know. This town is like so unhip.
-Ecch.
- I can't wait till we move to L.A.
- Me too!
Everything's gonna happen for us there,
Michele, and we'll never look back.
- Okay.
- Dance hall days
- Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
That hurt.
But it looked really good.
Dance hall days
Oh, everybody!
- Dance hall, dance hall days
- Okay, everyone.
Uh, it's the moment
we've all been waiting for.
It's time to announce
the king and queen of the prom.
- Ahh!
- And the winners are...
Billy Christianson
and Christie Masters!
Ohh! Ohh!
- Duh.
- Oh, it's me!
Boo-hoo!
I'm so surprised!
Thank you. Thank you.
God, Billy looks
cute in his tux.
- He does look cute.
- Really cute.
Do you think, since it's
the last night of school and
I might never see him again...
that maybe he would
dance with me?
I bet he would.
I mean, it's senior prom.
Nobody's going to say "no"
to anyone tonight.
Michele, since this is the
last night of school and all...
would you care
to dance with me once?
No.
I'll dance with you.
Nah. It's no fun unless
you really love the person.
Thanks, anyway.
Okay. Who can name the capitals
of all the 50 states?
Okay, Toby. Fuck off.
Heather! Can't you be
a little bit more sensitive?
Me? Me? Me be
more sensitive?
You are a jerk-off!
Another kiss
is what it takes
- Albuquerque.
- You can't sleep
- You can't eat
- Albany.
There's no doubt
You're in deep
Your throat is tight
You can't breathe
Another kiss is all you need
Whoa-oh-ohh
- Why are you tormenting me?
- You like to think
you're immune to the stuff
- Why don't you go fuck a sheep
or your sister or yourself?
- Oh, yeah
Brain-dead
redneck asshole!
Can't get enough
You know you're gonna have to face it
You're addicted to love
You see the signs
But you can't read
You're runnin' at
a different speed
Your heart beats
in double time
- Another kiss
- Um, Billy?
- And you'll be mine
- Hi.
- A one-track mind, you can't be saved
- Do you wanna dance?
- Oblivion is all you crave
- I mean, it's just 'cause...
this song is,
like, so great.
Mm. Never mind.
Unless, you know,
you want to.
- Whoa, you like to think
- Yeah. I mean--
- That you're immune to this stuff
- Y-Y-- Sure. Why not?
- Oh, yeah
- Really?
- Wh-- Um--
- It's closer to the truth
- Could you wait here?
- To say you can't get enough
- I-l-l'll be right back.
- Okay.
- You know, you're gonna have to face it
You're addicted to love
Might as well face it
- Might as well face it
- Hey, Christie.
- You're addicted to love
- That Romy girl just asked
me to dance with her.
- Might as well face it
- Oh, you're kidding me!
Oh, that's pathetic!
- Might as well face it
- W-W-W-What should I do?
Let me take care of this.
- Michele?
- Oh, God. Okay, so what did he say?
- "Sure. Why not?"
- Oh, my God!
- Thanks a lot, Romy.
- What?
Thanks for stealing
my boyfriend.
- What are you talking about?
- Billy just broke up with me.
Apparently he's had a crush on
you since Mr Roswell's class.
And now that he knows that
you like him, he doesn't want
to "pretend" with me any more.
My life was perfect
and you've ruined it.
Go for it
Groove ahead
I swear to God, Christie,
I didn't even think he'd dance with me.
- To whip it, Whip it good
- Wow. She is really P.O.'d.
- This is so cool!
- Oh, I know.
You know what is so weird?
I had this dream, where Billy
was like, in love with me.
And I mean, he was in
a wheelchair, but still, it's like
it's coming true or something!
- Uh-huh.
- How's my hair?
Perfect. Okay, Romy, you look so
good with blonde hair and black roots.
- It's like, not even funny.
- I have to say...
this is turning out to be one of
the very best nights of my entire life.
Yay, yay!
Lyin' in my bed I hear
the clock tick
And think of you
Caught up in circles
Confusion is nothing new
Flashback to warm nights
Almost left behind
- Suitcase of memories
- You know, maybe he's, like,
passed out in the bathroom.
- You want me to go check?
- Time after, Sometimes
- You picture me
- He's not in the bathroom, Michele.
I'm walkin' too far ahead
- I'll dance with you, Romy.
- You're callin' to me
- I can't hear what you've said
- Okay.
Then you say "Go slow"
I fall behind
The second hand unwinds
If you're lost you can look
and you will find me
Time after time
If you fall, I will catch you
I'll be waiting
Time after time
If you're lost, you can look
and you will find me
Time after time
- If you fall, I will catch you
I'll be waiting
- I will be waiting
Time after time
We just waited and waited.
- God, I was such an idiot.
- But wait till he sees you now.
You are so much cuter
than you were in high school.
- I guess I'm cuter.
- Yeah!
And look at the way we live.
I mean, just our lifestyle.
You know, I mean, we live in L.A,
and they are still stuck in Tucson.
You know what, Michele?
You're right.
We are gonna go back there
and blow them away.
Boy, there's a lot
of questions to answer.
Why do we have to fill these out?
They wanna know what we've been
doing for the past ten years.
- Oh!
- Okay. Here we go.
- Ahh!
- "Name."
- Ah! We're having so much fun already.
- Oh, I know!
- I cannot wait for this reunion.
- Me too!
"Occupation."
Cashier.
- Unemployed.
- No. Don't write that.
Um, okay, so your last job
was as a salesgirl?
- So say you're a freelance
fashion consultant.
- Ooh! Clever.
"Relationship Status."
Married.
- Nope.
- Engaged?
- No.
- Living with someone?
- Should I say you?
- I guess so.
- Okay.
- You know, Michele?
- Yeah?
- Now that I'm looking at this...
- Uh-huh?
our lives don't seem as
impressive as I thought.
- They don't?
- Well, do you think it's impressive...
that we're still single, and we've
been living together for ten years...
and I'm a cashier
and you're unemployed?
Well, not super impressive.
Well, then, what's the point of going
if we're not going to impress people?
Well-- Uh.
Romy, I still really,
really, really want to go.
- I know. Me too.
- Well then, can't we just,
like, think of something?
- Okay. Well, the reunion is still
like two weeks away, right?
- Right.
And all we really need is maybe some,
like, better jobs and boyfriends. Right?
Yeah!
But, okay. If those things were so easy
to get, wouldn't we already have them?
Well, I mean, we never
really tried before.
I mean, we never really had
a good enough reason, like going
to a reunion, to motivate us.
That's true.
Okay. So we're just gonna have to make
ourselves more impressive, that's all.
So I'm gonna go out and bag us
some boyfriends, while you can
look for a cool new job.
- Okay.
- Plus, I hate to say it...
but I really think that
we should lose some weight.
Oh.
Oh. Unh.
Okay. I don't think that, like,
one chip makes a difference.
It wasn't even
a whole chip.
All right. According to this chart,
if we want to lose a pound a day...
we have to burn twice
as many calories as we eat.
So, that means, if we want
to burn 4,000 calories...
we only have to run
20 miles a day!
Oh! Hey, Romy, remember
Mrs Chivas' class?
There was, like,
always a word problem.
Like, there's a guy in
a rowboat going "X" miles...
and the current is going, like,
you know, some... other miles...
and, how long does it take him
to get to town?
It was like, who cares? Who wants to go
to town with a guy who drives a rowboat?
Okay, guys, let's jump.
- Hey, Michele?
- Yeah?
- What does this remind you of?
Well, I know.
This lady is totally sick.
Uh, lemme just
say that, um...
I am, like, really familiar
with the entire Versace line,
and if you would just...
give me a chance, I know I could,
like, sell the shit out of the stuff.
And, uh, to me,
fashion is just, it's like...
everything. It's--
By the way, that blouse-- Hi.
That blouse looks great on you.
- Oh! Thank you!
- And see, I make a great salesperson...
'cause I just have this,
like, really believable way...
of telling people that they
look really good, even though
I'm just, like, you know--
I think
she heard me.
Thank you so much
for coming.
- That's okay, you're welcome.
- I don't think we'll be
requiring any new staff.
- You aren't taking on any what?
- Staff. Employees.
Ohh! Oh, "staff."
Okay, I didn't understand
with your big accent.
I couldn't
figure it out. Okay.
Fine. You know, you really shouldn't
let people fill out applications...
if you don't want them to
actually try to get a job here.
- It's a compli--
- No, no. That's all I have to say.
- Goodbye.
If there ain't no love
then there ain't no use
Ooh, better walk on by
Better walk on through
Hi. Hey, um, great suit.
Is that an Armani?
- Yes. Yes, it is.
- I thought so. So, what do you do?
- I'm a suit salesman.
- Oh, uh-oh
Would you excuse me?
I cut my foot before,
and my shoe is filling up with blood.
Ooh, if there ain't no love
then there ain't no use
Ooh, better walk on by
Better walk on through
Hey, hey, there's a woman in the world
that you can't use
Ain't no love, Ain't no use
Ain't no love
Yeah, well, my first choice was
to work at a boutique on Rodeo Drive,
but this would be okay.
Well, thank you. Unfortunately, we
don't have any openings here right now.
- Are you serious?
- Mm.
Although we might have
an opening at our discount outlet.
Okay, well, what street
would that be on?
Come on, Michele. At this point,
any job is better than no job at all.
A discount outlet? Me?
Fine.
So, any boyfriends yet?
No. All the guys with good jobs
must be going to some other club.
Oh, you know where Dana met her new
boyfriend? He's a William Morris agent.
Oh! Showbiz!
Good job! Where?
Hi. My name is Romy,
and I'm an alcoholic.
- Hi, Romy!
- Hey.
And you also get a five-percent
employee discount...
over and above our
everyday low prices.
You could make curtains
for the motorhome with this.
- I got this tie for a dollar.
- You paid a whole dollar for that?
- You betcha.
- Ah!
She's one
of our regulars.
So, what do you think?
I-l'd like to go away.
I know I'm supposed to wait
in that line, but listen.
I wouldn't even be here if this
weren't, like, a dating emergency.
Our cutoff is 25.
Try VH-1.
The reunion's less than a week
away. I mean, I just can't
believe you turned down a job.
Well, I thought the idea
was to impress people.
I mean, how am I going
to impress anyone by selling
Ban-Lon smocks at Bargain Mart?
I'm sick of this.
I'm gonna go weigh myself.
Oh, God! I've been killing myself
for eight days and I gained a pound.
That's impossible! Did you
deduct 16 pounds for your shoes?
Just forget it.
I'm not going.
- What?
- Come on. Get real, Michele.
We're idiots.
We can't get jobs and boyfriends,
and lose weight, in two weeks.
But I thought
you said we could.
Wow. God, the top female
executives are all so pretty.
Those aren't the actual executives,
Michele. Those are models.
Oh, I thought
they looked familiar.
God, they really look like
executives, don't they?
That's only because they're
wearing those stupid suits...
and phoney glasses,
and carrying briefcases.
- Huh!
- Oh, my God, Michele, that's it!
We can go to the reunion, and
just pretend to be successful!
I mean, who's gonna know?
They're in Tucson, we're here.
We could just show up
looking like businesswomen.
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Wait. Ohh. But if the people at the
reunion see us drive up in a Nova...
won't they know we're not
really businesswomen?
If you can make us
the clothes...
I can get us the car.
Clear out, boys.
I need to talk to Ramon.
Go!
Yes, cara mia?
Michele and I have this
high school reunion to go to...
and we need to show up
in a really cool car.
- Yeah?
- Todd told me that he gave
you a really great deal...
- on an XJS convertible and
that you're fixing it up.
- Yeah?
So...
can I borrow your car?
Well, if I loan
you my car...
what do I get?
- Uh, what do you want?
- Ohh, Romy...
you know what I want.
Oh, forget it. I'm not going
to have sex with you
just to borrow your stupid car!
I gotta get something.
Okay.
Close the blinds,
and we'll work something out.
Ohh! Ohh! Ohh, Ramon!
- Ohh, Ramon, ohh! Ohh!
- Check this out.
- Oh, yes. Ohh.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, man!
- Ohh! Ohh!
Ohh, Ramon!
Ohh! Oh, yes.
You are Columbus,
and I am America.
Discover me, Ramon!
Just discover me.
Hey, uh-- Explosions.
The earth is moving.
Explosions!
The earth is moving!
Ah, ooh-- is that an earthquake?
No, it's Ramon.
Is that an earthquake?
No, it's Ramon!
Ahh! It's Ramon!
Man stallion, fill me
with your giant love wand!
What? No, I'm sorry.
I don't think so.
Well, say something nice
about my penis!
Oh, Ramon, your penis
is so powerful. I'm coming!
- Okay, thanks. Get off me now.
- Aw, come on, wh--
- You wanted it to be believable.
- Aww.
I'm just a girl
in the world
That's all that
you'll let me be
Oh, I'm just a girl
living in captivity
Oh, my God!
You did it!
Yeah, I did.
All right, let's get going.
Oh, this is gonna
be so much fun.
- So, what'd you have to do to get it?
- I had to give all the guys...
in the service department
hand jobs.
Well, while you were doing that,
I taped all the nostalgic songs...
from high school,
to get us in the mood.
- Michele?
- Huh?
- I was kidding.
- What?
- You actually think I would
do something like that?
For a car?
- Okay, just get in.
- Okay.
Hey, look what else
I got us, little lady.
- Oh, my God. It's a flip phone!
- Uh-huh.
- How'd you get this?
- I bought it.
Okay.
- Are ya ready?
- Ready.
Let's do it.
Tonight
I gotta cut loose
- Footloose
- Footloose!
- Kick off my Sunday shoes
- Kick off my Sunday knees?
- Oowhee, Louise
- I have no idea what
the rest of the lyrics are.
- Me neither. Whoo!
- Jack, get back
- Watch out, Tucson, here we come!
- Come on before we crack
- Shit!
- Aww.
- Loose your blues
- Watch out, Tucson, here we come!
- Everybody cut footloose
Footloose, footloose
Kick off your Sunday shoes
- Shit!
- Aww.
- Footloose
- Whoo!
- You're playin' so cool
Obeyin' every rule
- Dig way down in your heart
- Down in your art--
- You're yearnin', burnin'
- You're flurnin', burnin', earnin'
- Somebody to tell you
- Somebody better tell you
- That life ain't passin' you by
- You have one hell of an eye
- Everybody cut, everybody cut
- Everybody, everybody cut footloose
- Footloose
I got your picture
I'd like a million of ya
all to myself
I want a doctor
to take a picture
So I can look at you
from inside as well
- You got me turning up and turning down
- Okay, I give up. What are you doing?
Pass this car.
This kid is so obnoxious.
- Turning Japanese
- Oh, my God. What is with that kid?
I don't know.
He is sick!
Turning Japanese
I think I'm turning Japanese
I really think so
Turning Japanese
I think I'm turning Japanese
I really think so
Turning Japanese
I think I'm turning Japanese
I really think so
Oh, I'm sorry. No.
No, not you. No. I was trying
to scare your little boy.
Oh, my God.
Are my lips that big?
Woke up this mornin'
happy as can be
- Some more of that?
- Yeah.
All right. Now, just remember,
from this point on...
we are sophisticated, educated,
successful career women.
Right. Okay.
God, this underwear is totally
riding up my butt crack.
Yeah. Hello.
Um, we need something to go.
- Okay.
- Do you have some sort of
businesswoman's special?
- Come again?
- Well, we're businesswomen.
- Yeah. From L.A.
- And you know some places have,
like, a lunch special.
For businesswomen.
We don't have
anything like that.
Well, then why don't you
just give us, um, two burgers
and fries and Diet Cokes...
- 'cause we're in a hurry.
- Mm. We're due in Tucson later.
For a business thing.
You know.
What kind
of business you in?
I can't believe we never thought
of what to say we did for a living.
Oh. Which one
of these guys...
will I have sex with
at the reunion?
Ooh!
Casey Degan!
- Aaah!
- Come on! Now, we're
running out of time.
I know. Why don't we say
that we own our own company?
Ooh, good.
Like what?
- Like, what if we invented something?
- Like what?
Well, okay, l-l think it should
be like something that-that
everybody has heard about...
but-but nobody really
knows who invented it.
Oh, my God! I've got it!
Post-lts!
- Everybody knows what Post-lts are!
- Yeah!
They're the little yellow things
with the stickum on the back, right?
Okay.
Okay, we're-we're working in this
advertising agency after college.
- Ooh, college! Good one!
- Yeah.
And we have, like, this big,
like, presentation...
to make to,
like, a client.
- Hmm!
- So-so-so we're, like, brainstorming...
and all of the sudden
we're out of paper clips!
- Good!
- And so, okay-- So then l, l, like--
Okay, I say--
I say-- Okay--
"Wouldn't it be great if there
was, like, this, like, stickum
on the back of this paper...
"so, like, it-it would just--
if I laid it on top of that
other paper it would just stay...
you know, like,
without a paper clip?"
- Yes!
- Ahh!
So then you've got, like, this
grandfather or this uncle...
that, like, has, like, a-- Iike a--
Iike a paper company or a paper mill...
and-and he's, like, really into it,
and the rest is history!
Oh, my God!
It is perfect!
Wow!
Don't you think?
Well, yeah, but--
- "Well, yeah, but" what?
- I don't know.
I mean, it just sounds like you invented
Post-lts all by yourself, you know.
-I mean, what did I do?
-Well, it was your grandfather or uncle.
Yeah?
Okay, you know,
so we could say that...
you were,
like, the designer.
Like, I thought of them, but you
thought of making them yellow.
Well, no, but it's like
most of these people...
have, like, known us
since elementary school.
I just think that you're
more believable as a designer...
rather than
as an inventor, you know?
- Uh-huh.
- You're my lover
Not my rival
- What are you doing?
- Look.
You're obviously
pissed at me.
No. Uh-uh. Why should
I be pissed at you?
Just because now I know
how you really feel about me.
Oh, my God,
I knew this would happen.
I mean, I try, for once,
to be honest with you...
and it blows up
in my face.
God!
You wanna be honest?
Okay, good!
Let's be honest!
I let you
have the ideas!
- What?
- Yeah, I let you have the ideas...
so you won't feel so bad
that I'm cuter.
- You are not cuter, Michele.
- I am so cuter.
It's, like, common knowledge, Romy.
Everybody thinks so.
I'm the Mary
and you're the Rhoda.
That's ridiculous. You're the Rhoda.
You're the Jewish one.
Oh, my God. I'm talking
cuteness-wise, Romy, okay?
And cuteness-wise,
I'm the Mary.
That's crazy! You have absolutely
no proof that you're cuter!
Oh, proof? You want proof?
Okay, fine.
- Who lost their virginity first?
- Oh, big wow!
With your cousin Barry.
I wouldn't brag about it.
Okay, so who always gets asked to
dance first when we go to clubs, huh?
No wonder you couldn't
find us boyfriends, Romy.
Well, so what?
You can't even get a job!
- I carry you, Michele!
Without me, you'd be lost!
- That is such a lie!
Oh, yeah? Well, let's just see.
Let's split up and see what happens.
W-What do you mean,
split up?
When we get to Tucson,
we're going our own separate ways.
Okay. Good.
Fine.
I don't care.
- Fine!
- Fine.
As of Tucson,
we're finished.
Well, drive fast!
Always something there
to remind me
Wow.
Billy Christianson?
Romy. Romy White.
No. No way.
My God, you--
you look fantastic.
I mean, l-- I never would have
recognized you in a million years.
Thanks.
So, what have you been doin'
since high school?
Well,
believe it or not...
I invented Post-lts.
So I told Prescott...
"You can either pay me the 150
or I am out of here. Bye-bye."
I mean, there are at least 12
other major markets that would
put me on the air tomorrow.
Wow. So you did it?
You're an anchorwoman?
No.
I'm a weather girl.
On the highest-rated
5:00 news in Tucson.
- Oh.
- So...
Michele,
what are you up to?
Uh, okay.
Um, I invented Post-lts.
- You're kidding!
- You must've made a fortune!
Well, yeah.
No offence, Michele...
but how in the world
did you think of Post-lts?
Um... well...
uh...
And I invented them
totally by myself.
I mean, all Michele did was say,
"What about making them yellow?"
Really?
- Actually, I invented
a special kind of glue.
- Oh, really?
Well, then I'm sure you wouldn't
mind giving us a detailed account...
of exactly how you concocted
this miracle glue, would you?
No. Um--
Well, ordinarily
when you make glue...
first you need to
thermoset your resin...
and then after it cools
you mix in a, um, epoxide.
Which is really just
a fancy-schmancy name...
for any simple,
oxygenated adhesive, right?
But then I thought maybe-- just maybe--
you could raise the viscosity...
by adding a complex glucose derivative
during the emulsification process.
And it turns out,
I was right.
Huh?
I don't believe it.
You must be the most successful
person in our graduating class.
Uh-huh.
And you're not. Bye.
Always something there
to remind me
This is so great.
Romy?
Can I ask you
something?
Romy! You will not believe
what just happened!
Michele, can't you see
that I am busy?
Fine.
Okay, just forget it.
Whoa! Oh. Oww.
Oww. Oww. Oww.
Oh!
Oh! Come on!
Oh, God!
Are you all right?
- What do you think?
- I am so sorry.
My-My-My driver
didn't see you.
Please. Come.
I have boxes of Kleenex
in my limo.
Let me make it up
to you.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
- Here. Help yourself, Michele.
- Thanks.
Wait. How do you
know my name?
It's me, Michele.
Sandy.
- Sandy Frink?
- Uh-huh.
But you're so dreamy.
Well, when I made
my first million...
my present to myself
was a new face.
Okay, I'm not
just saying this...
but you really picked
a good one.
Thanks.
I had this notebook...
with "Mrs Romy Christianson" written
on it, like, about a thousand times.
Now you think
I'm some sort of geek.
No. No.
No, not at all.
I'm flattered.
Hi, Billy.
I've been lookin'
all over for you.
You wanna dance once?
You know,
for old times' sake.
No, thanks.
I owe this one to Romy.
Hey, you guys, they're about
to announce the winners of the vote.
- Come on!
- Vote? What vote?
- Let's go. We gotta get in there.
- Okay.
Wait, I can't
find my top.
Where are you?
Hey, how you guys
doin' tonight?
I bet, uh, everyone
is as anxious...
as I am to hear
the results of the vote.
What vote?
The person voted Most Changed
for the Better Since High School is--
It's a tie.
The Most Changed for the Better
Since High School are...
Romy White
and Michele Weinberger.
Honey, go on up there
and get your medal.
Okay.
How weird. I didn't
even know we were voting.
Get me another daiquiri.
Here you go.
Um, I'm sorry.
I couldn't find my top.
Honey,
that is beautiful.
May I take that
for you, sir?
No, no, no.
You leave me alone.
Looking at your medal
from the reunion again, dear?
You miss her,
don't you?
Duh.
Michele...
have you been terribly unhappy
with me all these years?
Oh, no.
No, Sandy.
Oh, good.
I've just been lonely
with no one to talk to.
Why don't you call her?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Hello?
- Billy Christianson?
Oh, no, no,
I'm-l'm Billy Junior.
Oh, Billy, honey,
is your mommy home?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, but, uh, she can't come
to the phone right now.
She-She's on
her deathbed.
- Romy.
- Oh, dear.
Billy, honey...
tell your mommy that
Michele Weinberger-Frink...
is on the phone...
and would very much
like to speak with her.
No.
Not until you admit...
that I'm the Mary,
and you're the Rhoda.
I'm the Mary.
I'm the Mary!
I'm the-- You're a pasty hag
on a deathbed.
I'm the Mary.
Everybody knows.
Way to go, honey.
Oh, God.
Oh, we're really here.
- Oh, God.
- Good evening, sir.
Thanks for not
waking me up, Romy.
God, what a bitch.
Don't get me wrong
If I'm looking
kind of dazzled
I see neon lights
Whenever you walk by
Don't get me wrong
- Hey, Romy White.
- Hey.
- Where's Michele?
- I don't know.
Um, anybody see
Billy Christianson?
- Try the bar.
- Thanks, man.
Don't get me wrong
Oh, excuse me, excuse me.
You-you can't go in without a name tag.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
Uh, Michele Weinberger.
Oh, my God, Michele Weinberger!
My God, you look great!
It's me, Toby.
Oh, Toby Walters.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay.
Um, oh, here it is.
Here is your name tag.
And, um, Romy
is already inside.
- I could care less.
I am not here with Romy.
- You're kidding me.
No, we're not
even friends any more.
We had this big falling out
over Post-lts.
- Post-lts?
- It's a long story.
- See ya.
- W-W--
I'm only off to wander
Across a moonlit night
Once in a while
Two people meet
Seemingly, for no reason
they just pass on the street
Suddenly thundershowers
everywhere
Who can explain
the thunder and rain
But there's somethin'
in the air
Ooh, excuse me.
Hi, Romy.
How are you?
- Lisa Luder?
- Yes.
So, where's the rest
of the "A" group?
Oh, they're around here
someplace.
We sort of lost touch
over the years.
Wow. Isn't it weird when you're
not friends with your friends any more?
I mean, Michele and I just fell
out of touch about two hours ago.
Because she's selfish...
and she always,
like, devalues me.
And I'm sick of it,
you know?
God, you guys are easy
to talk to.
I invented Post-lts.
- You know, the yellow things
with the stickum on the back?
- Yes, I know what they are.
So, uh,
what are you up to?
I'm an associate fashion editor
for Vogue.
Wow! Wh--
Good job!
Boy, I must have, like,
every single issue of Vogue...
for the past ten years.
Okay, well, it was
very nice talking with you.
Nice talking to you too.
Okay, Romy.
It might just be
fantastic
Don't get me wrong
It was so cute.
My mom gave us
a new car seat for the baby.
And when the box arrived, little
Jake looks up at me and says...
"Mommy,
is that the baby?"
- Oh.
- I wish.
Hey, everyone.
- And so we meet again.
- Oh, hi.
Romy White.
You're the chubby girl.
Oh, well, I was, but I haven't
been for a really long time.
So, what are
all of you up to?
Christie, in the yearbook you said
that you wanted Jane Pauley's job.
Are you a big TV news
anchorwoman now?
Oh, no, I don't even
watch TV any more.
My priorities have changed
since I became a mommy.
Can you believe
this is number three?
Wow, three kids.
God, you must feel
really tied down.
Not at all.
I feel very fulfilled.
Besides, Billy always
wanted a big family.
- Billy Christianson?
- Mm-hmm.
- You married Billy Christianson?
For almost ten years now.
Billy's in
real estate development.
So, how about you?
Any kids?
Oh, uh, no.
I just haven't had time, you know, what
with running my own business and all.
Your own business?
Yeah.
I invented Post-lts.
No, really.
What do you do?
That's what I do.
I invented Post-lts.
Oh. You're kidding me.
Well, I've made
a lot of money.
Oh, you know who they say
has made a ton of money? Sandy Frink.
- The Frink-a-zoid?
- Yeah.
He invented some special kind
of rubber that's used in every
tennis shoe in North America.
Hey, if anybody
needs to make a call...
I've got a phone.
- Is Sandy Frink here?
- Uh, no.
-Uh, you can't go in without a name tag.
-Fuck off!
Heather Mooney? Oh, my God,
you're exactly the same.
Oh, my God.
Heather Mooney is here?
This ought to be so good.
Oh, God, don't look now.
It's Heather Mooney.
- What?
- Hello, Romy.
Uh-- E-- Uh-- You--
Oh, uh-- Heather,
you said you weren't coming.
Yeah, well, since Sandy
and Michele aren't married--
What a waste
of a tank of gas, huh?
Okay, well, come on.
I'll help you go find him.
Uh, he's not here. I already asked Toby
Dumbfuck. Obviously, I've interrupted.
Why don't you just go back to ignoring
me like you did in high school?
No, you can stay.
We're just discussing our class
success stories. So, what are you up to?
Ever hear of Lady Fair cigarettes?
I invented the quick-burning paper.
- Wow, we have a whole class
full of inventors.
- Meaning?
Oh, you know, Sandy Frink
invented something too.
- Hey, isn't that Sandy over there now?
- What did Sandy invent?
- Some kind of rubber.
- Romy here invented Post-lts.
- You did not.
- Yeah, I did.
Yeah, l--
Well, who did then?
A guy named Art Fry
from the 3M Corp.
We studied it
in business school.
You're kidding me.
You just
made all that up?
Oh, God,
you are so weird.
- Why don't you just leave her alone?
- Michele.
Oh, it's
the back brace girl.
- Hi, back brace girl.
Oh, shut up.
And what are you
picking on us for anyway?
We are not the ones
who got fat.
We're pregnant,
you half-wit.
Oh, yeah, well...
I hope your babies
look like monkeys.
Come on, Romy.
- Oh, Romy.
- Oh, please, go away.
Just leave me alone.
Why did I even
come back here?
Well, you know what? There are worse
things than telling some dumb story...
and having everybody
laugh at you.
- Like what?
- Like losing your best friend.
You know? I mean,
I had the worst dream, Romy.
I dreamt that we weren't friends
and we were really, really old.
But I mean, like, we were, like,
really, really old.
And-And we weren't friends.
I can't stand that
we're mad at each other.
Okay, I'm sorry
I said all those things.
You're as cute as me.
You are.
And-And in some cultures,
maybe cuter.
I'm sorry too.
I shouldn't have said that you weren't
smart enough to invent Post-lts.
Well, I mean,
maybe I'm not.
Although in my dream,
I did know the formula for glue.
So, are we friends again?
Well, duh.
Okay.
And you know what,
it doesn't even matter...
that we told, like, what,
four people some dumb lie.
Who cares?
Hi, everybody.
Settle down. Hi.
I'm Christie
Masters-Christianson.
I have been asked
to formally welcome you all...
to Sagebrush High's
ten-year reunion.
We have come a long way
in the past ten years.
Our own Lisa Luder is helping
set the style for the country...
as a fashion editor
for "Vogue" magazine.
And Travis McKinney
is in his fifth year...
as a member of the
Dallas Cowboys football team.
And...
Romy and Michele claimed...
they invented Post-lts.
All I ever wanted was
for people to think...
that we were better
than we were in high school.
And now we're just a stupid joke,
just like we always were.
No, Romy.
Can I tell you the truth?
I never knew that we weren't
that great in high school.
I mean, we always had
so much fun together.
I thought high school
was a blast.
And until you told me that
our lives weren't good enough...
I thought everything
since high school was a blast.
I think we should go back
out there as ourselves...
and just have fun
like we always do.
The hell with
everyone else.
I don't think I can.
Well, do you think you can
stop being such a baby?
God, I feel like
I've been, like...
chasing you all over
this reunion.
We have come
all this way.
Now we are going to enjoy ourselves
whether you like it or not.
God, Michele, I've never seen this side
of your personality before.
You're so bossy
and domineering.
- I like it.
- Me too.
She's got it
Yeah, baby
she's got it
- I don't believe it.
- What?
They're ba-ack.
Well, I'm your Venus
- Nice outfits.
- I'm your fire
Post-lts must be
really lucrative.
- Are you sure you want to do this?
- Oh, yeah, Michele, I am so sure.
What the hell is
your problem, Christie?
Why are you always
such a nasty bitch?
Do you get some kind of sick pleasure
from torturing other people?
I mean, yeah, okay, so Michele and I
did make up some lame story.
We only did it because we wanted you
to treat us like human beings.
But you know what
I finally realized?
I don't care if you like us
'cause we don't like you.
You're a bad person
with an ugly heart...
and we don't give a flying fuck
what you think.
- Come on, Michele.
- Okay.
And, yeah.
It's unbelievable.
They're as deluded about their lives...
as they are about
those hideous clothes.
Actually, Christie,
they've got nice lines...
a fun,
frisky use of colour.
All in all, I'd have to say
they're really not bad.
Well, we still think
they're ridiculous.
Don't we, girls?
Why don't you just let them
think for themselves for once?
You're just jealous...
because unlike a certain ball-busting,
dried-up career woman I might mention...
we're all happily married.
That's right, Christie.
Keep telling
yourself that.
- I do love those outfits.
- Yeah, sure do.
- Oh, great.
- Thanks.
Michele made them.
Well, I just sewed them.
We both designed them.
- Fifty-fifty.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
That's so cool.
Well, it's been really
terrific seeing all of you.
- Come on, Michele.
- Oh, okay, bye.
Hi.
I am sorry that I blew
your big lie for you.
Hey, that's okay.
It was better this way anyway.
It's ironic, isn't it? I really thought
you guys had it made in high school.
- Us?
- Yes, you.
With your long hair
and your long legs...
walkin' on your legs,
flippin' your hair.
I can't compete with that.
You made Sandy crazy.
And the whole time
you were makin' my life hell...
the "A" group was making
your life hell; I didn't know.
You know what? I bet in high school
everybody made somebody's life hell.
Mm-mmm, not me. Never had the
opportunity to make anyone's life hell.
You know what? I bet that's not true.
You were really unpleasant.
- You think?
- Oh, yeah. God.
Heather?
Oh, I'm off duty.
Um, since you never
got around to it in high school...
I was wondering
if you could sign my yearbook.
And, uh, please don't
tell me to fuck off...
because it really hurts
my feelings.
- I hurt your feelings?
- Yeah, all the time.
Tremendous!
That's tremendous!
Go get your stupid yearbook.
I would be happy to sign it.
Okay, great.
I'll-l'll be right back, okay?
Michele, I think maybe
we should leave.
There is no way this reunion
is gonna get any better.
Hey, everybody, Sandy Frink
just landed in a helicopter!
Sandy Frink
has a helicopter?
Yeah. Apparently he's worth,
like, millions.
He invented some kind of
special rubber or something.
Like for condoms?
Whoa-ohh-ohh
The hot summer night
Fell like a net
I've gotta find
my baby yet
You think I'm cute
A little bit shy
Mama, I ain't
that kind of guy
That's Sandy Frink?
What the hell was I thinking?
Whoa-ohh-ohh
Sandy, hi.
- Doctor, Doctor, give me the news
- You look so rich.
- I got a bad case of lovin' you
- I mean, great.
No pill's gonna
cure my ill
I got a bad case
of lovin' you
Michele.
- After all these years,
you still take my breath away.
- Thanks.
So you must be, like,
the most successful person...
in our entire
graduating class.
Well, I guess that depends
on how you define "success."
If, to you, success means
having a house in Aspen...
one in Acapulco, a penthouse in
New York, a mansion in Malibu...
a 60-foot yacht,
an eight-seat Windstar...
a Bell Jet Ranger, a Bentley,
a personal trainer, a full-time chef...
a live-in masseuse
and a staff of 24...
then, yeah...
I guess I am successful.
But no matter
how much I accumulate...
there's still one thing
I just don't have.
Your own country?
I don't have you,
Michele.
Will you dance with me?
Only if Romy
can dance with us.
Sure.
Lying in my bed
I hear the clock tick
and think of you
Caught up in circles
Confusion is nothing new
Flashback
Warm nights
Almost left behind
Suitcase of memories
Time after
Sometimes you picture me
I'm walkin'
too far ahead
You're callin' to me
I can't hear
what you've said
Then you say "Go slow"
I fall behind
The second hand unwinds
If you're lost, you can look
and you will find me
Time after time
If you fall, I will catch you
I'll be waiting
Time after time
If you're lost, you can look
and you will find me
Time after time
If you fall
I will catch you
- I'll be waiting
- I will be waiting
Time after time
See, I told you
it would pay off...
to go to those clubs
every night.
Come on.
Oh, Jesus,
Mary and Joseph.
What do you want?
You were right. I was
a brain-dead, redneck asshole.
Although I never screwed
a sheep or my sister.
Why not?
Couldn't catch 'em?
I guess I deserve that.
I was a jerk.
But I was so miserable
in high school...
I don't think I spoke more than
two words the entire time.
I just couldn't
breathe there, you know?
Plus, I had this
really bad stutter.
Listen, you, uh,
wanna go somewhere quiet?
Somewhere
where we can talk?
- You-You wanna talk to me?
- Yeah.
Okay, cowboy, I don't know
what your trip is...
- but if this is some kind
of a sick game--
- What? No.
If you fuck with me
in any way, I will rip...
each and every appendage from your body,
starting with your dick, capisce?
Look, I j-just
w-wanted to talk.
Okay.
What the hell.
What is your name?
- Clarence.
- I like your hat, Clarence.
- Thank you.
- Pick up the pace.
You wait here.
I'll prep my chopper.
- Okay.
- All right.
Oh, my God, somebody's
puking in the bushes.
Eeewww!
Hey, how you guys doin'?
Billy?
- Chubbo?
- The name is Romy.
Romy and Michele.
So, weren't you guys, like,
totally in love with me in high school?
She was.
You wanna get a room?
But you're married.
- To Christie.
- Yeah, but you've got children...
and you're a successful
real estate developer.
I do drywall for her old man's
construction company.
And-And you know this new kid?
Don't even know if he's mine.
So--
How about that room?
Okay.
Why don't you go
and get that room?
Go and wash your face
and take off all your clothes...
and I'll be up there
in five minutes.
All right!
Your fantasy
is gonna come true...
tonight.
- See you later.
- Ugh-- Okay.
- God.
- Now he's gonna see what
it feels like to wait.
- That's such a good one.
- Ladies.
- God, can you believe we're
going home in a helicopter?
- I know. It's so cool.
I just wish everybody inside the reunion
would come out and see us lift off.
Ohh!
Thank you.
Oh.
Oh, my God! I'm so glad you didn't
bring your big notebook with you.
Michele.
Ooh, baby, do you know
what that's worth
Ooh, heaven is
a place on earth
They say in heaven
love comes first
We'll make heaven
a place on earth
Ooh, heaven is
Billy. Billy!
Billy, where are you?
Billy. Damn it.
Damn it!
Oh, my God.
Is that Heather?
Go for it, Heather!
Ooh, baby, do you know
what that's worth
Ooh, heaven is
a place on earth
They say in heaven
love comes first
Thanks for stopping by.
Yeah. Enjoy your fashions.
Have a Romy and Michele day.
- That was a good one.
- Thanks.
I cannot believe
how busy we've been.
I know. Hey, maybe we can
pay back Sandy this week.
Um, I think we're about, like,
two years away from that.
Oh. Okay.
Heather, um, has anyone ever told you
that smoking can kill you?
No. No one. Thank you.
Okay, but if you burn it,
you bought it.
Like I give a shit.
I look like an asshole.
What? Nuh-uh.
You look totally cute.
This dress exacerbates the genetic
betrayal that is my legacy.
Okay, I don't even know what you're
talking about because of those words...
but come here.
- Ow!
- God, that has been bugging me.
- Stay away from my bikini area.
- Um, okay.
- I'm in a rush. Ring it up if you must.
- Okay.
Let me have the tag, please.
Thank you.
You really do look cute.
- You know what?
- Huh?
Despite that surly demeanour, I think
we've just given her a big gift.
Okay, I mean,
to give someone...
Iike Heather Mooney the chance
to express herself through fashion--
We could've really
changed her life.
Yeah. For me though,
it's like...
I've given birth to
my own baby girl, you know?
Only she's, like,
a big giant girl...
who smokes
and says "shit" a lot.
- You know?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Let's fold scarves!
- Okay.
- You know what, Michele?
- Huh?
I think you are, like,
the funnest person I know.
Me too.
With you.
See the people
walkin' down the street
Fall in line
Just watchin' all the feet
They don't know
where everyone can go
But they're walkin'
in time
They got the beat
Yeah, they got the beat
All the kids
just gettin' out of school
They can't wait
to hang out and be cool
Hang around
till quarter after twelve
That's when
they fall in line
They got the beat
Kids got the beat
Yeah, kids got the beat
Go Go music
really makes us dance
In the crowd
it puts us in a trance
We want to
So just give us a chance
That's when
we fall in line
'Cause we got the beat
We got the beat
Yeah, we got it
- We got the beat
- Everybody get out your feet
- We know you can dance to the beat
- We got the beat
- Jump back, kick 'round
- 'Round and 'round and 'round
- Whoo!
- We got the beat
- We got the beat, We got the beat