Help me get her
in the car, ray!
Okay, but this bitch
heavy as hell, cuz!
Let me finger
gangbang her at least, homie!
Just help me
get her to the hospital!
- Okay, one finger then!
- Ray!
All right, but we
ain't goin' inside, homie.
We gonna go around
the emergency loop,
roll her ass out like
we do all the homies
that get shot
in the hood, homie.
Why you snuff her fine ass
anyway, homie?
I wanted to bone, cuz.
She was possessed, ray!
Possessed?
Possessed like head
spinnin' around
vomitin' everywhere, possessed?
Or like possessed like kanye
when you take a picture of him?
Just drive like
you got warrants, please!
Nigga, I do got warrants!
Look! These right here!
Jaywalkin'!
For eating grapes
in the grocery store
without payin' for 'em!
Shavin' my dog's
balls in public.
Drivin' with my hands
off the wheel, cuz.
I be ghost-ridin'
my whip, cuz.
An altercation with
my moms, homie, but
she provoked me, cuz!
Ray-ray,
I think she's waking.
All right, here! Take this
and pistol-whip her
with the butt of the gun.
I'm not pistol-whippin'
my girlfriend!
All right, nigga, well,
you drive and I'll
pistol-whip that bitch!
Kisha, resist!
But you didn't!
I've seen you for the bitch
that you are, Malcolm.
What's she talkin' about,
homie?
Booty pirates!
Nothing,
she's possessed, man.
That's right, you fucker!
He's a ghostbuster!
That sound real suspect
back there, homie.
Was you in juvie, cuz?
If you don't cry,
you ain't no bitch
in there, homie.
I didn't cry.
Doodles on they dick.
Joke's on them, cuz.
By the powers vested to me,
that somebody gave me
while I was locked up...
Who are you?
It's father Williams, homie.
She do a mean impression
of that nigga, cuz.
I do a mean impression
of  the Butler. Check it.
"I'm here for the boss.
I'm here to serve the boss."
Who are you?
I'm forest Whitaker, homie.
From the movie
that's like  the help,
but he didn't doo-doo
in the pie, homie.
Ray, I'm not talkin' to you!
I'm talkin' to Kisha.
Are you gonna let that bitch
choke you out, cuz?
You a bitch, homie...
Get the fuck off me!
Kisha! Kisha!
Oh, shit, she breathed
in my face, homie.
I'll get the bird flu,
it's contagious...
She blacked out, ray.
Get us to the hospital.
Hurry!
Ray? Ray?
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God!
Kisha? Kisha!
Ray?
Ray!
It's a good thing I drank
that hennessy earlier.
I can't feel shit, homie!
I think Kisha's dead.
Good! Let's get the fuck
outta here, homie!
Listen.
We were never here.
I'm with you, cuz.
All right. Deuces!
We ghost hunters!
I don't know
about this place, baby.
You've said that about
every house we looked at.
There's just something creepy
about this place, like...
Give me the heebie-jeebies...
Like somethin' bad
happened in here.
Well, I love it.
And I love you.
There you go,
bribin' me with vagina.
Whatever works.
Know when I'm weak.
Disgusting.
Oh, it's disgusting
when we do it,
but when you kissing
the whole entire
sophomore class,
it's cool, huh?
Give me that damn camera,
you little gnat!
Oh, finger.
Real creative. Wow.
Cut her some slack.
She's just goin'
through a phase.
Yeah, a phase.
It's called "whore."
Look at that.
Last a lifetime.
Malcolm, stop!
No, see,
that's a phase.
Looks like
he met an imaginary friend.
It's normal.
What you doin' there, buddy?
Want to help me load some boxes?
Cool!
All right. My man!
Sorry, Malcolm. I can't.
Why not?
Tony says, "aw, hell no!
I ain't yo' slave!"
Is it me or does his
imaginary friend sound black?
Pretty progressive.
Why don't you
and your friend go play?
Okay.
That game sounds like fun!
Oh!
I don't like
the tripping game, Tony.
Look at all that sexy.
Come here. Give me a kiss.
Let's piss off your forefathers.
Malcolm, it's 2013.
Interracial relationships
are not a big deal anymore.
Yeah, you tell that
to the sistas.
You know, they be like,
"I know he didn't!"
"He did not kiss that
pasty ass white bitch!"
Pasty?
"Yes! Not with them
old thin ass lips.
"Look at them,
look like baloney slices!"
"Uh-uh.
See he straight scrippin'
"and it don't make
no damn sense."
Come here, shiloh junior.
There's my baby boy.
I still can't believe
you named our dog shiloh junior.
Well, I was gonna
name him shiloh two
or shiloh the sequel,
but he wouldn't
answer to those, so,
shiloh junior it is.
C'mon! Hey, come on,
shiloh junior.
Hey, babe, are you gettin' this?
Your obsession
with all these cameras.
Hey, you can never have
too many cameras, okay?
Hey, shiloh! Come on, baby.
You ready to go see
your new house, shiloh junior?
Come on, shiloh junior.
Shiloh junior!
Hey, get inside.
Don't make me put bass
in my voice.
Hey! Shiloh!
God, I don't know
what's wrong with him.
Oh, fucking...
Oh, shit!
Oh, breathe!
Come on, shiloh!
Don't go towards the light!
Call 9-1-1.
Tell 'em the dog is white!
Oh, God. I got a pulse.
Breathe! Shiloh, like this.
Fuck! Oh, my back!
Oh, my fuckin' back!
Please, help me!
My fuckin' dog is a pancake!
Get me a goddamn pump!
It's working! Come on!
Meet me at the hospital!
The hospital's that way!
So young, never had
a chance to lick his balls.
I'm okay. I'm fine. I'm good.
You know, I'm just so happy
I got to spend time with...
It's just every time I try
and say the name...
Shiloh!
Oh, God, it hurts!
Oh, God!
It's tingly in...
I'm goin' with you! Oh, God!
It's time to go bye-bye.
Shiloh!
Junior.
I bet you could put
a whole lot of
birth control in that.
I really hate you.
That's what your daddy said.
That's why the nigga gone.
What've you got there?
Just an old box
that I found in the basement.
Don't you think
we should return it
to the prior owners?
If they wanted it,
they would've taken it
in the first place.
Ooh.
Okay, look, Becky,
I'm not your dad.
I'm just the guy
that's like... your mom.
So I'll make you a deal.
I'll let you keep the box
if you promise to try
and make this work
between me and you, okay?
It's for your mom.
Fine.
I think we're gettin' somewhere.
I'm just messin' with you, bro.
Oh, shit!
I just do that when
I'm talkin' to  negritos.
It's all good.
Did he just call me a nigger?
What's goin' on, bro?
I just moved in with
my girl right here
and we was
just wonderin'
Hi.
Are you serious?
Dude, I live here,  puto!
It's my house!
- Oh, shit! I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God.
I just assumed...
You got the gloves
and the hat,
and the lawnmower and the truck.
Oh, 'cause I'm Mexican
I must be Jose!
Are you?
No, fool!
My name is Miguel!
Is that your truck?
- Yeah, that's my truck!
- Then who's Jose?
That's my middle name.
You wanna guess my last name?
No, no, no.
Oh, come on.
You guys are here,
you might as well.
I don't know. Rodriguez?
That's racist, bro.
You asked...
Did he ask me or what?
I'm just fuckin' with you!
For the record, my name is
Miguel Jose Jesus Gonzalez...
Smith.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- What?
Your last name is Smith?
Yeah, I'm Mexican
on my mom's side.
So, why is there
Gonzalez on your truck?
Shit, would you trust
your garden to
a guy named Smith?
Hey, my name is Malcolm, bro.
Yeah.
I bet your last name is Johnson.
See, that's some racist shit!
Am I right?
But you're right!
Nice to meet you, man.
Yeah, it's a pleasure
meeting you!
Nice to meet you.
Tuesdays. I can cut
your grass on Tuesdays.
What can I say,
I'm a gardener
by ethnic default.
Watch out,  guera!
Hey. What?
You gon' try
and tease a brother?
That's an invite?
One, two,  I'm done.
What's that?
What?
Oh! That's Abigail.
Ew.
I found her in the wardrobe
that was left here.
Yeah, well, put it back.
Hey, stop! She's creepy!
We look alike.
Yeah, same eyes and pigtails.
Wait, no, no,
don't put it on the bed!
Hey.
How you doin'?
You ain't gonna
say nothin', huh?
Girl, you stupid.
You don't want none of this?
Come here.
Oh, I can't play with it
but you can.
You gonna bite my lip?
Take that!
You fuckin' like this!
Uh-huh. It was gonna come.
It was gonna come!
Just wanna put the tip in.
I'm gonna put the tip in...
Ah! Ahh! Ahh!
Look at that.
Mmm. Uh-huh.
Mmm, yeah.
You got that goody.
Bite the pillow,
bite that fuckin' pillow.
You gonna eat
my butt now. Oh, shit!
Nigga, she...
She lickin' that.
You taste like doo-doo.
But I love it!
You on the pill?
I don't want to
get you pregnant.
You wanna make
little doll babies?
They gonna have my eyes
with your eyes...
Oh, you gonna give me splinters!
Fuck this shit.
I wanna cry! It feels so...
Don't look. Don't look.
Hold on a second.
This side is wet with soap,
this one is dry.
I mighta leaked in you.
I don't know if I came,
I leaked a little bit.
That's all right.
You ain't even ovulatin'.
Why you trippin'?
Come on, stop worrying.
Honey, we're home!
Oh, shit! You gotta go!
- Shit! No!
- Malcolm!
Hi, honey! Um...
Hey, where are you?
You gotta go!
We... I'm just upstairs!
You gotta get outta here.
Fuck!
Ah! Shit!
Mmm.
"Hanging out."
Sounds a little soft
for my taste, but... fuck it.
Yeah, I don't think
this is right.
Maybe I should
download the manual.
What the...
Great. Get up here.
Can't breathe.
Cut the camera.
Turn the camera off.
Wow.
I seen some shit,
but that was...
That was crazy!
A demonic figure tried to
hang a family in the backyard.
I gotta keep this from
Megan and the kids.
Is it weird that
I was aroused by this?
Why is my dick
bending in my jeans?
Hello? Hello?
Twinkle, twinkle little star
who is this? Hello!
It's a nigger.
Oh,
that's a ugly motherfucker.
Is that Steven Tyler?
What the hell? Same tree!
Shit! Kisha?
Megan, what you doing?
I almost dumped
the fuck out you!
You got to holler at me!
You can't just be walkin' up.
You gotta give me
like a "whoop-ti-whoo,"
a "kakow!" Or a "tsh-tsh"!
Just make your own up.
Please announce yourself!
Honey, you look like
you've seen a ghost.
I think I did.
Wait. So now
I look like a ghost.
Excuse me,
where you goin' with this?
So now I'm too pasty for you?
Malcolm, I can't do
anything about that!
What do you mean?
Unless you want me
to get skin cancer
from the sun.
And deep nasty wrinkles,
and then they'll have to
give me chemo
and I'll lose all my hair,
and then I'll look like
a nasty bald raisin!
Is that what you want?
No! I don't want you
to look like a raisin!
I don't like the raisin!
I don't like to date raisins!
I don't like the raisins
on Morgan Freeman's face!
I just don't like raisins.
I don't like the new ones
that Obama got,
the young raisins on his face!
I don't like raisins.
So please,
don't look like a raisin.
I need to go meditate and
get my chi back in alignment.
What chi? You were just...
Ah! Ahh!
Walk to the light!
It's bedtime.
What you all dressed up for?
We goin' to a club?
Mmm-mmm.
Foam party?
No.
We goin' to a pajama
jammy jam?
Just bed.
You gotta be more
comfortable
with this relationship...
You're right.
Put on some sweat pants
and some...
Oh, my Jesus lord!
Um, you're naked!
I am.
Oh, wow.
I like being naked, though.
I could be naked all day.
All day? But come on,
that's not practical, hon.
You don't wanna be
on the bus naked
or in Starbucks naked.
Why not?
'Cause that coffee
spill on you, it's hot!
It's gonna leave a scar.
Melt one of your
nipples off or somethin'.
Hey, hey, hey.
The camera's on, baby.
Good. Just make sure
you film my good side.
What the fuck?
Are you serious?
We gonna get all angles
on that... oh, shit.
Baby, your creepy doll
is makin' my dick scared.
Just let her watch.
You just said
the right type
of nasty shit!
Oh, God!
I gotta replenish my fluids.
After round two.
Whoo! Ah! Whoo!
- That was wild.
- Come on, Malcolm.
What,
aren't you done yet?
I am now.
Ready for round three?
Seriously...
Baby, you gotta train
for some shit like this!
Come on, Malcolm,
bell's ringing.
Time for round four.
No, no, baby.
My ding-ding is
knocked out cold.
I can't do it.
Corner's throwin' in the towel!
Let's go, Malcolm.
I gotta get some enswell
if we keep goin'!
Malcolm.
Wait, no, baby!
Right now she is tearin' me up!
Oh, my God!
Aw!
Want me to choke you?
Is that what you like?
Huh? Huh?
Stop being a bitch!
Yeah! Come on!
Oh! You want some of this?
You like that?
It's kind of like a blindfold
except you can't
fuckin' breathe! Huh?
Are you crying?
That thing just moved!
Except you can't
fuckin' breathe!
Thing was watching!
You little...
Who was watching?
Oh, baby, come here.
Check this out!
Oh, my God!
Did you see it?
How could I not?
I thought I was trippin'!
I am so fat!
Look at me!
I look like a huge blubber ass!
I'm like miss piggy in there!
What're you talking about?
You said you were gonna
shoot my good side.
I did shoot your good side.
Look, I got all that
ass up in...
Look at all that ass, girl.
I'm black, brothers like an ass.
You know I do mean that
as a compliment, right?
You hate my vagina!
You think it's too loose!
It's not!
It's only on the outside,
but once you choose a wall,
it's pretty damn tight.
You know what, Malcolm,
I have had two kids!
I mean, do you think
the stork just dropped 'em off
on the doorstep?
No!
You're knocked up
for nine months
and then your lady parts
are stretched to limits
you cannot even fathom!
Okay, baby.
I think your vagina's cute.
Erase the tape
or we are never
having sex again.
Well, since
you put it that way.
Erase the tape!
Okay, I'm erasin' the tape!
I want to see you do it.
I'm erasing the tape.
I'm erasing it.
Erase it right now! Do it!
It's erasing. Baby,
I like the way it sounds.
Erase the tape!
It's not loose!
I like the way it sounds!
Sound like a blown speaker.
Just...
You know, it's kinda like
Doug e. Fresh's beatbox.
When I'm hittin' it.
It's just...
Mmm...
Who the hell's hittin' me?
Abigail?
You got a page?
"In a relationship
with Malcolm Johnson"?
I only hit it once!
27,000 views?
What in the hell?
I think I might've
fucked the wrong bitch.
Now she's blowin' up
my cell phone? Look at that.
Straight up stalker!
She's crazy!
Listen, it's time to turn
my camera game up a level.
I'm talkin' bathrooms,
countertops, computers,
stuffed animals,
mouths and asses!
It's goin' down everywhere!
I'm gonna live.
Kitchen? Oh, yeah, I see you.
Uh-huh. Perfect.
Yeah, and I got the ass, too.
All inconspicuous.
Told you, cameras everywhere.
Hey, Becky,
wanna play hide and clap?
Fuck off!
That's, "no, thank you."
Let's do this.
Oh, lady's blindfold.
You got this out
your momma's room, right?
Oh, boy. Things me
and your momma do with this!
Sometimes she ties my hands
and flip me over
and toss that... salad.
Tony likes salad.
Anyway.
I'll put this on.
Let's do it!
One, two, three.
First clap!
Come on. Give me a clap.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm gettin' close.
I smell you. I smell you.
You smell like kids,
like worms, coins
and doo-doo. Like...
Shit!
Can we just play tag
next time?
I just wanna play tag.
Wyatt? Wyatt?
Where you at, you little shit?
Third clap.
A-ha!
I got you, Wyatt.
I win!
You took your blindfold off.
You're right, Tony.
Malcolm is an idiot.
Take your camera, loser.
Yeah, I wanna learn
how to start a fire.
What the hell was that?
I coulda swore...
Shit!
Fucked you up!
Fuck, are you crazy?
You know who the fuck I is?
Malcolm!
Baby?
Oh, my God!
You can't be jumpin' out
on brothers like that.
You'll get knocked
the fuck out every time.
It was supposed to be a joke!
You okay?
'Cause I fucked you up!
Like, I hit you with
the force,
like with the follow-through.
I wanna instant replay
that shit. Damn!
'Cause you got froze.
You went...
"Please help me."
God, I hope this works.
What is that thing?
That is not human.
That was weird.
A-ha!
I caught your ass!
No, you didn't.
Oh, shit!
Becky...
It's your box.
What?
I want you to touch me.
Mmm.
Okay.
Not that box.
You know I love you
and those kids, right?
Yeah.
And I'm gonna do
everything in my power to
keep you guys protected.
Yeah.
What was that?
What?
That!
The wind?
Nigga, the windows
are closed! Okay?
I'm tellin' you,
that was either
a ghost or a demon.
Or maybe it was a demon
pregnant with a ghost.
Oh, this is cute!
I will so wear this,
all day, every day.
Why the fuck
are you excited?
It's a burglar!
Either way it goes,
it's some scary shit!
Okay,
not all burglars are scary.
It is a burglar or a ghost!
If you talk to him,
he'll leave.
You shoot it in the face!
If you talk to him,
he'll leave.
And if the motherfucker's
foot do this, you shoot him
in the face again!
That is way too harsh.
What're you gonna do?
I know what I'm gonna do.
You are not allowed
to shoot anyone
in the face, mister!
Becky?
What in the...
Becky! Oh, God!
Becky! Becky!
Megan!
Oh, my God!
Get me somethin',
Megan! Becky!
That shit's gross.
That fuckin' sound,
it bothers me.
Gimme!
Oh!
That's all I got!
Okay, gimme!
Get that thing outta here!
I got an idea!
Come on! Bitch,
why ain't you movin'? Fuck!
See, now this is a good idea.
All right.
Goodnight, Becky.
Night, sweetheart.
Hey, buddy,
what you doin'?
Havin' a tea party.
Oh.
You wanna go outside
and do somethin'
a little bit more masculine?
Like play some football?
No, not really.
Hey, don't sit there!
That's Tony's seat!
Oh, sorry.
My bad, Tony.
Tony says, "no problem,
bee-yotch." Want some tea?
Uh... yeah. Sure.
Um, you know, Wyatt,
about your little buddy, Tony.
I don't think he's
such a good influence
on you, know what I mean?
What the...
That's straight vodka!
Tony calls it tea.
He drinks a lot of tea.
I really think you guys
need to stop this friendship.
Tony doesn't think
that's such a good idea.
You know what, you tell Tony
that I said you and him
ain't gonna be friends
no more, and that's final!
On second thought,
you and Tony have
a beautiful friendship.
Okay, I'll be downstairs
doin' somethin' with
less spooky shit.
This isn't good.
It's happening again.
It's really fuckin' happening.
What the fuck?
Who is it?
Hello?
That's a spooky knock.
Oh, you better run!
Knock on my door,
come out there and slap you...
What the fuck!
I got a knife!
What the...
"Miss me?" Abigail!
Oh, hell no!
Look, we gotta talk.
This is a mistake, okay?
This shit gotta stop.
It's gone too far.
You see this? "Miss me?"
In the house with Megan,
are you fuckin' crazy?
I take full responsibility,
all right? This is my bad.
I don't mean to sound cliched.
It's not you, it's me.
Don't play fuckin'
innocent with me,
you knew I had a girl!
I'm just being
selfish right now.
I would love to have you
and Megan and...
To be honest with you,
my stuffed animals.
I'd like to bring them
in the mix.
I'm tryin' to make this work.
You're just not makin' it easy.
I swear to... ah! Fuck!
You see what you made me do?
Only you do this to me!
Fuckin' crazy! Oh, you lucky
my momma told me
don't hit bitches!
Fuckin' yeah, bitch.
True enough.
Fuck, you scare my...
I didn't touch you!
You get outta my life,
I'll get outta yours.
I'm done.
Make no mistake.
After this, it's over.
You ready to go again? Yeah.
Hello, Malcolm?
Hey, hey, Professor wilde,
how you doing?
Malcolm, I'm glad
you reached out.
What exactly
am I dealing with here?
Well, the being
you described to me
is a demon.
Fuck, I knew it!
A rare and obscure one
from babylonian times
named aghoul.
And he's a trickster!
And chances are this is
not your first encounter
with this demon.
Have you had paranormal
experiences in your past?
Actually, yeah.
About a year ago.
This is way worse
than I had thought...
Oh, shit!
Oh, fuck!
Ah!
Nigga, I thought somebody
was shootin'!
Thai food!
It's spicy going in,
but it's twice as spicy
going out!
That's scientifically
impossible!
I smell you in here!
What in the hell?
Ah, excuse me.
I hire based on skill level.
Are those titties?
We're making meth,
not baby aspirin.
All the stories revolve around
aghoul's attempts
to trick people into
bringing him into our world
and it can come through
the form of a possession,
a spirit that
only a child can see
or an ancient object that
lures in the impressionable.
So what you're saying is,
something is coming after me
and my family.
Malcolm, that's exactly
what I'm saying.
Damn it, Jessica,
you've got your tit
in the pseudoephedrine!
Sorry, Malcolm.
I wish you good luck.
Gotta get my  breaking bad on.
Tonight you drown.
Not again.
Sink. Sink. Sink.
Ruined a perfectly good
leather jacket!
That's it.
Now we drown. Drown!
Drown!
Prepare to meet hell.
Ow! God, that hurt!
My balls.
This isn't over!
Is aghoul the same demon
that possessed Kisha?
When are the Republicans
gonna slip
and call Obama the n-word?
When are they gonna
stop makin' scary movies
without the wayans?
They fuckin' suck!
What the hell?
What the heck...
Steroids, bitch!
You messed with
the wrong nigga today!
Oh, my God!
Baby, put it down!
What are you doing?
I come in the hallway,
this fuckin' creepy box
with some weird
fuckin' lighting on it!
And I knew that it was
death in the box!
So I killed it!
Baby, it was a gift!
But it ain't Christmas.
Baby, no.
Kwanzaa?
You were so upset
when shiloh junior died
that the kids and I thought
we would get you...
Don't look. Don't look.
Oh, my God! Wyatt,
go upstairs. Go to your room!
I killed a baby.
Oh, God,
I think it's still breathing.
You're so fucking crazy.
He's still breathing.
I gotta take him
out of his misery.
- I gotta kill him!
- Oh, my God!
No! Malcolm!
Becky?
Yoo-hoo.
All right, let's see
what's in this box now.
Yeah.
Oh, God! Whoo!
Wow! That is rancid.
What the hell are you doing?
Nothing. Just, uh...
You know your pillows
have blue faces on 'em?
Stay away from my box!
Calm down!
Would you calm down?
I don't wanna calm down,
I want you to stay away
from my box!
Do you have to
say "box" so loud?
What is going on in here?
Nothing.
We just, uh, playin'.
Dolls 'n stuff.
Malcolm came into my room
and touched my box.
Malcolm, is this true?
Yes, but I only touched it
for like two seconds.
It was stinking!
Like, it was rancid!
Here, smell this. I don't know
how she play with that!
He had two fingers
in my tight little box, mom.
- Stop lyin'.
- It is...
Baby, there's nothin'
tight about her box.
It's fuckin' huge!
I could put my
whole fist in it.
Like, I almost was
up to here for a second.
It's crazy big.
You said, "no means no!"
And that is exactly
what I said. I said, "no!"
Time the fuck out.
Hold up.
She's trying to
dateline special a nigga!
Where's Chris Hansen?
Chris! Chris!
Chris, come on, I know you
out here somewhere!
I know he's in here somewhere.
You tryin' to set a nigga up!
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Right now.
There's something really strange
Wyatt? Wyatt, see,
Wyatt used to be my boy.
Like that was my lil' nigga,
like we was like, boom, boom.
When my dog died,
that lil' nigga held me down!
But lately, he hasn't even
talked to me! Like,
he won't even play with me!
His little imaginary friend,
Tony?
I don't think he's really...
You're crazy, Tony.
...Imaginary.
Did you see that shit?
Look! You missed it!
Okay, look, forget him. Becky.
There's something in that
old box she carries around
that's making her go crazy!
She sleeps with it,
she eats with it,
she even goes
to the bathroom with it!
Who takes a shit
with a box in their hand?
It's fuckin' weird!
And by "weird" you mean
I'm a terrible mother.
What? No. Wait.
Where did you go?
Hold on. Hold on a minute.
If you were just
a little bit less judgmental,
she wouldn't feel like
she needs to carry her
pain around in a "box"!
This is not about me!
It is always about you,
Malcolm!
"You're too fat,
you're a terrible parent,
"you like black guys 'cause
they have bigger cocks!"
That sounds like you!
Do you see this?
That's not fuckin' normal!
Okay, she is just trying
to get attention!
When she was a baby,
she would cry and cry and cry
all damn day in her crib
until finally she realized
I wasn't gonna come
and pick her up!
If you were a parent
you'd know it's called the
"cry it out method," Malcolm!
Just pick the little bitch up!
She needs to learn
to self-soothe.
See what I'm saying?
That is called parenting.
Wow! Mother of the year.
Thank you.
That crazy doll keyed my car!
Whoo! Bro,
somebody fucked your car up!
Yeah. You wouldn't know
anybody with an auto body
shop, would you?
Why, contrary to popular
belief, all Mexicans
don't have body shops, man.
What, you think
we all have low riders
with a bunch
of primer all over it
with a frickin' Mexican horn?
You think I have like six kids
and all my relatives
livin' there, huh?
Probably chase chihuahuas
and make burritos,
is that what you think?
Dude...
Look at the neighborhood, man!
I didn't think any of that!
I just want my
fuckin' car fixed!
I'm just
fuckin' with you, bro!
You're so easy, man.
Oh, shit.
Man, I got a cousin,
his name is chucho,
he can hook all that shit up.
Stop fuckin' with
the crazy bitches, man.
I gotta go,
I got the family waiting.
All right? Be good, man!
Where did she go?
- Take it easy,  vato!
- Where you goin'?
Goin' to the swap meet.
We're gonna get
some chihuahuas.
Wow.
Now that's racist!
So I moved into
the house across the street
and I just love it.
The streets are so quiet.
It's perfect for a haunting.
You know something,
I never got your name.
Kisha? What in the fuck!
You two know each other?
Oh. Well, yeah.
You know the boyfriend
that I told you abandoned me
and left me in a ditch to die?
That's him.
Awkward!
Yeah!
I think I'll let you two
have at it.
And thank you so much, Megan,
for the coffee, really.
And, Malcolm,
it was great seeing you.
See you around, Malcolm.
Um...
Really?
How come you never
told me about her?
Well, it was just
a time in my life
I just wanted to forget.
Okay, well you need to
start remembering.
She was fucking beautiful!
She was aight.
"Aight"?
I mean, she got nice legs.
Legs.
Little ass, but...
Ass. How 'bout all this?
It's fuckable.
Okay? But that's the...
It's all this...
She's crazy!
She was crazy, baby,
like she was possessed!
You mean she was possessive.
No, the bitch was possessed.
What?
Yes!
First of all,
she was verbally abusive.
Eat your mother's pussy
you fucking fuck!
Okay.
I don't know.
It was like she gave up.
Eventually I was able to
drag her to couples' therapy.
Well, Dr. rousch,
me and my girlfriend,
we're kinda goin' through
a little rough patch.
I mean, she won't
communicate with me.
No matter what I do,
she just sits there.
Okay, and she'll growl
a little bit.
Yes, I can hear that.
And the smallest things
just set her off.
Like crucifixes, or questions.
Is that right, Kisha?
You got a prescription
for "crazy bitch"?
Malcolm, I'm so sorry.
It sounds horrible.
Well, it wasn't all bad.
Wait, I'm gonna come.
Shut up,
you sound like a bitch!
Oh!
I think you just
knocked out a tooth!
Whose ass is this, huh?
Whose ass is this?
The devil's!
See, now you just made it weird.
Look at me, God damn it!
Oh, my God, that was awesome!
Baby, you're makin'
my toes do this.
You're makin' my toes do this.
Really, Malcolm?
You know what they say
about the crazy ones.
What? Too soon?
There's something
goin' on with this box.
I'm gonna get
to the bottom of this.
What the heck
is this little pervert doing?
Ah!
Oh, dude, that is just weird!
Oh, really?
Oh, wow.
What kind of sweet
tooth fairy is this?
- This nigga need a daddy.
-  "Dear diary.
"I lost my virginity
to Joey today.
"Actually,
that's not totally true.
"I mean, I've only
had sex with 17 guys
"but only in the butt,
so it doesn't count.
"I mean, I've sucked
a lot of dicks, diary.
"I stopped counting
after the blowjob party
at Ashley's house.
"There must've been
30 or 40 guys there."
She ain't got no bone
in her neck.
She got that plastic man.
Diary, I'll never
stop sucking dicks. Ever!"
Wow.
Oh,
would you look there?
A mood ring.
So, what mood is that?
It's called,
"you're not my father."
Oh, yeah, that's bitchy
lil' white teenager.
See, that'll get you slapped
in most black neighborhoods.
Are you okay?
Becky? Hey.
Ouch!
Ugh.
That is some serious
meat-mouth you got
goin' on there.
It's easier going down
than it is coming up.
Yeah, it's weird.
Breath smell like sirloin.
I hope that hole cold
ain't contagious.
Professor,
it's kinda loud there. Um...
Did I catch you at a bad time?
Indica? I'm a sativa man.
I got important shit to do!
Hold on! I'm at a party.
I need some of my medicine.
Professor! How do I
get rid of the demon?
Professor! Professor!
Malcolm, that demon's
tryin' to get to you
through your family
and he's not gonna stop!
You've got the
paranormal equivalent of
a perfect storm, my friend!
Oh, shit! The po-po!
Professor, please!
What's goin' on?
I got 12 ounces of crystal meth
jammed up my anus.
I gotta get outta here!
Police!
Oh, fuck!
Professor! Professor, please!
Hands up now!
I can't go back in!
Professor! How do I
get rid of the demon?
Oh, fuck.
You're under arrest!
You on the screen, freeze!
Hey, knothead!
Oh, no, not my favorite shirt.
That bitch.
What the...
Oh, my God!
Are you fucking kidding me?
No, no, no!
Not my clothes! No!
Phew.
Oh! Shit!
This crazy wooden bitch!
She's burning my clothes!
Oh, my God!
It's  fatal attraction.
She's gonna boil a rabbit!
Can I get you
something to drink?
Sure, man.
Tequila?
Really, bro?
What, you bring
the Mexican into your house
and, "he must want Tequila,
we should give him Tequila.
"I'm glad he parked his  burro
so now I can offer him
some of his beverage."
I should've walked in here
with a serape and a sombrero
for you, too, huh?
That's what you wanted
really, wasn't it?
You get me all worked up, man!
Look, I could use a drink now.
What kind of Tequila is it?
Is it silver?
'Cause I can't drink that
gold shit. That's for  cholos.
Thank you, man.
It's nice, man.
We're becomin' friends, right?
Uh, now we are.
I could trust you
with things, right?
I'm good at that shit.
The neighbors next door to me
don't even know there's
a black guy living here yet.
So, what do you
wanna talk about?
Um...
Okay, you know the people
that lived in this house
before me?
Mmm-hmm.
Was there anything strange
goin' on, like were they
actin' weird or anything?
You saw something a little...
Spooky or supernatural?
I seen some shit.
Come on, man,
you don't believe in that,
do you?
'Cause if you did, you know,
you'd have been like,
"nigger, I'm out!
The deuces."
You mean to tell me
you don't believe
in the paranormal?
Of course I believe
in that shit!
I'm half Mexican, bro!
I believe in all that shit
people don't believe in.
Freakin'  LA llorona,
El cucuy, chupacabra,
bigfoot, obamacare.
Interracial dating.
Nuclear war.
You name it, I'm all for it.
Me personally, I wouldn't
stay one night in this house.
Shit!
Look, I'm gonna be
honest with you, bro.
When I first found out that
there was a black guy
movin' in the neighborhood,
I was like,
"There goes the property value.
"I'm gonna have to
keep the kids inside,
there's gonna be gangs,
"I'm gonna have to
cover up graffiti,"
but you turned out to be okay.
You're really cool!
You're very accommodating.
I think I can help you.
Really?
I need you to
cut the chicken's neck.
Oh, hell fuckin' no!
You wanna get rid
of the demon or not?
I know, but can't we just
go down to the store
and just like, buy a chicken?
No, man!
You need a blood sacrifice.
Right. Come here.
Let's do it.
Hold on!
Hold up, wait a second!
Let me get my shit together.
You gonna shit in
my baby's cereal,
chicken?
You wanna piss on my momma?
In her face?
I'll fuck...
Don't you...
Where did you get
this chicken?
Your Uncle's farm?
No! A cock fighting ring.
That's a dead motherfucker.
Whassup, chicken?
You scared? Whassup?
You don't want none of this,
motherfucker!
Oh, shit!
- Bite him back, Malcolm!
- Bite him back!
Drown, bitch!
I'm gonna kill you.
Watch what I do
to your fuckin' baby!
What you doin', man?
What'd you do?
This  pollo is  loco!
You got him,
Malcolm! That's right!
Yeah, you fucked
that chicken.
Malcolm...
Yeah!
You about to go to
that great bucket in the sky!
Tell the colonel I said hi!
That was like an intense-ass
game of  angry birds, man!
Fuck, bro, you did it!
I think this house is clean!
Well, maybe not clean,
but the demon's gone for sure.
What the hell are we gonna do
with all this chicken,
Malcolm?
Oh, yeah, ask the black guy.
Mmm-hmm.
Mmm. Hey.
Cheers.
Right on!
What in the fuck?
You! This ends now!
You hear me, you googly-eyed
wooden bitch! Come on!
You're making me
bury your fuckin' ass!
Get in there!
Die, you stink bitch!
B-I-t...
Fuckin' bitch!
You want some of this?
All right,
prepare to meet your maker!
That's right, I'm sending
you back to Taiwan!
You smell like piss and shit!
Come on! You make me sick!
You know what brown
can do for me? Take this!
You sign!
Get the fuck outta here!
Oh, see, I tried to do it
the easy way.
Now you're gonna
make me violent.
Come on, you...
Get the fuck over here!
Shut up!
How you like that, bitch?
I want you to watch.
Let's see you write it now!
Miss me? This is fun.
Oh, we about to have
a barbecue.
Get in there.
Yeah! Hey, how you doin'?
You gonna fuckin'
burn today, baby!
That's what fucking
hell feels like!
You fuckin'... fucking die!
I will watch your life
come out of you.
Just die, you little...
I'll fuckin' cut your
goddamn eye out, you bitch!
Malcolm!
What did you do to our room?
Say fucking nothing.
Honey, it's not
what it looks like, okay?
Really?
It's not what it looks like.
Listen, listen to me.
She's crazy!
It's not me, she's crazy!
You're crazy.
No, honey! Megan!
It's not what it looks like!
Get away from me.
I'm not done with you,
you fuckin' home-wrecker!
God!
See, nobody will
listen to the black guy
till everybody dead!
I see how you lookin' at me.
Let me tell you something.
This house...
This house is haunted.
You know that little doll
that you like so much?
Abigail?
Yeah, well, let me tell you
something about Abigail.
She's alive!
That's right, she's alive!
Not like "alive" alive,
but alive as in
"is possessed."
You know how I know?
'Cause it made me have
sex with it! Repeatedly!
Upstairs, downstairs,
in the kitchen, in the yard!
While you were sleepin'
next to us!
Right there
where you're sitting, twice!
And that's why,
when you came upstairs
and you caught me
and I was killing the doll,
because I was just like,
"you're fuckin' up
my relationship!"
And that box? It's cursed!
That box and that box.
That's haunted with a demon.
That box, cursed with dudes.
But that's a whole
other story.
And your son, his little
imaginary friend that
teaches him curse words
and gets him crunk off vodka!
Yeah, yeah,
I'm blowing your spot,
little man.
Well, he's not so imaginary!
He's cray!
No, no, no.
You cray! You cray-cray!
You and your whole lot
of other ethnic words
that's going out of style.
You ain't funky fresh or dope.
So, how about that, cray-cray?
Mom, he's scaring me.
Is this the nigga
whose room exploded?
I'm scaring you!
Opie, you something else!
You know what, that's it.
I've had enough of this whole
haunted house craziness!
It's bad enough
that you think it's real,
but now you're scaring the kids!
I'm scaring the kids!
Yes!
Ain't that the pot
callin' the kettle a nigga!
No, no, no, baby!
Your kids are scaring me!
Okay?
Look at this one!
She's Marilyn manson
in the skin
and Charlie manson
in the eyes!
Her eyes look crazy, okay?
That's a crazy woman
carrying around a box
like fuckin' Lionel
from the  peanuts,
and he's hangin' out
with dead niggas
and I'm crazy?
Oh! So, what am I supposed
to do with all this?
Maybe you weren't ready!
Maybe we moved in too soon.
Maybe you're not
ready for a family!
But we come as
a package deal, okay?
This ain't about you
or them, okay? You...
Oh, shit. No! Hey!
Don't touch that shit!
Don't touch it!
That's a demon ring.
Don't you answer that, you hear?
That's the devil
callin' right there.
That is an evil ring!
You hear that?
Yeah, I said it, a demon ring!
And you can insta-tweet
that on your gram-o-vine!
Nobody touch it!
Stop ringing!
Stop ringing! Stop!
Oh, that's a demon callin'.
Uh, Malcolm?
Your pocket.
Huh. Oh.
We gotta change my ringer.
Why do we even have
home phones anymore?
I mean...
Yeah? Who is it?
What the hell?
Hey, how you doin', officer?
Come on in.
We got a call about
a domestic dispute.
Are you Malcolm Johnson?
Uh, yeah, that's me,
but there's no dispute.
I mean, I threw the phone,
but...
You're under arrest.
Hey! For what?
Oh, my God!
Just raised my voice
a little bit!
Malcolm, our phone is broken.
I know what...
It's the doll! It's the doll!
It was the doll, brother,
listen!
This is all a misunderstanding.
It was this doll. I was
fuckin' this doll, right?
He's on pcp.
Let's take him.
No, I'm not on pcp!
You fuckin' bitch!
Malcolm, maybe
this is for the best.
Can't escape my wrath,
for I am death.
Now you burn. Fire.
Help!
What is...
Malcolm?
Mmm...
Damn, son, you look fucked up!
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me!
Mom, your man's in here pukin'
like a little bitch!
See that shit, Tony?
Sometimes the victim
may be tormented
by more than one demon.
These cases lead
to transference.
Trans-who?
What the fuck is that, dog?
Father Williams!
Mind your tongue.
You are a man of the cloth!
Damn, man,
ain't like I'm rapin'
motherfuckers no more,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Shit. Keep on wit' your
little lesson, brother.
Victims have also
been known to break
their own bones
during the possession.
True.
That happened to me.
I was first in prison,
I was tryin' to
give myself head, right?
'Cause I ain't know nobody.
If I woulda knew somebody,
I wouldn't have had
to do it to myself.
And it wasn't no gay shit.
First get that out your head.
That's enough!
I've had enough
of your insolence!
My what?
My insolence?
Dog, you going to bring up
my condition right now?
You gonna bring up
my diabetes, dog?
Talkin' about my insolence.
'Cause I like cake?
Yeah, I like cake, guys.
I like cake, birthday cake,
all kinds of cake.
I'm talking about,
cake, cake, cake!
Man, you know what?
I'm sick of your shit!
Get outta here!
Everybody break out.
Take your boy with you.
Yeah. I mean really, man.
Ooh.
Malcolm?
Hey, father Williams!
Fuck, nigga, what'd I tell you
about callin' me that?
I'm sorry. Hey, Doug!
Roll down, man!
I'm sorry you
caught that, man.
I'm so stressed out, man.
I had to shank a muthafucka.
You saw that, right?
I didn't see nothin'.
That's a good answer.
If you saw it...
'Cause I was gonna say
if you woulda said yes,
I woulda...
Oh, shit!
That's all right,
I don't have nothin'.
That's the only one I had.
I used to have two shanks,
but I don't keep
that anymore.
I stopped doin' two shanks
'cause it just was a thang, and
everybody was like,
"two shanks."
Yeah, so, how you doin'?
I, uh... I need your help.
It's happenin', Doug.
Hell no!
You know I'm not
comin' over there
and fuckin' with you and your
creepy lil' bitch again!
I ain't even with
that bitch no more!
I'm beggin' you, man,
I just need your help.
I just don't know
who else to go to.
Let me just explain to you
why I became a priest.
Now, obvious one is
for the little boys. Yes.
What're you talkin' about?
It's a joke, Malcolm!
Oh, God, no, it was a joke.
I did that, you know,
for the other priests
and we laugh, that's all.
But I don't know if
I can help you with
your demon situation
because I haven't
been stayin' steady
on my demon fightin' skills,
is what I'm
tryin' to tell you.
So Malcolm, day after day,
when you know you can't win,
you're just
prolonging the inevitable!
All you gotta do is let them in.
Are you talkin' about the devil?
Worse. The Kardashians.
Yeah.
Yeah, did you see 'em?
It's the crazy mama,
it's Kim, khloe, kourtney,
crazy, the two little ones...
They gonna be freaks.
They got lamar,
they got Scott...
Rob, fat as a motherfucker,
Bruce with the acne.
Oh, Bruce...
What the fuck is wrong
with Bruce jenner face?
He look like a monster!
He scares me at night!
And he on in daytime.
He don't look like
the nigga that was on
the wheaties box!
And kanye! And kanye!
And julianne hough!
I love it and I hate it.
They took kanye
and they changed him.
Doug, you know... Doug...
You have to let go of me, Doug.
You can't...
Doug, you gotta let go of me!
There's no place you can hide.
He has a plan for you.
Doug, get off of me.
He will get you!
Doug, get your hands off me!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Oh, you're the one
that got us out here
in the hot heat!
Making me bang all
on the windows with my
good church hat!
Hon, I could be at
home watchin' that new
madea movie!
With the little girl
from  the fresh prince?
You know the one, she played
the head of NASA!
With the aliens!
Boom!
Madea goes to Mars, that's it!
Hold up,
ain't you that brother
that just moved
into old Burton place?
Yeah, it's just...
With a white woman!
Well, she's not
all the way white.
She's a white woman,
damn near clear!
Come on now, it's 2013.
Interracial relationships
is not a big deal.
What? You need to
tell that to the lonely sista.
Look at this one right here.
Right here!
Honey, show him how you
drop it like it's hot!
Whoo! Hold up, Bertha,
hold up. Hold up.
We ain't got no defibrillator.
They do that cungalingus,
the finga-ligga-linga.
- What is it, the fellatio?
- Uh...
That's what it is, they go deep.
You know they
ain't got no insides.
I think that's my cue to go.
Excuse me, sistas.
Have a good sermon.
Where you goin'?
Love is love.
You're so bitter.
Brothers be trippin'.
That's why I got me
a white man at home.
- Yeah, girl.
- Vanilla my flavor.
Hello, Malcolm.
Oh, Professor wilde, thank God.
I've been tryin' to reach you!
I'm sorry, Malcolm,
I've been a bit tied up.
I haven't been able to find
any more on aghoul,
though my resources
are a bit limited.
Uh, Professor?
Where the hell are you?
Ooh, doin' a stretch
of five to 10.
Apparently, the authorities
frown on sellin' meth
to college students.
Yeah, apparently.
You need to hang up
come over here and kiss me
on my hot mouth.
I'm feelin' romantical.
Well, Malcolm,
I suppose I should get going.
But I will be
e-mailing you the contacts
of associates
who'll be able to help.
I don't mean to be pushy,
but any way
you could do that
before you get raped?
What part of mandingo party
do you not understand?
It's time to power
the white rabbit.
You know. Dirty the snow.
Don't!
That's not that bad.
Lights, please. Thank you.
So after several
exhausting days
of the exorcism,
I threw some
holy water on her,
read an incantation
and the demon left
the woman's body.
I suppose I just
sat back and watched.
I mean, I'm just
the medium who puts her
life in danger
every time she reaches out
to demonic forces.
But you've got a Bible
and a bottle of holy water,
so you make
the world a safer place!
The fact is, people,
is that God is real,
the devil is real,
and monsters exist.
Well...
They're vicious,
terrifying entities!
But the good news is,
Santa claus doesn't exist
so you don't have to worry
about some creepy old guy
coming down your chimney.
So, what exactly are you guys?
And who the fuck hired you?
You can call us ned and Noreen.
See?
This is why you don't
hire from craigslist.
Asshole!
I don't understand
why you always
have to take the credit!
I mean, even your
name comes first
on our book cover,
and I am the one with a gift!
It's not my fault
that ned comes before
Noreen in alphabetical order!
Is that why ned
comes before Noreen
in the bedroom?
Just once I'd like
you to do that thing
with your thumb
and your forefinger.
Yeah, well,
I would like you to do that
thing with my balls and the...
Hi!
Hi! Can we help you?
Yes. Um, there's
something horrible happening
in my house.
My family doesn't realize
what's going on, but I do!
I'm sure that there's
a rational explanation...
Please! They're white!
Oh, my God!
Why didn't you say that?
Yeah, you should lead with that!
I mean, if you're
black we just assume
that your hauntings are
bill collectors or
racist police officers.
But 99% of all hauntings
happen to white people,
that's a fact.
What he means to say is,
of course we'll help you.
Thank you so much.
So we're here to
help you people.
And before you get worked up,
I mean "you people"
as a couple.
It wasn't racist
till you explained it.
The bad news is
you have
a demon in your house.
Here we go again.
Okay, wait. So the house
really is haunted?
Megan, it's not
the house that's haunted.
A-ha! I knew it! I knew it!
It's always
the little white girl.
Think about it.  The exorcist,
the last exorcism,
the exorcism of Emily rose.
All white girls.
'Cause there ain't no black
parents gonna have
no little white girl
talkin' like that.
"Bitch, who are you?
Who're you cursin' at?
"And turn
the fuckin' air down in here!"
Malcolm, Malcolm,
just listen for a second.
Yes.
When we first met you,
there was something
attached to you.
Oh, that was a hemorrhoid.
That was... it's good now.
This dark entity has
attached itself to him
and now it's
feeding off of all of you.
So what you're
saying is that this is
all Malcolm's fault.
That's right.
Your family could've
left here at
any time, but now you're stuck.
Like a piece of toilet paper
stuck on your shoe
when you leave the bathroom.
And your wife
knew the whole time,
but she didn't tell you
because she wanted
you to walk around
and look like an idiot.
Oh, get over it!
I'm not the one who
had an affair
with some low-rent
palm reader from akron!
And you never
would've known if you
weren't a psychic!
But I am psychic, ned!
Oh!
Ow.
Shit!
What is that for?
What you'll be
thinking about doing
to Megan in two seconds.
"Thinking about
doing to Megan?"
One, two, see?
Uh, guys,
we came on short notice.
We may need
an extra pair of hands.
Anyone you trust to help?
I know a guy. He's Mexican.
Megan,
let's go to your contacts.
Hey, nice camera.
Right?
I take it your third cousin
owns electronics shops.
Eh, somethin' like that.
He sells them out of
the back of his truck.
It's a mobile operation.
Let me know if you want one.
Hey, ned, something weird.
All these clocks stop at 3:27
when the hauntings happen.
Normally, it's 3:07.
Nope, we're on cp time.
The demon will manifest itself
in many ways.
To your son,
it's his imaginary friend.
To your daughter
it's the voice inside the box.
For Malcolm it's that
sexy little doll Abigail.
See? It's a manifestation!
You think I'd bang
a doll for no reason?
Malcolm! Shut up.
What we're about to do
is the first step in
banishing the demon
to the netherworld.
Oh, what is that?
This helps me communicate
with the demon.
Organic,
hydroponically grown og kush.
Very strong.
This is some good shit.
Well, pass the mask, shit.
We grow it ourselves.
High water bill.
That's that shit right there!
Let me get another hit.
I'm goin' to the further.
Tony, where are you?
Smells like that og kush.
Mom!
What...
Becky!
Cool!
Wyatt, get upstairs!
- Wyatt, come on!
-  Fuck you, you bitch!
Why are you tying
my baby to a chair?
Because the bitch
got a demon in her!
Make it stop!
This is some scary
cucuy shit right here, man.
I don't know who  cucuy is.
A  cucuy is a
ghetto Mexican bogeyman.
Oh, like George Lopez.
I know, huh?
I agree, it is scary as fuck.
This spirit is more powerful
than I thought.
We're gonna need
to get a priest
and perform a real exorcism.
I know a guy!
He's a little unconventional.
I don't know, Malcolm.
I know, that bitch
don't look right.
No, why you gotta
call her a bitch?
You disrespecting the little ho.
Nigga, did you just sell me out?
There's certain words
that trigger white folk.
I mean, bitch, ho, slut.
No offense.
You can't say those words.
That's like our...
Hey!
What the hell are
you talking about?
Are you out your damn mind?
We would never say that.
Oh, we would
behind closed doors.
I mean,
I wouldn't say it in a bus
or a waffle house.
Or in
the parking lot of a kfc,
but, yeah, I would say it.
Hey, I ain't your boy...
I got your back.
This is a lovely
scarf you're wearing.
It's a sash,
you know what I'm sayin'?
I'm selling these.
This a part of my
new clothing line,
"Jesus pieces," and I got, like,
the shoe that
the pope be wearin'.
In leather,
suede, in green, brown,
and the pope hats!
I can't keep that shit,
you know
niggers love big hats.
Okay, you know what,
that's enough.
Thank you so much.
That's right.
Can we help my daughter,
please?
Hell, she went
really white girl on me.
"Oh, my God!"
I was like, "whoa."
Speaking of white...
Are you doin' cocaine again?
Cocaine?
No, man, this stuff's Molly!
Oh!
Can I try?
- It's all good.
- Oh, wow.
I'm gonna take
a little pinch for later.
He's just bringing drugs?
It's Molly.
Wrap it up!
Yeah, I'm sorry. I told you
he was unconventional.
All right.
Hey, chill. Calm down, man.
Doug! Doug! Doug! Whoa.
Y'all some crazy
ass motherfuckers.
Y'all thought I was
gonna shoot this bitch?
I'm just gonna pistol-whip her
until she weakens.
You're not
pistol-whipping
my daughter!
He know's what he's doing.
The man is a genius.
In the name of the father
and the holy ghost...
I need three other white people.
Peyton Manning!
Peyton Manning, kristen Stewart.
Paula deen!
Where's Doug?
I can't find his
black ass in this dark!
Where the hell is he?
Like a forest
creature in a cartoon.
Father Doug!
He's over here!
Doug! Nigga, please, don't.
Father, please don't!
No, wait!
It's better if he points the
gun at himself and not at us.
Just talk to him, Malcolm.
Listen to my voice,
okay, Doug?
Listen to my voice.
This is not what niggas do!
We don't do suicide!
Murder, yes! Suicide?
That's what they do.
Yeah, we do that.
I've tried at least 20 times.
Motherfucker got
me acting all crazy,
actin' the fool!
You know damn well I wouldn't
peel my own cap!
I can't stop it! I can't
stop it! Man, it keeps...
There's somethin' in my head
that's tellin' me
to blow off my head.
Is it in here? Is it in there?
No, no, no! Yeah, up there!
Demon break.
Who wants a mojito?
Oh, the black guy's
still got a gun.
Oh, God!
This demon is
a son of a bitch, man!
Father,
why have you abandoned me?
Is it because I cuss a lot,
even during prayer?
"Amen, motherfucker,"
sounds dope.
Is it because...
I don't get Ryan seacrest.
I don't get him.
I know what it is,
'cause I dressed up as
a foreclosure sign
when people was getting
kicked out of their house.
On Halloween I just
stood in the yard.
I knew it was wrong,
but it was funny to me.
Out of all of
the people on the  Brady bunch,
it was Alice that
I wanted to fuck.
In the station wagon,
on top of Mr. Brady's
architect desk.
Just used it for
protractors and rulers.
Is it because I
actually kinda thought
that it was okay that
Chris brown hit Rihanna?
I know that bitch
hit him first, man!
She talk too much shit!
She an island girl.
"What you doin', Chris?
"Where you goin'?
Who's this bitch talkin'
"about Chris?"
Shut the fuck up, bitch!
Somebody help me.
Doug! Fight it, Doug!
No!
Nigga, that's a bigass gun!
That's gonna hurt, nigga.
Malcolm,
he has a message for you.
He says...
"Hi, bitch."
Oh, my God!
No!
We're gonna need
another priest!
It's too late.
I have to perform the exorcism.
It's true.
Although ned's only
formal training was at
ghostbusters summer
camp back in 1988.
Never cross the streams.
Never cross them.
And he is dumb!
I mean, dumb, dumb, dumb!
The point is, you can do this!
Do you remember
what you said to me
on our wedding night?
"I have whiskey dick
and I'll make it up
to you in the morning."
No! You said God
brought us together
for a reason.
That doesn't sound like me.
Must've been really drunk.
Just fucking do it, dummy!
Okay.
Becky!
Did it work?
Please help me.
I'm sorry for everything!
I think you did it!
Full inversion.
We got a full inversion.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, my God!
Time to die!
It was him! It was him!
No, don't do me like that!
It actually was him.
Better him than me.
That looked like
it hurt, shit.
Whoo! Now, that's what
you call a blowjob.
A leaf blower?
- Don't judge me.
- Malcolm!
Demon, you leave
our daughter alone!
That's not your
daughter anymore!
I didn't mean like
a daughter-daughter...
I was just saying that...
Seriously?
Malcolm, help her!
Okay. God damn it!
Go get 'em, buddy.
Wyatt, are you okay?
Yeah, but Becky?
She looks pretty fucked up.
How about you leave,
and we'll pretend
none of this ever happened?
The bitch is mine!
You heard the man,
the bitch is his. I tried.
Seriously?
She said the bitch is his.
That's pretty emphatic.
Malcolm, please help me.
I'm so sorry.
Becky will rot in hell!
Okay, which one is it?
Go rot in hell or you
want me to help you?
Malcolm, help her!
The bitch is confusing me!
Okay. Demon,
you leave her alone!
You take me instead!
Deal.
Wait, no, no, no.
Here, take him instead!
I haven't heard
a demon scream for a while.
I think it's safe
to go back up there.
I still have a bad feeling.
For God's sake, come on, guys!
Come on!
All right.
Oh, my God! Wyatt,
get upstairs right now!
They're cuddling!
The demon's gone!
I did it! This house is clean!
Look at his eyes!
They're rolling to
the back of his head!
That's the face that he makes
when he has an orgasm.
I think he's okay, you guys.
This is not over.
Are you guys
watching this?
Yes, we're watching it, dummy!
I'm so intrigued by this.
Oh, man!
He's all twisted up
like a chocolate pretzel!
Such flexibility
and the dexterity!
Oh, my God.
This is
making me queasy!
It's like he could
suck his own dick.
I don't wanna suck my...
Please help me!
If I could do that,
I don't think
I'd ever talk to you again.
Stop it, you unholy demon!
Oh! Oh! That is greasy shit!
Probably Murray's.
The power of
Christ compels you!
It burn like bum piss!
That means it's working!
Pour the whole thing,
like I just won
the super bowl!
Go!
Oh, my God.
Are you crazy?
Is that all you got, bitch?
Oh!
Wait, guys!
Stop! Everybody, stop!
Malcolm, are you okay?
No, I think I'm gonna be sick.
What?
Hold up.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, my God, I can't...
Oh.
Puking like a runway model.
- I'm good. I'm good.
- Are you done?
You're gonna want to
febreze all of this.
You're gonna
wanna just clean this.
I feel so much better now.
Whoo!
Oh!
Can't be too sure. Oh, shit.
I gotta get the hell outta here.
Once they see a black
guy in a pool of blood,
you know who they're
gonna come after next.
I gotta go. Hey, watch out!
Now this place is clean.
It sounded
better when I said it.
Get the box.
Thank you guys so much.
No need to thank us.
We're happy to help.
Come on, ned.
And we'll just take
Abigail with us as well,
for safekeeping.
Yeah, I know what
you plan on doing
with that doll.
What? No, I'm a professional.
She's a freak bitch.
Stop it.
Trust me.
Hey. How come Noreen ain't
pickin' up on the vibes?
You know how
when you're trying
to last longer,
you think about baseball?
Mmm-hmm.
It's kind of like that.
Throws a haze in their head.
It's the only way to
survive when you're
married to a psychic.
Come on, ned.
I know you're thinking
about fucking that doll.
Hey, hey, hey.
You've had enough.
Bye, doll.
It's so nice
being able to just
relax on the couch
and watch  the bachelorette.
Yeah.
Huh?
You didn't hear that?
What?
My nigga senses is tinglin'.
It's like my spidey senses.
Oh, would you hush?
It is fine!
My white senses
say we're fine.
Everything's okay.
It's over.
Okay? It's over.
Okay, okay. I'm trippin'.
That's right.
...Dead white bitch!
You already know
how it's going down,
motherfuckers, all right?
I looked on my
dora the explorer app,
this the motherfuckin'
correct address.
This ain't a drive-by,
homie, okay?
This a walk-in, homie.
So ain't no escape plan!
My cousin is in here, cuz!
Y'all ready?
Hey, yo, Malcolm!
Whassup, my niggie?
I'm here, cuz!
Oh, shit!
What the fuck are you doin', man?
I gotta run for it!
This is bullshit!
Oh, my God!
I'm scared as fuck!
I'm good, dog.
Let me get my motherfuckin'
bearings together, homie.
All right,
let's go up in there, cuz.
It smell like dead ass,
baloney and sweat socks
up in there, homie.
It smell like
honey boo boo's boo-boo,
homie!
Malcolm?
Where you at, cuz?
Ain't nobody in here, cuz.
Oh, shit!
Megan got fucked up!
Head twisted all
backwards, niggie.
Now, upon further
examination, my niggie,
this white bitch
smell like she been dead
about a week, maybe two.
I watch  Dexter,
New York,
Atlanta.
Don't nobody get
killed on there,
but they need to, my nigga.
Stevie j.,
you know what I'm sayin'?
This bitch smell
like poverty, cuz!
Yah! Taekwondo! Oh, shit!
They done killed
the little mini
white bitch, too, cuz!
Fuck happened down here, cuz?
Hello?
Oh, shit! There's another
dead body, cuz.
Who the fuck is it,
though, huh?
Who the fuck is it?
Oh, God, it's Malcolm!
They done
kill my cuz, cuz!
It's like  boyz n the hood,
he's supposed
to go to college!
Why the fuck they
let doughboy live
and Ricky dead?
Doughboy was
the evil nigga, cuz!
Oh!
I can't believe this!
See if the nigga got
some money, though.
What you hit me for, brah?
You know better
than to be poppin' up
on me like that, cuz!
You get knocked out
every motherfuckin'
time, homie.
World star! World star!
You hit me with a brick!
Where's my family?
Are they okay?
Nigga, they dead as fuck!
All of them?
Even the little boy?
He's on the back
of a motherfuckin'
milk carton, niggie!
Good. He may have lived.
Where's Kisha?
Nigga, I don't know
where the fuck Kisha
is at, cuz!
Shh! Shh!
She did this shit!
The white girl's neck,
snapped it back.
Kisha did that shit?
Nigga, that bitch
is gangsta, cuz!
Shh! I came down to
the basement on some
creep shit, like...
I was just sittin' here
waitin' for this bitch,
like, "nigga, what?"
"Bitch, you want
some of this?"
So I'm gonna sit
here incog-negro
up under this blanket like,
nigga, like what.
Let my sneakers be all,
so she be like,
"that nigga dead."
The throat, like,
"bitch, you want
some of this?"
You can't kill me!
I'm like a roach!
I don't die, I multiply!
I got God on my side, bitch!
Twinkle, twinkle little star
she's right
behind me, isn't she?
How I wonder...