[door creaks]
[footsteps clacking]
[door thuds]
[woman laughing]
[bell tolling]
- I'm so tired.
I could sleep a thousand years.
- Don't worry.
You'll pick up again tonight.
[liquid pouring]
[light switch clicks]
- It hasn't changed much here.
- It has changed.
It changes slowly.
- How?.
- It changes slowly.
That's all.
- Wait.
I'd like to talk to you.
- I'm listening.
Is this a proposal?.
The jewel, is it a proposal?.
You stare at me...
And seem to want to hurt me.
Then your face
turns normal again.
It's the old you.
You continue to stare at me.
And then...
I feel you're coming.
As you come between my thighs,
I feel your sperm rise up
within me
and fill me
and flow out through my eyes.
There are white tears,
thick ones, coating my cheeks.
My mouth is red,
and the white tears
trickle over it.
I don't want to wipe them away.
I cry so much.
I can't stop crying.
You don't have an emerald?.
- No, I don't have an emerald.
- Maybe next time.
- Maybe.
You always remember
your dreams?.
- [whispers] No.
[bluesy rock music]
"HOUSE OF PLEASURES"
- ~ That hurt you ~
~ Mmmm ~
~ Baby ~
~ I don't wanna be the one ~
~ That causes you pain ~
~ Hey, hey, hey, hey ~
~ Somebody find me a preacher ~
~ So I can buy the rights ~
~ I wanna love you ~
~ Listen, baby ~
~ I'm so weak ~
~ And I know a man ~
~ Should be stronger ~
~ Hand in hand ~
~ We gonna walk ~
~ Down that aisle together ~
~ Whoa, all I need ~
~ Is your promise ~
~ That you'll love me forever ~
~ Hey, hey, hey, hey ~
~ Someone fetch me a preacher ~
~ So I can buy the rights ~
~ I wanna love you ~
~ Listen, baby ~
~ Baby ~
"HOUSE OF PLEASURES"
"November 1 899"
"The twilight
of the 19th century"
[girls talking at once]
- Near the mirror.
Near the mirror, Clothilde.
- I'll show you.
- Pass me a hairpin?.
- Leave me some.
- Don't worry.
- He's nice but heavy.
Physically heavy too.
When he's on top of me,
I'm crushed.
- I hope he hasn't given me
the clap.
- Claptrap.
I hope Victor
doesn't come tonight.
I'm sick of him.
Three times in a row.
What a drag!
Always asking what I think
of his crooked cock,
before I kiss his ass.
Who did you have?.
- Michaux.
- He's sweet on you.
- For now he is.
It's only been twice.
- He doesn't want me now.
- Do you like him?.
- Yes, I like him.
- That's all?.
- It's something.
- You like him or you think
he could pay your debts
to get you out?.
- Is that a problem?.
Maybe I have fewer debts
than you.
- I doubt it.
[bell tolling]
- Sir...
- Good evening.
[girls laughing]
- Mine doesn't work.
- You lose!
- There.
- Can we come closer?.
- Of course.
She's very meek.
I call her Ninon.
- A female?.
- Yes.
[festive piano music]
~ ~
- Alla vostra!
[laughter]
[people talking indistinctly]
[applause]
- Show me your hands.
- You won a point?.
- Yes, my blow got me the...
- Doctor, you've lost.
- You have to drink.
- I've lost?.
- See you later.
- I just finished
an amazing English novel,
full of aliens and Martians...
who invade Earth using rays
and chemical weapons.
They're very powerful
and easily eliminate
human beings.
They devastate the cities...
But not being immune
to human diseases,
they end up dying.
The story is told
by a journalist
who escapes the first attacks
and who seeks his wife
in a deserted land.
Idiotic but pure genius.
Have you read it?.
- No, my only books are
Sade's diaries and the Bible.
And I haven't read the Bible.
Samira, Louis's glass is empty.
I had this letter today.
Shall I read it?.
"Madame,
"Having heard of L'Apollonide
"and keen to enter your house,
I hereby offer myself.
"I'm 1 5 and a half.
"I'm pretty, with nice hair
and fine teeth,
"shapely, with very white skin
and not a blemish on my body,
"and if you want to send someone
from Paris to check
"if the details I mention
are correct.
"l have a kind heart,
and I shall be obedient.
"lf I prove suitable,
"you may send someone
to fetch me
"and bring me to your house.
Pauline Deshaies."
She drew a self-portrait.
She's pretty.
- A pretty drawing
means nothing.
- May l?.
- Yes.
- Very nice, Marie.
I'd like to be here
to welcome her.
- She's a baby.
- With the countess dead,
who'll be
the 20th century's beauty?.
- I say you are.
- What was that?.
- The Jewess is the new beauty.
- Thank you.
[door slams]
[laughter]
- ll mio maestro.
I've missed you.
- Caca, I was here two days ago.
- But not yesterday.
[bell tolling]
Where were you?.
- With my wife.
- No!
The shame of it...
- It's been two weeks.
- I stayed in.
I wasn't in the mood for it.
- And now?.
Are you in the mood?.
- Very much.
- I had an odd dream about you
last week.
- All the girls say that.
- I swear, it's true.
- What was it?.
- It's rather unusual.
- Want to tell me upstairs?.
- I'd like that.
Get drinks and come to the room
with black curtains.
- What are you doing?.
- It's a gift.
[door rattles]
[bell tolling]
- I'm so tired.
I could sleep a thousand years.
- Don't worry.
You'll pick up again tonight.
[glasses whistling eerily]
- Give me a glass?.
- Which one?.
- I don't mind.
- Got any antiseptic soap?.
- I can't afford any.
- And you?.
- You're a pain.
I'll lend you some,
but buy your own.
- Thank you.
- Clothilde?.
Can you help me?.
Hold this.
Thanks.
- What are you doing?.
- It's a gift.
- What's wrong?.
- Nothing's wrong.
- [sighs]
No one knows
what you're thinking.
- I don't think anything.
- She's nearly done.
- Send her to me after.
She's as pretty
as a blazing flower.
- My fingers must be cursed...
- The sound of the sirens...
- I start to undress.
And you put a box down
on the bed.
A tiny box.
I open it.
There's an emerald inside.
You still say nothing,
so I'm convinced that...
Well, I ask if it's a proposal.
You don't reply.
[glasses whistling]
- That's it then.
Loubet has pardoned Dreyfus
at last.
- If the talk turns to Dreyfus,
I'm going up.
- Come on.
Let's go up.
- With pleasure.
- Shall we have commerce?.
- I'd love to.
- You always remember
your dreams?.
I want to tie you up.
May l?.
- Yes, you may.
- He's envious of everything.
I'm happy with you.
[jaguar purring]
- Vuitton...
- [laughs]
[upbeat piano music]
- What?.
Vuitton?.
- I love saying that name.
He's a genius.
- Vuitton.
- I love this song.
- [screaming]
"March 1900"
"The dawn of the 20th century"
- Spread your thighs.
Go on, spread them.
- No!
- I need to see inside your sex
to paint you.
Even to do your face.
It's very important.
Men never look into
the sex of women enough.
There...
I'm beginning to see
the picture.
I have the impression
I've painted your face 40 times.
This face...
You smell nice.
- Jicky by Guerlain.
- I know.
I loved a woman who wore it.
- I'm not jealous.
- How old are you?.
- Why do you ask?.
- So I'll know.
- I'm 28.
- How long have you been here?.
- 1 2 years.
- I'll leave this here.
It's for you.
I really have to go.
- It moved!
It moved!
- Even with two
I lose.
It's pathetic!
[upbeat music over phonograph]
~ ~
- How are you, children?.
Say hello to Pauline.
Okay, girls?.
Met Pauline?.
- We saw her earlier.
- Chinese arm lock!
- You didn't get me.
- Where are you off to?.
- Maurice is taking me out
for the afternoon.
- Lucky you.
I want to go out too.
- Hello.
- Caca...
- Julie, please.
My name's Julie.
- Everyone calls her Caca.
- My name's Julie.
What are you doing
with my doll?.
Bimba, dame un po'.
Don't touch it!
- You are pretty.
You went for your permit?.
- Yes, before I came here.
- They examined you?.
- I'm perfectly healthy.
- Any scars?.
- No.
- Your breasts...
Are they firm?.
- Very.
- Even without a corset?.
- They're firm.
- All right.
You have your permit?.
- Yes, I told you.
My papers are in order.
- Undress, please.
- Now?.
- Yes, get used to it.
You're not here to make jam.
How old are you now?.
- 1 6.
I have a letter from my parents.
- Do you speak well?.
You're polite?.
- Yes, I've been taught.
- Can you read?.
- Yes.
- And write?.
- Go on.
Turn round.
Nice buttocks.
Nice breasts.
- I'm young.
- You mustn't slim.
Can you let your hair down?.
Your voice...
- What about it?.
- It's a bit weak.
- I can try harder.
- Try.
- I'll manage it.
- Show me.
- If I say I'll manage it,
I will.
- This isn't a knocking shop.
- I know.
That's why I wrote to you.
- If you don't fit in,
I can't keep you.
You learn the job as you go.
It's not easy.
- Can I get dressed now?.
- You have a nickname?.
La Petite.
Will that do?.
Do you have a lover?.
- No lover.
- Are you a virgin?.
Tell me.
It's not a problem.
I can check.
Are you a virgin?.
- No.
- Why choose this place?.
- To be independent.
To be free.
- To be free?.
In a house of tolerance?.
Freedom's outside, not here.
- To earn money of my own.
- Do you want to marry?.
- No.
- Why are you lying?.
Don't fool yourself.
A man rarely marries
a prostitute.
- We all live together.
We're always together.
We're nice to each other,
respect each other.
All right?.
We share beds.
You can sleep here.
There's room with Clothilde.
You stay until the clients go,
but get up when you want.
When you get up,
go down to the dining room.
You never go out alone.
Only with Madame or a man.
If you're alone outside,
that's soliciting.
At around 4:00, we wash.
We have to be clean.
Very clean.
Smell nice. Clean hair.
Soap your body and hair daily
and rub down with cologne.
Often we do it in pairs.
I wash you, you wash me...
I'll show you the creams.
A hairdresser comes at 6:00.
He can curl your hair,
dye it and so on.
You don't pay him.
Madame does.
If a client likes your hair
one particular way,
don't change it too often.
Come on.
If a client says you smell
or you're dirty,
Madame will fine you.
It'll only increase your debts.
So wash yourself.
We all buy our own perfume.
You don't use another girl's.
You buy your own.
After each client,
rinse your mouth with water
and a few drops of mouthwash.
It's strong, but it works.
- My name's Léa.
- Pauline.
- I know.
Welcome.
- When the client undresses,
discreetly check his cock.
Check for sores or spots.
Check his body for rashes too.
Any doubts, don't have sex.
After each job,
wash your lips,
rinse and rub them
with cologne.
Ever used it?.
- No.
- It stings,
but that's normal.
- When you get to the room,
what do you do?.
Talk?.
- Yes, you talk.
You chat a little.
They might talk
about themselves.
You have another drink.
It helps.
Find out what he's like
and adapt.
- After a while,
you get the same ones.
- Just arouse them
and make them come.
But fake it during sex.
- Why?.
- Because.
That's how we do it.
- Hello.
Pauline.
- Madeleine.
This is for you.
- What's that?.
- A wine stain.
I can't get it out.
- Let me see.
I'll wear it anyway.
The old woman will only add it
to my debts.
- Tighter.
- Don't move.
- Looking for wrinkles?.
Let me see.
No, you're fine.
Just a few around the eyes.
- That's okay.
You don't have one.
- They'll come.
[bell tolling]
- Want to try?.
It helps with love.
- Good evening.
- I'm Jacques.
I follow you?.
- Did Madame buy you
from another house or not?.
- No.
- You have no debts then.
- What were you before?.
- A seamstress.
- I was a laundress.
It was torture, believe me.
My lungs are full of ammonia.
- What did you do before?.
- Me?.
I did nothing special.
- You're from the bourgeoisie?.
- The petty bourgeoisie.
Very petty.
[laughter]
- You have no debts then.
- We all have debts.
- You work to pay them off.
- In your dreams.
She makes sure you never pay
them off and leave.
Even with a lot of clients,
you always need perfume...
- Go easy on that stuff.
- But, Madame,
Mondays are quiet.
It helps us relax.
- It won't be quiet for long.
Come on, up you get.
He's a new one.
Are you all right?.
- Yes, fine.
- That's good.
Very good.
Just...
- Michaux could pay off
your debts.
- If he does, I'll marry him.
- The tall girl is popular.
Next to her, the Algerian.
Samira.
That young one there is 15.
She's a virgin.
I can send for a boy too.
19, very pretty.
He can be here in an hour.
- I need to think about it.
- [laughs]
[bell tolling]
- Do you like champagne?.
- Not really.
- But he loves it.
- Come on.
- It's cold.
- You'll get used to it.
You'll see, it's delicious.
- Very nice.
[twinkly piano music]
[laughter]
- It's wonderful here.
You see girls without corsets...
- Léa...
- Someone for you.
- Who is it?.
- Victor.
Hurry up now.
He's in the blue room.
Michaux will be in at one.
Try to see someone else first.
[upbeat piano music]
When Pauline finishes,
check it went well.
- Why me?.
So shall we have commerce?.
- No, not today.
- Why not?.
- Because.
- Pity.
Who did Charles go with?.
- Léa.
- She milked the first one?.
That other guy...
Who did he go with?.
- No idea.
[cork pops]
- Won't you sit down?.
Can you lift your veil?.
What's your name?.
- The Jewess.
- No. Your real name.
- Madeleine.
- I'm Jacques.
- Why did you come up?.
- I paid for the night.
Does that hurt?.
- No.
- How did it happen?.
You don't have to tell me.
- It was a man...
A man I knew well.
We were in one of the rooms.
He asked
if he could tie me up.
I said he could.
I played along.
And that was that.
- No one ever comes to see you?.
- No.
- So what do you do here?.
- I make the beds.
I help in the kitchen.
I help in the laundry.
I look after the girls.
- Does she hide you?.
- No.
Why are you asking me all this?.
- I don't know.
Didn't you want to have
a normal life?.
Outside.
You could find a job.
I can help if you want.
- I don't know.
Do you want to make love or not?.
I don't want to talk anymore.
- Vuitton...
[melancholy piano music]
~ ~
- Thank you again.
- My pleasure.
- I'll get my animal.
[door slams]
[piano music continues]
~ ~
- I adore her.
- I've never had her.
- When she goes off you,
you get this.
- Pussy fur?.
- Who were you with?.
- My Julie.
Caca.
- How many?.
- Four.
You?.
- Six.
- Five.
- Three.
I'll never get out of here.
- Okay?.
- This shit is sticky...
- Let me help.
What's this?.
- It's not easy in a bathtub
but I'm okay.
- Want some ointment?.
- I'm okay.
- Did it go well?.
- I think so.
How do I clean the sperm
with the sponge?.
- Use this cream and rub gently.
It stings but that's normal.
- It's so depressing.
It'll be dawn soon.
- I've drunk too much.
- Thank you.
- 80.
"Mr. Prefect,
"l am a widow
raising two children.
"My duty is to provide for them
and make a decent living.
"As I advance in years,
"finding a trade other than
the one I have is impossible.
"You know I run
a respectable house.
"My girls are healthy,
"and we abide by the rules
for such houses.
"l know the law and uphold it.
"I've never offered a girl
to a politician
"or used one for corruption.
"ln a word, the house is clean.
"The landlord,
the notary Hallereau,
"knows of your affection
for this house
"and so demands
a large increase in rent.
"He refuses to negotiate.
"l paid for all the fittings.
"Business is now good.
"But this increase in rent
would force me into debt,
"obliging me to sell up
and move out.
"l have no one else to turn to.
"Please allow me to make
a living and raise my children.
"Allow me the consolation
an indebted woman requires.
Marie-France Dallaire."
- It reeks of sperm
and champagne here.
- Why do they call you Caca?.
- Why do they
call you Caca?.
- Why am I Long Hair?.
- Let's just say...
I have a specialty.
- I get the picture.
- Want to know anyway?.
- Julie, we're eating!
- Why?.
- Don't spoil it.
- Does it still hurt?.
- Only a little at night now.
- Did Madame make you?.
- No.
She asked me.
- And?.
He paid for the night,
but didn't want sex.
- Why not?.
- Probably just to see
the monster close up.
He was sweet.
He said he'd come back
next week.
But I don't believe him.
- Want to check in the cards?.
- No, it's okay.
- Last night was
a real freak show.
I had one...
He keeps going to confession
to talk filth
to get the priest hard.
He wanks off at the same time.
- That's sick!
- I'd like to see
a brothel for women.
A great place with great men
who are hard all the time
and tell us we're pretty,
even if we're old
with saggy tits.
- We'd never ask
the stupid questions they do.
- Do you like my tits?.
Do you like my big tits?.
- What's "whore" in Arabic?.
- "Zaniya"...
or "Qahba,"
depending how polite you are.
- What's the polite one?.
- "Zaniya," the kept woman.
- I don't mind being
a kept woman.
- Is Maurice going to propose?.
- Perhaps.
If his wife dies.
- Are you in love?.
- No.
But he's sweet.
The other day,
we went to the Wepler
for oysters.
Then we went dancing.
Know what I told him?.
"l would pluck out my eyes
for you
"so you'd have more holes
to make love to me."
He loved that!
- Is this only for Madeleine?.
- No, for all of us.
Four show the past,
four the present
and four the future.
- Oh, cazzo.
- No, it's all right.
That's the good spade card.
It means stability, luck,
security...
The nine of clubs
means a job, a situation.
The Queen is a kind woman.
There's a young man, single.
He's next to a diamond card.
There's a romantic project,
but it's upside down.
That means there's a problem.
A girl with long hair.
She's upside down too.
You have to be wary of her.
- Are you sure?.
- Of course.
- That it's upside down.
- It's in relation
to the dealer.
- They're only cards.
- If you draw them,
they're more than that.
- You're a bit of a mystic?.
- I want to stop.
- We've started, let's finish.
Come on, the future.
- What did they call you before?.
- The Jewess.
- Which is the worst one?.
- The ten.
[bell tolling]
- Do you like that?.
- Yes.
[knocking]
- What do you want?.
- To see the Woman Who Laughs.
- For sex or just to see her?.
- To see her first,
then decide.
- lnside a room,
you do as you like,
but you see girls here for sex,
the normal way.
- I'd like Léa as a doll then.
[dramatic music]
- Come here.
You smell nice, my doll.
- Who did you have?.
- Simon.
And you?.
- Louis.
- [yelling]
- Julie, no!
Help me!
Julie!
- I want the peach.
- Well?.
- I'll get you!
You have to strip right now.
Catch.
Marie-France, where do
the clients get their money?.
- In industry, textiles,
paper...
Family fortunes too.
Fortunes of the aristocracy.
- Are there a lot
of aristocrats?.
- Yes.
We get a lot of aristocrats.
- What does Louis work in?.
- Louis is in textiles.
He made his fortune
in textiles.
Michaux has a family fortune.
Charles is a family fortune too.
- Who's the richest one?.
- The richest one?.
Charles.