He doesn't spend the most,
but he's the richest one.
- Has he been coming long?
- Yes, since the days
when I worked at L'Apollonide
like you do.
- My back hurts.
I'm sick of his doll thing.
- Don't complain.
There's worse.
- I'm not saying that,
just that I'm sick of it.
- You do as you want.
You get rid of creeps
with a few pussy hairs.
My whole bush wouldn't do that!
- It feels like an eternity
since we had a day out.
[gagging]
It's me.
Give me your cigarette.
All right.
What is it?
I was thinking a Lanvin hat
would suit you.
Go on then, Polo.
Treat me to a hat.
The fresh air loosens you up.
Want a drop of champagne?
Please.
Want some too?
Yeah, okay.
[coughing]
Gently!
Sorry.
Pardon me.
It slipped out.
Calm down, Polo.
Oh, you know...
I'm sorry, it's old age.
This is nice.
Oh, yes!
I feel so good!
- I don't think
I'll be here long.
- I said that too.
Now look at me.
- We'll see.
I don't have any debts yet.
- "I understand
your sense of injustice,"
"and I've always given you
my support."
"But, as a prefect,
I can't work miracles."
"I cannot oppose
a landlord's decision."
- Good evening.
- Who's here this evening?
- The same ones.
Still want to see the Jewess?
- Pardon me?
- The Woman Who Laughs.
Want to go up to see her?
You can,
but it'll cost you more.
- No.
I was a bit tipsy last time.
Who else is there?
- Who else...
Sweetness, Clea, Climbing Rose,
Fine Thigh...
- Afterwords, women couldn't
compete in the games.
- Why not?
- Good question.
They were thrown from a rock
if ever they went there.
But now they can go.
- They couldn't go
because the athletes were nude.
Now they're dressed.
So women can take part.
- Will you go up with me
and another girl?
- Who?
- Anyone.
You choose.
- I don't know.
I'd rather go alone
if you don't mind.
- Shall I put you in my will?
Do you want to be in my will?
- No.
I want you to stay alive.
- If anyone here is alive,
I am.
- Good evening.
- Ah, Louis!
- A drink
or shall I call Samira?
- Both.
- "I understand
your sense of injustice,"
"and I've always given you
my support."
"But, as a prefect,
I can't work miracles."
- Thank you.
- Some women
have very large breasts.
[bell tolling]
They could have an accident,
knock themselves out...
- Yes, that's true.
- They could bandage them.
- It's not so much fun.
- Fine Thigh.
- Fine Thigh...
- Clothed or naked?
- I prefer you naked.
- It costs more.
- I know.
- Talk to me in Japanese.
Go on, make it up.
Make it up.
[speaking Japanese]
- More.
- What does that mean?
- It means my tongue
comes towards you.
Slowly.
It slithers across the floor.
It slips under the bed.
It rises up the side of it.
It reaches your feet.
It licks them.
It glides up along your leg.
Along your thigh.
It reaches your sex.
It winds around it.
It swallows it completely.
Sword swallower.
- Your Japanese is very good.
Do you want some?
[speaking Japanese]
- You don't have to smoke it.
You can take a bit and eat it.
- It's okay, I know.
- I want to see you often.
- Won't Clothilde
be angry with me?
- I can see more than one girl.
Now stop asking questions
and talk to me in Japanese.
You're very young.
- Not that young.
- Really?
- Not many girls my age
have been fucked in champagne.
- Did you like it?
- I loved it.
- Men never look into the sex
of women enough.
Wonderful.
After one night with you,
I could kill myself.
- Say "Ah."
Good.
What's that spot?
- Nothing.
- Have you had it long?
- It's nothing.
- All right.
One month? Two?
- No, a few days.
- All right.
Any itching?
- No.
- No new rashes on your body?
- Let me take a look.
Let me see.
Lie down now
and let me examine you.
Let me see.
Nothing around the anus.
I'll use the speculum now.
- If ever I get out of here,
I'll never make love again.
- No...
- Yes.
I have to examine you.
You have to lie down.
- No!
- I have to examine you.
I have to.
Come on.
Now spread your thighs.
No two ways about it.
I can't see your sex otherwise.
Come on now.
Look at me.
You have to lie down.
Lie down and spread your thighs.
You have to do it.
The cervix is fine.
Heavy but normal discharge.
How about your period?
- It comes and goes.
- When did you last have it?
Two months ago?
Three?
- Not long ago.
I forget.
- Six months?
You don't have your period
any more?
- I'm not pregnant.
- Six months...
- I just don't have my period
any more.
- How about your period?
- Same thing.
It comes and goes.
- And you?
- Normal.
- And you there?
- Mine's fine.
- Let me examine you.
Lie down.
- Okay?
- Yes, I'm healthy.
- Well?
- I'm fine.
I'm healthy.
- And the others?
- I don't know.
- I swear...
- What am I supposed to do now?
You think they're not pregnant?
- No, I'm sure.
But, I'm sorry,
that girl there has syphilis.
- It's okay. I accept it.
- Bravo.
- I'd just like someone
to give me a hug.
I want a macaroon.
- What a shit job.
- Fucking is a fuck awful job.
- It won't be easy tonight.
- No.
- Have you seen my bracelet?
- Which one?
- The pearl one.
- I think I saw it in the box.
- I put a charm on her doll.
I got a needle and...
- It's not your fault, Samira.
It could have been me or you.
It's the clap.
- Samira, go down.
Louis will be here soon.
- Madame...
I have my period.
- We're too busy.
Take a cold bath.
- Please...
- I can't.
I'm already one girl short
as it is.
You'll have to work more.
- Yes, Madame.
- And try to show
a little joy tonight.
All right?
- Tonight,
just pretend I'm dead.
[bluesy rock music]
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I don't Wanna be the one ♪
♪ That hurt you ♪
♪ Mmmm ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ I don't Wanna be the one ♪
♪ That causes you pain ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Somebody find me a preacher ♪
♪ So I can buy the rights ♪
♪ I Wanna love you ♪
♪ Listen, baby ♪
♪ I'm so...♪
[no audio]
♪ Somebody find me a preacher ♪
♪ So I can buy the rights ♪
♪ I Wanna love you ♪
- You really have a tiny head.
- So?
A tiny head is pretty,
isn't it?
- It's very pretty.
Charming.
You have a tiny head too.
- I'm sorry?
- The size of your head...
- My head is fine and delicate.
- I knew it.
A woman called Pauline Tarnowsky
has written a scientific study
on prostitutes.
She says their heads are smaller
than average.
The same is true of criminals.
- Really?
- I can lend it to you
if you want.
- If it's good.
- It's very good.
- Right now, a normal girl
goes for 300.
400 for a Negress.
Plus the debts.
- I can't.
Even keep Julie without working,
I can't.
Paris is too expensive now.
- I have a friend
who organizes special evenings.
The Woman Who Laughs
interests him.
- I want to pay off your debts.
- Five times six.
- Eight...
- 30...40.
- 40.
- Here you are.
- Five times seven?
No, five times nine.
- What time is it?
- It's only 8:00.
Go to bed.
You'll look like hell tonight.
Five times nine?
- You're still here?
- Will you sleep with me?
- No.
It's too late now.
Or too early.
- I didn't mean sex.
Just sleeping.
I don't want to go home.
I feel bad.
- Just sleep then?
At 8:00 a.m.,
there's no more commerce.
You can lie
between Samira and me.
- I promise.
I'll be fine between you.
- Léa, go to bed.
- Sorry.
Good night.
- I can't bring myself
to go home.
Where's Pauline?
- She's asleep by now.
- Who with?
Do you mind
if I stay here awhile?
If I go home, I'll be a wreck.
- You've gone off Clothilde?
- I don't know.
I adore her, but...
we don't have fun.
I make her sad.
But I'm very fond of her.
I love whores.
I find them wonderful.
They move me.
I'm happy with them.
Terrible, isn't it?
- I understand.
I understand you.
[knob rattling]
- It's occupied.
"Anthropometric Study
of Prostitutes and Thieves."
"Pauline Tarnowsky -1889"
[inhaling deeply]
- Spread your legs.
So I can see you.
Tighter.
My geisha...
[crying]
- "The prostitute
is a female criminal."
"We observe an encephalon
several millimeters smaller,"
"due to the fact"
"that prostitutes
have smaller heads."
"Consequently, this means they
have much less brain matter."
"Their weak intelligence"
"and mental abnormality
is natural."
"The dull spirit of some
can become stupor in others"
"and even attain
a state verging on idiocy."
- Get up, Clothilde.
[pounding]
- I'm fine here.
- You are?
Stupefied, you're fine?
You'll end up
in a Marseille brothel
turning tricks
on a vermin-ridden mattress.
- No.
Know what I'm going to do?
I'll sell myself
to another house.
For a high price,
so I can pay off my debts.
- Of course.
No one will want your debts.
- Well, I'll sell my teeth.
- A Marseille brothel,
with the clap.
- Great.
Fine.
We deserve the clap.
We deserve our punishment.
- Ooh.
- I've been here 12 years.
The clap will be a nice break.
- Be brave.
- Good-bye.
- My dear Julie...
my little Caca...
it hurts me to write this
because it will hurt you
to read it.
You're ill, my little Julie,
and I Wish I was there
to comfort you.
But there are things {must say.
Don't think I'm abandoning you.
I'd never abandon someone
I cherish as much as you
after all these months.
But I must tell you this.
Our relations must change.
I don't want to catch
your disease.
I never hesitate
to sacrifice myself,
but now that sacrifice
would hurt me and not help you.
You know I cannot pursue
your disease.
I think I have eluded it
as I have no symptoms,
but I'm not safe yet.
I have to Wait two more Weeks.
Julie, if I were ill,
I would forgive you.
But no one in my family
has ever had such diseases,
and I Wouldn't like
to infect others.
Men have secrets
but no mystery,
and I'm so sorry,
my little Julie.
I stiff love you,
even more now
because you're ill.
Your loving friend, Maurice.
- "Men..."
"Men have secrets
but no mystery,"
"and I'm so sorry,
my little Julie."
"I still love you,"
"even more now
because you're ill."
"Your loving friend, Maurice."
- Where was it?
- In the mail.
- Tear it up.
She mustn't read it.
- That's really sick.
- I can keep her
because he's still paying.
Even if he no longer sees her.
Any news of Pauline?
- No.
Is the house closing down?
- I don't know.
- Does it suit me?
[somber classical music]
♪♪
- It's funny.
She looks like an old doll.
- No, she's too thin.
She's like a big puppet.
But I like her breasts.
- Pinch her nipples
to see if she stops smiling.
- Has Pauline left,
or did something happen to her?
- Could Madame have sold her
without saying?
- Will she sell us one by one?
Will she sell us one by one?
- I don't know.
God only knows
where we'll end up.
Maybe in some seedy brothel,
with revolting clients.
Especially past 25.
- Looking at the freak?
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
- You too.
I don't want to die.
- You're not going to.
I promise.
- I want to see Maurice.
- He's going to come.
Soon.
[women humming]
♪♪
♪ Letters I've Written ♪
♪ Never meaning to send ♪
♪ Beauty I'd always missed ♪
♪ With these eyes before ♪
♪ Just what the truth is ♪
♪ I can't say any more ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes, {love you ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you ♪
♪♪
♪ Gazing at people ♪
♪ Some hand in hand ♪
♪ Just what I'm going through ♪
♪ They can't understand ♪
♪ Some try to tell me ♪
♪ Thoughts they cannot defend ♪
♪ Just what you want to be ♪
♪ You will be in the end ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
♪ Yes, {love you ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you ♪
♪♪
I Oh, how I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ 'Cause I love you ♪
♪ Yes, {love you ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪♪
- I feel your sperm fill me up
and flow out through my eyes.
There are white tears,
thick ones, coating my cheeks.
My mouth is red,
and the white tears
trickle over it.
I don't want to wipe them away.
I cry so much...
I can't stop crying.
You don't have an emerald?
- No, I don't have one.
I want to tie you up.
May I?
Shh.
[metal clicking]
- You were on the floor.
I picked you up.
- Thank you.
- You said something
in your sleep.
- What did I say?
- "If we don't burn,"
"how will the night be lit?."
"Michaux..."
"my fragment..."
"meteorite."
- I said that?
- Shh.
Don't be afraid
to express your love.
Don't be afraid.
[crying]
[bell tolling]
- What's your name?
- Madeleine.
- No nickname?
- Just Madeleine.
[glasses clinking]
- Long live France.
[laughter]
- Where will they go?
- I've sold some
to other houses.
A man has bought Samira.
The others will do
what they can.
Enjoy them while they're here.
- I'm not staying.
I'm in no mood for fun
I just wanted
to give you a kiss.
- A new Jeanne Paquin dress?
- Yes.
- You're ravishing.
- Thank you.
Cheers.
- My favorite sound.
- It's not crystal now,
just glass.
- Never mind.
It's still champagne.
- You look wonderful.
- Look, they're having fun now.
- Do it.
Go on.
- I attended the opening
of the metro yesterday.
It's horrendous.
[cork popping]
It's dark, the seats are hard,
and it's so grim.
Everyone seemed happy.
Stupidly happy.
They loved crossing Paris
underground!
It's appalling.
I walked back from Porte Maillot
to Palais Royal.
I thought of you.
What will we do without you?
- You'll have other experiences.
All the other houses
will be closing too.
It's sad, but too bad.
Today love is out
on the street.
No one can stop that.
- What will you do now?
- I don't know.
I'm a bit tired.
[laughing]
- Promise to stay yourself,
even without L'Apollonide.
Keep the flowers, the music,
the fine dresses,
the color, the champagne,
even in glass...
Make noise, please.
We're going to need it.
[chimes clinking]
[twinkly piano music]
[all talking indistinctly]
- Have we met before?
- Perhaps.
- I'd remember.
What's your name?
- Madeleine.
- A little perfume...
- What are you like under there?
- However you want.
How do you want me to be?
- I don't know.
Aren't you asking me
what I'm like?
- No.
[piano music continues]
♪♪
- Léa?
- Léa's up in a room.
[jaguar purring]
[fireworks popping]
- Hear that, Simone?
The fireworks?
It's the fireworks!
[fireworks popping]
[jaguar purring]
- Don't be scared.
My pretty Ninon...
It's Bastille Day,
but no one's beheading you.
[people shouting]
Musik bitte!
[fireworks whistling]
[man singing operatically]
♪♪
[moaning]
- It's the fireworks!
- I want champagne.
Musik bitte!
[opera music continues]
♪♪
[knock at door]
- Come in.
[door creaks]
[jaguar growling]
[Opera music]
[both moaning]
- You really do like it.
- I want to stop.
I don't like it any more.
- I'm paying, so I decide.
[moaning loudly]
- Shh.
- What will you do now?
- I don't know.
[traffic whirring]
[bluesy rock music]
♪♪
- This is a song
about a bad girl.
Something that happened to me
a long time ago.
Everybody was telling me
how the little girl
was running around.
But I had a head of my own.
And I just Wouldn't listen
to nobody.
My father, he told me,
my mother said I would cry.
"Said, " Son, this Woman'//
break your heart,
and then she'll put you down."
That's when I told Mama
these Words.
Lord, have mercy.
♪ Bad girl, Mama ♪
♪ Bad ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Mama, they call her
bad girl ♪
♪ All because she Wanted
to be free ♪
♪ Mama, I'm in love
with the little girl ♪
♪ And I believe
that she loves me ♪
♪ What my heart feels,
my lips must confess ♪
♪ That I would never
let her on ♪
♪ I don't care
if they call her bad ♪
♪ Bad girl, Mama ♪
♪ Lord, have mercy ♪
♪ A-ow! ♪
♪ Bad! ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Girl been a mystery ♪
♪ Too bad to be explained
by anything ♪
♪ But I believe
one of these days ♪
♪ The whole World
will understand ♪
♪ What my heart feels
my lips must confess ♪
♪ That I will never let
the little girl on ♪
♪ I don't care
if they call her bad ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ You gotta believe me, Mama ♪
♪ A-ow! ♪
♪ Bad! ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Ah! ♪
I Ah!
Whoa! ♪
♪ Bad! ♪
♪ Bad girl, Mama ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Lord, have mercy ♪
♪ Oh, bad ♪
♪ Bad, bad girl ♪
♪ Lord ♪
♪ A-ow! ♪
♪ Bad! ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ A-ow! A-ow! A-ow! ♪
♪ Bad! ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Lord, have mercy ♪
♪ Bad! ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ Bad ♪
♪ Bad girl ♪
♪ Whoof ♪
♪ Lord! ♪
♪ You Won't understand
what I'm saying... ♪