Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I'm so tired.
I could sleep a thousand years.
Don't worry.
You'll pick up again tonight.
It hasn't changed much here.
It has changed.
It changes slowly.
How?
That's all.
Wait.
I'd like to talk to you.
I'm listening.
Is this a proposal?
The jewel, is it a proposal?
You stare at me...
And seem to want to hurt me.
Then your face
turns normal again.
It's the old you.
You continue to stare at me.
And then...
I feel you're coming.
As you come between my thighs,
I feel your sperm rise up
within me
and fill me
and flow out through my eyes.
There are white tears,
thick ones, coating my cheeks.
My mouth is red,
and the white tears
trickle over it.
I don't want to wipe them away.
I cry so much.
I can't stop crying.
You don't have an emerald?
No, I don't have an emerald.
Maybe next time.
Maybe.
You always remember
your dreams?
No.
"HOUSE OF PLEASURES"
"November 1899"
"The twilight
of the 19th century"
Near the mirror.
Near the mirror, Clothilde.
I'll show you.
Pass me a hairpin?
Leave me some.
Don't worry.
He's nice but heavy.
Physically heavy too.
When he's on top of me,
I'm crushed.
I hope he hasn't given me
the clap.
Claptrap.
I hope Victor
doesn't come tonight.
I'm sick of him.
Three times in a row.
What a drag!
Always asking what I think
of his crooked cock,
before I kiss his ass.
Who did you have?
Michaux.
- He's sweet on you.
- For now he is.
It's only been twice.
He doesn't want me now.
Do you like him?
Yes, I like him.
- That's all?
- It's something.
You like him or you think
he could pay your debts
to get you out?
Is that a problem?
Maybe I have fewer debts
than you.
I doubt it.
Sir...
Good evening.
Mine doesn't work.
You lose!
There.
- Can we come closer?
- Of course.
She's very meek.
I call her Ninon.
- A female?
- Yes.
Show me your hands.
You won a point?
Yes, my blow got me the...
Doctor, you've lost.
- You have to drink.
- I've lost?
See you later.
I just finished
an amazing English novel,
full of aliens and Martians...
who invade Earth using rays
and chemical weapons.
They're very powerful
and easily eliminate
human beings.
They devastate the cities...
But not being immune
to human diseases,
they end up dying.
The story is told
by a journalist
who escapes the first attacks
and who seeks his wife
in a deserted land.
Idiotic but pure genius.
Have you read it?
No, my only books are
Sade's diaries and the Bible.
And I haven't read the Bible.
Samira, Louis's glass is empty.
I had this letter today.
Shall I read it?
"Madame,
"Having heard of L'Apollonide
"and keen to enter your house,
I hereby offer myself.
"I'm 15 and a half.
"I'm pretty, with nice hair
and fine teeth,
"shapely, with very white skin
and not a blemish on my body,
"and if you want to send someone
from Paris to check
"if the details I mention
are correct.
"I have a kind heart,
and I shall be obedient.
"If I prove suitable,
"you may send someone
to fetch me
"and bring me to your house.
Pauline Deshaies. "
She drew a self-portrait.
She's pretty.
A pretty drawing
means nothing.
May I?
Yes.
Very nice, Marie.
I'd like to be here
to welcome her.
She's a baby.
With the countess dead,
who'll be
the 20th century's beauty?
I say you are.
What was that?
The Jewess is the new beauty.
Thank you.
I've missed you.
Caca, I was here two days ago.
But not yesterday.
Where were you?
With my wife.
No!
The shame of it...
It's been two weeks.
I stayed in.
I wasn't in the mood for it.
And now?
Are you in the mood?
Very much.
I had an odd dream about you
last week.
All the girls say that.
I swear, it's true.
What was it?
It's rather unusual.
Want to tell me upstairs?
I'd like that.
Get drinks and come to the room
with black curtains.
What are you doing?
It's a gift.
I'm so tired.
I could sleep a thousand years.
Don't worry.
You'll pick up again tonight.
Give me a glass?
- Which one?
- I don't mind.
Got any antiseptic soap?
I can't afford any.
- And you?
- You're a pain.
I'll lend you some,
but buy your own.
Thank you.
Clothilde?
Can you help me?
Hold this.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
It's a gift.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
No one knows
what you're thinking.
I don't think anything.
She's nearly done.
Send her to me after.
She's as pretty
as a blazing flower.
My fingers must be cursed...
The sound of the sirens...
I start to undress.
And you put a box down
on the bed.
A tiny box.
I open it.
There's an emerald inside.
You still say nothing,
so I'm convinced that...
Well, I ask if it's a proposal.
You don't reply.
That's it then.
Loubet has pardoned Dreyfus
at last.
If the talk turns to Dreyfus,
I'm going up.
Come on.
Let's go up.
With pleasure.
Shall we have commerce?
I'd love to.
You always remember
your dreams?
I want to tie you up.
May I?
Yes, you may.
He's envious of everything.
I'm happy with you.
Vuitton...
What?
Vuitton?
I love saying that name.
He's a genius.
Vuitton.
I love this song.
"March 1900"
"The dawn of the 20th century"
Spread your thighs.
- Go on, spread them.
- No!
I need to see inside your sex
to paint you.
Even to do your face.
It's very important.
Men never look into
the sex of women enough.
There...
I'm beginning to see
the picture.
I have the impression
I've painted your face 40 times.
This face...
You smell nice.
Jicky by Guerlain.
I know.
I loved a woman who wore it.
I'm not jealous.
How old are you?
Why do you ask?
So I'll know.
I'm 28.
How long have you been here?
12 years.
I'll leave this here.
It's for you.
I really have to go.
It moved!
Even with two
I lose.
It's pathetic!
How are you, children?
Say hello to Pauline.
Okay, girls?
Met Pauline?
We saw her earlier.
Chinese arm lock!
You didn't get me.
Where are you off to?
Maurice is taking me out
for the afternoon.
Lucky you.
I want to go out too.
Hello.
Caca...
Julie, please.
- My name's Julie.
- Everyone calls her Caca.
My name's Julie.
What are you doing
with my doll?
Don't touch it!
You are pretty.
You went for your permit?
Yes, before I came here.
They examined you?
I'm perfectly healthy.
Any scars?
No.
Your breasts...
- Are they firm?
- Very.
- Even without a corset?
- They're firm.
All right.
- You have your permit?
- Yes, I told you.
My papers are in order.
Undress, please.
- Now?
- Yes, get used to it.
You're not here to make jam.
- How old are you now?
- 16.
I have a letter from my parents.
Do you speak well?
- You're polite?
- Yes, I've been taught.
- Can you read?
- Yes.
- And write?
Go on.
Turn round.
Nice buttocks.
- Nice breasts.
- I'm young.
You mustn't slim.
Can you let your hair down?
- Your voice...
- What about it?
It's a bit weak.
- I can try harder.
- Try.
- I'll manage it.
- Show me.
If I say I'll manage it,
I will.
This isn't a knocking shop.
I know.
That's why I wrote to you.
If you don't fit in,
I can't keep you.
You learn the job as you go.
It's not easy.
Can I get dressed now?
You have a nickname?
La Petite.
Will that do?
Do you have a lover?
No lover.
Are you a virgin?
Tell me.
It's not a problem.
I can check.
- Are you a virgin?
- No.
Why choose this place?
To be independent.
To be free.
To be free?
In a house of tolerance?
Freedom's outside, not here.
To earn money of my own.
Do you want to marry?
- No.
- Why are you lying?
Don't fool yourself.
A man rarely marries
a prostitute.
We all live together.
We're always together.
We're nice to each other,
respect each other.
All right?
We share beds.
You can sleep here.
There's room with Clothilde.
You stay until the clients go,
but get up when you want.
When you get up,
go down to the dining room.
You never go out alone.
Only with Madame or a man.
If you're alone outside,
that's soliciting.
At around 4:00, we wash.
We have to be clean.
Very clean.
Smell nice. Clean hair.
Soap your body and hair daily
and rub down with cologne.
Often we do it in pairs.
I wash you, you wash me...
I'll show you the creams.
A hairdresser comes at 6:00.
He can curl your hair,
dye it and so on.
You don't pay him.
Madame does.
If a client likes your hair
one particular way,
don't change it too often.
Come on.
If a client says you smell
or you're dirty,
Madame will fine you.
It'll only increase your debts.
So wash yourself.
We all buy our own perfume.
You don't use another girl's.
You buy your own.
After each client,
rinse your mouth with water
and a few drops of mouthwash.
It's strong, but it works.
- My name's Lea.
- Pauline.
I know.
Welcome.
When the client undresses,
discreetly check his cock.
Check for sores or spots.
Check his body for rashes too.
Any doubts, don't have sex.
After each job,
wash your lips,
rinse and rub them
with cologne.
Ever used it?
No.
It stings,
but that's normal.
When you get to the room,
what do you do?
- Talk?
- Yes, you talk.
You chat a little.
They might talk
about themselves.
You have another drink.
It helps.
Find out what he's like
and adapt.
After a while,
you get the same ones.
Just arouse them
and make them come.
But fake it during sex.
- Why?
- Because.
That's how we do it.
Hello.
Pauline.
Madeleine.
This is for you.
What's that?
A wine stain.
I can't get it out.
Let me see.
I'll wear it anyway.
The old woman will only add it
to my debts.
- Tighter.
- Don't move.
Looking for wrinkles?
Let me see.
No, you're fine.
Just a few around the eyes.
That's okay.
You don't have one.
They'll come.
Want to try?
It helps with love.
Good evening.
I'm Jacques.
I follow you?
Did Madame buy you
from another house or not?
No.
You have no debts then.
- What were you before?
- A seamstress.
I was a laundress.
It was torture, believe me.
My lungs are full of ammonia.
What did you do before?
Me?
I did nothing special.
You're from the bourgeoisie?
The petty bourgeoisie.
Very petty.
- You have no debts then.
- We all have debts.
You work to pay them off.
In your dreams.
She makes sure you never pay
them off and leave.
Even with a lot of clients,
you always need perfume...
Go easy on that stuff.
But, Madame,
Mondays are quiet.
- It helps us relax.
- It won't be quiet for long.
Come on, up you get.
He's a new one.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, fine.
That's good.
Very good.
Just...
Michaux could pay off
your debts.
If he does, I'll marry him.
The tall girl is popular.
Next to her, the Algerian.
Samira.
That young one there is 15.
She's a virgin.
I can send for a boy too.
19, very pretty.
He can be here in an hour.
I need to think about it.
- Do you like champagne?
- Not really.
But he loves it.
Come on.
It's cold.
You'll get used to it.
You'll see, it's delicious.
Very nice.
It's wonderful here.
You see girls without corsets...
Lea...
- Someone for you.
- Who is it?
Victor.
Hurry up now.
He's in the blue room.
Michaux will be in at one.
Try to see someone else first.
When Pauline finishes,
check it went well.
Why me?
So shall we have commerce?
- No, not today.
- Why not?
Because.
Pity.
Who did Charles go with?
Lea.
She milked the first one?
That other guy...
Who did he go with?
No idea.
Won't you sit down?
Can you lift your veil?
What's your name?
- The Jewess.
- No. Your real name.
Madeleine.
I'm Jacques.
Why did you come up?
I paid for the night.
- Does that hurt?
- No.
How did it happen?
You don't have to tell me.
It was a man...
A man I knew well.
We were in one of the rooms.
He asked
if he could tie me up.
I said he could.
I played along.
And that was that.
No one ever comes to see you?
No.
So what do you do here?
I make the beds.
I help in the kitchen.
I help in the laundry.
I look after the girls.
- Does she hide you?
- No.
Why are you asking me all this?
I don't know.
Didn't you want to have
a normal life?
Outside.
You could find a job.
I can help if you want.
I don't know.
Do you want to make love or not?
I don't want to talk anymore.
Vuitton...
- Thank you again.
- My pleasure.
I'll get my animal.
I adore her.
I've never had her.
When she goes off you,
you get this.
Pussy fur?
Who were you with?
My Julie.
Caca.
How many?
Four.
You?
Six.
Five.
Three.
I'll never get out of here.
Okay?
This shit is sticky...
Let me help.
What's this?
It's not easy in a bathtub
but I'm okay.
- Want some ointment?
- I'm okay.
Did it go well?
I think so.
How do I clean the sperm
with the sponge?
Use this cream and rub gently.
It stings but that's normal.
It's so depressing.
It'll be dawn soon.
I've drunk too much.
Thank you.
80.
"Mr. Prefect,
"I am a widow
raising two children.
"My duty is to provide for them
and make a decent living.
"As I advance in years,
"finding a trade other than
the one I have is impossible.
"You know I run
a respectable house.
"My girls are healthy,
"and we abide by the rules
for such houses.
"I know the law and uphold it.
"I've never offered a girl
to a politician
"or used one for corruption.
"In a word, the house is clean.
"The landlord,
the notary Hallereau,
"knows of your affection
for this house
"and so demands
a large increase in rent.
"He refuses to negotiate.
"I paid for all the fittings.
"Business is now good.
"But this increase in rent
would force me into debt,
"obliging me to sell up
and move out.
"I have no one else to turn to.
"Please allow me to make
a living and raise my children.
"Allow me the consolation
an indebted woman requires.
Marie-France Dallaire. "
It reeks of sperm
and champagne here.
Why do they call you Caca?
Why do they
call you Caca?
Why am I Long Hair?
Let's just say...
I have a specialty.
I get the picture.
Want to know anyway?
Julie, we're eating!
Why?
Don't spoil it.
Does it still hurt?
Only a little at night now.
- Did Madame make you?
- No.
She asked me.
And?
He paid for the night,
but didn't want sex.
Why not?
Probably just to see
the monster close up.
He was sweet.
He said he'd come back
next week.
But I don't believe him.
Want to check in the cards?
No, it's okay.
Last night was
a real freak show.
I had one...
He keeps going to confession
to talk filth
to get the priest hard.
He wanks off at the same time.
That's sick!
I'd like to see
a brothel for women.
A great place with great men
who are hard all the time
and tell us we're pretty,
even if we're old
with saggy tits.
We'd never ask
the stupid questions they do.
Do you like my tits?
Do you like my big tits?
What's "whore" in Arabic?
"Zaniya"...
or "Qahba,"
depending how polite you are.
What's the polite one?
"Zaniya," the kept woman.
I don't mind being
a kept woman.
Is Maurice going to propose?
Perhaps.
If his wife dies.
Are you in love?
No.
But he's sweet.
The other day,
we went to the Wepler
for oysters.
Then we went dancing.
Know what I told him?
"I would pluck out my eyes
for you
"so you'd have more holes
to make love to me. "
He loved that!
Is this only for Madeleine?
No, for all of us.
Four show the past,
four the present
and four the future.
No, it's all right.
That's the good spade card.
It means stability, luck,
security...
The nine of clubs
means a job, a situation.
The Queen is a kind woman.
There's a young man, single.
He's next to a diamond card.
There's a romantic project,
but it's upside down.
That means there's a problem.
A girl with long hair.
She's upside down too.
You have to be wary of her.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
That it's upside down.
It's in relation
to the dealer.
They're only cards.
If you draw them,
they're more than that.
You're a bit of a mystic?
I want to stop.
We've started, let's finish.
Come on, the future.
What did they call you before?
The Jewess.
Which is the worst one?
The ten.
Do you like that?
Yes.
What do you want?
To see the Woman Who Laughs.
For sex or just to see her?
To see her first,
then decide.
Inside a room,
you do as you like,
but you see girls here for sex,
the normal way.
I'd like Lea as a doll then.
Come here.
You smell nice, my doll.
Who did you have?
Simon.
And you?
Louis.
Julie, no!
Help me!
Julie!
I want the peach.
Well?
I'll get you!
You have to strip right now.
Catch.
Marie-France, where do
the clients get their money?
In industry, textiles,
paper...
Family fortunes too.
Fortunes of the aristocracy.
Are there a lot
of aristocrats?
Yes.
We get a lot of aristocrats.
What does Louis work in?
Louis is in textiles.
He made his fortune
in textiles.
Michaux has a family fortune.
Charles is a family fortune too.
Who's the richest one?
The richest one?
Charles.
He doesn't spend the most,
but he's the richest one.
Has he been coming long?
Yes, since the days
when I worked at L'Apollonide
Like you do.
My back hurts.
I'm sick of his doll thing.
Don't complain.
There's worse.
I'm not saying that,
just that I'm sick of it.
You do as you want.
You get rid of creeps
with a few pussy hairs.
My whole bush wouldn't do that!
It feels like an eternity
since we had a day out.
It's me.
Give me your cigarette.
All right.
What is it?
I was thinking a Lanvin hat
would suit you.
Go on then, Polo.
Treat me to a hat.
The fresh air loosens you up.
Want a drop of champagne?
Please.
Want some too?
Yeah, okay.
Gently!
Sorry.
Pardon me.
It slipped out.
Calm down, Polo.
Oh, you know...
I'm sorry, it's old age.
This is nice.
Oh, yes!
I feel so good!
I don't think
I'll be here long.
I said that too.
Now look at me.
We'll see.
I don't have any debts yet.
"I understand
your sense of injustice,
"and I've always given you
my support.
"But, as a prefect,
I can't work miracles.
I cannot oppose
a landlord's decision. "
Good evening.
Who's here this evening?
The same ones.
- Still want to see the Jewess?
- Pardon me?
The Woman Who Laughs.
Want to go up to see her?
You can,
but it'll cost you more.
No.
I was a bit tipsy last time.
Who else is there?
Who else...
Sweetness, Clea, Climbing Rose,
Fine Thigh...
Afterwards, women couldn't
compete in the games.
Why not?
Good question.
They were thrown from a rock
if ever they went there.
But now they can go.
They couldn't go
because the athletes were nude.
Now they're dressed.
So women can take part.
Will you go up with me
and another girl?
Who?
Anyone.
You choose.
I don't know.
I'd rather go alone
if you don't mind.
Shall I put you in my will?
Do you want to be in my will?
No.
I want you to stay alive.
If anyone here is alive,
I am.
Good evening.
Ah, Louis!
A drink
or shall I call Samira?
Both.
"I understand
your sense of injustice,
"and I've always given you
my support.
But, as a prefect,
I can't work miracles. "
Thank you.
Some women
have very large breasts.
They could have an accident,
knock themselves out...
Yes, that's true.
They could bandage them.
It's not so much fun.
Fine Thigh.
Fine Thigh...
Clothed or naked?
I prefer you naked.
- It costs more.
- I know.
Talk to me in Japanese.
Go on, make it up.
Make it up.
More.
What does that mean?
It means my tongue
comes towards you.
Slowly.
It slithers across the floor.
It slips under the bed.
It rises up the side of it.
It reaches your feet.
It licks them.
It glides up along your leg.
Along your thigh.
It reaches your sex.
It winds around it.
It swallows it completely.
Sword swallower.
Your Japanese is very good.
Do you want some?
You don't have to smoke it.
You can take a bit and eat it.
It's okay, I know.
I want to see you often.
Won't Clothilde
be angry with me?
I can see more than one girl.
Now stop asking questions
and talk to me in Japanese.
You're very young.
Not that young.
Really?
Not many girls my age
have been fucked in champagne.
Did you like it?
I loved it.
Men never look into the sex
of women enough.
Wonderful.
After one night with you,
I could kill myself.
Say "Ah. "
Good.
What's that spot?
Nothing.
Have you had it long?
It's nothing.
All right.
One month? Two?
No, a few days.
All right.
Any itching?
No.
- No new rashes on your body?
- No.
Let me take a look.
Let me see.
Lie down now
and let me examine you.
Let me see.
Nothing around the anus.
I'll use the speculum now.
If ever I get out of here,
I'll never make love again.
- No...
- Yes.
I have to examine you.
You have to lie down.
- No!
- I have to examine you.
I have to.
Come on.
Now spread your thighs.
No two ways about it.
I can't see your sex otherwise.
Come on now.
Look at me.
You have to lie down.
Lie down and spread your thighs.
You have to do it.
The cervix is fine.
Heavy but normal discharge.
How about your period?
It comes and goes.
When did you last have it?
Two months ago?
Three?
Not long ago.
I forget.
Six months?
You don't have your period
anymore?
I'm not pregnant.
Six months...
I just don't have my period
anymore.
How about your period?
Same thing.
It comes and goes.
And you?
Normal.
And you there?
Mine's fine.
Let me examine you.
Lie down.
- Okay?
- Yes, I'm healthy.
Well?
I'm fine.
I'm healthy.
And the others?
I don't know.
I swear...
What am I supposed to do now?
You think they're not pregnant?
No, I'm sure.
But, I'm sorry,
that girl there has syphilis.
- It's okay. I accept it.
- Bravo.
I'd just like someone
to give me a hug.
I want a macaroon.
What a shit job.
Fucking is a fuck awful job.
It won't be easy tonight.
No.
Have you seen my bracelet?
- Which one?
- The pearl one.
I think I saw it in the box.
I put a charm on her doll.
I got a needle and...
It's not your fault, Samira.
It could have been me or you.
It's the clap.
Samira, go down.
Louis will be here soon.
Madame...
I have my period.
We're too busy.
- Take a cold bath.
- Please...
I can't.
I'm already one girl short
as it is.
You'll have to work more.
Yes, Madame.
And try to show
a little joy tonight.
All right?
Tonight,
just pretend I'm dead.
You really have a tiny head.
So?
A tiny head is pretty,
isn't it?
It's very pretty.
Charming.
You have a tiny head too.
I'm sorry?
The size of your head...
My head is fine and delicate.
I knew it.
A woman called Pauline Tarnowsky
has written a scientific study
on prostitutes.
She says their heads are smaller
than average.
The same is true of criminals.
Really?
I can lend it to you
if you want.
If it's good.
It's very good.
Right now, a normal girl
goes for 300.
400 for a Negress.
- Plus the debts.
- I can't.
Even to keep Julie
without working, I can't.
Paris is too expensive now.
I have a friend
who organizes special evenings.
The Woman Who Laughs
interests him.
I want to pay off your debts.
Five times six.
Eight...
- 30... 40.
- 40.
Here you are.
Five times seven?
No, five times nine.
What time is it?
It's only 8:00.
Go to bed.
You'll look like hell tonight.
Five times nine?
You're still here?
Will you sleep with me?
No.
It's too late now.
Or too early.
I didn't mean sex.
Just sleeping.
I don't want to go home.
I feel bad.
Just sleep then?
At 8:00 a.m.,
there's no more commerce.
You can lie
between Samira and me.
I promise.
I'll be fine between you.
Lea, go to bed.
Sorry.
Good night.
I can't bring myself
to go home.
- Where's Pauline?
- She's asleep by now.
Who with?
Do you mind
if I stay here awhile?
If I go home,
I'll be a wreck.
You've gone off Clothilde?
I don't know.
I adore her, but...
we don't have fun.
I make her sad.
But I'm very fond of her.
I love whores.
I find them wonderful.
They move me.
I'm happy with them.
Terrible, isn't it?
I understand.
I understand you.
It's occupied.
"Anthropometric Study
of Prostitutes and Thieves"
"Pauline Tarnowsky - 1889"
Spread your legs.
So I can see you.
Tighter.
My geisha...
"The prostitute
is a female criminal.
"We observe an encephalon
several millimeters smaller,
"due to the fact
"that prostitutes
have smaller heads.
"Consequently, this means they
have much less brain matter.
"Their weak intelligence
"and mental abnormality
is natural.
"The dull spirit of some
can become stupor in others
and even attain
a state verging on idiocy. "
Get up, Clothilde.
- I'm fine here.
- You are?
Stupefied, you're fine?
You'll end up
in a Marseille brothel
turning tricks
on a vermin-ridden mattress.
No.
Know what I'm going to do?
I'll sell myself
to another house.
For a high price,
so I can pay off my debts.
Of course.
No one will want your debts.
Well, I'll sell my teeth.
A Marseille brothel,
with the clap.
Great.
Fine.
We deserve the clap.
We deserve our punishment.
I've been here 12 years.
The clap will be a nice break.
Be brave.
Good-bye.
My dear Julie...
my little Caca...
it hurts me to write this
because it will hurt you
to read it.
You're ill, my little Julie,
and I wish I was there
to comfort you.
But there are things
I must say.
Don't think I'm abandoning you.
I'd never abandon someone
I cherish as much as you
after all these months.
But I must tell you this.
Our relations must change.
I don't want to catch
your disease.
I never hesitate
to sacrifice myself,
but now that sacrifice
would hurt me and not help you.
You know I cannot pursue
your disease.
I think I have eluded it
as I have no symptoms,
but I'm not safe yet.
I have to wait two more weeks.
Julie, if I were ill,
I would forgive you.
But no one in my family
has ever had such diseases,
and I wouldn't like
to infect others.
Men have secrets
but no mystery,
and I'm so sorry,
my little Julie.
I still love you,
even more now
because you're ill.
Your loving friend, Maurice.
"Men...
"Men have secrets
but no mystery,
"and I'm so sorry,
my little Julie.
"I still love you,
"even more now
because you're ill.
Your loving friend, Maurice. "
Where was it?
In the mail.
Tear it up.
She mustn't read it.
That's really sick.
I can keep her
because he's still paying.
Even if he no longer sees her.
Any news of Pauline?
No.
Is the house closing down?
I don't know.
Does it suit me?
It's funny.
She looks like an old doll.
No, she's too thin.
She's like a big puppet.
But I like her breasts.
Pinch her nipples
to see
if she stops smiling.
Has Pauline left,
or did something happen to her?
Could Madame have sold her
without saying?
Will she sell us one by one?
I don't know.
God only knows
where we'll end up.
Maybe in some seedy brothel,
with revolting clients.
Especially past 25.
Looking at the freak?
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
You too.
I don't want to die.
You're not going to.
I promise.
I want to see Maurice.
He's going to come.
Soon.
I feel your sperm fill me up
and flow out through my eyes.
There are white tears,
thick ones, coating my cheeks.
My mouth is red,
and the white tears
trickle over it.
I don't want to wipe them away.
I cry so much...
I can't stop crying.
You don't have an emerald?
No, I don't have one.
I want to tie you up.
May I?
Shh.
You were on the floor.
I picked you up.
Thank you.
You said something
in your sleep.
What did I say?
"If we don't burn,
"how will the night be lit?
"Michaux...
"my fragment...
meteorite. "
I said that?
Don't be afraid
to express your love.
Don't be afraid.
What's your name?
Madeleine.
No nickname?
Just Madeleine.
Long live France.
Where will they go?
I've sold some
to other houses.
A man has bought Samira.
The others will do
what they can.
Enjoy them while they're here.
I'm not staying.
I'm in no mood for fun.
I just wanted
to give you a kiss.
A new Jeanne Paquin dress?
Yes.
You're ravishing.
Thank you.
Cheers.
My favorite sound.
It's not crystal now,
just glass.
Never mind.
It's still champagne.
You look wonderful.
Look, they're having fun now.
Do it.
Go on.
I attended the opening
of the metro yesterday.
It's horrendous.
It's dark,
the seats are hard,
and it's so grim.
Everyone seemed happy.
Stupidly happy.
They loved crossing Paris
underground!
It's appalling.
I walked back from Porte Maillot
to Palais Royal.
I thought of you.
What will we do without you?
You'll have other experiences.
All the other houses
will be closing too.
It's sad, but too bad.
Today love is out
on the street.
No one can stop that.
What will you do now?
I don't know.
I'm a bit tired.
Promise to stay yourself,
even without L'Apollonide.
Keep the flowers, the music,
the fine dresses,
the color, the champagne,
even in glass...
Make noise, please.
We're going to need it.
Have we met before?
Perhaps.
I'd remember.
What's your name?
Madeleine.
A little perfume...
What are you like under there?
However you want.
How do you want me to be?
I don't know.
Aren't you asking me
what I'm like?
No.
Lea?
Lea's up in a room.
Hear that, Simone?
The fireworks?
It's the fireworks!
Don't be scared.
My pretty Ninon...
It's Bastille Day,
but no one's beheading you.
It's the fireworks!
I want champagne.
Come in.
You really do like it.
I want to stop.
I don't like it anymore.
I'm paying, so I decide.
What will you do now?
I don't know.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player