Why did you leave me?
My love, I am here to fetch you.
You've come back?
According to an age-old belief...
and based on experiences
of people whose friends...
or relatives have passed away...
a dying person often sees the ghosts...
of their loved ones
who are already deceased.
We all have spirits who will fetch
each of us on our last hours.
They are our...
HARBINGERS Of DEATH
Take cover.
Go around them at the back.
Take cover to the left.
Take cover.
Doc, the patient is hyperventilating.
Let's go.
You check.
Careful now.
This way.
Move a bit over there.
Oi!
Why did you let go?
Please be careful.
We're sorry, ma'am.
Hello.
I'm still in Baguio.
Um, family matters.
No, nothing like that.
I had Mama's remains transferred.
Are you really sure of your plans?
That family
is the cause of your Papa's death.
Didn't you tell me yourself...
that even the land
isn't enough to pay...
for my brother's life, your father?
And these papers won't bring
Papa back to life.
I want to end all this.
That is for you to decide on, Louella.
If you really want to renew ties
with Romano's family...
I won't stop you.
But...
make sure that what you're doing
comes from the heart...
because when the time comes...
that everything you know
hasn't been forgotten yet...
and you discover
that you're not ready to forgive...
it might become very difficult for you.
It's 500 pesos.
Okay. Don't forget to finish
Mrs. Lapuz's statue by Friday.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Alright.
Edong, place this in the
storeroom at the back.
Okay, ma'am.
Do it fast.
Who is she?
Oh.
Aunt Menggay.
Louella?
Please come in.
Take a seat, please.
I'll just call Romano.
Make yourselves at home.
Romano?
Come down here.
You have a visitor.
Isabel?
Sister, Louella?
Yes, it's me.
Sister Louella,
why did you leave so suddenly?
Louella.
How are you?
I'm okay. How about you?
Baste.
Yes?
I came here to give this back to you.
That caused the feud
between our families.
How about my debt to your father?
He's no longer here.
I want to end whatever
misunderstanding we all have.
Thank you.
I also came here to tell you that
I have a doctor-friend...
an eye specialist.
Sabel might be interested
to have an eye check up.
Brother, can we see him?
What do you think made Louella
change her mind?
When she came home last year...
on her father's death anniversary.
Linda said Louella kept drinking.
What's more, she was blaming
all of you for his death.
And then she's trying
to patch things up with you now.
I think there's nothing wrong with that.
We've been friends
since we were young.
Well, I think it's high time
everything gets settled.
By the way, Isabel.
I'll have your clothes washed
and then let's pack your bags.
Okay. Thank you.
Do you really want to see
a specialist again?
Why?
Don't you want me to?
It's not like that.
Try not to get your hopes up.
Brother, I'd rather have something
to hope for...
than just missing you.
I won't be able to see again.
Alright.
Romano...
Isabel needs someone
to go with her to Manila.
I'm already old...
and no one will be left to take care
of your family's business here.
I don't want to see
my sister getting hurt.
Is that the real reason?
Or you really don't to leave
the house?
What are you really afraid of?
Nothing.
Romano, your sister needs you.
And this is her only hope.
That's what I've been telling you,
Victor.
You're too generous.
Now, we're the ones in need.
How can you get better now?
Let's not worry about it.
Not worry about it?
Victor, you're very sick.
You have cancer...
and the medications are expensive.
If you didn't allow yourself
be swindle by Romano's father...
then we might have more money now
to buy your medicine.
Baste.
Yes?
Can I hitch a ride with Aunt Lumen
to Manila later?
Yes, of course.
Will Doc Louella mind?
She might not like the idea.
It's okay. What are neighbors for?
I'm just thinking of our bus fare.
I can save it and add
to our funeral expenses.
Baste.
- Sister Louella.
- Please put this there.
Sister Louella. This is Mrs. Lumen.
They're asking
if they can hitch a ride with us.
Brother.
Sister Menggay
wants me to give you this.
Thanks.
I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
You're really going with me to Manila.
But can you please take a bath first?
You smell a little.
It might be embarrassing
especially to Sister Louella.
- Always take care of yourself.
- Okay.
- And remember to pray always.
- I will.
I will.
Good evening, Mrs. Menggay.
- Good evening to you, too.
- Hi Isabel.
I'll put this at the back.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Please take care.
Let me help you with that.
- Thanks Louella.
- Thank you.
Where's your brother Romano?
He'll be here in a minute.
Here he is.
It's a good thing
we were able to persuade him to go.
Wait, why are we stopping?
What are you doing?
I said I just wanted
to hitch a ride with you.
Don't be such a prude.
I'll introduce you to some people
who can build up your career.
Introduce them to me first.
I've heard too many offers already.
Please.
What are you doing? I said stop it.
C'mon, please...
Stop it!
You jerk!
Hey, give me my things!
You're so ugly.
- You creep!
- You will regret if you overact.
What do you think of me?
- I won't settle for someone like you.
- You boasyful!
Go away!
You think you're handsome?
You're so disgusting! Shit!
And your breath stinks!
Stupid.
Oh, well!
Now, where am I?
Oh my God.
Shit.
It's so cold...
Who's there?
Let's ask her to ride with us.
Shit, just when I've managed
to get a ride, the rain stops.
In fairness ha.
Thank you. You're all kind.
Did you know that I'm an actress?
You really are?
Of course!
I have a primetime show
with Dennis Trillo.
I was with him in...
in a scene in a restaurant.
My legs looked so good there.
And my line was,
''may I take your order, sir?''
- That's it!
- Cute, right?
Baste.
Baste!
Mom.
Baste, stop the van!
What happened?
Where is he going?
Romano?
What's happening to you?
Let's go!
Brother,
what really happened a while ago?
Nothing.
I just had a bad dream.
At leat you woke up.
If not, we might be all dead by now.
I don't want to die that way.
I might look disfigured,
especially my skin.
I paid a lot for my face.
It really looks like it.
What were you dreaming of, Romano?
What?
Didn't you just say
you had a bad dream?
Thanks.
I can't remember it.
I'll just go to the ladies' room.
Wow, that looks delicious.
Oh, sorry.
- Romano?
- What was that?
Hi. Looking for something?
Romano...
I'm sorry for the intrusion, Romano.
I just want to help you.
Don't you believe me?
No, Louella.
That's not what I meant.
Is someone there?
Oh...
this is a gift from Carlos.
Mother asked me to go
with Aunt Lumen to Manila.
Her husband died.
It's really hard to accept a death...
especially if it's by accident.
My best friend died.
He killed himself last year.
That's so sad.
Okay, I paid for it already. Let's go.
Let's go.
Wait, Aunt Lumen isn't back yet.
Aunt Lumen?
Aunt Lumen!
We won't disregard
the angle of foul play here.
We'll investigate this further.
But you can't bring the body with you...
still under investigation.
Eric, will you be staying here?
No. I'm coming with you to Manila.
I need to inform my relatives there.
Eric, my condolence.
Thanks, Kristina.
C'mon, smile for me.
There's my house.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Hey handsome, thanks a lot.
I hope we meet again.
Bye!
- Bye!
- Take care.
Bye!
My daughter.
What were you dreaming of, Romano?
Nothing.
Baste!
It's a good thing you woke up.
If not, we might be all dead by now.
I don't want to die that way.
After what happened to my brother...
he didn't leave the house anymore.
Every week, his senior officer
from the military came to our house...
to convince him to go back to service.
But he didn't talk to him.
Do you think he was traumatized
by what happened to him?
Maybe.
Please take a seat.
When we were at the highway...
I felt that he saw something.
Whatever it was, I really don't know.
Aunt Menggay told me that...
my brother went with her
one time to buy groceries.
His face suddenly went blank.
Then he asked her
if they could go home already.
I had an accident when I was little.
I was playing with my brother.
I fell from a tree and hit my head hard.
My eyesight went bad ever since.
We'll do a series of tests again...
to evaluate the condition
of the cranial and optic nerves...
which were probably damaged
as a result of her head injury.
We can also perform laser surgery.
But that's not a guarantee
that we can restore her vision...
It's a 50/50 chance.
I hope that after this,
I can finally be able to see.
I really want to see you
and my brother.
Maybe he's very handsome.
And maybe you're very pretty, too.
And I won't argue with that.
- Thank you.
- Double 7.
- I got flowers.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Still plenty.
- Cheater!
- I lost.
They will look again, eh.
- Open it.
- Oh gosh.
Sister Louella... hold on to the rails.
Here, have some juice.
Thanks.
Eric.
Isabel.
Thank you for coming
to my uncle's wake.
Isabel, sit down here.
Sister, brother, please take a seat.
Thanks.
Any news about your
Aunt Lumen's death?
They say we can get her remains now.
But we're still waiting
for the release papers in La Union.
By the way, we're going back
to Baguio in 2 days.
Sister Louella is thinking
you might want to ride with us.
That's okay. Thanks.
I already talked to my mother.
She said she's going here
to attend her sister's wake.
All of us have someone to fetch us.
When death is near,
they will come to pick us up.
They are the harbingers of Death.
They will come for us
and bring us to the other life.
All of us have someone to fetch us.
When death is near,
they will come to pick us up.
They are the harbingers of Death.
They will come for us
and bring us to the other life.
You... who will come to fetch you?
Damn!
you double-crossed me!
You're stupid!
- There's a fight going on.
- Why?
What's that, what?
What's happening outside?
I don't know.
Isabel?
Isabel!
Sister Louella!
Isabel, open the door!
Eric, what's happening?
When death is near,
they will come to pick us up.
They are the harbingers of Death.
They will come for us
and bring us to the other life.
Death is here now.
Eric?
Why is it wet here?
- Isabel, open it now!
- Isabel!
fric!
Eric, what's happening?
Eric!
Isabel !
Brother, what's going on?
Why has this happened to Eric, too?
This is bad luck.
Why are we experiencing
bad things one after the other?
Romano, I know
you're hiding something to us.
You know something about this.
The incident that happened
in the highway.. .
to Lumen... to Eric.
What really was that?
Why don't you just tell us?
I myself can't understand it.
After my accident...
I went on comatose.
When I woke,
strange things started happening.
When I dreamt
that we were in an accident...
I asked Baste to stop the van.
I saw something.
What did you see?
Spirits.
5 souls.
They were surrounding the van.
What do you mean by "spirits''?
Before Lumen's death.
When we were eating at the canteen...
I saw this spirit again.
Outside the doctor's office.
When Isabel had her eyes checked...
I saw another one again.
That was the soul
I've seen during the wake.
Before Eric's death.
Brother Romano, I know a spiritist.
She may be able to help.
Let's see her tomorrow.
I saw it upstairs, near the table.
Romano, how does it feel
like whenever you see a ghost?
It doesn't seem real.
You think you're just seeing things.
Then your hair starts to rise.
And you suddenly feel light-headed.
You know what, when Papa died...
I always wondered what I would feel
when he shows himself to me.
Will I get scared
or be happy to see him?
I waited and waited
for him but he never came.
I guess I really don't have
the eye to see those things.
The books says that anyone
can see a spirit if he wants to.
You just need to focus.
Concentrate on the room...
in every corner.
Then try to open your eyes
in different ways.
Try to feel everything around you.
Whisper whatever you want
to the wind.
Okay, I'll read it.
I'll go inside now.
Give me one kilo of pork.
One kilo of porkchop.
Hold on, please.
Here.
140.
Excuse me, boss.
Do you know where I can find
Mrs. Elma?
Oh, Mrs. Elma.
She's over there.
Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Excuse me...
are you Mrs. Elma?
Why? What do you want?
Your Mrs. Elma.
Brother Romano, she's Mrs. Elma.
I want to ask you something.
Hurry up. I don't have all day.
Ma'am Elma...
I can see things that I don't
understand.
Do you have money?
Let's go to a place that's more quiet.
follow me!
Hey, faster!
Careful now.
What do you see?
Ever since I woke up...
from being comatose...
I've been seeing spirits.
But now...
they're bothering me.
And everytime I see a ghost...
someone dies.
Like one of our friends...
before she died in the accident.
I'm just thinking of our bus fare.
I can save it and add to our
funeral expenses.
I saw the spirit of her husband.
The other one...
I saw his friend.
My best friend died.
He killed himself last year.
Your 3rd eye is open.
It may have opened during the
accident you encountered.
The spirits you see...
are no doubt the harbingers of Death.
We all have someone to fetch us
when our time comes.
Your brother, sister...
wife...
best friend...
relative.
But why are they after Romano?
Maybe...
they know that Romano sees them.
And they want to tell him something.
That's why I saw them in the tunnel.
The tunnel?
Yes.
We almost met an accident.
But Romano saved us.
I see other spirits, too.
There are more?
If that's the case...
you have cheated death.
Now, Death wants you to pay.
What should we do?
You were given that power to
see those spirits.
And they are here to warn you.
But how can we escape from Death?
What I know...
is that when you cheat death...
you have to pay with death, too.
What are you getting?
What's wrong, Brother Romano?
Romano...
have you seen another one again?
Yes.
He's the old man...
I saw at the highway,
while we're walking.
He's wearing a necklace.
A necklace?
With an animal tooth pendant?
Brother Romano, he's my grandfather.
He was the one who raised me.
Am I next?
Am I going to die?
Romano.
Louella...
go to the van.
Run!
Baste got away.
But is he really safe?
How about us?
Who's next in line?
We need to calm down.
Brother, who else did you see at
the highway.
I saw 5 souls.
The 3 have already reappeared.
There are 7 of us.
This means 2 will be saved?
I saw my mother.
What?
It's either Isabel or I...
who's next.
But who's the 5th one?
A woman.
I don't know who she is.
Her hair covered her face.
And there's another one.
You saw another one?
I didn't see it.
I just heard it?
What did you hear?
I heard a baby crying.
Let's go. We need to see Kristina.
She left her cellphone while in a hurry.
But she'll be here soon.
She's coming from a shooting.
Oh, here she is. Kristina.
Hey, Baste.
My fare.
Romano!
I missed you.
Did you miss me, too?
We need to talk.
I don't remember anything.
Besides, I really don't have a child.
And I don't even have a niece or
nephew who died.
Aren't you forgetting someone?
We haven't had any child deaths in
our family.
I think we're a family with long lives.
Wait, are you really telling the truth?
Kristina, serve them some coffee first.
Ma'am...
please don't take this personally but...
has she never given birth?
I am sure of it.
She doesn't even have a boyfriend.
She's very choosy.
Hey handsome, here's your coffee.
I made this for you.
Kristina, why won't you believe in us?
We'll just go out for some fresh air.
Come, Isabel.
Sister Kristina, please be careful.
How sweet.
Your sister's so nice.
But I don't like the other girl.
She's always frowning at me?
I think she has a crash on you.
What we're saying is true.
We came here...
to warn you.
You know what?
I'm not afraid of dying.
What can I do if my time is up?
Will I fight against Death?
I'll just tire myself out.
I just don't want to die looking ugly.
But if you want to...
look after me...
protect or guard me...
24 hours a day,
I won't stop you.
What did she say?
She still doesn't believe me.
Be careful.
Baste...
let's go back to Kristina's place.
Why? Did you forget something?
Just do what I tell you.
Romano, what's wrong?
I know who has come to get her.
Your daughter had a twin.
Tell me the truth.
How did you know about it?
That's no longer important.
I had to give up the other
because we were very poor.
I chose Kristina because she's
sweeter and more quiet.
What I know is that...
that the people who adopted her
treated her badly.
She got very sick and died
because of this.
Where is Kristina now?
She's in her manager's spa.
Yes, ma'am.
Miss...
- Yes?
- is Kristina here?
Oh, the one who is taking a spa?
Yes, she is.
- Where is she?
- She's inside.
Sir, you can't go in there.
Kristina!
- Sir!
- Kristina!
I'll follow Romano.
Please take care of Isabel.
Don't leave her alone.
How much for everything?
23.
- Here you go.
- Oh, it's a big money.
Don't you have a smaller amount?
Sorry, I don't have loose change.
Okay, wait for me.
What's wrong?
Hey!
If I see a scratch there,
you'll be paying for it!
Let's go! Hurry up!
Kristina!
Help me.
Baste.
Romano!
Romano, please help me.
Kristina?
Kristina!
Kristina! Kristina!
Baste!
Isabel !
- Baste!
- Isabel, please help me!
What's happening to you?
Kristina?
Do you think we will avoid any
accidents now?
We're fighting against spirits
Romano, not humans.
He can do anything he wants.
We can't hide from him.
We are all going to die.
I'm a doctor.
I've seen death.
But not this way, not like this.
I don't want to believe,
but how couldn't I?
We need to do everything to
keep us safe.
You don't understand what Mrs.
Elma told us.
Death is chasing us.
We need to sacrifice a life.
He is after someone alive,
now we need someone in exchange.
What do you want to do?
Kill someone?
Brother...
isn't that...
I'm to blame for all of this.
If it wasn't for me...
we wouldn't have been here in Manila.
Don't think about those things.
It's not your fault.
Go get some rest.
Brother, is mom fetching me or you?
Do you remember that picture?
The drawing in Isabel's hand?
I did that.
Those are stick figures of a family.
A dad and a mom...
and a baby.
Louella...
you don't have to worry about
anything.
I can't see any spirits right now.
That could fetch you.
I told myself before...
that when I have a child...
a boy.
Romano...
that crying baby you heard.
I am being fetched.
What do you mean?
I got pregnant...
It was a bad time for me.
when I was in med school.
I had the baby, my child... aborted.
I aborted the child.
That's why I know that I'm
the next one.
My baby is coming to get me.
He's coming to get me.
Romano, we need to be careful.
Where are you?
Show yourself to me!
Show yourself!
Isabel.
Mom.
Isabel !
That's enough.
That's enough! I can't take it
anymore!
That's enough! Stop it!
Stop it!
That's enough!
Isabel...
what are you doing there?
Brother, please come here.
Go down there.
Isabel.
Brother.
Louella?
I won't die now.
I've already sacrificed a life.
It's all your fault!
It's your fault why Papa is dead now.
Isabel had to pay with her life.
I don't want to die yet.
You killed Isabel?
She can't kill me.
She can't go after me.
I need to stay alive.
You need to die now.
Do you come to fetch me?
I don't wanna die yet.
Subtitles: Arigon
Get away from me!