Why did you leave me?
My love,
I came back to fetch you.
You came back?
According to an ancient belief...
and based on experiences
by people whose friends...
or relatives have passed away...
a dying person often
is visited by the ghosts...
of their loved ones
who have already died.
We all have spirits who will fetch
each one of us in our final hours.
They are our...
HERALDS OF DEATH
Take cover.
- Go around them from the back.
- Take cover on the left.
Take cover.
Doctor, the patient
is hyperventilating.
Come on.
Check applicator.
Careful now.
This way.
Move over there a little.
Oops!
Why did you let go?
Please be careful.
We're sorry, ma'am.
Hello.
I'm still in Baguio.
Um, family matters.
No, no, no,
nothing like that.
Uh, I had mom's
remains transferred.
Are you really sure
of your plans?
That family is the cause
of your Papa's death.
Didn't you tell me yourself...
that even the land
isn't enough to pay...
for my brother's life,
your father?
And these papers won't bring
Papa back to life.
I want to end all this.
That is for you
to decide on, Louella.
If you really want to renew
ties with Romano's family...
I won't stop you.
But...
make sure that what you're doing
comes from the heart...
because when the time comes...
that everything you know
hasn't been forgotten yet...
and you discover that
you're not ready to forgive...
it might become
very difficult for you.
It's 500 pesos.
Don't forget to finish Mrs. Lapuz's
statue by Friday, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Alright.
Edong, take this to the
storeroom in the back.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Do it quick.
Who is this?
Oh.
Hi...
Aunt Menggay.
- Louella?
- Hm.
Please come in.
Have a seat, please.
I'll just call Romano.
Make yourselves at home.
Romano?
Come down here.
You have a visitor.
Isabel?
Sister, Louella?
Yes, it's me.
Sister Louella,
why did you leave so suddenly?
Louella.
How are you?
I'm okay.
How about you?
Baste.
Yes?
I came here
to give this back to you.
That caused the feud
between our families.
How about my debt
to your father?
He's no longer here.
I want to end whatever
misunderstanding we all have.
Thank you.
I also came here to tell you
that I have a doctor-friend...
an eye specialist.
Sabel might be interested
to have her eyes checked.
Brother, can we see him?
What'd you think made
Louella change her mind?
When she came home last year...
on the anniversary
of her father's death.
Linda said Louella kept drinking.
What's more, she was blaming
all of you for his death.
And now she's trying to
patch things up with you now.
I think there's nothing
wrong with that.
We've been friends
since we were young.
Well, I think it's high time
everything gets settled.
By the way, Isabel.
I'll have your clothes washed
and then get your bags packed.
Okay. Thank you.
Do you really want to see
a specialist again?
Why not?
Don't you want me to?
It's not that.
Just don't get your hopes up.
Brother, I'd prefer to have
something to hope for...
besides just missing you,
otherwise I will never
be able to see you.
Alright.
Romano...
Isabel needs someone
to go with her to Manila.
I'm to old for that...
and no one will be here to take
care of your family's business.
I don't want to see
my sister getting hurt.
Is that the real reason?
Or you just don't want
to leave the house?
What are you really afraid of?
Nothing.
Romano, your sister needs you.
And this is her only hope.
That's what I've
been telling you, Victor.
You're too generous.
Now, we're the ones in need.
How can you get better now?
Let's not worry about it.
Not worry about it?
Victor, you're very sick.
You have cancer...
and the medications
are expensive.
If you wouldn't have let yourself
be swindled by Romano's father...
then we might have the money
to buy your medicine now.
Uh, Baste.
Yeah?
Uh... can I catch a ride
with Aunt Lumen to Manila later?
Yes, of course.
What about Doctor Louella?
You don't think she'd mind?
She might not like the idea.
It's okay.
What are neighbors for?
I'm just thinking
about the bus fare.
I could save it and use it
for the funeral expenses.
Baste.
- Sister Louella.
- Please put this in there.
Uh... Sister Louella.
This is Mrs. Lumen.
She was wondering
if we could give them ride.
Brother.
Sister Menggay
wants me to give you this.
Thanks.
I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
You're really going
with me to Manila.
But can you please
take a bath first?
You smell a little.
It might be embarrassing
especially to Sister Louella.
- Always take care of yourself.
- Okay.
- And remember to pray always.
- I will.
I will.
Good evening, Mrs. Menggay.
- Good evening to you, also.
- Hi Isabel.
I'll put this in the back.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Please take care.
Let me help you with that.
- Thanks Louella.
- Thank you.
Where's your brother Romano?
He'll be here in a minute.
Here he is.
It's a good thing we were able
to persuade him to go.
Wait, why are we stopping?
What're you doing?
I said I just wanted
to hitch a ride with you.
Don't be such a snob.
I'll introduce you to some people
who can help you with your career.
Introduce them to me first.
I've heard
too many stories already.
Please.
What're you doing?
I said stop it.
Come on, please...
Stop it!
You jerk!
Hey, give me my things!
You're to damn ugly.
- You creep!
- You're gonna regret this.
Who the hell you think you are?
What'd you think I am?
- You're a bitch!
- Get lost!
You think you're mucho, huh?
You're disgusting!
Ass-hole!
And your breath stinks!
Damn idiot.
Oh, well! Huh?
Now, where am I?
Oh my God.
Oh, shit.
It's so cold...
Who is this?
Let's stop and see
if she needs a ride.
Shit, I finely I get a ride
from someone the rain stops.
In all fairness, thank you.
You're all very kind.
Did you know I'm an actress?
Are you really?
Of course!
I have a primetime show
with Dennis Trillo.
I was with him in...
in a scene in a restaurant.
My legs looked so good there.
And my line was,
"may I take your order, sir?"
- That's it!
- Cute, right?
Baste.
Baste!
Mom.
Baste, stop the van!
What happened?
Where is he going?
Romano?
What's happening to you?
Let's go!
Brother,
what really happened a while ago?
Nothing.
I just had a bad dream.
At least you woke up.
If you hadn't,
we might all be dead now.
I don't want to die that way.
I might look disfigured,
especially my skin.
I paid a lot for my face.
It really looks like it.
What were you
dreaming about, Romano?
What?
Didn't you just say
you had a bad dream?
Thanks.
I can't remember it.
I'm just going to
the ladies' room.
Wow, that looks delicious.
Oh, sorry.
- Romano?
- What was that?
Hi. Looking for something?
Romano...
I'm sorry
for the intrusion, Romano.
I just want to help you.
Don't you believe me?
No, Louella.
That's not what I meant.
Is somebody there?
Oh...
this is a gift from Carlos.
Mother asked me to go
with Aunt Lumen to Manila.
Her husband died.
It's really hard to accept a death...
especially if it's by accident.
My best friend died.
He killed himself last year.
That is so sad.
Okay, I already paid the check.
Come on.
Let's go.
Uh, wait,
aunt Lumen isn't back yet.
Aunt Lumen?
Aunt Lumen!
We're not ruling out
foul play of course.
We'll investigate this further.
But we can't
release the body to you...
until we're finished
with our investigation.
Eric, will you
be staying here?
No. I'm coming with you
to Manila.
I need to inform
my relatives there.
Eric, my condolence.
Thanks, Kristina.
Come on, smile for me.
That's my house.
Uh, guys, thank you.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Hey handsome, thanks a lot.
I hope we meet again.
Bye!
My daughter.
What were you
dreaming about, Romano?
Nothing.
Baste!
It's a good thing you woke up.
If you hadn't,
we might all be dead now.
I don't want to die that way.
After what happened
to my brother...
he wouldn't leave
the house anymore.
Every week, his senior officer from
the military came by our house...
to convince him
to go back into the service.
But he didn't talk to him.
Do you think he was traumatized
by what happened to him?
Maybe.
Please take a seat.
When we were at the highway...
I felt that he saw something.
Whatever it was,
I really don't know.
Aunt Menggay told me that...
my brother went one time
with her to buy groceries.
His face suddenly went blank.
Then he asked her
if they could go home already.
I had an accident
when I was little.
I was playing with my brother.
I fell from a tree
and hit my head hard.
I lost my eyesight and...
haven't been able to see since.
We'll do a series of tests again...
to evaluate the condition
of the cranial and optic nerves...
which were probably damaged
as a result of her head injury.
We can also perform laser surgery.
But that's not a guarantee
that we can restore her vision...
It's a 50/50 chance.
I hope that after this,
I'll be able to see again.
I'd like to see how you
and my brother look.
He's probably real handsome.
And maybe you're
very pretty, too.
And I won't argue with that.
- Thank you.
- Pair of sevens.
- I got a straight.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Still plenty.
- Cheater!
- You lost.
They will look again, eh.
- Open it.
- Oh gosh.
- Sister Louella?
- Hold on to the rails.
Here, have some juice.
Thanks.
Eric.
Isabel.
Thank you for coming
to my uncle's wake.
Isabel, sit down here.
Sister, brother,
please take a seat.
Thank you.
Any news about your
Aunt Lumen's death?
They say we can get
her remains now.
But we're still waiting for
the release papers from La Union.
By the way, we're going back
to Baguio in 2 days.
Sister Louella thought that
you might want to ride with us.
Uh, um...
That's okay. Thanks.
I already talked to my mother.
She said she's going to stay
to attend her sister's wake.
All of us have someone
to fetch us.
When death is near,
they will come to pick us up.
They are the Heralds of Death.
They will come for us
and bring us to the other life.
All of us
have someone to fetch us.
When death is near,
they will come to pick us up.
They are the Heralds of Death.
They will come for us
and bring us to the other life.
And... who will come
to fetch you?
Damn it!
you double-crossed me!
You're stupid!
- There's a fight going on.
- How come?
What's that for?
What's happening outside?
I don't know.
Isabel?
Isabel!
Sister Louella!
Isabel, open the door!
Eric, what's happening?
When death is near,
they will come to pick us up.
They are the Heralds of Death.
They will come for us
and bring us to the other life.
Death is here now.
Eric?
Why is it wet here?
- Isabel, open it now!
- Isabel!
Eric!
Eric, what's happening?
Isabel!
Brother, what's going on?
Why has this happened
to Eric too?
This is bad luck.
Why are we experiencing
bad things one after the other?
Romano, I know
you're hiding something from us.
You know something about this.
The incident that happened
on the highway...
to Lumen... to Eric.
What was that really?
Why don't you just tell us?
I can't understand it myself.
After my accident...
I went in a coma.
When I woke up,
strange things started to happen.
When I dreamt
that we were in an accident...
I asked Baste to stop the van.
I saw something.
What did you see?
Spirits.
Five souls.
They were surrounding the van.
What do you mean by "spirits"?
Before Lumen's death.
When we were eating
at the cafeteria...
I saw this spirit again.
Outside the doctor's office.
When Isabel
had her eyes checked...
I saw another one again.
That was the soul
I've seen during the wake.
Before Eric's death.
Brother Romano,
I know a spiritualist.
She may be able to help.
Let's see her tomorrow.
I saw it upstairs, near the table.
Romano, what's it feel like
whenever you see a ghost?
It doesn't seem real.
You think you're just
seeing things.
Then your hair starts to rise.
And you suddenly feel light-headed.
You know what, when dad died...
I always wondered how I would feel
when he shows himself to me.
Will I be scared
or happy to see him?
I waited and waited
for him but he never came.
I guess I really don't have
the eye to see those things.
The books says anyone
who wants to see a spirit...
can definitely see the spirit,
if they really wanted to.
You just need to focus.
Concentrate on the room...
in every corner.
Then try to open your eyes
in different ways.
Try to feel
everything around you.
Whisper whatever you want
into the wind.
Okay, I'll read it.
I'll go inside now.
Give me one kilo of pork.
One kilo of porkchop.
Hold on, please.
Here.
140.
Excuse me, boss.
Do you know where I can find
Mrs. Elma?
Oh, Mrs. Elma.
She's over there.
Come on.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Excuse me...
are you Mrs. Elma?
Why? What do you want?
Your Mrs. Elma.
Brother Romano, she's Mrs. Elma.
I want to ask you something.
Hurry up. I don't have all day.
Ma'am Elma...
I can see things that I don't
understand.
Do you have money?
Let's go to a place
that's a litte more quiet.
follow me!
Hey, faster!
Careful now.
What do you see?
Ever since I came out...
fom a coma...
I've been seeing spirits.
But now...
they're bothering me.
And everytime I see a ghost...
someone dies.
Like one of our friends...
before she died in the accident.
I'm just thinking
about the bus fare.
I can save it and use it
towards funeral expenses.
I saw the spirit of her husband.
The other one...
I saw his friend.
My best friend died.
He killed himself last year.
Your 3rd eye is open.
It may have opened during the
accident you encountered.
The spirits you see...
are no doubt
the Heralds of Death.
We all have someone to fetch us
when our time comes.
Your brother, sister...
wife...
best friend...
relative.
But why are they after Romano?
Maybe...
they know that Romano sees them.
And they want to
tell him something.
That's why I saw them
in the tunnel.
The tunnel?
Yes.
We almost met an accident.
But Romano saved us.
I see other spirits, too.
There are more?
If that's the case...
you have cheated death.
Now, Death wants you to pay.
What should we do?
You were given that power
to see those spirits.
And they are here to warn you.
But how can we escape from Death?
What I know...
is that when you cheat death...
you have to pay with death, too.
What are you getting?
What's wrong, Brother Romano?
Romano...
have you seen another one again?
Yes.
He's the old man...
I saw him on the highway,
while we're walking.
He's wearing a necklace.
A necklace?
With an animal tooth pendant?
Brother Romano,
he's my grandfather.
He was the one who raised me.
Am I next?
Am I going to die?
Romano.
Louella...
go to the van.
Run!
Baste got away.
But is he really safe?
How about us?
Who's next in line?
We need to calm down.
Brother, who else did you see
on the highway.
I saw 5 spirits.
3 of them
have already reappeared.
There are 7 of us.
This means 2 will be saved?
I saw my mother.
What?
It's either Isabel or me...
who's next.
But who's the 5th one?
A woman.
I don't know who she is.
Her hair covered her face.
And there's another one.
You saw another one?
I didn't see it.
I just heard it?
What did you hear?
I heard a baby crying.
Let's go.
We need to see Kristina.
She was in such a hurry
she forgot her cellphone.
But she'll be here soon.
She's coming from a shooting.
- Oh, here she is. Kristina.
- Hey, Baste.
My fare.
Romano!
I missed you.
Did you miss me, too?
We need to talk.
I don't remember anything.
Besides,
I really don't have a child.
And I don't even have a niece
or nephew who died.
Aren't you forgetting someone?
We haven't had any
childrens' death in our family.
I think we're a family
with a long live expectancy.
Wait, are you really telling the truth?
Kristina, serve them
some coffee first.
Ma'am...
please,
don't take this personal, but...
she has never given birth?
I am sure of it.
She don't even have a boyfriend.
She's very choosy.
Hey handsome,
here's your coffee.
I made this for you.
Kristina, why won't you
believe us?
We'll just go out
and get some fresh air.
Come, Isabel.
Sister Kristina,
please be careful.
How sweet.
Your sister's so nice.
But I don't like the other girl.
She's always frowning at me?
I think she has a crush on you.
What we're saying is true.
We came here...
to warn you.
You know what?
I'm not afraid of dying.
What can I do if my time is up?
Will I fight against Death?
I'll just tire myself out.
I just don't want to die
looking ugly.
But if you want to...
look after me...
protect or guard me...
24 hours a day,
I won't stop you.
Brother...
What did she say?
She still don't believe me.
Be careful.
Baste...
let's go back
to Kristina's place.
Why? Did you forget something?
Just do what I tell you.
Romano, what's wrong?
I know who has come to get her.
Your daughter has a twin.
Tell me the truth.
How did you know about it?
That's no longer important.
I had to give up the other
because we were very poor.
I chose Kristina because
she's sweeter and more quiet.
What I know is this...
that the people who adopted her
treated her badly.
She got very sick
and died because of it.
Where is Kristina now?
She's in her manager's spa.
Yes, ma'am.
Miss...
- Yes?
- is Kristina here?
Oh, the one who's in the spa?
Yes, she is.
- Where is she?
- She's inside.
Sir, you can't go in there.
Kristina!
- Sir!
- Kristina!
I'll follow Romano.
Please take care of Isabel.
Don't leave her alone.
How much for everything?
23.
- Here you go.
- Oh, that's a large bill.
Don't you have anything smaller?
Sorry, I have nothing smaller.
Okay, wait for me.
What's wrong?
Hey!
If I see a scratch on there,
you gonna pay for it!
Let's get outta here!
Hurry up!
Kristina!
Help me.
Baste.
Romano!
Romano, please help me.
Kristina?
Kristina!
Kristina! Kristina!
Baste!
Isabel!
- Baste!
- Isabel, please help me!
What's happening to you?
Kristina?
Do you think we will avoid any
accidents now?
We're fighting against spirits
Romano, not humans.
He can do anything he wants.
We can't hide from him.
We are all going to die.
I'm a doctor.
I've seen death.
But not this way, not like this.
I don't want to believe,
but how couldn't I?
We have to do everything
that keeps us safe.
You don't understand
what Mrs. Elma told us.
Death is chasing us.
We need to sacrifice a life.
He is after someone alive,
now we need someone in exchange.
What do you want to do?
Kill someone?
Brother...
isn't that...
I'm to blame for all of this.
If it wasn't for me...
we wouldn't have come to Manila.
Don't think about those things.
It's not your fault.
Go get some rest.
Brother,
is he fetching you or me?
Do you remember that picture?
The drawing on Isabel's hand?
I did that.
Those are the figures
of a family.
Of a daddy a mommy...
and a baby.
Louella...
you don't have to worry about
anything.
I don't see
any spirit right now.
That wants to fetch you.
I told myself before...
that when I have a child...
a boy.
Romano...
that baby you heard crying.
Is why I'm being fetched.
What do you mean?
I had an abortion...
It was a bad time for me.
when I was in med school.
I got pregnant,
aborted... my baby.
I aborted the child.
That's why I know that I'm
the next one.
My baby is coming to get me.
It's coming to get me.
Romano, we have to be careful.
Who is there?
Show yourself to me!
Show yourself!
Isabel.
Mama?
Isabel!
That's enough.
That's enough! I can't take it
anymore!
That's enough! Stop it!
Stop it!
That's enough!
Isabel...
what are you doing there?
Brother, please come here.
Come down from there.
Isabel.
Brother.
Louella?
I won't die now.
I've already sacrificed a life.
It's all your fault!
It's your fault
why Papa is dead now.
Isabel had to pay with her life.
I don't want to die yet.
You killed Isabel?
She can't kill me.
She can't come after me.
I have to stay alive.
You'll have to die.
You have to die now.
Did you come to fetch me?
I don't wanna die yet.
Stay away from me!