June 26, 2010
A documentary team,
which was filming a documentary about
'The Haunted House Explorers,'
went missing.
The six missing persons are:.
producer Lee Young-joo,
cameraman Choi Gyu-suk,
sound recorder Jung Ji-young,
'The Haunted House Explorers' club members
Lim Wan-soo, Won Mi-jin and Choi Woo-ram.
June 28, 201 0
The production staff,
who went to look for them, found their tapes.
They were badly damaged.
July 5, 201 0
The tapes were digitally restored,
and their last remaining hours
can be witnessed through them.
Hello?
At 4:.40 AM on the day of the incident,
Won Mi-jin's call to the emergency line
was recorded.
Please help,
people are dead here...
Someone's tryni to kyll me!.
This is 'intro'
for the documentary
that producer Lee Young-joo was
working on prior to the incident.
This doesn't look right.
Do you know where you're going?.
Yeah, but GPS is off here.
One day someone called
Mr. Kim came to town,
and said he wanted
to build a factory.
When we asked
what kind of factory,
he said a cookie factory.
He built it and succeeded.
It was doing really well
for a couple of years.
People were slaughtered there.
Mr. Kim's family was butchered.
'Entyre Famyly Found Dead'
The killer?. Not caught yet.
Police just gave up.
It was a grudge,
it was a robbery,
so many possibilities popped up,
but there weren't any evidences
nor any leads.
Killer didn't kill just one person,
but five people.
I don't know how
he could sleep at night.
Then... Mr. Kim had an affair
with a female worker.
His wife didn't know
about the affair,
but when she found out,
tragedy struck.
Just before his family was killed,
he had a relation with the secretary,
and had a big fight with his wife.
You could hear it from a mile away.
But...
after that incident...
the secretary disappeared.
She was reported missing,
we filed her missing.
But if that person
is not found in 60 days,
she's automatically
classified as deceased.
And the detectives in charge of the case
halted the investigation.
She was presumed dead.
One day the female
worker just vanished.
So the rumor was... it must've been
the president's wife who killed her.
People said the ghost
of the secretary
killed the president's entire family,
and that the body of the secretary's buried
inside the puddle beside the factory.
Afterwards,
the ghost would come out
wearing white dress
and messy hair, screaming...
On rainy days, steam would rise
from the puddle.
But when you touch the
surface even in the winter,
there's absolutely no temperature.
Hot water's supposed to be hot.
That shop must be it.
It's a haunted house...
Just leavel.
Head of the village thought
he had to do something,
so he called a shaman for an exorcism,
it was a huge exorcism.
But he passed out foaming
at the mouth.
Then they heard the body
was in the puddle
so the police called in
a hydraulic shovel
to dig the puddle.
But it crashed and the operator died.
After the rumor of ghost appearing
from there, no one went near it.
It was quiet for
a few years but
a new rumor started
several days ago.
They say kids saw
a bleeding female ghost
while playing there.
And one of them
went crazy afterwards.
It's that corner shop, yeah,
that shop owner's daughter.
She was a smart kid but she became
an idiot after going there
with her friends.
You should not go there.
You'll not come out alive.
The ghost will possess
whoever enters the house.
It will kill you
without you knowing,
no one comes out alive.
Possessed by ihosts
THE HANTED HOASE PROJECT
The following is shot
by producer Lee Young-joo
and cameraman Choi Gyu-suk
during their trip to the house prior
to the main shoot.
I think we're lost...
Should I call him?.
Yeah, do it.
Hold on...
Do you know where you're going?.
Ah, hello?.
Wan-soo?. Oh, hi.
We're looking for the house but
we can't find it with your directions.
We're passing Bokwang Steel right now.
- Yeah, head straight...
- Look out, a truck.
One moment.
The road's really rough here...
A temple sign straight ahead?.
Then turn left?.
Hold on...
Is it beside the building
with blue roof?.
How would he know like that?.
- I'm not sure...
- Over there, we found it.
Ah, I found the temple sign.
Yeah, that's it...
Great, thank you.
We're here.
How do you find a place like this?.
That's what I'm saying.
Did the intro come out all right?.
It has to be good...
I have to debut with this.
All right.
You'll be big help.
Didn't the shaman
say there's a ghost?.
That would be nice.
'Chanisoo Food, InC.'
Gyu-suk, the sign over here.
Safety line's in the way.
- Should I cut it?.
- Yeah.
This ain't too bad.
Isn't your camera still on?.
Huh?. What the...
Something there?.
No, nothing.
Gyu-suk, hurry up, let's go.
This place is really grim...
This must be the puddle
where the accident took place...
where that hydraulics
operator got hurt.
It was like this for 1 0 years...
Do you think there really is
a body down there?.
You think it's real?.
I doubt it.
What the... an attic room?.
I guess old houses had these.
I'll go check it out.
Yeah?. Okay.
It's very narrow.
Need help?.
Up you go.
- Be careful...
- Damn... so dustyl.
Careful.
Have fun!
Ah! Shit!
Hey, are you okay?.
Gyu-suk, I'm gonna
look around outside.
Yeah.
- Are you in charge here?.
- Who are you?.
Are you in charge?.!
- No, I'm not...
- Turn that damn camera off!
Sir, just a moment!
We're planning to
shoot something here.
Shoot what?.
We're here to check out
the location of our doc.
There's an online club that explores
these haunted houses...
Turn that damn thing off!
You son of a bitch!
He's not shooting.
- A documentary?.
- Yes sir.
What kind of doc?.
Leave. Both of you.
Who are you?.
Are you the current owner?.
Leave! I said leave
the fucking premise!
No need to swear at us.
Couldn't you let us film?. We...
I don't think he's the owner...
He looks crazy.
Yeah, crazy all right.
What a basket case.
Godammit...
Hello?.
Yeah, what?.
We came down to see the place.
Yeah.
Whatever, it's weird here.
Some asshole just came
and bitched at us.
And the camera
doesn't go into standby.
Then I scraped my leg.
Yeah.
We'll talk when I come back
after the shoot.
Yeah, yeah.
It's on again...
What is that?.
'Another Happy Day!. '
'Always HyiyenyC'
Shit...
What the...
Damn it!
Huh, what's wrong with this?.
Gyu-suk, what happened?.
Are you okay?.
This is edited footage of the
restored tape found at the scene.
How's the camera?.
Is it fixed?.
Yeah, it's fine.
Absolutely sure?.
Yep!
Why aren't they here already?.
Shouldn't you call them?.
Hello!
Oh, hi there!
I'm sorry we're late.
It was a bit confusing getting here.
But we met around here last time.
Yeah, but it was still confusing...
I'm sorry.
Okay, let me introduce you to
our cameraman.
- And our sound recorder.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
Is it just two of you?.
No, there's one more...
She's not here yet?.
Where is she...
We live far away from each other
so we decided to meet up here.
She said she wasn't far.
- Is that so?.
- Yeah.
- She'll be here soon.
- Ah, there she is.
Mi-jin! Over here!
Yep, that's the one.
You sure have a lot of luggage.
We'll be staying overnight.
Hello.
- Hurry up!
- Hurry!
- So we're all here then?.
- Yeah, everyone's here.
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you!
We'll be on our way soon,
so... Iet's make a great show!
Sure!
We'll do our best!
Thank you!
Okay, Wan-soo,
could you briefly introduce your team?.
- Right now?.
- Yeah, one at a time.
Ah, okay.
First of all,
this is our club's youngest,
'Black Widow', aka Won Mi-jin.
Hello.
She's the most
beautiful girl in our club.
Beside him is Choi Woo-ram,
or 'Horror Master'.
Lastly I'm the club administrator,
'Ghost Hunter' Lim Wan-soo.
Thank you.
Before we leave,
I would like to conduct
individual interviews.
I'd like to ask you about the expedition
so answer them naturally.
Sure thing.
How was this expedition organized?.
Our club was formed in 2003
and has been active since then.
Currently there are over a thousand
registered members.
But those who participate
in expeditions are about 40-50.
We have regular expeditions with
the entire members every year.
Or with a core group
for the purpose of research.
In this case, think of it as a field
investigation with permanent members.
- So you're all permanent?.
- Yes.
Is it usually three of you?.
Well, Woo-ram and I are
the regulars in today's expedition.
We often swap one or two members
pending expedition conditions.
So this time,
we decided to go with three members.
I see. How many members
are usually enough?.
We take photos and
investigate with equipment,
so it's different every time,
but usually two or three.
Like today?.
Yes. We brought six members
at one time,
but it was hard to concentrate
with so many people,
so three is just right
for the purpose of field investigation.
Okay!
Mi-jin, during the interview,
you could look at me or the camera.
Let's do it!
I heard this is your first expedition,
how do you feel?.
Um, well... A little excited
and intimidated
but I really want to see a ghost.
I've only observed through
writings or pictures at our site...
It's okay,
just say what you feel.
I forgot...
You've only seen pictures,
how would you feel
if you see one in person?.
I don't think seeing it in person would be
as scary as the writings and photos
I've seen at our club...
I can't do this.
Okay, I heard this is your
first expedition, how do you feel?.
I'm excited and intimidated but
I really want to see a real ghost.
And it wouldn't be as scary
to see it myself
than the writings and
photos I've seen online.
Is that okay?.
Yeah, that's great.
When did you first get interested
in ghost expeditions?.
Yeah, I've always enjoyed
horror movies and thrillers,
and I wondered what it would be like
to experience it myself.
So it was around high school?.
That's when I started.
Wan-soo, or Ghost Hunter,
I met him and learned a lot from him.
It was like that for a while,
but I'll be drafted to military soon.
So I told him,
we should go somewhere hardcore.
He said there was a place where no one
dares to enter because it's so haunted.
That's how I first heard
about this place.
I got very excited when I heard
we're really going there.
Was there a particular reason
for choosing this house?.
Yes, after hearing about the place,
I checked it out while passing by.
It was during the day,
but it still felt very weird.
But most of all, I took a picture there
and something was caught in it.
A picture?.
Yes. I posted it up
on our club once.
There was a lot of debate,
and Wan-soo and
I talked about it,
and he said this would be
our next expedition.
That's why I'm very excited.
Could we see the picture?.
I don't think it's a good idea
to show the picture here.
Perhaps next time...
Why?.
It's a picture that was pulled down...
You said you would show it to us.
Is it that reflection
on the window?.
Yes.
It kind of looks like a face.
Doesn't it?.
I knew it was a ghost right away.
When you took this,
was there anyone around the house?.
Nope, I was all alone.
'The Haunted House Explorers'
We'll get a shot of you guys arriving.
Woo-ram, right?.
Yes.
You'll enter from
that side with her,
Woo-ram, I mean Wan-soo, you'll
greet them from here and get in the car.
Okay, okay.
Ms. Jung, please get ready.
We'll begin now!
- Please go ahead, Wan-soo.
- Okay.
Over here. Good to see you.
Hey!
- Didn't sleep well?.
- Shoot inserts of signs as we go
Iike you're doing now.
There'll be plenty of things to shoot.
Wan-soo, how many expeditions
have you done?.
Last year I think l...
Have you had lunch yet?.
Yeah, we had some.
Why don't we stop by at a rest stop
and get some snack for the road?.
Walnut cookies! Walnut cookies!
- Closer?.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- How's this?.
- Yeah, lower it a bit.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- Let's start with them entering.
- Producer, could you check the angle?.
Careful, careful.
Floor's slippery so watch your feet.
Who stepped on this beforehand?.
Why must we go through here?.
Okay?.
Here, over here.
Look around...
Tons of dust so be careful, Mi-jin.
It's asbestos all around.
Are you all right?.
What happened?.
Wan-soo, we'll get a shot
from inside.
Please do what you just did,
look around and flash the light,
see what's on the floor
and on the walls.
- You got it?.
- Yep, yep.
And look as natural as possible.
If you're expressionless,
it'll look dull on the screen.
Shine the light, look intrigued
and use a lot of gestures.
- Okay, okay.
- Let's do it.
- We'll start beforehand.
- Okay.
- Give us a sign!
- One sec.
Producer Lee, can you ask Wan-soo to
not point the flashlight at the camera?.
Okay, I got it.
- Everyone! Wan-soo!
- Yeah?.
When we shoot, could you not
point the flashlight towards the camera?.
Point it at the wall
or the ground.
- Okay!
- Let's shoot!
- Yeah!
- Ready?.
Yep.
Camera!
Hold on!
- What?.
- Am I in the shot?.
No, but you can go in deeper.
Okay, let's begin.
Sound!
- Is sound ready?.
- Roll!
Cue!
Let's go this way.
Mi-jin, dust will fly everywhere
if you touch that.
It's covered in asbestos, remember?.
It's bad for your hands too.
Mi-jin, cue!
Ms. Jung, be careful.
Watch your head.
This looks like kitchen.
Ouch!
Hey, be careful!
You good?.
Over here,
the dining hall's here.
That cracked mirror looks
like a kid's face.
Wow! That's amazing.
Come.
Hold it up like this... Whoa!
Be careful.
Mi-jin, don't wander around,
it might be dangerous.
Hold on, I'll step on it first.
- Are you okay?.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
It just sounds loud.
Here, here. Watch your feet.
Keep rolling, they look
natural resting like that.
Hey kitty!
Tired?. Feeling okay?.
Drink some water and rest a bit.
- We'll rest some and move on.
- Drink some water.
Washroom?. Go ahead.
Thank you.
- Hey! Hey!
- What's going on!
How?.!
I'm... fine.
- Woo-ram!
- I'm sorry.
I was so startled before.
Who does a prank like that?.
Only in grammar school.
They're just kids.
- They feel like kids.
- Yeah.
Maybe I can plant some tricks,
we might get some good reaction shots.
You could do that for the night shoot.
Yeah?. Okay.
Almost there.
- Over there, a door!
- We're here!
Let me explain the layout
of the premise.
That right there is...
What's that over there?.
That?. It's storage.
Oh, not the factory?.
This building is the
owner's private residence.
I see...
We'll spend the night here...
What about that?.
And that's the employees' dorm.
Interesting layout over there.
I can't quite figure out whether
that's a storage or factory.
Careful with second floor,
don't go up there alone at night.
It's dangerous.
Can't see anything at night.
- Sir! Let's take a picture!
- We have to take a group photo!
Um, l...
- Just one picture! Please! Come!
- Ms. Jung, join us.
Sir! Sir!
Take a photo with us!
- No, I'm fine.
- It's to commemorate.
No, it's okay.
Then, could you take the photo?.
Could you do that?.
Is it just point and shoot?.
Yeah just click the button.
- Wan-soo, over here.
- Stand beside me, Ms. Jung.
It's a special occasion.
Strike a pose everyone.
Ready?.
Two, three!
Done.
Thank you.
- Will you upload it?.
- No, not to our site.
What's wrong with this?.
We'll only upload what we take.
This is called elord.
This is usually used by
those practicing feng shui
in order to find water underground.
So when presence of spirit
or water is detected,
the rods spread apart like so.
This is called EMF detector.
It's originally used to
detect electromagnetic waves,
but we use it to detect magnetic field
released by astral bodies,
and check it with this screen here.
This is a thermal camera.
Think of it as a thermometer
in a camera form.
Hypothetically, you would see
the shape of ghosts with it.
Woo-ram, have you seen a ghost?.
I haven't but my grandma
has seen them though.
Grandma?.
Yes. She was known
to possess such energy.
So I've heard many ghost stories
from grandma when I was young.
That's probably why
I think ghosts exist.
- Will you switch to different angles?.
- No, no. We'll follow them.
How's a shot from inside
then another following them?.
Sure, but should we go in
after the sun sets?.
- Am I doing this right?.
- Yeah.
Hm?. It's spreading.
What?.
Step aside for a sec.
Weird.
- Mi-jin?.
- Yes?.
Could you open that closet?.
I don't want to do it...
Something wrong?.
- It's fine, try it.
- No, I don't want to.
It's nothing.
No.
Wan-soo, could you open it then?.
Sure... Hold this.
Here we go.
Could you lift up the clothes there?.
- Down here?.
- Yeah, yeah.
I gotta put on my gloves.
Why the gloves?.
It'll get really dusty.
It doesn't suit you.
Gyu-suk! Gyu-suk!
Come out now!
Please come out!
- Gyu-suk!
- Come out! Come out!
- Go!
- Mi-jin!
- Gyu-suk!
- Come out!
- Was anyone outside?.
- What just happened?.
Did you see that?.
Did someone throw something
from outside?.
Did you capture all that?.
- Yeah.
- Got it?.
- Ms. Jung?.
- I got the breaking sound.
How...
- Wasn't anybody outside?.
- Are you okay, Mi-jin?.
Mi-jin, you okay?.
- I think...
- I think the DP should go in alone
and shoot some footages.
Let's wait till tomorrow morning,
when it's bright.
I think that's the best way.
No, that's not right.
I'm just concerned about
the kids getting hurt.
Wan-soo, we can't do that.
We'll go in and shoot first.
Go on.
Hold on a sec.
What?.
I should've done this before.
What is that?.
- Spraying salt will help repel ghosts...
- Really?.
- Okay, ready.
- Let's go.
Hey! Hey!
Take the camera.
Ji-young, are you okay?.!
Oh my god!
Ji-young!
Quickly!
Are you okay?.
Ji-young, catch this!
- Gyu-suk, be careful!
- Grab it!
Are you okay?.
Over here!
Grab it!
Go find some towel for her.
Are you okay?.
Take this.
Producer Lee!
Please turn the camera off!
Turn it off!
Here, kitty!
Kitty!
- You okay?.
- Uh, yeah.
Are you shooting inserts?.
Come down.
It was a family of five.
4-year old, and 1 2-year old daughters
were found stabbed in their rooms.
And the 4-year old son
suffocated in the iron pot.
Mom's charred body was
discovered in the kitchen.
Father and president
of the factory Mr. Kim
was found hanging by his neck
in the second floor of
that building.
It happened on
a long holiday weekend,
so no one was at the factory.
Thus the bodies were
discovered late.
Police stated that
someone held grudge
against the family
but no one was arrested.
Another thing is, distant family
tried to sell the factory,
but probably due to the incident,
there weren't any buyers.
So the premise remained untouched
exactly as you see here,
since the lMF era 1 0 years ago.
Wait, wait, Mi-jin.
Huh?.
It's so cold.
Is that good?.
Yes!
Ms. Jung?.
Yeah?.
Is Gyu-suk there?.
He's not here.
They'll be tired then.
I'm about to pass out.
Have you caught a cold?.
No.
- We look like caterpillars.
- Why aren't you sleeping already?.
We need a shot of you sleeping.
Okay! We can do that!
Please lay down for one minute.
Okay!
Mi-jin! Okay!
- One minute.
- Yes.
Woo-ram, please.
It's so cold!
Oh... Hold on... Hold on...
Producer! Producer Lee!
Yes?.
Could you come up for a minute?.
- Why?.
- Just a minute.
Go on.
I'm picking up strange noise,
I think you should check it.
What strange noise?.
Where is this coming from?.
I think it's from over there.
Come downstairs,
we need to talk.
Wan-soo, lay down
for one minute, okay?.
Okay.
Wan-soo, which way?.
Up and turn right.
What the heck?.
What are you doing now?.
This is something we do
on every expedition.
Think of it as a spell that will
bring out the ghosts living here.
We put the rice
at the bottom like this,
and light the candle on top of it.
Then,
cover the pot with this paper and
receive message from ghost through soot.
It's a superstition.
I'll be back.
- Okay, starting timer!
- Be careful!
Where are you going?.
I'm on a mission to find an object
at the site of murders.
We hide something
for each other to find.
That's what I have to do.
What do we do while waiting?.
Check the time,
- and see how long he takes.
- No, not that...
Hey, I found it!
Good job!
Why did you hide it there?.
Scared the hell out of me.
- Stopping timer.
- How long did I take?.
3 minutes and 8 seconds.
Not too bad.
It was pretty quick.
You did well.
- Mi-jin, it's your turn.
- You're up.
- I really have to go alone?.
- Of course!
- He did it on his own.
- Yeah, it was just me.
Are you ready?.
Don't be nervous!
I'm ready!
Mi-jin! Mi-jin!
Mi-jin! Are you okay?.!
Mi-jin! Snap out of it!
Mi-jin! Wake up!
Take her shoes off!
Is there water?.
Woo-ram, check the bag!
She's not breathing!
Are you calm now?.
Yes.
Would it be okay if I interview you
about what happened?.
Okay.
Ground was damp...
When I sat down,
the ground was damp.
I think my hand got wet.
I shook the water off
with my fingers.
Then... there was total silence.
It was quiet for a moment...
Suddenly... suddenly
I had a weird sensation...
Into my pants...
Pants?.
Like something came in and out.
What went inside your pants?.
I don't know...
Can you describe
the texture or feeling?.
Tell us about that.
It was hair...
Hair?. Are you sure?.
Hair... Iong hair...
Did you see what color it was?.
It was hair...
Just hair?.
I think it was just hair... hair...
Could you explain
a bit more in detail?.
Did you see it?.
Do you remember
what kind of hair it was?.
- It was... human hair...
- One moment.
I think it's best we
continue this later.
Could you do that later?.
Please turn it off.
Please don't...
Can't you see she's sick?.
Turn the camera off.
Don't! I said don't shoot!
Mi-jin! Mi-jin!
Slowly,
drink slowly.
Take it easy.
That's enough!
Woo-ram, go to the car
and bring some meds.
- Meds?.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Hurry up!
Mi-jin, are you okay?.
What are you doing?.
What's wrong?.
What?.
I'm leaving...
Mi-jin, where are you going?.
Wait a minute, will you?.!
Mi-jin, you're not well,
you shouldn't leave in this condition.
Rest up.
Take a break and go.
Yeah, where will you go
in the middle of the night?.
Ms. Jung, we should leave together.
We can't continue.
You think this is a joke?.
Then how can we go on
at this point?.
Mi-jin, wait!
You were very startled earlier.
Come in!
What was that?.
I think it came from upstairs?.
Just leave! Run outside!
- Wait...
- What?.
- How can we just leave him there?.!
- Just leave for now!
Find the exit first!
- No signal here!
- Hurry!
- What's going on?.
- Why are we back here again?.!
What is that?.
There! There!
Something's wrong here!
Damn it! This door's locked!
What?.
Shit!
Anyone out there?.!
Go!
Producer!
Anyone outside! Please!
We were just here!
All right!
We'll never leave...
We have to find the exit!
Mi-jin, snap out of it!
We're locked in...
Wait a minute.
Wan-soo!
Where's Wan-soo?.!
Wan-soo! Wan-soo!
Where did he go?.!
Please help...
Mi-jin, save me...
Please help me, please!
Mi-jin, please...
Help me...
Mi-jin...
Gyu-suk...
Is that you?.
Mi-jin!
Thys ys 911.
Hello?.
What's your emerienCy?
Please save me,
people are dead here...
Someone's trying to kill me...
Please stay Calm...
Leave! Leave!...
I told you to leave!
Leave!
We've lived here
for about 30 years.
Yes, that's about right.
1 5 years ago, someone came to town
and wanted to build a cookie factory
and built Changsoo Food.
His family arrived
and they were doing well.
But there was a female employee.
There was a rumor that she had
an affair with the president
but there weren't any evidences.
Suddenly the employee disappeared.
Another rumor went around
that the wife had killed the woman.
There was a big puddle
behind the factory.
Another rumor said
the wife had killed
the employee and
dumped the body there.
Mr. Kim's family was butchered.
When she first disappeared
no one took any actions,
but once the family was killed,
everyone took notice, even the police.
any witnesses and evidences,
neither for the disappearance
of the employee nor
the killing of the
owner's family.
Then people started saying that
a ghost appears beside the puddle.
The ghost would appear
and disturb villagers,
and on rainy days
steam would rise from the puddle.
Some people say that they've seen the ghost
or a woman with disheveled hair.
Most people left town
and moved far away.
Aside from several elders, who can't leave,
there's no one left here...