Are you mad?
Why did you come here?
Isabella might see us...
- Do you have any?
- No
I can't stand it
I can't stand it any more
Don't be like that, Franco.
Have you asked Isabella?
I had a fight with her
Damn her, she even stole the bit I had.
Try to hold out.
We'll find some when I finish work.
Trust me, I'll help you.
Go now.
I'm counting on you.
Thanks. I'll be waiting.
Isabella, your scarf!
Thank you -Bye!
What's wrong?
The sign's come off again.
Do you want me to fix it tonight?
No, not tonight.
Do it tomorrow.
As usual,
Isabella's late again.
What's wrong with her?
It's the third time.
No need to get upset.
Just hit her with a fine.
I certainly will, and I'll fire
her if she's as late as yesterday.
- Good night, Madam.
- Good night.
Nicole!
Look at this dress!
Take more care.
We have another show tomorrow.
Okay, I'll be more careful.
Always in a hurry to leave.
You girls think of nothing else.
What does she want?
Being a widow is hard for her.
Isabella!
No thanks
How long where the lights out?
Ten minutes.
How long had she
worked for you?
About 2 years.
What was she like?
She was very lively.
Rather undisciplined,
but I can't criticize her.
Do you know if she had
many friends?
I can't help you much,
Inspector. I'm the administrator.
Ask the two girls
who lived with her.
Unbelievable! It's awful.
It still hasn't sunk in.
Inspector Silvestri,
Countess Cristina, the owner.
Good morning.
Haven't we met before, Madam?
Or am I mistaken?
Yes, actually we have met.
After my husband's accident.
Precisely...
It was a car accident.
I imagine you can help.
You'll know all about your girls.
This isn't a boarding school!
I don't know or care
what they do after they leave.
Well... I'll go into the studio.
- Will you excuse me?
- Certainly.
Come now, Peggy.
Stop crying.
What time was it when you
went out to fix the sign?
About seven. The banging
bothered Ms. Cristina.
So I went out to fix it,
but it was a patch-up job.
I protest! Mr. Morlachi,
I demand an explanation.
As soon as I entered
the villa,
these men grabbed me.
- Ask the Inspector.
- Inspector? - Calm down.
Why are you here?
- I'm Marquis Riccardo...
- Yes, but answer my question.
He came to get me.
He's my fiance.
Fiance!
What's so funny?
We live together.
You knew Isabella?
Isabella?
You introduced us once, didn't you?
Yes, let's say I knew her,
but only by sight.
I see.
Come on, Peggy...
Be brave.
She's the only one
who seems distressed.
They were good friends.
- You lived together?
- Yes.
Who did your friend
go out with?
I don't know.
Leave her alone. Everyone
knows who Isabella's lover was.
- Who are you?
- Cesare Lazzarini, designer.
Will you give me the name?
- The lover's name. - Franco Scalo,
the famous antique dealer.
- Police. Is the Inspector here?
- In there.
I assure you, I know nothing.
Excuse me for a moment.
It's be confirmed.
- So, shall I go?
- Yes, go.
So...
What sort of relationship did
you have with Isabella?
We were friends.
Or lovers?
I have a confession,
but don't be shocked.
I don't believe in everlasting
relationships.
I understand.
Do know know what this is?
No, I don't.
What is it?
Cocaine.
It was found in the house
of your friend Isabella.
At Isabella's?
So you didn't know?
No.
Never mind.
But I must ask you
to remain at my disposal.
I'll see you again.
Autumn evening
Turn around
All right, you can go.
Quickly, now!
What's wrong?
This was for poor Isabella.
- Yes...
- Now who'll wear it?
- Let me see. Peggy...
- No, please, I can't.
Don't cry
or your make-up will run.
- Greta, you wear it.
Sorry, but I can't.
- Don't be silly.
- It'll be bad luck.
- Someone has to.
- I will, Madam.
Hurry up.
That's no surprise.
She's such a cynic.
Ok, you may go.
Hurry up. Good. Now walk.
Just a minute!
Something's missing.
The green brooch.
No problem
Where is it?
Isabella brought her own.
She kept it in a box there.
Here it is.
Look what I found!
Isabella kept a diary.
It sounds interesting.
""He's a man who"
"stirs deep feeling in me.""
"-"I would die for him.""
- Show me.
- We don't have the right...
- Are you all mad?
This isn't the time.
Go on, get ready!
We should give this
to the police.
I found it and I'd like to hand it in
myself, if you don't mind.
As you wish.
Hello?
Hello Franco!
Why didn't you come?
I didn't feel well.
You know why.
Yes, but try to come right away.
I got some.
And listen, Franco.
I found a diary.
- Isabella's diary.
- Isabella's? Who else knows?
Everyone, unfortunately.
I realized too late it might
be compromising you.
I kept it and said
I'd take it to the police.
Good, then we'll have time to
take a look at it.
- I'll come straight over.
- You sound very sick, Franco.
Franco!
Franco? Can you hear me?
Yes, Nicole.
Sorry, I can't breathe. But you
have some, so I'll be better soon.
I'll be waiting.
Hurry girls!
Greta, you're next.
- Everything okay, Marco?
- Yes, Madam.
Where were you?
I'm here.
I have to do everything myself
around here.
Nicole!
Nicole! You're wanted on the phone.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
- Hello?
- Is that you, Nicole?
- Yes, who's this?
- It's Franco.
I can't come there.
I'm too sick.
Please come now!
I'm suffocating.
I can't get away right now.
All right, I'll do my best.
I'll try to come right away.
That's fine.
Peggy, Franco's sick. I have to
go to him immediately.
Lend me your car.
But the show isn't over.
So? Give me the keys
but don't let anyone see you.
Peggy!
- What are you doing?
- Just getting my hanky.
The alarm's
in the glove box
Ok! Thanks
Franco?
- Have fun but don't be too late
- Don't worry
Marco!
I want to stay and keep you
company till Nicole gets back.
Aren't you scared of
being home alone?
I'm very tired and I'd like
to go straight to bed.
But you'll have to stay up till
Nicole returns your car.
Please.
All right. As you wish.
Come on.
Thank you.
I couldn't leave you.
I'd have to worry about you,
alone in that house.
Clarice, you're still here?
Good evening, Miss.
Yes, I've just finished.
Isn't Miss Tao Li with you?
No, she'll be back later.
Clarice is our guardian.
Well, I'll be going. The dinner
is warming in the oven.
And Miss Tao Li's concotion
is ready for her to warm up.
Thank you, Clarice.
See you tomorrow.
Peggy...
- You never listen to me.
- I do listen!
You don't. And I'm tired of
telling you the same thing.
I've told you a thousand times.
I'm afraid I've fallen in love
with you.
But you don't care, why?
Calm down and come over here.
You see...
I'm not well.
I know you think I'm nuts,
and that drives me crazy.
I'm sick, unhappy...
Don't be like that.
I'm your friend.
Cheer up.
I'll take a cigarette.
- No, stop! Don't!
- I just wanted a cigarette.
What have I done?
I'll get it
or you'll mess up my bag.
Here.
Hello?
Hello, it's Inspector Silvestri.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm calling about your car.
We found it abandoned.
Has it been stolen?
No, I lent it to my friend Nicole.
Yes, she had to visit a sick friend.
Is something wrong?
I'd prefer not to do it over
the phone. May I come over?
Very well, I'll be there.
What's up?
They have my car but no Nicole.
God, what's happened?
The inspector is coming?
Yes, to see me.
Then I'll leave. I don't want the
police to find me with you.
Yes, it's better if no one knows
you were here.
Yes, it's better.
Especially for you.
- I'm sorry. See you tomorrow.
- Till tomorrow.
""I caught Peggy"
"stealing 100,000 lira from my bag.""
""She cried"
"and said she needed it.""
""She's pregnant"
"but can't handle the scandal.""
""I felt sorry for her, so I loaned"
"it to her""
""Tomorrow I'll ask the bastard"
"for 200,000 liras.""
""Where is the diary?""
I burned it!
Miss Peggy...
Good evening.
I know it's late to be visiting,
but it's urgent.
Don't worry. Do sit down.
What's this about?
Charles, you may go.
I just got back and found
Nicole in my shop...
- Murdered!
- My God!
I went to pick up Nicole...
You remember...
we bumped into each other.
I looked everywhere
but I couldn't find her.
So I went back home.
Believe me, I'll never
forget what I found.
Excuse me...
...but why did you come here
instead of the police?
Nicole was my friend.
She was killed in my shop.
The police are sure to blame me.
I need an alibi.
You must help me!
Me? Why do you ask me?
Because you're in
as much trouble as I am.
We must say we were together
till we left the fashion house.
I'll vouch for you
if you vouch for me.
It's in both our interests.
You're mad!
There's no reason
they'd suspect me.
You're the one in the fix.
Maybe you really did kill her.
No, call the police right
now or I will.
Fine, but tell them
about the IOUs too.
Which IOUs?
The collateral for Isabella's
7 million lira loan...
That you couldn't pay.
Is that true?
Riccardo, you didn't tell me!
Oh my God...
My dear Marquis,
you're flat broke.
You're ruined,
and scared of the scandal.
That's an excellent reason
to kill Isabella.
And maybe Nicole,
to make sure
the police didn't get the diary.
Who knows...
maybe it contained all the due dates.
Don't lie, Riccardo.
I told you
Nicole found Isabella's diary.
As you can see,
we're tied to each other.
If you don't want the police
to snoop into your affairs
you'd better do as I say.
Now I'll go to my shop
and ring the Inspector.
I'll tell him we were together.
Agreed?
Good night.
Why don't you believe me?
I burned that diary.
It contained things about me
that I didn't want made public.
I burned it!
I swear I burned it.
Believe me!
No, no!
How did that girl
get in here?
- She had a key.
- And why is that?
I gave her one. She visited me one time...
- Her too?
- Don't think...
- I left Isabella for Nicole.
- Who else had the keys?
- No one. Except me, of course.
- Of course.
Did you take drugs with her too?
- What Inspector?
- Come on, Scalo!
Who are you fooling?
You have a habit.
It's written all over your face.
I could even tell you
where you get your drugs.
And...
and as for the girls who,
shall we say, keep you company,
or who try to fight
your habit, like Isabella,
or who take drugs,
like this one, for instance...
That may well be,
but it doesn't make me a murderer.
Besides, I have an alibi.
I was...
I haven't asked you...
for the moment.
We'll discuss it later.
- When?
- Right away, in my office.
- Do you recognize this?
- Yes, that's it.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
Wait, I took down the first numbers.
Here, 4,5,3. What did I tell you?
Did you see whether the driver was a man or a woman?
A man, I'm sure. He wore black
and seemed to have no face.
He could have been wearing a mask.
No idea. I looked
when I heard the horn.
- What horn?
- The car horn, Inspector.
It didn't go for long though.
All of a sudden, it stopped.
Could the alarm
be connected to the horn?
Wait, I'll check.
Yes, it's at the back
of the glove box.
- How long did it sound?
- I don't know.
- Not long, like I said.
- Tell me how long.
More or less that long.
Stop, not longer then that.
If you don't know where it is,
it takes a while to find.
Yes.
But if you know where it is hidden
it just takes a few seconds.
Come in.
Did you ever see any of these men
in Miss peggy's car?
- Hello, Mr. Morlachi
- Hello, Clarice.
- You saw him in the car?
- Of course, Inspector.
In the car and on foot.
Nothing strange about that.
I didn't say there was.
- I saw him in the car.
- What a revelation!
So what?
This is all a farce.
Be quiet.
I'm not the only one you saw.
Open your eyes, you fool.
You saw him too, for instance,
didn't you?
You only want to know
who's been in her car?
Why?
Because that gentleman
came home last night.
He came with Miss Peggy.
We're getting somewhere
at last!
You bastard! What's your point?
Do you want to ruin me?
I kill you!
Damned murderer!
Damn you!
Confess, you're the murderer!
Inspector, get him examined.
He's impotent.
That's why he hates women.
He can't have them!
Go on, tell the Inspector
that's why your wife left you.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, I'm suffocating.
Take him to the infirmary.
Let me go!
- Anyone know he had epilepsy?
- I didn't.
You may go.
Goodbye, Clarice.
I'm very sorry,
but I'll have to hold you,
Mr. Morlachi
and also you, Mr. Lazzarini.
What does that mean?
I'm legally detaining you.
But to do that Inspector,
you must have a reason.
Miss Nicole's murderer
had been in Peggy's car
since he knew where
the car alarm was hidden.
- May I go? - May I?
- No, you two will stay here too.
That's absurd.
I've supplied an alibi.
- The Marquis confirmed it.
- Yes, we were together.
Don't worry gentlemen,
I haven't forgotten.
You were together till after 11,
Miss Nicole was killed after 10.
- So why do you need us?
- Well...
When I called Miss Peggy
to tell her we'd found her car
it was about 11:30.
I arrived at her place
15 minutes later,
but she was gone
and the house was a mess.
Maybe she was killed too
and hidden who knows where.
With respect to this last event,
I'd say your alibi is worthless.
9:00
Why must we be in the dark?
As if we're not scared enough
Just try to stay calm.
How can we stay calm?
Don't you think enough has happened.
I'm scared too.
I'm not hiding that fact.
But it's no use panicing
If only the men would come back.
We're the only ones left here.
Hello...
Mr. Moriachi, at last,
what happend?
What?
But...
That's aburd. But why?
What right do they have?
Oh, yes...
I see.
Very well... of course...
All right.
Yes, don't worry.
- They've detained all five.
- But why?
It's clear the police believe
one of them is the murderer.
I expected that.
Madam...
May we go now?
Yes, you may go.
- Be brave.
- Good night.
I envy them, they live together.
They have each other.
- I'll go too Madam.
- Yes, of course.
Wait...
Why don't you sleep over
at my place tonight?
What? I live close by,
you live out in the country.
Then I could come to your place.
No, I'm sorry,
but I'd rather be alone.
Besides, you'd feel more afraid
at my house.
Aren't you scared? Isabella's been
murdered, and Peggy...
I know.
But I'm sure
nothing will happen tonight.
All the men
have been detained
and I'm sure
one is the murderer.
Good night, Madam.
Madam, I want to sleep here.
I don't want to go home.
No my dear, leave like the others.
But I'm scared. I live alone
in an isolated house.
Don't be childish, Greta.
Tomorrow's a heavy day.
The work must go on.
Listen to me, Isabella and Nicole
were involved in something
which doesn't concern us.
Therefore, we have
nothing to fear.
Go now, and don't worry.
- Good night, Madam
- Good night.
Miss...
The Marquis asked me
to tell you
he's stuck in town on business.
I know.
Make me a tea, please.
Right away, Miss.
Hello? Hello?
Your tea, Miss.
Just a minute please.
Come in.
Leave it there, Charles.
I'll help myself.
Good night, Miss.
See how he butchered
that poor girl?
Maybe with a hot iron.
He must be a madman.
Or a homicidal sex maniac.
- Who kills only beautiful girls.
- Absolutely.
Perhaps it's the female beauty
that makes him kill.
Now we'll have to start
from scratch.
Inspector, Forensics
are outside by the footprints.
The prints start there.
The murderer came by car
and walked down the slope
to the house.
They match those
outside the fashion house.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, we took casts of them.
I could have sworn the culprit
was one of the five men.
- We'll have to release them.
- Of course.
This time they all have
cast iron alibis.
And I supplied them with it.
Riccardo Morelli.
- Check that it's all there.
- Of course, I do.
Massimo Morlachi.
Come in.
Mr. Morlachi, could I talk to you
for a moment?
Yes dear, come in.
Mr. Morlachi, I'm a calm woman,
not at all nervous.
But the thought of a sex maniac
inside our fashion house...
It doesn't please me at all.
So I've decided
to take some leave.
I'm booked on
tomorrow's Paris flight.
Paris?
All right, Tao Li.
By the way, do you
still live with the Countessa?
- Yes, why?
- Nothing, just memories.
When the Count was still alive
I visited them a lot.
It's a beautiful home.
You can see all of Rome
from the terrace.
Yes, but now
I'd rather see Paris rooftops.
- I don't doubt that. Have fun.
- Goodbye.
Look as much as you like.
I burned everything compromising.
When I heard about your arrest
I got rid of Peggy's body.
They could have found it.
And I killed Greta
to give you an alibi.
Perfect!
Perfect, but horrible.
I don't know how I did it.
I never thought I had it in me
to kill.
I did it for you...
I can imagine what it cost you.
But tell me,
how did you get
Peggy's body to Morelli's house?
I didn't take it there.
I just put her into the trunk.
And Greta did the rest.
Why did you use Greta?
Because I knew she
would be alone in the house.
- That would make it easier.
- Well done.
The police are certain they're
dealing with a sex maniac.
Isabella, Nicole...
Peggy...
and now Greta...
That makes four.
Stop it.
What's wrong my darling?
Kiss me.
Are you worried, my dear?
What a mess.
All because of that fool,
that idiot Isabella.
Her blackmail was intolerable.
Money, money and more money.
It was precisely because
she unfortunaly found out.
That my husbands death
was no accident...
she should have realized it
was dangerous to push it.
But no... no...
The more we gave her,
the more she wanted.
She asked for it.
She thought she had us.
She felt she was the only
witness to a perfect crime.
Her death would have
been perfect too,
if only that damn diary
hadn't surfaced.
But now it's all over.
We have nothing more to worry
about, my darling.
Nothing.
No, you are very wrong.
We'll never have any peace
until we give the police the culprit.
Listen to me, we'll never
get off scot-free
unless we put a face to
their sex maniac.
They'll watch us until
they catch him.
Every victim was at the
fashion house.
They have nothing on us, but the
case is well known now.
It's in all the papers
and the
scandal is raging.
We must find a solution.
So what do you want to do?
I know, darling!
We should leave for the moon.
We must kill again one last time.
And you'll be the one to do it.
- Oh no!
- Yes!
Yes, they are sure
to be watching me.
Don't worry, dear, I'll
give you the perfect alibi.
Relax.
No Massimo,
you can't ask me to do that.
I refuse. I can't do it.
You've done it before.
Yes, I've done it before,
but with very different motives.
I had to
because you were in danger.
I knew that if I didn't do it
I'd have lost you forever.
Only my love for you gave me strength.
But it was horrible,
horrible...
Don't cry. Listen to me.
You must do as I say.
You must kill Tao Li.
You must make it look like suicide.
Is that clear?
They will find the mask beside her
and think she was the culprit.
Otherwise, everything
will have been pointless.
Surprised to see me alive,
aren't you, Massimo?
Yes, you had a
very ingenious paln.
It was all going to be perfect,
just the way you like it.
But you didn't reckon on
a shop awning
which broke my fall.
- Please...
- Shut up.
I know what you want to say.
You want to deny it.
You organized everything.
Only you knew I'd use the ledge
in case of danger, remember?
You suggested it to me.
It was your idea!
Cristina, I swear it was
an accident.
Do you still think you
can fool me?
Yes, it was a very clever plan...
Finding me in those clothes would
have made it all clear
and you would have been free.
Now I understand why
you married me in secret
and so quickly.
You were so in love with me.
So in love!
Yes, but with my villa, the house,
the fashion house, my money...
You wanted to take
all I own by killing me.
Cristina, I beg you...
You are mistaken, my dear.
It isn't true.
I love you.
It's all in your imagination,
darling, believe me.
I swear Christina...
It was just an accident.
I didn't plan it.
How could you think that?
I love you very much, darling.
We'll go away.
We'll always be together.
Police...
Get me Inspector Silvestri...