Ju-On is the curse of a person who died with a deep grudge. This grudge is accumulated in the place where that person lived and becomes its "Karma". Whoever gets in contact with this curse loses his life and a new curse is being born.
[Fansubbed by Shadowlord]
The Grudge - Old Lady in White
Fumiya
Excuse me.
I'm coming in.
Yes.
I'm from the Nicola pastry shop.
I've got the Christmas Cake you've ordered.
I'm busy right now, but I'll come soon.
Yes.
Erm... excuse me...
It's pretty big... family-size... so...
I'm busy right now, but I'll come soon.
Yes.
Are you OK?
Excuse me.
Erm... are you OK?
Hey!
Wait!
Yes.
I'm busy right now, but I'll come soon.
Kashiwagi
Dear passenger, we've arrived.
Dear passenger!
The fare's one trillion yen.
Just kidding!
Hey...
Don't you really want that I bring you to school?
No, it looks strange if an elementary school student comes to school by taxi.
Why shouldn't a father bring his daughter to school?
Oh, I've got private lessons today, so eat without me, please.
Just skip those private lessons today!
What?
It's Christmas Eve today!
You can't keep Santa Clause waiting.
Santa Clause doesn't exist.
Oh, he does exist!
Where?
Right here.
I'm going.
Yes, have fun.
What is this?
Huh?
Something slimy.
Ahhh... I'm sorry.
Must be from that passenger I had yesterday.
Here.
Sorry.
Yuck!
Disgusting.
Sorry, sorry.
Bye!
Akane!
Merry Christmas!
Damn...
Taxi dispatch center here.
Yeah, yeah...
Yes, this is car 125.
Kashiwagi, where are you right now?
Now... well...
Wait a moment...
Come on... what do you want?
Night shift is beginning soon, so I'm about to go home.
Some police officers are here.
Police?
They said they want to ask you something.
What?
I don't know...
something about a passenger you had yesterday.
...a passenger I had yesterday?
Kashiwagi...?
Kashiwagi?
Yes, understood, understood.
I'm returning to the dispatch center right now.
Tell them.
Roger! Bye.
Akane
[Tokyo Sakuradai-Secondary School]
Akane.
What's up? Are you OK?
Yes.
Kashiwagi.
There's something I want to ask you...
Doesn't move at all!
You mustn't pull your finger away.
Hey.
Do you really have that ability?
That ability?
Since you're a child...
you're always seeing and hearing those things,...
right, or not?
Yes.
That won't work.
We're doing it wrong anyway.
We would move that thing ourselves, anyway.
We need someone to contact to.
Right?
What about Okada?
No, not a living person. It must be a dead one.
Oh!
What about your father?
Huh?
Ayumi!
But he's dead, isn't he?
He's just disappeared.
Right?
Right.
Sorry.
It's OK.
It was seven years ago.
Just stop this.
Yes.
Kokkurisan-Kokkurisan...
Wait!
It's not me.
Mi-
-ra-
-i
Mirai.
Mirai - this means future, right?
Could also be a name.
Hey, Akane!
Akane! Kashiwagi!
She doesn't answer.
Maybe I've upset her?
What? Why?
Because I've talked about her dad.
She said, it was OK.
What?
I've forgot something!
I'll get it. Here!
Wait a second!
Hurry!
Isobe
Yes, please, please.
Come on in.
Wow!
Good, huh?
Not that bad.
Wow, what a big room!
Look, mother, our new home!
Shall we take a look around?
Brother!
It's awesome here! Hurry, hurry!
Where's the bathroom?
This way.
Do you like it?
Yes. And so much room.
Hey, isn't the price way too low?
Well...
Maybe something had happened here.
What do you mean?
Maybe someone died here or so.
You really have no sense of humor, do you?
I want to have this room.
Sure.
Here you are, Atsuji.
Yes.
It's quiet here. Perfect for learning.
Since you're having your bar examination this year.
My brother gets a room on the first floor?
Hey, father.
Yes.
I've looked at it. It's quiet there.
Indeed.
Granny.
Here.
Don't pinch it!
Brother.
Is everything OK?
Chiho
I'll come.
I'll come soon.
Are you OK?
Huh?
Fumiya!
Chiho.
Here.
Merry Christmas.
Open it.
Yes.
Cute, right?
Sorry.
What?
Even though you were so looking forward to it...
We can still do this on another day.
Christmas at home is also nice.
OK.
Come on, blow them out.
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas.
Yes.
Shall we eat now?
It's OK.
I need to rinse my mouth with water.
Huh?
Mirai
Akane.
Thanks.
Say, don't you really want to lie down?
Not necessary.
The fever's almost gone, too.
Here.
Thanks to this!
Ah!
Thank you very much...
Just keep it if it helped you.
OK.
So it worked, yes?
Yes! I knew it from the moment you gave it to me.
Granny.
This is Atsuji's ball, right?
He'll get angry again.
I'm visiting her.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
Are you OK?
Maybe I should go...
It's OK, it's OK, please stay here for a while.
I feel better when someone's here.
But your brother's here, right?
And that's the reason why.
Third: An example for...
That's right. You need to limit this to...
...exactly...
No way.
Does your mother know about that?
Why not?
I can't tell her, even though we're living in the same house.
Since when?
Since we've moved to this house...
suddenly...
my underwear...
isn't there anymore for some reason when I come out of the bathroom...
Huh?
It wasn't me. It was granny.
Don't you want to go home already?
But...
Mirai...
This house...
Huh?
Go away! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Mirai!
Kane!
Stop it!
Granny!
Akane!
Sit down.
Show me your homework.
Not necessary.
I don't think so.
You're sweating, right?
Huh?
Wait...
Wait... huh... what... huh?
Wait... what?
Wait... don't touch me!
Granny!
What?
Yasukawa
[Amanuma police headquarters]
Oh, there you are, Kawabata.
Say...
And? Do you want to have children with Tsukawa?
You two really fit together well.
I'll come.
I'll come soon.
What are you listening to?
Kawabata!
I'll come soon.
I'll come.
Kawabata!
I'll com...
Yasukawa.
The family massacre of Nishiogi?
Just when was that?
And what does that have to do with that cassette?
The culprit of that case committed suicide.
After he killed all of them...
he hung himself...
He...
recorded the moment of his death on a cassette.
There...
was also...
that colleague of mine.
Her name was Makabe.
She was working overtime...
and listened to that cassette alone.
But...
when we wanted to listen to it together on the next day...
only the cassette was there and Makabe had disappeared.
I've tried to call her over and over again,...
but she didn't answer the phone.
That's why...
I went to her house to see what's going on.
But Makabe was dead.
Huh?
She hung herself in the bathroom.
You mean, because she listened to that cassette?
Why did she kill herself?
Yasuka...
It was the voice.
The voice...
from before...
No, another voice.
The voice of a child.
Where are you going?
I'm going to burn this thing.
Is that really necessary?
I've thrown it away.
Huh?
Seven years ago, I've thrown this...
cassette away.
I've brought it far away into the mountains...
It shouldn't have been here.
Stay out of this.
Absolutely stay out of this!
[5 family members slaughtered - Suginami residential quarter
Murder on Christmas Eve
He didn't even spare the children
Residential quarter shocked
Hate crime?]
[Crime late at night of the 23rd?
Blood of a suspect in a taxi
Eldest son disappeared without a trace
Murder case of a family in Nishiogi]
[Child beheaded
No traces of a fight in the house
Is the culprit an acquaintance?]
[Isobe Kentaro - Miho - Haru - Atsuko - Mirai]
[beheaded]
Hurry.
Atsuji
[Failed
Name: Isobe Atsuji
Place: Tokyo
Test-Number: 4529
Heisei, 14. year, bar examination
Second examination paper
Note of the result
Subject: Distribution of profits
Grade: F]
Yes.
So.
We'll take this one, then.
Yes, family-size.
Yes, please.
Yes, thanks.
The cake!
It'll be delivered tomorrow morning.
I didn't know he's that stupid.
So, then the result of that stupid test wasn't that good in the end...
I don't want to her that!
I'm just telling.
I don't want to hear that!
You need to care for him better, you're his mother after all.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to excuse.
You're not his real mother, after all.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
What?
Not now.
Why does he always fail?
Just for how long does he want to be a drain on my pocket?
That's so disgraceful, we mustn't talk to anyone about that.
Here we go again!
You too!
Becoming pregnant with sixteen...
and then you're coming back here!
I don't want to have that child, too!
There are still so many things I want to do.
Then have an abortion.
I would, but...
120.2.2.
I'll come.
I'll come soon.
Hurry.
I'm scared.
Come here.
Miho.
I think, granny called.
Yes.
I'm busy right now, but I'll come soon.
Are you hungry?
Shall I make you something?
Yes?
Miho.
What?
No!
Ah! That hurts!
Ouch!
That hurts! That hurts! That hurts!
Stop it!
No!
I don't want that!
Dear passenger.
Do you have any plans for Christmas?
I'll spend Christmas together with my daughter.
She's in the fourth class.
But I still don't have a present for her...
Do you know what children of that age like?
I'll come.
I'll come soon.
Hurry.
I'm scared.
Come here.
Sorry.
I'm home.
[I'll be late from work today. Please eat without me. - Mom]
Welcome home!
Mom?
Akane.
Akane...
I'm sorry.