They're coming!
-Let's go to the water!
- They're heading for the beach!
Down by the beach!
-Run!
-Look out!
Run, Doc! No! Doc, no!
Don't stop moving!
They're down there!
There they go! Okay.
Lay down! Lay down!
Lay down or I'll shoot you, goddamn it!
-Hurry up!
-Lay down!
That's right, shoot them!
I give up, Mr. Glenn. Please!
-Shut up, Henri!
-Please, don't hit me! Please!
Clean him up! Take him to the hole!
And call the press!
Dateline: San Francisco.
Alcatraz was the scene last night
of a dramatic escape attempt.
Four desperate prisoners
were apprehended...
...on the rocky beach below the prison.
The recently completed
Golden Gate Bridge serves as a backdrop.
So near, yet so far from freedom...
...the surviving escapees, Henri Young
and Rufus McCain are escorted back...
...while their less fortunate cohorts
are destined for the morgue.
The body of Doc Barker,
son of the infamous Ma Barker...
...lies bullet-riddled,
cooling on a steel gurney...
...attended by a triumphant guard.
The jubilant correctional officers
who foiled the escape...
...congratulate each other
and reluctantly show their battle scars.
A proud Warden Humson,
supervisor of three penitentiaries...
...Folsom, San Quentin and Alcatraz,
and confidant of J. Edgar Hoover...
...congratulates his troops.
Humson returns to his duties...
...as the inmates are sent
through metal detectors...
...cells are searched,
extra guards are called up...
...and Alcatraz goes on full alert
to forestall any additional trouble.
As public interest reached a frenzy...
...Warden Humson
and Associate Warden Glenn...
...left the island in the bay
for a press conference...
...headed for the San Francisco City Hall...
...which was inundated with a plethora
of reporters from around the globe...
...all gathered to hear the official reaction.
Associate Warden Milton Glenn...
...introduces Warden John Humson.
Warden Humson will now make
a brief statement and...
...if you please, no questions at the end.
Thank you.
l just want to reassure
the American people that...
...Alcatraz is an escape-proof prison.
They have nothing to fear.
The inmates, McCain and Young...
...will be brought up on escape charges.
There will be time in solitary confinement.
Privileges will be taken away from them.
And the whole rehabilitation process
will begin.
Definition of rehabilitate:
''To restore to a state of physical...
''...mental and moral health
through treatment and training.''
Hello.
Hello, hello, hello.
Eleven times 1 1 ...
...121 .
Twelve times 12...
...144.
Thirteen times 13...
...169.
Fourteen times 14....
When Henri Young began
his rehabilitation...
...I was in my first year of law school
at Harvard.
How long?
Alcatraz was opened as
a federal penitentiary in the spring of 1934.
In the era of the gangster...
...it was opened more for
the publicity value than the incarceration.
Alcatraz was the most feared prison
in the world...
...and the most expensive.
There were only so many Al Capones
and Machine Gun Kellys...
...so the prison had empty cells.
To justify the costs, the government took
incorrigibles from other prisons...
...men that had committed smaller,
more petty crimes...
...men like Henri Young.
''Our Father who art in heaven.
''Hallowing be Thy name.''
Prior to 1938, there had been
five escape attempts.
No one had made it.
The reputation of Alcatraz as being
unescapable was secure.
Six inmates had died.
The ones who didn't die
sometimes wished they had.
The federal guideline regarding
solitary confinement states...
...that the maximum stay for an inmate
shall not exceed 19 days.
''Our Father who art in heaven.
''Hallowed be Thy name.
''Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done...
''...on earth, as it is in heaven.
''Give us this day our daily bread.
''And forgive us for our trespasses...
''...as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
''And lead us not into temptation...
''...but deliver us from evil.
''Amen.''
Thank you, gentlemen.
Alcatraz is a half-mile
off the coast of San Francisco.
There were 276 inmates,
1 10 guards with their wives...
...and children stationed on the island.
And the Associate Warden, Mr. Glenn.
This is the story of Henri Young
as I know it.
1936:
American League Yankees visiting
National League Giants.
The Yankees score 18 runs...
...a series record and every single man
in that lineup hits at least once.
Every single man in that lineup scores
at least one run.
Daddy!
Hello.
Have you been a good boy?
Take Daddy's lunchbox.
We'll go see Mommy.
Good news, Henri.
lt's over. You're out of the hole.
You stink, boy.
l did it. l made it.
Come on.
-Did good.
-l made it.
l did it. l did it. l did it.
They were fucking killing you.
You did good.
The only other survivor
of the escape attempt was Rufus McCain.
He had betrayed his fellow inmates
by tipping off the associate warden.
McCain was rewarded
and left in the general population.
Henri Young was sent to solitary.
Come on.
Henri.
Some men are broken...
...by the laws that they break...
...unable to resist...
...the forces that are pulling them down.
Other men...
...live by the rules...
...that society has set down.
You're not one of them.
Henri, l have a job to do here at Alcatraz.
Do you know what that is?
To protect you...
...from yourself.
You were among the selected sinners...
...the state set apart
so that you could simmer in scum.
The good people of the United States
have decided...
...that you are better off here.
l had nothing to do with that decision.
But where l play a part in your life is
to make sure that you stay here.
That you rehabilitate yourself...
...become a model prisoner...
...a better human being.
That's my job, Henri.
You too have a job.
And trying to escape...
...is not one of the duties
of your job description. Understand?
ln life...
...for every action...
...there is a definite and distinct reaction.
Action...
...reaction.
-Yes, Mr. Glenn.
-Now, if you escape, action:
l lose my job.
Reaction: l have a family...
...that l will not be able to provide for!
l'm not done yet.
Now, knowing this information...
...can you tell me...
...why you would possibly
want to escape...
...and jeopardize my family?
l've done nothing to you but my job.
And instead of letting you learn...
...by breaking the rules,
l feel l need to show you how to...
...obey them.
Tolerance.
Tolerance for pain.
My tolerance of you.
But tolerance can be mistaken
for kindness.
And kindness can be mistaken
for weakness.
And we can't have weakness,
can we, Henri?
l understand. l will be good.
l'm not gonna try and run again.
No, you won't.
Action, reaction, Mr. Glenn.
Action, reaction.
Good.
Clean him up, take him to the hole.
Christmas, 1939,
I celebrated visiting with my brother.
Henri Young celebrated in Alcatraz.
''Let nothing you dismay
''Remember Christ our Savior
Was born on Christmas day
''To save us all from Satan's power
When we were gone astray
''Oh, tidings of comfort and joy''
Stop it!
Get in there!
Please, no, no! Please, don't put me back!
Please, don't put me back!
l don't want to! l don't want to! No!
They sound great.
Merry Christmas.
''Standing 'round a flagpole
And he caught himself a head cold''
He sings it over and over.
l can't get him to shut up.
lt gets on your nerves.
In January of 1941,
I had passed the bar exam.
Henri Young was in his third year
of rehabilitation.
Welcome to Alcatraz, gentlemen.
Step off the boat and onto the dock.
Eyes straight ahead at all times.
There was a boat
named after Warden Humson...
...which handled the traffic
to and from Alcatraz.
In the morning and afternoon, it shuttled
the children to San Francisco for classes.
It was also used to transport prisoners
to the island.
When possible, having children
and prisoners on the boat...
...at the same time was avoided.
Don't look at the children.
l'll take the kids to the city.
We'll go shopping.
Honey, can l call you back?
The warden's here.
Good morning, Warden.
Good morning.
-When did you arrive on the island?
-About 20 minutes ago.
Good.
-Sit down.
-Thank you.
Mr. Glenn...
...l've been going over
the rotation figures...
...in the solitary-confinement cells.
ls there something wrong?
Well, l don't know.
l don't think this can be right.
What's that?
Here, 244.
According to this, he's been in there
since March of '38.
l don't believe there's been
an attitude change with regard to 244.
He's not like the other inmates.
That's over three years!
He masterminded
the escape attempt in '38.
There hasn't been one since.
If you let those animals believe
that escape is possible...
...you might as well stick in
a revolving door.
I think he has learned his lesson.
Come on, Henri. Let's go.
Henri Young had been rehabilitated.
I was now a public defender
in San Francisco. We'd meet in three days.
Eat, Young!
You know the rules!
You don't eat, you go to solitary!
Now, get with it!
Two times two is four.
Two times three is six.
Two times four is eight.
Eight.
Two times five...
...ten.
Twelve times...
...eight...
...ninety-six.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe more--
Henri, McCain, he put you in the hole.
Put you in the hole.
McCain's still here. Look!
McCain put you in the hole!
Put you in the hole!
McCain, he put you in the hole.
Get them back!
Get them back against the wall now!
Do it now!
What happened?
l don't know.
The United States of America
vs. Henri Young.
Charged with murder in the first degree.
Approach the bench.
''Henri Young, Rufus McCain...
and there, striking and wounding...
''...sharp steel instrument...
to wit, a spoon.''
No, this can't be right.
lt's right.
lf you say so.
''To wit, a spoon
about four inches in length...
''...which, striking and wounding,
described as foresaid...
''...caused the said Rufus McCain
thereafter, to wit...
''...on June 1 1, 1941 to die.''
Trial set one week from Thursday, June 22.
This court stands adjourned.
l know you can do it!
Come on, boy!
You can do it! You've got four furlongs!
Don't be cursing this street!
Pick them up and lay them down!
Let those legs pump like pistons!
Yes! Come on! The spirit is willing!
l can see it in your eyes.
Come on!
Pump it! Go!
Remember Jesse Owens
at the '36 Olympics?
Maybe tomorrow, sonny boy!
Watch it, buster!
Sorry, Counselor!
You're all right?
Mary, l'm sorry.
l'm sorry. Mary, you okay?
-Stop that!
-Okay, l'm sorry!
lf Henkin saw us, he wouldn't think twice
about suspending us.
-All right.
-Fix your tie.
Why?
You need to look good
when you thank Henkin.
What do l want to thank Henkin for?
The man's a cretin.
-He's given you a case.
-Case of what? Scotch?
Yes, James, a case of Scotch.
An actual case where l stand
in front of a jury?
-Federal murder one, no less.
-Henri Young.
He's a convict who killed another convict
in front of 200 witnesses.
Was it self-defense?
With a spoon.
What with a spoon?
That was the murder weapon.
He used a spoon to kill the man.
Weren't any forks or knives available?
My first case l can't possibly win.
Do this one for the experience, for the next
time, when maybe your guy didn't do it.
You could learn a lot.
Go see your client
and make nice to Henkin.
-l'll see you tonight?
-Maybe.
Thank you for your confidence in me
in getting this case.
l don't have any confidence in you.
The guy is guilty.
A monkey could try this case
and not make it any worse.
-l see.
-Remember that.
-Thank you, sir.
-A monkey.
l guess l'm a monkey.
-James Stamphill to see Henri Young.
-l need you to sign the release.
-lt's a nice day.
-Yeah, great.
Where are you going?
To the cell, talk to my client.
What, are you nuts?
l want to speak to him face to face.
Well....
You've already signed the release.
lt's your life.
Hi.
So, then, Mr. Young, is it?
You're Mr. Young, is that correct?
Mr. Young, that is your name, isn't it?
Henri Young?
l'll just assume that's your name
until you tell me differently.
Mr. Young, l will be acting
as your defense attorney.
l'm James Stamphill
and anything you tell me...
...will be protected under the rules
of confidentiality...
...of the attorney-client relationship.
So feel completely free...
...to answer my questions
in an honest and forthright fashion.
Just for the record,
your name is Henri Young, right?
This isn't an admission of guilt.
lt's just your name.
You speak English?
Yeah, you do speak English.
lt says so right here in the file.
Mr. Young...
...l am your attorney but l can't provide you
with much of a defense if one of us is...
...catatonic.
You see...
...we both have to be able and willing
to answer when our name is called.
Can you hear?
Mr. Young?
You okay, Mr. Young?
Henri Young was born in Kansas in 1913.
His parents died ten years later...
...leaving Henri to raise his younger sister.
At the age of 17, Henri went into
a local store to try to get a job.
He was refused work.
Out of desperation he reached
into the cash register and took $5.
The store also doubled
as the town's post office.
Henri was tried and convicted
of the federal crime of mail robbery.
Henri's sister was taken
to live in an orphanage.
He would never see her again.
Eleven years later,
Henri would kill Rufus McCain.
Mr. Young...
...you killed a guy, so...
...you're not catatonic.
l know that you can talk.
l don't know...
...maybe you could write something.
You want to write something? Write here.
Something. Just....
Look, you want to give it a try?
You want to write?
Something...
...please.
Mr. Young, you're looking at me.
You hear me, don't you?
lf you won't answer my questions,
maybe we can start with something else.
What do you want?
There has to be something.
Can't be to sit there, because if you do,
they'll just stick you in the gas chamber.
Do you understand that?
Look...
...Mr. Young, l've read your file.
l am trying to help you.
That's all l'm trying to do.
l just want to help you.
Maybe there are...
...extenuating circumstances in your case.
Getting sentenced to Leavenworth
for stealing...
...$500, that's extenuating.
You have to understand, l'm on your side.
$5.
What, Mr. Young?
lt was $5, not $500.
l knew you had it in you. Now, come on.
Why did you kill Rufus McCain?
You just talked. Don't do this again.
Come on, don't quit now.
Come on, you just talked!
Why did you kill McCain?
What?
-What are you saying?
-How....
How? How? How?
Are you saying ''how''?
How.
How?
How. What are you, a fucking lndian?
Don't quit now. How what?
How is....
You want to know how somebody is?
l'll find out immediately.
How is....
Who?
DiMaggio.
How is DiMaggio?
ls he a prisoner over at Alcatraz?
How is...
...DiMaggio...
...doing this year?
DiMaggio, the baseball player?
Yeah.
How is Joe DiMaggio, the baseball player,
doing? That's what you're asking?
Mr. Young...
...l don't really follow baseball.
You know.
Excuse me, Mr. McNeil,
I'm James Stamphill.
-Counsel for Henri Young.
-Yes.
l was wondering if l could talk to you
about continuance?
No.
You don't understand.
He just sits there and won't speak.
Maybe he's practicing for the gas chamber.
Tell him to take deep breaths.
You won't even consider a joint motion
in the interest of justice?
-Are you old enough to be a lawyer?
-Yes, sir, l am.
No joint motion for a continuance.
No psychiatrist.
And trust me, pal, no plea bargain.
Your boy's gonna suck the pipe.
l don't know who you pissed off
to get this shit case and l don't care.
No breaks.
Mr. Young, DiMaggio is having
a great year.
Last year he was the American League
batting champ with a .352 average...
...which was just a bit off the year before
when he had a .381 average.
The Yankees, they too had a good year.
New York defeated Chicago 4-0...
...led by jolting Joe DiMaggio hitting 400.
400, that's pretty good, isn't it?
June 1 7, 1941 ...
...our friend DiMaggio hits safely
in 32 straight games.
Twelve more and he will tie
Wee Willie Keeler's all-time record...
...who set the mark in 1897
for the Baltimore Orioles.
Joe Louis was the victor in what some
consider the toughest win of his career.
Here we go.
Here's some entertainment news.
Betty Grable.
See?
Says here she's just--
How old are you?
What, Mr. Young?
l'm 24.
l think...
...l am too.
No, you're...
...you're 28.
Would you like me to keep reading to you?
This ought to make you
a little bit more comfortable.
The defense requests a new jury.
Having been eliminated from this process--
Three new members.
And that's it.
Next.
The defense requests a continuance
of 60 days...
...so l may confer with my client--
He doesn't need 60 days.
The facts in this case are so clear,
six minutes should do it.
My client has been almost catatonic.
-Yesterday was the first day--
-He wasn't so catatonic...
...that he couldn't walk over and slit
a guy's throat in front of 200 witnesses.
ls it your contention
that the defendant is insane?
ls that what you mean by ''catatonic''?
Approach the bench, Counselor.
ls this laying the groundwork...
...for a not-guilty by reason
of insanity plea?
l don't know yet. l haven't even spoken
to him about the case--
One week, Counselor.
Then you will either tell me
you are ready for the trial...
...or you will come in here with a request
for a competency hearing.
One week.
This court is in recess.
Mr. Young, you and me,
we've got to talk now.
Would you like a cigarette?
No, thanks.
That shit will kill you.
That's...
...kind of funny.
''That shit'll kill you.''
l'll die in that gas chamber anyway,
so that's kind of a joke.
What's this about Nazis? We at war?
No, not yet, Mr. Young.
-lt's brand new.
-What?
-Mr. Glenn told me.
-The associate warden?
He says it's brand new.
He said they're gonna try it out on me.
No.
You only have a week.
You've got to talk to me. Okay?
Why did you kill Rufus McCain?
How could you not know about baseball?
You said, ''l don't follow baseball.''
-How could you not?
-Why'd you kill him?
Over and over, it must have been
maybe a year, l don't know.
All l did was hear them in my head.
What are you talking about?
Are you talking about McCain?
l'm talking about baseball.
The great American pastime.
l went over every game
l ever heard on the radio.
l went over every game l ever heard.
Just playing them over in my head.
You had all those games to go to...
...and you didn't even care.
l'm talking about Rufus McCain.
l'm talking about three fucking years
they had me in that bucket!
Three fucking years!
Without any fucking light!
You had all those games to listen to!
You didn't even know
what DiMaggio hit this year.
What kind of asshole are you?
Calm down, boy!
You know the average length of time
an inmate would be in solitary?
Nineteen days.
l understand, but he killed a man.
Henry did three years in total darkness.
ln a black hole.
That's tragic, but he took a life.
Your brother will tell you what l did.
-You won't get him off.
-He's the best lawyer l know.
He can tell me if we've got a chance
for some kind of insanity plea.
Your brother won't give a damn.
Your client is a two-time loser.
This case is much more
about you than him.
He has no future.
This is your first time in the spotlight.
lt's what you worked for.
This case is a lost cause...
...so you must handle it like a lost cause.
Maybe you're right,
but the guy's not exactly Al Capone.
No, he isn't.
All they had him on was
income tax evasion. Your boy...
...they got on murder one.
Hi.
How are you?
Hi, Henri.
Listen.
You're not mad at me
for blowing up at you yesterday?
Nobody talks back.
No, l'm not mad at you.
l'll get the hang of it.
l got a sense of humor.
We gonna have some good times
before this is through.
You know how to play cards?
Could you get some?
l set this up for you. Sit down.
How much light got into the cell
you spent three years in?
-Like when you offered me a cigarette.
-l want to get that straight.
That was pretty good, huh?
You gotta help me if l'm going
to defend you now.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Have a look here.
Did you kill this man here? Rufus McCain?
l must have. l'm here.
l don't remember it,
but everybody saw me, so, yeah.
-But you don't remember it?
-No. So what?
Did you want to?
Once there was this spider
that crawled over me.
lt was like having company.
l looked for him again, couldn't find him.
He had a way out.
McCain landed you in the bucket, right?
142 times 93. Ask me that one.
-How long after you came out--
-13,206.
13,000? You mean, days?
What are you talking about?
No, that's the answer. 142 times 93.
-Concentrate on what l'm saying!
-l know what you're saying.
-How long was it?
-l don't know! l don't remember!
Who's the new girl l've seen in the papers?
lngrid Berger?
She's a looker. You seen her movies?
l want you to think!
l don't want to think!
l spent three goddamn years in the dark...
...smelling my own shit and piss...
...doing nothing but thinking!
l hate thinking!
l'm sorry, Henri.
l'm sorry.
l'm just trying to help you.
You got a girl, right?
Take your jacket off.
-What?
-Let me smell it.
You were easier to understand catatonic.
What's she like?
-Who?
-Your girl. That's perfume.
Let me smell your jacket.
l'll make you a deal.
l'll give my jacket, my pants,
whatever you want. Sports, girls....
But you gotta tell me just one memory
about something l ask.
Deal?
Sure.
l've never been with a girl.
Let me try it on.
How long was it you went
without any daylight?
Did they ever let you out for any exercise?
-Merry Christmas.
-Please, don't hit me.
-Get the tear gas.
-How long l been in here?
-You're out of the hole.
-l made it! l did it!
lt's Christmas, 1940.
You've been down there two years.
Two years!
l did it.
Two fucking years.
l made it. l made it.
l'm not too crazy, am l?
l did it! lt's over!
Nothing's over, Henri.
Thirty minutes exercise, that's all you get.
No!
You don't want it, we take you back.
l want it!
l want it.
l'll be good. l'll be good.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury:
The defendant, Henri Young...
...is accused of murder in the first degree.
It is your responsibility,
as a juror, to deal with truth.
Rufus McCain was murdered...
...by Henri Young.
Mr. Stamphill...
...public defender...
...will play upon your sympathies.
He'll use every trick in the book.
Why?
To avoid the gas chamber.
The United States of America
will demand...
...that you return a verdict of guilty...
...so that this...
...this animal...
...will receive the punishment
commanded by the Bible.
''An eye for an eye.''
A life for a life.
For if ever there was a man
guilty of murder...
...it is Henri Young.
And if ever a man deserved
to die for that crime...
...it is the accused.
Thank you very much, Mr. McNeil.
Mr. Stamphill, are you prepared
to make your opening statement?
Your Honor...
...ladies and gentlemen of the jury:
When l was a kid, my heroes
weren't Babe Ruth or Lou Gehrig...
...they were Clarence Darrow
and Émile Zola.
ln other words, l have waited
for this moment all my life.
To stand, like l am, in front of a jury
of 12 good people...
...to plead the case of an innocent man
who's been unjustly accused.
The only problem is he did it.
l know it, the prosecutor, Mr. McNeil,
knows it.
Henri doesn't know it 'cause he can't
remember it, but he won't deny he did it.
All those witnesses the prosecutor
will bring forth will tell you...
...Henri Young killed Rufus McCain.
Now that we all know that,
why don't we find the man guilty...
...and gas him because that's
what we all know is going to happen?
Right, Henri?
What?
There's only one problem that'll keep us
from wrapping this up in record time.
Henri Young did not act alone.
They haven't caught all the killers.
There was a co-conspirator. Because of
this co-conspirator, whom we shall name...
...Henri Young is innocent
of the crime of murder.
What?
Objection, Your Honor! l must protest!
l figured you would.
This is absurd.
Before the counselor is allowed to waste
this court's time and this jury's time...
...l'd request that he supply some proof
or evidence of this co-conspirator.
Can you bring forward evidence
of the existence of a co-conspirator?
Not at this time, but it is my intention
to do so during the course of the trial.
He's not going to provide such proof
because no proof exists.
This man spent three years
in solitary confinement...
...during which time no one had
any influence over him...
...because no one had
any contact with him.
He came out of solitary.
He went directly to a shower.
Then he went directly to a haircut.
Then he went directly to the dining hall...
...where one convict had said
one sentence to him.
This does not a co-conspirator make.
l'm inclined to agree with the prosecution.
Unless you can justify
that line of defense...
...l will sustain the prosecution's objection.
The district attorney, with his own words,
has just made my case for me.
That'll be the day.
Your Honor...
...for three years,
three long, tortuous years...
...no one and nothing had any influence
whatsoever over Henri Young.
No one and nothing.
This was a man whose only crime was
to steal $5 from a local post office...
...to feed his starving sister.
He came to Alcatraz a petty criminal
who had never harmed...
...or attempted to harm
another human being in his life.
He came out of the dungeon a vicious,
barbaric, maniacal murderer.
A man who had been put
into a psychological coma.
Within an hour of coming out
of that hell hole...
...he did what would've been unthinkable
to him three years before.
Unthinkable!
His only thought was murder!
His only instinct was murder.
His first act was murder!
He himself was a murder weapon,
but the hand that held that weapon...
...and plunged it into the throat of McCain
belonged to someone else.
l point to Associate Warden, Mr. Glenn...
...Warden Humson and the institution
known as Alcatraz and say, ''l accuse! ''
-Objection!
-l accuse them individually and collectively.
l accuse Alcatraz of the torture
of Henri Young!
-l accuse Alcatraz of McCain's murder!
-Come to order!
Silence! This court will come to order!
Henri Young is not going to be
the only defendant here!
Alcatraz is on trial!
I will address your objection
tomorrow morning!
Henri Young, on trial for his life, is seen
leaving the San Francisco courthouse...
...followed by his young and now very
popular public defender, James Stamphill.
Stamphill has accused the infamous Rock
of torture, using the tag line...
...''crimes against humanity.''
He has turned the once quiet trial
of a convict killing...
...into a media circus.
ln most cases, they do get better.
ln the case of Henri Young...
...this happens not to be true.
Young is a...
...noisemaker.
Some prisoners have a problem
when they're in...
...solitary.
All we do is try to discourage misconduct.
This is the first verbal attack
on the jewel of the prison system.
This bastion that houses evil
opened in 1934.
It brought gangsters like Capone...
...Machine Gun Kelly and Henri Young
close to the magical city by the bay...
...less than one half-mile
from the world-famous Fisherman's Wharf.
We went to the streets
to find out public opinion.
You can't put a place on trial.
lt's a prison for prisoners.
Now the murderers are accusing
the wardens of this and that.
Doesn't make a lot of sense.
Humson seems like a good guy.
lf Alcatraz wasn't here l wouldn't live here.
-You think it's too close?
-l think it's perfect.
He's innocent until proven guilty.
He'll get a fair trial, but, nonetheless,
he's a murderer.
This grizzly evidence bears mute witness...
...to the brutal crime
perpetrated by Henri Young.
Note the spoon.
Can a prison be put on trial?
Judge Clawson's ruling tomorrow
may clear the way...
...to put Alcatraz on trial.
''The warden can be relied upon
to carry out the instructions...
''...of the Bureau, that no brutality...
''...or inhumanity shall be practiced.
''Sustained food and medical attention
shall be given.''
We have wholeheartedly followed
those instructions.
Thank you.
So many opinions being expressed.
We attempted to get a statement
from the recent Harvard graduate...
...assigned to defend Henri Young.
Why don't we keep the trial
in the courtroom? Thank you.
l would like to address a few words
to the counsel for the defense.
Mr. Stamphill, you are hereby
put on notice...
...that this court has no interest
in newspaper headlines...
...and will not be swayed by them.
l further admonish that counsel's attempts
to try this case in the press...
...and not before this court,
will put him in the utmost peril.
ls that clear, Mr. Stamphill?
Yes, Your Honor.
Good.
Bailiff, approach the bench.
Before l hand down my ruling
on Mr. McNeil's objection...
...l'd like to address a few words
to the counsel for the defense.
While l cannot give legal advice
and sit on the bench at the same time...
...l will express grave concern
with the defense's strategy.
Counselor, l strongly recommend
you walk a straight line...
...in terms of your defense.
Anything you state in this courtroom
will be evaluated not only by the jury...
...but very closely scrutinized by myself.
ls that understood, Mr. Stamphill?
Yes, Your Honor.
Very well.
Prosecution's objection is overruled.
You may pursue your line of defense...
...concerning the penitentiary at Alcatraz...
...and l will rule on any objections
on a point-by-point basis.
Exception.
Noted.
Mr. McNeil, you may call
your first witness.
Prosecution calls Terrence Swenson.
Terrence Swenson.
Witness shall remain standing
until sworn in.
Put your hand on the Bible.
Cut it out.
Do you swear to tell the truth
and nothing but the truth...
...so help you God?
So help me God.
You may be seated.
Mr. Swenson, as a guard at Alcatraz,
did you know Henri Young?
Yes, sir.
Could you point him out for us?
That's him right over there, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Whitney.
Thank you.
Now, on the morning of June 1 1, 1941,
where were you?
l was on duty in the dining hall.
Everything was normal.
And l saw the defendant--
Henri Young.
That's correct.
l saw him standing over Rufus McCain.
He lifted up his chin and....
-Excuse me, l'm nervous.
-lt's all right.
And he plunged a metal object...
...which l later learned was a spoon...
...into McCain's throat.
He then ripped it open.
Did the defendant ever appear
to be ranting...
...or raving?
No, sir.
Mr. McKeon, was he frothing
at the mouth?
No, sir.
Did he in any way give the impression
of one who was insane?
Objection. This man is not
a qualified psychiatrist.
Sustained.
So, it appeared to you that it was a cool,
calculated and deliberate act?
-Objection!
-Overruled.
The witness may answer the question.
Yes, sir. Young did it,
just as cool as a cucumber.
Thank you.
No further questions.
This court will reconvene
after the holiday...
...9:00 a.m., July 5.
All rise.
You should have played cards with me.
Alcatraz.
lt was built by the military
during the Civil War.
ln May of '33, the War Department
abandoned the island.
lt was leveled, all except for the lower
floor which is now used for storage.
Note to myself:
Get access to the lower level...
...because that's where the dungeons have
gotta be located.
The only guard on record to be fired...
...or dismissed during Henri's solitary time
was Derek Simpson.
Locate Simpson.
The prison opened in June of '34
under Warden Humson.
He insisted on a high level
of guards to prisoners.
Glenn was the first appointee.
Mr. Henkin.
Two things: First of all, you work for me.
Let me finish!
You work for me, which means
when l call you, you drop everything.
Return my call or you will cease
to work for me.
l don't care if you're with Rita Hayworth!
Understand?
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
What the hell are you doing with this trial?
Defending my client.
Then why don't you defend him
for Christ's sake?
Try to knock down the charges
as a crime of passion or figure out...
...how you'll cross-examine
the witnesses...
...instead of this ''psychological coma'' crap
that doesn't mean anything in court!
l think it does. As long as it's my case--
Fair enough. l tried to talk reasonably
to you, but you're not going for it, so...
...you're not handling this case anymore.
lt's done.
Mr. Henkin...
...they're printing my opening statement
in 250 newspapers across the country.
lf you want me off the case because
you're afraid of taking on Alcatraz...
...that's your choice.
But l'll just go to Jerry Hoolihan
and tell my side of the story.
lf you want to play hardball, sir,
l'll play hardball too.
l'm trying to be your friend.
You know who the warden of Alcatraz is?
He's the most highly respected warden
in the US dealing with hardened criminals.
lf you try to make Humson
look like a Nazi...
...they will eat you for breakfast.
You'll die if l can't get corroboration
about what goes on over there.
l need names! Names of men
who'll come and testify.
What made you think
these men will come and testify?
Maybe you got some friends
you don't know about.
-You want to play cards?
-l'll make them testify with a court order!
What about when they're back
on the Rock with Mr. Glenn?
They'll kill them, that's what.
This is our only chance.
We're talking about your life.
For a smart guy, you're awfully slow.
l'm already dead. l told you that.
You can't change Alcatraz.
lt just is.
So why fight it?
You stand in court preaching. l don't
even know what you're talking about.
Justice. l'm talking about justice.
l killed him, they saw it,
they're going to kill me.
Nothing you say will change that.
So l don't see what you're
so excited about.
This trial doesn't interest you at all?
You don't care about it a bit?
You look like you're having
a good time, so....
No, l don't care.
Main thing is, l got a friend my age
to talk to until they gas me.
l'm not your friend, l'm your attorney.
l'm trying to save your life. Guard!
You know, l have a sister, but...
...l ain't seen her since they put me in jail.
l got nothing. l got nobody.
l don't need a lawyer. l need a friend.
You're doing all this to prove something
to a guy named Darryl, not for me.
You want to do something for me?
Let's play cards.
Go ahead and play cards.
l got a case to try.
Hold it, Jim. Where are you going?
Where are you going?
I'm Henri Young's attorney.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
I'm going to call prisoners to the stand
to testify about life on Alcatraz.
Where are the dungeons?
What is solitary time
in those dungeons like?
I want the jury to know and understand.
You tell them to get caught
robbing a bank. They'll find out.
l'm done talking.
Mr. Murphy...
...if we can get decent treatment for you,
it makes it possible for everyone.
lf we ignore cruelty in one place,
it makes it more acceptable everywhere.
l ain't gonna do shit for you.
You can't get me no good time
knocked off.
You can't get me no privileges.
You can't even get me seconds at dessert.
lf l testify for anybody...
...l testify for the DA.
He's got some juice here.
Mr. Baker, could you tell me anything
about Henri Young?
Don't know Henri Young.
Could you tell us anything
about Mr. Glenn?
Warden Glenn has always been
good to me.
Have you ever been in the dungeons?
l don't know nothing about no dungeons.
That's all, ma'am.
l gotta go now.
Fuck you.
Did Mr. Glenn tell you
not to cooperate with me?
Fuck you.
Where are the dungeons located?
Don't take my fucking picture!
You know l can get
a writ of habeas corpus testificandum...
...and force you to come
and testify in court?
Fuck you!
Thank you very much for your time.
Don't mention it.
And you, sweetheart....
l'd like to fuck you.
I hope your day has been fruitful.
l don't see your photographer.
ls he still taking pictures?
He's trying to.
We're not receiving a great deal
of cooperation.
lt almost seems as though someone told
the prisoners not to talk to us.
There's no conspiracy.
No one talked to them.
Maybe it's because they are
dangerous people who belong here...
...with no interest in you or your case.
-l'd like to see the dungeons.
-l'm sorry? Dungeons?
The old citadel, the sub-level of the prison.
That's mostly storage...
...a few solitary cells.
No dungeons.
l would like to see
the solitary-confinement cells.
l would love to show those cells to you,
but l can't.
lt's an insurance risk to visitors during a
riot. lf you're there, we can't protect you.
Thank you for your concern.
l could show you the exercise yard.
You have papers.
l have papers, so you can cut
the good-guy act.
l do consider myself
as one of the good guys...
...and perhaps more than you...
...l know what the bad guys are like.
l'd like to read them. Please.
Thank you.
That's a court order...
...instructing you to permit us access
to the solitary-confinement cells.
And to allow the photographer
to take pictures of the same...
...to be used as exhibits in the trial
of The People vs. Young.
You are also instructed
to hand over to us...
...the complete medical
and disciplinary files as to therein.
If you refuse to do so...
...you'll have to appear in court
and show just cause.
Why don't you take Miss McCasslin
out for some air?
l was told not to leave you alone.
l don't care. You may be used to
these conditions but obviously she's not.
We've been searched. Take her outside,
or we'll discuss this with Mr. Glenn.
All right.
No more photos.
You all right?
Thanks.
l just need some air.
My God!
My name's James Stamphill.
l'm Henri Young's attorney.
l can force them to let you out
so you can testify...
...in San Francisco in a court of law.
You just have to give me your name.
I promise I will do what I said for you.
James, she's okay. Just needed some air.
Can we go now?
Feeling any better?
l guess l'll make it.
-Did you get anything?
-l got three names.
Let's go.
Where did Stamphill get
the three names on this list?
l don't know.
Can you trust these cons? They're smart
enough to look after their own interests.
They told Glenn...
...James said he'd get them out of solitary
if they would testify for the defense...
-...and lie on the stand!
- That's a lie.
-He wanted to find one convict willing--
-Jesus, this is goddamn bribery.
It's prejudicing a witness.
You could get disbarred. It's gone too far.
Fire him. I don't care how you do it.
Why do you have to make it be like this?
Henri Young's my client.
lt's my job to defend him !
Not anymore.
What?
He's been notified that Henkin
wants you off the case.
Henri will never go for it.
-He did. He's been assigned a new lawyer.
-Who?
Me.
Henkin assigned me to the case.
l could take it or be fired. l had no choice.
You stabbed me in the back?
l'm not stabbing you!
l'm trying to save your job and mine!
What about Henri's life?
lsn't that more important than profit?
l don't have a brother who's a partner
in a big law firm.
There aren't any other jobs
waiting out there for a woman attorney.
The only option l had was to do
what he told me to do.
What could l have done?
l'll see you.
What we need to do is establish exactly....
We have a lot of work to get to today,
if you don't mind.
Stop that.
Jesus Christ, all l was doing was looking.
l want to set you straight--
You set me straight
the minute you walked in.
-Mr. Young--
-Please, call me Henri. Please.
Mr. Young, l am not here to satisfy
any sexual fantasies that you may have.
You're not?
No, l'm your attorney.
They're gonna kill me anyway.
You won't do me any good as an attorney.
You may as well be good for something.
-Mr. Young, l can't--
-Please, call me Henri, can't you?
l just want to hear a lady call me Henri.
Can't you, please?
Just once.
Please.
Henri, listen, we have so--
Yeah, yeah. That's it. That's it.
l'm gonna touch you just a little bit.
Just a little.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, sure. lt won't hurt you
to let me touch you.
Don't make me call the guard.
We're running late on....
Stop that.
Stop.
Stop that! Stop that!
l'm not touching you. l'm touching me.
Guard!
You have a problem?
Did he do anything?
No.
Let me know if he does.
No, l'd like to leave now.
-He wants to see you in there.
-What?
He wants to see you in there.
So, why'd you want to meet here?
Neutral territory?
Want to be my lawyer again?
What happened to the other one?
l don't know if l want her.
Since l had her, l mean.
She was good, though.
She was everything l wanted
my first experience to be.
l was just talking and she came over.
-She started touching me--
-That's great. That's great.
Jim, l'm just playing a joke on you.
l know she was your girlfriend.
l remember from the smell of the perfume
on your jacket.
So, Lawyer...
...you want to come back?
l resigned.
l guess that means
l'm in private practice now.
l could've had her though.
Of course...
...she don't play cards.
After I got arrested, they...
...took my sister away.
They...
...put her in a home or orphanage and...
...I don't know....
I don't know what happened to her.
Never saw her again.
My parents died when I was 7.
It was just me and my brother, and he
didn't know anything about raising a child.
He sent me off to boarding school.
I did get to come home on holidays.
He put me through law school...
...then got me the job
at the public defender's office.
He wanted me to do well.
We had a plan until you came along
and messed everything up.
l wish l had been able to take care
of my little sister.
l mean...
...family's family, right?
Henri, l'm sorry you're here.
This here's paradise
compared to my last home.
How about the case?
Do you want to talk about it a bit now?
You never give up, do you?
How about the Redskins?
How do you think they'll do
against the Yankees this year?
Redskins are a football team.
Yankees are a baseball team.
Personally, l think the Redskins
will kick the shit out of them.
Henri, l'm trying.
l know.
This is going to be
a private conversation, Byron.
lt never took place, all right?
-ls that all right, Thurgood?
-l suggested it.
That brother of yours is making
quite a little name for himself.
We even heard his name in Washington.
My brother has resigned from the case.
Well, he was hired back again last night.
What do you mean he was hired back?
Your work here has been stellar.
l'd hate to see anything--
What exactly are you saying?
This administration is not going to allow...
...public attention to be diverted
from all the good it's done...
...by some kind of a witch hunt
in the Justice Department.
l'm just telling you what the score is.
lt's up to you to take care of him.
Why would J. Edgar Hoover care
about what happens to Henri?
Grow up. He doesn't care
about what happens to Henri.
He cares about...
...Alcatraz, the Justice Department...
...Humson, the Administration.
He can't have some kid from the P.D.'s--
l'm not a public defender anymore.
You know the point.
The point is l'm trying to do what's right.
l'm talking about justice here.
You're disgusted about what happened
on Alcatraz. So am l.
But if you tear the whole system down...
...what does that say about America?
We're wrong.
We can't be wrong.
The world is fighting right now
to preserve our system, our way of life.
You can't attack it blindly.
We're talking about one man here.
lt's not that big of a deal.
-You're under surveillance.
-What?
Everyone is watching you.
Tell me how you plan to continue.
You have to realize, no one will talk.
Everyone has been gotten to.
l have somebody.
Who?
l can't tell you.
So, now you don't trust me?
You're my brother. l love you.
l need your help.
l can't do it. l'm sorry...
...but l can't.
l can't.
James, as a consolation...
...please don't put Humson on the stand.
Why?
Humson was handpicked by Hoover.
lt would save a lot of embarrassment
if you were to avoid Humson.
l'll think about it.
Thank you.
l'm sorry, Byron.
Yeah?
Mr. Stamphill?
This is James Stamphill.
This is Derek Simpson.
Remember we talked before?
Right. Of course, I remember.
Have you made your decision?
I've been thinking about what we were
talking about and I'd like to be a witness.
Wonderful.
You do understand you must testify
in court under oath...
...about the brutality you witnessed
at Alcatraz.
I know that.
Particularly in reference to Henri Young.
I know some things.
Do you hold any sort of grudge...
...against Warden Humson
or Associate Warden Glenn?
No.
I'll come over and we can speak in person.
Yes. I'm in Chinatown.
It's an alley called Scotland Court.
The number there is 964.
Mr. Simpson, are you in here?
Mr. Simpson, are you all right?
You all right?
Do you still want to be a witness?
Who's she?
She's a court reporter.
What happened to your face?
My face had a little accident this morning.
We need to get one more deposition...
No.
...regarding the beatings you received.
Your eye, your leg....
Remember when you told me
you'd never been with a woman before?
Henri, this is Blanche.
Blanche, this is Henri.
Nice to meet you.
You got about four minutes before
the next guard arrives, so you gotta hurry.
l can't leave the room. l'm just going
to be over here. l'll turn my back.
We can get acquainted.
Come on, honey, we don't have all night.
Thanks, Jim.
You're a good friend.
Oh, boy.
Thanks. Hi, Charlie.
What's the story?
The attorney and a reporter inside
with the prisoner.
-ls he shackled?
-Yeah. Otherwise, it's pretty quiet.
Sweetie...
...you have to get it up first. That's like
sticking an oyster into a slot machine.
Give me that.
-l can't.
-You can.
Yeah, you can.
l can't, sorry. l'm sorry.
-Except for the $5 you owe me.
-For what?
What, you didn't listen?
Louis knocks Nova out in the sixth round.
That bum.
Give me the money.
-l can't.
-Yeah, you can.
l can't. l can't.
-You can.
-l can't!
Adíos, Charlie.
You know what?
lt's gonna cost extra, you know.
Just do what you have to do.
l can't.
l'm sorry.
Hey, we only had a few minutes.
You got another guy in the room.
That's okay.
Shh, baby.
Your Honor, the defense calls
Associate Warden, Mr. Milton Glenn.
Do you swear to tell the truth
and nothing but the truth?
-So help me God.
-You may be seated.
As associate warden, you are responsible
for the day-to-day running of the prison?
You could say that.
Then you must be familiar
with the dungeons.
l'm sure you've heard of them.
Some prisoners refer
to the lower levels as dungeons.
They refer to bread and water
as piss and punk.
The dictionary definition of a dungeon is:
''A close, dark prison...
''...or vault, commonly underground.''
The walls of those cells are 6 feet by 9,
and the roof 5 to 6 feet tall.
-Would you call that close?
-ln my opinion, no.
-Are there any light fixtures?
-No, but there aren't any books.
Your Honor...
...the defense offers these photographs
as defense exhibits B, C, D, E and F.
How much light is in these cells
with no window and the door closed?
-Not much.
-How long was Henri held in such a cell?
l don't know exactly.
Three years and two months!
l have the records, if you'd like to see.
-That sounds right.
-Three years and two months.
ln that time, how often was Henri Young
allowed outside for exercise?
Mr. Stamphill, l do not believe that
the exercise time of an inmate is relevant.
l do. Answer the question.
-Objection!
-Objection overruled!
Henri Young tried to escape.
When a criminal escapes from prison,
he doesn't go job-hunting.
He robs somebody or kills somebody.
We do all we can to discourage escape.
ln three years and two months, how often
was Henri allowed outside for exercise?
-Men sentenced to Alcatraz--
-Answer the question!
How often was he allowed
outside for exercise?
-Objection! He's badgering the witness.
-Objection overruled.
Mr. Glenn, you will answer that question.
Young man, l do not recall.
You don't know?
Surely a half hour a year isn't
too difficult to recall, now, is it?
-There is no place in my court for sarcasm.
-Sorry.
l have here a list with 32 names on it.
These are men who were prisoners
at Alcatraz during your tenure. Correct?
l can't remember the name
of every prisoner.
l have committal papers with your
signature as well as the late Dr. Kiley's.
This is defense exhibit G.
All these men were taken off Alcatraz in
straitjackets and put in mental institutions.
-ls that correct?
-Objection!
The question is immaterial.
lmmaterial? Your Honor, l'm saying in lay
terms that Alcatraz drives people insane.
lt has already done so in 32 instances.
lf this is not true, the witness can say so.
lf it is true, it is most material...
...and the jury ought to be privy
to that knowledge.
Objection overruled.
Thank you.
Now...
...is it not true that these men were taken
off Alcatraz in straightjackets...
...and placed in mental institutions
and you and Dr. Kiley signed the papers?
True.
ls it not also true that of these 32 men...
...28 of them had never before set foot
inside a mental institution?
-l don't know.
-Would you like to see the records?
l'll take your word for it.
Here are men who came to Alcatraz
legally sane...
...were subjected to the conditions
of Alcatraz, then deemed to be insane.
ls that correct?
Yes, but you can't say
that one causes the other.
lnsanity's not a virus, is it?
lt's not something we're all going to catch.
Objection, the witness is not
a psychiatrist!
Objection sustained.
Mr. Stamphill...
...confine your questions to areas
of Mr. Glenn's expertise.
Very well, Mr. Glenn's expertise!
Have you ever beaten a prisoner?
No, that's illegal.
-Not even when provoked?
-No!
You've never hit, kicked,
used a blackjack or a razor?
You've never punched a prisoner
in your entire career?
-Objection, Your Honor!
-Sustained.
Confine yourself to one question at a time.
ls it not true you ordered two guards to
throw Henri down a steel flight of stairs?
That you smashed his face
with a blackjack?
That you took a straight razor, sliced open
his ankle, hobbling him for life?
Answer the question!
Objection!
-He testified he didn't beat any prisoners.
-He's testified to a lot of things.
Are you aware that, in a federal court
system, perjury is a crime?
-You could go to jail!
-Young is on trial!
Mind you, young man, that Henri Young
is the one on trial here, not me!
l am a public servant!
l am not the bad guy!
l will not be treated the same way as this,
this lying, murdering...
...two-time loser!
Silence, Mr. Glenn!
Mr. Stamphill, you are perilously close
to contempt of this court!
You will proceed with caution!
ls that understood?
Temper, temper.
Would you care to withdraw
any testimony?
You wouldn't want somebody to testify
to the contrary, would you?
No. l would not withdraw any testimony...
...no matter what Henri Young
has told you.
l'm not talking about Henri Young.
Who would believe him?
Mr. Simpson, did you ever beat
this man, Henri Young?
Objection! This has no bearing.
No bearing? Beatings have a bearing
on a man's state of mind.
So does three years of darkness.
Do we need to be psychologists to know
that? You know that. l know you do.
Objection overruled.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Did you ever beat Henri Young
with a blackjack?
Yes.
Did you ever throw Henri Young
down a steel flight of stairs?
Yes, I did.
-You were ordered to do this?
-Yes, sir.
Tell us the name of the man...
...who was your superior who ordered you
to do these things.
Mr. Glenn.
You never went to Warden Humson
about these matters?
No, sir.
Thank you very much. l won't ask where
you got your bruises. l already know.
The prosecution would like to mark
for identification...
...the employment records
of Mr. Derek Simpson.
Do you recall...
...being suspended on November 4, 1936...
...and again on July 6, 1937?
Yeah.
Speak up.
Yes.
ls it not a fact you were fired from your job
as a guard because you are a drunk?
-Objection!
-That's not true!
Objection!
-Overruled.
-Mr. Glenn...
...wouldn't tolerate this in a prison.
lsn't it true, having cost you your job...
...you would say anything
to get even with Mr. Glenn?
The jury will disregard
Mr. Simpson's testimony.
Good afternoon, Mr. Stamphill,
is everything all right?
-Son of a bitch!
-What happened?
You know exactly! You set me up!
What are you talking about?
You took Simpson's picture
off of my desk!
They never would've known
to tear him down if you hadn't told them !
Are you going to hit me now?
Go ahead.
lt's about time you grew up
and were a man.
You're my brother.
You had me beaten up.
That was not supposed to happen.
Only Simpson. You walked in,
it was bad timing.
Bad timing?
Humson will testify.
Why, James?
Humson doesn't know anything!
He runs three prisons. He has to know
something. Unless he's never there.
Son of a bitch.
He was never there.
Never there.
You never saw him?
You'd hear about him visiting,
but l never saw him.
Your own brother did that to you?
Your brother did that to you?
Jesus, rich people are weird.
You hear DiMaggio broke Keeler's record?
Forty-five straight games.
Wouldn't it be great if he never stopped?
Dock records would show his visits.
Every trip is recorded. l had to sign in
myself that one time l went.
-What?
-We're friends, huh?
Yeah, sure.
ls it over? l mean, you know?
ls that all?
Nothing more you're going to do
with the trial?
Thought you didn't care.
No, l don't care.
lt's just that as long as you got shit
to throw at them, we can keep talking.
But when it's over, it's over.
l'm not here to entertain you
until the executioner comes.
This trial isn't a game.
lf l was on the outside, if there was...
...a good fairy and she waved a wand
and l was on the outside...
...you and me, would we be friends then?
Yes.
No, no, no, we wouldn't.
You wouldn't have nothing to do with me.
You know it.
What l can't figure out is why. l mean...
...we both ain't got nobody else
and we're the same age, sort of.
lf l'd have lived in your house...
...and they'd have switched us
when we was babies...
...l could have been just like you.
lf they stuck you in the hole...
...you could be sitting here...
...like me, asking why we couldn't
be friends on the outside.
You ever steal five bucks?
Once.
When l was a kid, from my...
...brother's wallet.
What happened?
He told me not to do it again.
Why'd they put me in that hole
for three years?
l could have been just like you.
l'd just like to ask them, you know.
Raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the whole truth
and nothing but the truth?
So help me God.
You may be seated.
Warden Humson, in a book you wrote,
you refer to the convicts as your children.
You liken your job to that of a parent,
providing for their physical needs...
...and molding their character.
Yes, l wrote that.
l have a record of a prisoner
named Johnson...
...who did a total of 500 days
in the lower cells.
The hole, the dungeon.
This was over a ten-year period for such
offenses as not finishing all his food...
...having an extra pair of socks in his cell,
keeping an untidy cell...
...smuggling food from the dining room,
crumbs, in fact, for a pet lizard.
ls this what you mean
''molding character''?
No, no, no.
You're twisting things here.
The isolation cells were simply a tool
of a temporary nature...
...for extreme cases
within the general population.
Moreover, you make it sound like
the prisoner did 1,500 days at one stretch...
...for one infraction.
That's not true.
Prisoners were held...
...for 19 days at a time.
-That's all.
Perhaps you can tell me why Henri Young
did over 1,000 days in the dungeon?
Not 19 days, but 1,000 days...
...in total darkness with only 30 minutes
of daylight a year.
He tried to escape.
You can't compare his offense with that
of a man who smuggled food to a lizard.
Was this the first time a sentence
of three years had been imposed?
lt wasn't a sentence.
lt was an administrative decision
to place him there...
...for an undetermined amount of time.
Why not a time limit? Doesn't that seem
a little bit inhumane? No time limit.
Put simply, no.
While we strive to prevent crime...
...what should we do with a man
who has committed it?
We aim to make him his better self.
His better self.
l'm sure that Henri Young thanks you
for his better self.
lt's a fact you simply put Henri Young
in that dungeon and forgot all about him.
Washed your hands of him.
Henri wanted me to ask you, ''Why?''
Why would you do that, sir? Why?
That's not true.
Objection.
l withdraw the question.
l apologize to the jury--
lt's not necessary that you apologize.
Actually, Your Honor, it is.
l made a mistake.
The warden couldn't simply have washed
his hands of Henri Young...
...because he had absolutely no idea
he was there.
lsn't that true?
You're never there. You permit Glenn
to run that prison any way he sees fit.
l am there as much as l need to be.
l run three penal institutions.
lt's impossible to know every detail
of every inmate.
l have the Port Authority records that you
signed every time you went to Alcatraz.
You went seven times in '38,
five in '39, ten in '40...
...and only twice so far this year.
Twenty-four day trips in over 3-1 /2 years...
...while Henri Young was in that dungeon
over 1,000 days.
Twenty-four out of 1,000 days.
That's how much you needed to be there?
You knew nothing about a man who was
left to die in a dungeon for 3-1 /2 years.
Absolutely nothing!
ln fact, you have never even met
Henri Young, have you?
Right now, in fact, is the first time
you have ever seen this man! Look at him !
That's him there! That's Henri Young!
Right there!
-He tried to escape.
-Yes, he did.
But the fact, the cold, brutal fact is
that this man...
...who had never,
never before in his entire life...
...harmed or attempted to harm
another human being...
...was now a murderer!
That is a fact!
-Yes, but he tried to escape.
-lt's a fact--
You can't let them get away with this.
lf we let them, where would we be?
-Should we let murderers roam free?
-Henri Young was not a murderer!
Henri Young was not a murderer
until Alcatraz got a hold of him !
The prison runs under your guidelines,
so you created the murderer, didn't you?
Didn't you?
He tried to escape.
That's the thing, you see.
Do you have any further questions
for this witness?
-No, Your Honor.
-The witness may step down.
But he tried to escape.
I'd been trained all my life for that day.
Control the witness, go for the kill.
Win, victory.
School prepared me well.
My brother, he had prepared me well.
Years later, he and I would reconcile.
Family's family, you know.
Mary congratulated me...
...but we'd already begun to drift apart.
When you only try to win,
you sometimes lose sight of the goal...
...which should have always
remained Henri.
The most you'll get is
second-degree murder.
Maybe manslaughter, ten years.
If you get a recommendation
for clemency, you'll walk.
-You have your whole life in front of you.
-Monday morning...
...go up to the judge and tell him
there's been a change of plan.
l want you to change my plea to guilty.
ls that a joke?
Not to me, it's not.
l'm not doing it.
What have l been doing here?
Why have l been wasting my time?
l never thought we'd win.
l thought you wanted to fight.
l just...
...wanted a friend.
l am your friend.
No, you're not. lt's always about you.
lt's never about me.
You don't understand.
l already lost and you just keep talking...
...and talking and you never listen.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You just don't know what it's like.
What what's like?
Alcatraz!
Where do you think they'll send me
for those ten years you're talking about?
They'll send me back to Alcatraz!
When it's over, you'll be alive!
l'm Henri!
l'm the one that's got to do the time,
not you!
And l can't do it! l can't do it!
l can't, all right?
lt's not worth it.
Nothing's worth going back there.
Sixty-seven thousand fans
at Municipal Stadium in Cleveland...
...watching to see if Joe DiMaggio can keep
his 56-game hitting streak alive.
Jim Bank is on the mound,
count one and one, runner on first base.
Here's the pitch. DiMaggio swings.
It's a double play! DiMaggio's 56-game
hitting streak is stopped!
Mrs. Rosetta Dial?
Why are we in here?
Maybe there are some things
worth fighting for.
Henri?
Do l know you?
l'm Rosetta, Henri.
l'm your sister.
My baby's name is Henri.
Mr. Stamphill says--
l was...
...beginning to think...
...that you wasn't real. That l...
...made you up in my mind.
l want you to come--
l want you to tell Jim that l appreciate...
...him bringing you down here
and knowing...
...that you turned out okay.
That means a lot. l want you to tell him,
come Monday morning...
...he's going to plead me guilty
just like l said.
l wish l wasn't...
...so scared of them, Rosetta.
l wish to God l wasn't.
You take care of yourself now.
You may call your next witness.
Just a second.
l'm your friend.
On the outside, l'd be lucky
to consider you my friend.
So l'm not going to kill you.
-Are you going to call a witness today?
-Yes, Your Honor.
lf you want to change your plea,
you go do it. l'm not going to do it.
-l want you to plead me guilty.
-l don't think you are.
-Doesn't matter.
-Does to me.
Counselor, l am very close to finding you
in contempt of--
The defense calls Mr. Henri Young.
No!
He just lost the case.
You go up and change your plea.
l repeat, l'm not going to do it for you.
Counselor--
He's coming.
Go ahead, tell them.
Tell them, not me.
Better ask the right questions.
-l'll ask what l want.
-l'll answer what l want.
-Fine.
Guilty, guilty, guilty, guilty.
Stand up.
Put your hand on the Bible.
Do you swear to tell the truth, and nothing
but the truth, so help you God?
So help me God.
State your name.
Henri Young.
Be seated.
Your Honor--
Wait until l've asked a question!
-l haven't asked you yet.
-He's trying to trick me.
Please instruct the witness to remain silent
until l ask a question...
...and only answer the question l ask.
He's your witness.
He won't listen.
He's trying to trick me!
Silence, Mr. Young.
Here's the way it works.
Mr. Stamphill will ask you a question...
...and you answer that question.
However, Mr. Stamphill cannot coerce you
into testifying against yourself.
You do understand that?
Yeah, l just want to--
Did we have a conversation in which
you said you wish to change your plea--
You will wait until l have finished
instructing the witness.
lt's okay. l wanted him to ask that.
lt is not okay.
And l do not need you to tell me
what is or is not okay.
ln this courtroom,
l am the one who decides...
...what is or is not okay.
Okay?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Counselors, approach the bench.
Do you mind telling me
what the hell is going on here?
l'm trying--
Your own defendant is looking to me
to protect him from you.
So what's going on?
l know it seems very strange but--
ln my opinion, you're an idiot to put him
on the stand for any reason.
You're asking him to testify
against himself.
lt doesn't seem to make sense,
but the prosecution isn't objecting so--
No, l'm not. Let him continue.
Shut up.
Enough damage has been done.
l can't make it any worse.
Yes, you can.
All right. But you're on a very short leash.
A very short leash.
l will throw you in jail
for contempt myself.
Now...
...let's get this goddamn show on the road.
l think you're doing a great job.
Mr. Young, stop playing with that!
Now, do you or do you not wish
to continue testifying, Mr. Young?
lt's okay. He asked me the right question.
Counselor, you may proceed.
Mr. Young, did you and l not have
a conversation last Friday...
...in which you told me you wished
to change your plea to guilty?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
l want to change my plea.
That's what l said.
l'm going to ask you the single
most important question l can ask you.
lt's what this whole trial's about.
Are you guilty of the murder
of Rufus McCain?
l want to change my plea to guilty.
l said that.
l didn't ask what you wanted to do.
l asked if you are guilty.
Objection!
He's badgering the witness.
-He's my witness, for Christ's sake!
-l'm not your nothing!
lf the accused wants to enter
a plea of guilty--
Silence! Mr. Stamphill,
you are skating on very thin ice here.
Maybe, Your Honor,
but l'd like to get to the other side.
Very well. You may proceed...
...at your own peril.
Thank you.
Let me take this one step at a time.
We had a conversation in which
l told you l felt...
...with the way the trial was going...
...the most you'd have to face, more than
likely, would be another ten years or less.
-l don't care--
-Ten years, that's what l said.
Yeah, yeah, but--
Did you say to me...
...you were the guy who had to do
the time, not me?
That they'd stick you back in Alcatraz
for those ten years, right?
That's what l told you.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because if you change your plea to guilty,
they will execute you.
-You will die!
-So fucking what?
l'd rather die than go back there!
What'd you say?
l said...
...l'd rather die than go back there!
Can't you understand that?
Why, Henri?
Why do you want to die?
Because....
Because l'm...
...scared of them.
l'm scared to go back there. l'm scared.
l'm scared. l'm scared.
-Objection! He's finished--
-l haven't finished anything!
Henri, look at me.
Henri, look at me. Look at me.
You were right. You were right,
l was wrong. l'm sorry.
l'm just talking to you right now.
Not the judge or the jury.
lf you want to die, we'll back you up.
But l swear to God...
...l'll fight these bastards
so they'll never do this to anyone again.
You're not going to die for nothing!
The choice is yours.
What do you want to do?
l want to stop being afraid.
All right.
Henri Young...
...are you guilty of the murder
of Rufus McCain?
l was the weapon...
...but l ain't no killer.
They're the murderers.
Bailiff, you may remove the prisoner.
Escort the prisoner to the holding room.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
you have received your instructions.
You may find the defendant guilty
of involuntary manslaughter...
...which carries with it a maximum penalty
of three years...
...in which case the defendant
will be remanded...
...to the custody of the warden of Alcatraz.
Or you may find the defendant guilty
of murder in the first degree.
Without a recommendation for mercy...
...that verdict will carry with it
a sentence of death.
This court is now in session.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
how do you find?
The defendant will rise.
We, the jury,
find the defendant, Henri Young...
...not guilty of first-degree murder...
...and guilty only
of involuntary manslaughter.
Order! Order!
We would like permission to address
the court, if possible.
Very well.
We have this day signed a petition
which l would like to read to the court.
''We would like the following to be read
into the record of this proceeding.
''Though we know it will have
no legal or binding effect...
''...we'd hope that it will have
a moral effect.
''We, the members of the jury,
recommend the immediate investigation...
''...by the proper federal authorities...
''...of the federal penitentiary
known as Alcatraz.
''We find this institution, its wardens...
''...and associate warden,
guilty of crimes against humanity.''
Thank you.
The jury is dismissed.
This trial is concluded.
All rise. The defendant is remanded
to the custody of Alcatraz.
News from San Francisco.
The Young trial concludes.
The Rock will be investigated
as Young is vindicated...
...by a verdict of involuntary manslaughter.
As I walked out of the courtroom
that day...
...I did not fully realize how much
Henri and I had actually accomplished.
It all just happened so fast.
l'll to be up to see you as often as l can.
Then you can bring that Blanche back
for a second shot.
l'll see what l can do.
No place like home.
Henri, it's not over.
l'm going to appeal to have you moved
to another prison.
l'm going to file motions to have
your original case reopened.
Henri and Jim, together again, huh?
That's right. Henri and Jim,
together again.
Henri and Jim, together again.
l won, didn't l?
l mean, l really did something.
l won!
That's right, you won.
How many games was
DiMaggio's hitting streak?
Fifty-four?
No, l got you.
lt was 56, wasn't it?
l'll see you soon!
Take care of yourself.
The definition of victory is:
''Success in any contest or struggle.
''An engagement ending in triumph.''
That was to be the last time
I was to see Henri Young alive.
Before the court date was set for
an appeal, his body was found in a cell.
He laid beneath a single word
he had scrawled with a rock:
''Victory.''
Henri Young had taught me
the meaning of the word.
He was the only man that I have known
who gave more than he asked.
All that he ever wanted was a friend.
I will always remember him
as one of the best friends I have ever had.
Unlike many men that live much longer...
...Henri Young did not die in vain.
In the end, he was not afraid.
He lived and he died in triumph.
If only we could all do that.
Welcome home.
l've missed you.
You can beat me...
...you can put me back in that hole,
whatever you want to do.
lt doesn't matter to me.
Action:
l won.
Reaction:
You can't ever take that away from me.
Take him to the hole!
Charles Dickens once said
that solitary confinement was inhumane.
Seven months later,
the Supreme Court agreed.
And as a result of the facts brought out
in the trial of The People vs. Young...
...the dungeons of Alcatraz
were closed forever.
Associate Warden Glenn was brought up
on charges of mistreatment.
He was found guilty. He would never work
in the penal system again.
I remained in private practice.
I also became a baseball fan.
You did it, Henri.