[Girl Narrator:]  'Just you wait a little while,
the nasty man in black will come,
With this little chopper,
He'll chop you up,
You're dead.' ['dead' echoes]
[German]  Tell me what you feel.
[German]  Tell me what you feel!
[German]  Tell me...what you feel.
MURDER-SET-PIECES
- Jade, wait up!
- Come on, hurry!
- I'm coming!
- He'll  be here any second!
Haven't you ever ditched before?
Not really.
Well, at least we had fun.
Yeah, I know.
Is your sister's boyfriend cool?
- He doesn't say much.
- Well, what's he like?
I don't know.  He's not
from around here though.
Ah, Shit!  He's here!
Cool car!
I know.
- So where are we taking you?
- It's just up this way.
Thanks.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye, Megan.
So how was your first day
at school, Jade?
Fine.
Like your teacher?
I have more than one, you know?
Mmm..so what's
your favorite subject?
- History.
- History?
Very good!
You see, it's my favorite too.
Why do you like
to take pictures?
- Because pictures never lie.
- What does that mean?
The frame of a 35mm camera is alive.
It lasts for ever.
Unlike people.
Nothing lasts for ever.
What happens to you
when you die?
I don't know.
I guess you just rot away.
And you believe that?
Yeah, I guess....
Remind me to take your picture sometime.
Why?   You never take pictures of my sister.
Don't worry.
I will.
Hi Benny!
Hi!
Well, tell me all about it!
I will later.
-Now stop that!  Go back into that chair!
I haven't seen your sister
in three months.
She's getting to be
quite a big girl!
- Nah, she's still just a little squirt.
- I am not!
Seen any cute guys?
Well, listen to you
miss matchmaker over there!
A couple.  But they were
a little too old for you, Candy.
You little shit!
- Where's your ride?
- He's out parking his car.
You mean your ride,
don't you Charlotte?
You watch your mouth!
Charlotte's dating a German prince!
- Really?
- Yes, I chide you  not!
Don't be jealous!
- Hi, how are you?
- Great!
I was just talking
to Jade about her school.
You got to be more careful
little girl!
Was she complaining?
No,  not at all.
Well, maybe she can tell
us all about it over dinner.
Oh, not tonight. I have
to shoot some girls.
- Are theypretty?
- Of course they're pretty!
- As pretty as me?
- Never as pretty as you!
[Series of breaths interspersed
with ever louder screams]
What do you see in him?
He's a big klutz who carries
around a stupid camera.
Jade, stop it!
I can't believe you went out
and bought a pair of shoes just for him!
He's no fun, and he looks at me weird!
He's not weird just because
he's not from around here
and he has different ways.
You're always complaining that he's
never around and he never returns your calls.
Do you know how many guys
would love to go out with you?
Come on Jade,
I don't want to hear now this right now!
I don't like the way he talks to you.
Why do you love him,
he doesn't love you?
Then why did he give me
a key to his house?
It's probably a fake!
Listen, I just have a
really bad feeling about him, OK?
You and your feelings!
You know, you're not always right!
I am this time!
He thinks he's better than everybody else!
I mean...
look at the way he talks:
'Hi, I am from Germany,
and I wear tight pants...
and I think I am so cool because I take pictures of
naked girls with my stupid camera.'
What I am going to do with you, huh?
This wine is really good!
So Jade, how was school today?
There's no school on a Saturday.
Of course!
Forgive me!  I think hard and I work late.
It's all right!
Do you always eat
your meat that bloody?
Yes,  blood is good!
It's good for you.
Blood contains iron...
and you need iron to
replace your blood cells.
See, that's the problem with women.
Women have an iron deficiency.
[Laughs]
Among others things.
And, women need more iron than men.
It's ironic…
Women suck blood
out of men every day.
But at the end of every month…
…it leaks out!
It's just punishment.
So want some ice cream tonight?
That sounds great!
I have to use the bathroom first.
Where is my sister?
In the bathroom.
Where you're supposed to be.
Last time we talked about your school...
you said something about history.
Well, this is my history.
He was my grandfather.
He was a hero, you know.
He fought the bad guys
during the Second World War.
Yeah...    but…
Wasn't he German?
[Sound of engine accelerating]
[Sound of win and coins dropping]
Boy, aren't you the luck one?
- Tell me your name!
- Andrea, silly!
Of course!
-A nice big smile!
-OK.
Very good!
I...  You really are very beautiful.
Why, thank you!
Are you OK?
Excuse me...be right back.
OK.
OK...you promise that you won't say anything?
[Sounds of shutter clicking repeatedly]
She told Candy that
he wouldn't even fuck her.
- That's weird!
- Yeah, I know!
- His grandfather was a Nazi.
- A Nazi?
A Nazi, like in
World War II.
Nazis, like Adolf Hitler and Germany
and that weird cross thing they had to wear.
How do you know that?
I saw a picture of him
plus, he told me.
And when I told Charlotte about it,
she said that I was just exaggerating.
So, what are you going to do about it?
He just freaks me out.
Charlotte's never going to listen to me.
It's just like that last asshole she went out with.
She'll always let guys walk all over her.
Well, your sister's smart,
she's going to jump in....
Well maybe, but...
I just don't see him going away.
[Car engine-varying pitch over time]
Take your clothes off!
[Muffled screams]
[Indistiguishable German with woman screaming]
[Car engine]
You're late!
As usual.
Man, this hemi has been
giving me fits.
But then, you wouldn't know
anything about that, would you?
Maybe I'll just find myself
a young girl and pimp her out...
then I could afford to buy such a car.
You don't have a daughter, do you?
I don't think so.
Can't everybody be as lucky as me.
Or as pretty.
Let's go in the house.
Have a seat.  I'll be a minute.
Let's go to the bedroom.
[In German] It's made in-house
in Germany.
[In German]  Germany will rise again!
500 dollars.
American.
I'll bet you that old girl in there
has already got her panites off.
For an extra $500. I'll walk
down to 7-11 and buy another 12 pack
And drink it there .
I gotta shoot some
girls tonight.
I bet you do!
Going to hell is easy...
It's getting out that's hard.
- Ah, Eh, Ah...You Fucking Bitch!
- Please stop!
If you fail me, I swear...
The whole fucking world
is going up in flames!
And you are the biggest part
of the problem!
The biggest fucking problem is you!
This is an evil generation!
Everyone is so seeking for a sign...
but there shall not be given
any signs to them!
I see the signs,
I feel it!
Relax, you're going to be in Hell soon enough!
Pig!
Elephant cage cleaner...
well...maybe.
Pay or play, Pal!
[Under his breath]  Jesus, I need another job...
General labor....
Septic tank cleaner...
What do you need?
Some lubrication?
Video head cleaners?
Blow-up Betties?
I got a blow-up Betty over there.
Damn, What are you about 6' 2"?
I got a nice synthetic doll for you, man, $69.95.
That floats your boat?
- I'm looking for a snuff film.
- A what?
- Called “The Nutbag”.
- Excuse me?
A snuff film.
No, we got all kinds of stuff in here, man,
take a look around...
you want nude dancers,
a lap dance…want some tokens?
- I look for a film.
[Making fun of accent] - A film?
- I'm looking for a snuff film.
Called  “The Nutbag”.
Snuff? You mean like:
Snuffy, Grumpy, Dopey…?
That's the seven dwarves, man.
Hello?
Ok, fuck off!
- I'm looking for something very specific.
- You still here?
Sorry, if I didn't make myself clear...
I don't like to reapeat myself,
but I guess I have to...
-Uh hah!
I'm looking for a SNUFF...FILM...
called “The Nutbag”.
Do you have that in your archive anywhere?
OK, I tell you what, we under suspense, OK...
because I don't have time
for your fucking freaky shit today, alright?
You don't come in here looking for that kind a shit!
You look like a fucking degenerate cop!
This is an adult book store, OK...
ADULT--BOOK--STORE.
So what do you want?
Don't come in here fucking asking
for some fucking...degenerate...ass...
What kind of fucking degenerate...
fuck-ass....are you, man?
Get the fuck out of here!
What the fuck you think this is this, man...huh?
Get the fuck out of my place!
Get out of my store!
[Calling employee] Jeremy...!
You fucking weird-ass...motherfucking freak!
[Woman screams]
Alright, all you fuckers, down on the ground!
...the fuck out of my way!
Alright, watch that motherfucker right there!!
Hey...
- Put your guns down motherfuckers now!
- Lower your weapon now!
-You're going down motherfucker!
-You're going down right now!
- Put your gun down right now!
- Put your gun down now or
I'll blow your fucking head off!
[Gun shots]
Which one of you is the fucking manager?
What are you looking at motherfucker?
Who is the manager?
Watch him!
- Easy, easy now!
-Shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up!
- Open the register!
Open the fucking register!
- Open the fucking register!
- Yeah!
- Open it!
- I'm right there, I'm right there!
- Open the register!
- Yes, just give me a minute.
Watch him!
[Mayhem, all yelling]
Just wait a minute!
Jesus!
Jesus Fucking Christ!
God damn it, man!
You shot 'em both...ha!
God Damn!
You got 'em both!
Dude...Dude, look you want anything
from the store,you can
have anything you want!
What do you need...Huh?
What you want, Dude?
What the fuck are you doing, man?
No, man, not like this, alright?
In my mind's eye,
I  light fires in your cities.
No.
[Screams and German]
Oh, God!
You like that?
Do you like that?
I can't hear your open fucking mouth!
Because I like it!
I like it a lot!
Tell me that you like it!
Come on!
I  can't hear you!
Ah...Fuck...Ah...Bitch...Ah...
More!
You're gonna die!
Fuck!
OK.
Lick around!
Beautiful.
Hold it right there!
Excellent.
Put your hands up!
Bring your hands up a little bit.
OK!  I want you to slap her ass, alright?
Yeah, lift up the skirt.
Put your face down by her ass.
Yeah, that's great, great.
Beautiful.
You're doing OK, yeah, very nice!
OK, show me your tongues.
Beautiful.
[Car engine]
[Crying]
[Screams]
Just relax!
Time to fill it up.
[Cries muffled]
Stop moving!
Don't go anywhere!
Shut Up!
Tell me the truth, you fucking cunt!
I want to go as a witch.
No, that's boring.
I want to go as a zombie.
That's cool!
What time can your sis' drop you off?
I don't know if I can.
Why?
Because she's really upset, and I don't
want to leave her alone tonight.
- Well, can't she just forget about him?
- No.
Why?
Because he won't go away.
[Child's voice] Please Stop!
Don't kill me!
Leave me alone!
...I See...
Kill me!       Kill me!
Kill me!
- I 've seen him!
- Please!...
This is hard enough without your bullshit!
I'm telling you the truth,
I've seen him at my school!
He sits there and he watches me
in his fucking car!
Stop it!   Just stop it!
Quit lying to me!
I am not lying!
You can even ask Megan.
She was with me, she saw him!
Look, you got what you wanted!
He's gone!
Now, leave me the fuck alone!
I'm scared of him!
Try to kick your legs, Babe!
- Dad, I got to go to the bathroom.
- OK, hold on Baby.
Whoa!
OK, Sweetheart, you can go.
- Don't forget to wash your hands, Honey.
- OK.
[Recording of Adolph Hitler speech playing]
interspersed with    [Series of groans as he does push-ups]
And        [Sirens in background]
[Girl Shrieking]
[Repeating sounds of Thunder
interspersed with his cries]
[Television]  Police say
10 year-old Megan Wade
was last seen late Saturday afternoon
As she left her apartment to go
Trick-or-Treating with some friends.
Police have little to go on,
but the Amber alert is in full effect.
The gruesome murders of several young girls
here in Las Vegas, have been attributed to...
You could talk to me, you know.
You saw Megan last.
She must have told you where she went.
She didn't run away.
Jade, Honey, please tell me.
- Tell you what?
- Tell me where she is.
She is dead and it's all my fault.
What the hell are you talking about?
[Telephone Rings]
Hello?
[Sound of a key hitting the ground]
[Whispering voices]
[with whispering voices continuing behind]
You Mother...Fuck...her!
Just tell me how to kill you .
I am the bastard son
of a God-damned whore!.
That's who I am.
[Car engine]
[Door knocker]
You're late, as usual!
- I am tired.
- I sent the baby-sitter home an hour ago!
- Say something!
- I am hungry.
You make me sick!
[German]  Are you still in love with me?
Answer me!
I never promised anything.
[German]  Liar!    Liar!
Time to move on.
You got what you wanted.
Motherfucker
It's time to move on.
Get out, don't come back!
It's enough!  Get out!
Go!  Go!
Where were you?
Where were you when you were needed?
[Baby crying]
[winding sound then
tinkling music with baby
still crying]
[Baby screaming]
[Sound of explosion]
...No....No...Go Away!
What are you doing in my car?
I need help.
What's the matter with you?
Where are your parents?
You're not out here all alone?
Please.
Please, just drive.
I am not here with anyone.
I am all alone.
You are all alone.
Alright.
I  gotta go.
Hey!
Come here!
I don't know what your problem is...
but don't you ever hitchhike again!
[Woman crying]
[Sound of chain saw with woman screaming]
Charlotte?
[Jade Screaming]
I'll get you, you hear me
I'm going to kill you!
Charlotte..?          Charlotte..?
Are you here?
...It's real...
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Jade screams repeatedly]
Let me go!
Fuck!...You bitch!
[Jade screams repeatedly]
You fucking bastard!
[Whispering voices...]
You don't look like
you're from around here.
Excuse me?
Ah...you just don't look
like you are from this area.
So, where are you headed?
To the City of Angels.
Oh...you too huh?
Let me guess...
You are going to be an actress.
A superstar, Hah...
Well, something like that,
I guess.
What does that mean?
I said that you have
a beautiful smile.
You see...
Everyone starts out with a picture.
It's a cool camera.
I save it for
very special occasions.
How's this?
Great...  Smile!
[Scream]