MAN: February 23, 1942.
"Out of Poland have come
these appalling pictures
"of the end product
of German conquest.
"They show mass misery and death
carried by German thoroughness
"to an extreme
rarely seen before in history.
"They also show
the kind of thing
"the fighting foes
of Nazism may expect
"if they really lose the war.
"The methodical massacre
takes on
"an emotional quality of sadism,
"as applied by
the Nazis to the Jews.
"Herded in Polish ghettos,
forbidden to walk out
"or use a railway,
machine-gunned in their synagogues,
"thrown by thousands
into the rivers,
"stripped of clothing and food
and possessions.
"The Jews of Poland
are literally dying out.
"These are the grim
statistical facts.
"The details of human agony are
multiplied beyond the telling."
'Life' magazine.
NARRATOR:
At the start of 1942,
almost all the news was bad.
The Soviet Union,
the United States' new ally,
was under unceasing attack
from the Germans,
who had encircled Leningrad
and reached the outskirts
of Moscow.
Japanese troops
had now taken Singapore,
the Gibraltar of the East,
and with it, all of Malaya.
They had seized Borneo
and Burma and Hong Kong.
And they had taken
Guam and Wake Island,
Makin and Tarawa.
There was not
a single American base
between Hawaii
and the Philippines.
But President Roosevelt
and British prime minister
Winston Churchill agreed
that, for the time being,
they would have to remain
on the defensive in the Pacific.
Germany, they decided,
with its vast armies
and mighty industrial machine,
was the greatest danger.
Victory in Europe would require
not only the mobilisation
of a generation of young men,
but also billions
of rounds of ammunition,
millions of guns, hundreds of
thousands of tanks and airplanes
and fleets of ships
to bring them to battle.
Producing all of that
would take time.
Meanwhile, the survival of
Britain and the Soviet Union
depended on
a steady stream of food
and fuel and weapons
from America.
BURT WILSON: When I was seven
years old, in Theodore Judah School,
a boy from England,
an English refugee,
came into our class.
His name was
William Murgathroid Buchanan.
We all called him Roid -
Roid Buchanan.
And we developed
a great friendship.
And, one day,
Roid came over to my house,
and I was upstairs,
and he called, "Burt! Burt!"
And I looked out the window,
and I said, "Hi, Roid.
What's going on?"
And Roid said, "Do you know what
"a dirty German sub
did to my father?"
And I said, "No. What?"
He said, "It killed him."
And I don't...
I didn't know
how to deal with that.
I went downstairs,
and we sat down under the tree
and talked awhile.
But it was still something that
I'd never had any experience
with, up until that time -
one of my best friends
telling me
that his father
was killed in a war.
NARRATOR: On the evening of
January 13, 1942,
as American troops tried to stop
the Japanese on Bataán,
a German U-boat surfaced
silently off Manhattan.
Its commander was astonished
but gratified to see that,
more than a month
after Germany declared war
on the United States,
America's largest city
was still ablaze with lights.
Using those lights
to silhouette his target,
he sent a torpedo
hissing toward the side
of an American oil tanker...
...then slipped back
beneath the sea
and moved south
in search of further prey.
Within 12 hours, he had sunk
seven more unarmed vessels.
The United States seemed
totally unprepared for this kind of war.
By the end of January,
U-boats would sink 25 tankers
along the east coast,
continuing a fierce struggle
for supremacy of the seas,
called the Battle
of the Atlantic,
and threatening to choke off
America's allies.
American beaches
were black with oil.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
All along the Gulf Coast
and all on the shores
of Mobile Bay,
we could go sit on the beach,
but we were not allowed
to light a fire,
because of the U-boats.
We heard often in Mobile
that ships were sunk
just as they went out
of Mobile Bay.
And we know this to be true,
because the life preservers
and the canned goods
washed up on our beaches.
NARRATOR: For a time,
the waters from Jacksonville, Florida,
to Galveston, Texas,
were considered
the most dangerous
shipping lane in the world.
"The only safe run,"
said one wary merchant seaman,
"is from St Louis to Cincinnati."
GLENN FRAZIER: I really fought
the first few days
for the good Old Glory...
you know, like everybody else,
you're saying,
"Good old United States.
"We're going to fight, we're
going to whip these Japanese
"in a matter
of six months," and so forth.
But when it really hit me that
this was not a short situation
and that they were hitting
us hard,
then I think I changed
pretty much to protect myself
and my fellow Americans,
and I think I was fighting more
to save my own life.
NARRATOR: Nearly 80,000
American and Filipino troops
had managed to escape
the Japanese around Manila
and take up positions
on the Bataán Peninsula.
Once again, General MacArthur's
planning had faltered.
Most supplies had been
left behind.
Rations had to be cut in half.
Bataán's humid forests
bred malarial mosquitoes.
Clean water was in short supply.
There was little medicine
on hand.
One field hospital had eight
operating tables...
and 1,200 battle casualties
in need of surgery.
Still the men struggled
to hold on...
...fighting off one attack
after another,
then retreating
halfway down the peninsula.
For weeks, the men on Bataán
continued to hope
that rescuers were coming.
Again and again, MacArthur
had assured them of it.
"Help is on the way,"
he promised.
FRAZIER: On the 'Voice of America',
one time, I remember it,
we were getting it
on short-wave radio.
It said, uh,
as far as the eye can see,
these ships and planes coming
to the Philippines.
We were told continuously that
we were getting reinforcements.
We were told that when we
retreated back into Bataán,
it would only be
for a few weeks.
NARRATOR: But no troops, no planes
had ever been dispatched.
They could not have made it
through, anyway.
The Japanese now controlled
the South Pacific.
"There are times," Secretary of War
Henry Stimson confided to his diary,
"when men must die."
By early March, three out
of four of Bataán's defenders
were incapacitated in some way -
sick, exhausted, wounded,
weak from hunger,
suffering from beriberi.
FRAZIER: At the end, close to the end,
there was one can of salmon
issued to 35 men
and some rice
and very little rice,
so our situation was getting -
deteriorating and getting worse
every day.
NARRATOR: MacArthur managed
to leave his quarters on Corregidor
to visit his men on Bataán
precisely once.
They began calling
him 'Dugout Doug'.
The soldiers' bitterness
intensified when,
acting under direct orders
from the president,
MacArthur, his wife,
4-year-old son
and 17 members of his staff
slipped out of Corregidor
in a PT boat.
From Australia, he issued
a brief statement.
"I came through," he said,
"and I shall return."
FRAZIER: When he left
and went to Australia,
that's what I call
doomsday for Bataán,
because we knew
then that we had to fight,
and he issued orders
to fight to the last man,
and that's, we knew what
our fate was going to be.
NARRATOR: On April 9, 1942,
Major General Edward L. King
sent a soldier forward
with a white flag.
It was the largest surrender
by the United States Army
in its history -
78,000 American
and Filipino troops.
General King asked a Japanese
officer just one question -
would his men be treated
decently.
"Yes," said the officer,
"we are not barbarians."
But Japanese tradition held
that those who surrendered
rather than die on the battlefield
were cowards,
unworthy of respect.
The prisoners were prodded
northward, 300 at a time.
They were to walk from Mariveles
to San Fernando,
then be loaded
onto railroad cars
for the journey to Camp O'Donnell
in central Luzon.
What followed would be
remembered
as the Bataán Death March.
FRAZIER: If we had known what was
ahead of us at the beginning
of the Bataán Death March, uh,
I would have taken death.
It was very, very difficult
for us to understand,
because we had had no contact
with the Japanese whatsoever
as to what these people
are all about
and what they're like.
And they immediately
started beating guys
if they didn't stand right
or if they were sitting down.
We didn't know
where we were going.
We didn't know anything.
And we were stopped on the way,
some of us were,
and searched and beat again.
And all our possessions
were taken away from us.
Some of them had rings that they
just cut the fingers off
and take the rings.
They poured the water out
of my canteen
to be sure that I didn't
have any, any water.
I saw them buried alive.
When a guy was bayoneted
or shot,
laying in the road and
the convoys were coming along,
I saw trucks that would just
go out of their way
to run over the guy
in the middle of the road.
And when by the time you have
15 or 20 trucks run over you,
you look like a smashed
tomato or something.
And I saw people that had
their throats cut,
because they would take
their bayonets
and stick it out through
the corner of the truck at night
and it would just be high enough
to cut their throats.
And beating with a rifle butt
until there just was
no more life in them.
I saw Filipino women cut.
Their stomachs were cut open.
Their throats were cut.
I saw Filipinos
and Americans beheaded
just with one swipe of a sabre.
I marched six days
and seven nights, never stopped,
I did not have but one sip
of water and no food.
Now, they say that you can't
do this, but I did.
When I got to the end
of the march after,
uh, at the end of the entire
march where I stopped
to get on a train -
they put us on a train -
my-my tongue wouldn't even
go back in my mouth.
And if you look and talk to
somebody about that,
they'll tell you that's
how close to death I was.
NARRATOR: No-one knows
precisely how many men died
on the Bataán Death March -
somewhere between 6,000 and
11,000 Filipinos and Americans.
And at the end of the march,
Camp O'Donnell
provided no relief.
An unfinished
Philippine army base,
surrounded by barbed wire
and machine gun towers,
with little water
and little shelter from the sun,
it would eventually hold nearly
60,000 miserable, desperate men.
Food was nothing but lugao,
watery rice soup
filled with weevils and worms.
It was best to try and swallow
it after dark,
one man recalled,
so as not to have to look at it.
Some 16,000 more Filipinos
and Americans would die
at Camp O'Donnell -
of dehydration, malnutrition,
malaria, beriberi, scurvy,
dysentery, hopelessness.
"Their bodies went by
in an endless column,"
one sergeant remembered.
"Day and night, they were
carried to the cemetery."
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
We had all been so distressed
about leaving our boys
in the Philippines.
There was no way of rescuing
them, we know now,
but at the time, we didn't know
that there were no ships.
Remember, they didn't tell us
how much had been sunk
at Pearl Harbor,
and we kept thinking,
"Why don't you go in there
"and get the boys
out of the Philippines?"
(MAN SHOUTS
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
NARRATOR: One day, Glenn Frazier
volunteered for burial detail.
FRAZIER:
On some days, we buried 250 men,
so I didn't know
that one day it might happen to me.
So, my idea was I had two sets
of dog tags.
And I said to myself,
"Well, I think I'll just throw
one of these sets of dog tags
"in the mass grave, so if I'm
alive when the war ends,
"there's no problem."
But if I'm missing or dead,
I didn't... I wanted my family
to know and have some kind
of ending, and so forth,
so they would think that I was
in this grave.
(EXPLOSION)
NARRATOR:
On May 6, 1942,
Corregidor, the last American
stronghold in the Philippines,
fell to the Japanese.
(SEAGULLS CRY)
SAM HYNES:
I went to Seattle in 1942.
One memory
is very clear and strong.
It's a Saturday, and I'm taking
a bus into the centre of town
and across the public square
in front of the town hall,
I guess it is...
And I see ahead of me
a line of people standing
patiently by a bus stop.
And as I approach, I see that
they're all Japanese
and that they're getting
onto buses.
And I realise that these are
the Japanese-American citizens
of Seattle and the neighbourhood
who are being sent off
to what amounted
to a concentration camp.
And I think,
"Well, those are my enemies."
But they don't look like enemies
standing there
in their American clothes
with their cardboard suitcases
waiting to be sent off
into the desert.
NARRATOR:
On February 19, 1942,
President Roosevelt had signed
Executive Order 9066.
Its tone was carefully neutral.
It authorised the War Department
to designate "military areas"
and then exclude
anyone from them
whom it felt to be a danger.
But it had a specific target...
...the more than 110,000 people
of Japanese ancestry
living along the west coast.
They were about to be forced
from their homes
and moved inland.
Thousands of German and Italian
aliens were also locked up,
but millions of German-
and Italian-American citizens
remained free to live their
lives as they always had.
Only Japanese-Americans
on the west coast
were singled out.
"A Jap's a Jap,"
said General John L. DeWitt
of the West Coast
Defence Command.
"It makes no difference whether he is
an American citizen or not.
"I don't want any of them."
Almost no-one protested
the government's plan,
which also classified
all Japanese-Americans
as unfit for military service.
DANIEL INOUYE:
1 -A is physically fit,
and 4-F,
something's wrong with you.
But 4-C means enemy alien.
And here I was, 17 years of age.
I considered myself
a good American but, uh...
made into an enemy.
NARRATOR: In Sacramento,
soon after Order 9066 was issued,
hand-lettered signs went up
all over town,
saying "Japs must go."
The orders to leave
arrived in May.
Susumu Satow and his family
could scarcely believe it.
They were given
one week's notice.
It was middle
of the harvest and...
but still, yet we had
to abandon it and leave.
And so, of course, we made
arrangement with our friends.
"Hey, come and pick
the strawberries
"because it's ready
to be marketed."
And so I imagine they did that.
And so you put just essentials
in your suitcase.
You know, first day,
when we had to pack up our thing
and go to the train,
I really wondered what's going
to happen to us?
NARRATOR: Asako Tokuno
was still a freshman
at Berkeley that spring.
Her parents and her grandfather
were evacuated first,
because they had been born
in Japan.
She and her sister
were left behind for a time
to close
the family flower business.
We all somehow gathered the
flowers, bunched them and got
them to the market, to the
flower market in San Francisco.
And so we were able to keep
the business going.
And all those flowers didn't go
to waste, you know.
They were just in the height of
their beauty at that time
of the year, getting ready
for Easter and all the holidays.
We were really...
kind of caught in the middle
when the war happened, although
no question about our loyalty
to our country, you know,
and how we felt.
(Voice breaks)
This is our country,
and when this whole evacuation
thing happened, I mean,
it was like we had no country,
because we weren't from Japan
and, and they took away our,
our rights, actually.
We couldn't protest, and we
wouldn't have protested,
because we had to do what the
government told us to do.
And so, uh, I think our parents
realised, of course,
they were, you know,
not citizens,
so they accepted
the whole thing.
But for us,
I think it was a lot harder,
the fact that we had no rights.
(PROJECTOR CLACKS)
NEWSREEL: This was
the Russian front in 1942.
The Germans advanced, looting,
torturing,
murdering as they went.
The casualties ran
into the millions.
They had driven 1,000 miles
deep into Russian territory,
but Russia, with her
'scorched earth' policy,
left nothing of value behind.
Wheat, which could not be
harvested, was set afire.
Bridges were blown up, dams,
railroads, power plants.
NARRATOR: Although the German
invasion of the Soviet Union
had stalled outside Moscow,
with both sides suffering
unspeakable losses,
a new Nazi offensive
in the spring of 1942
had sent more
than 225 divisions
steadily advancing
across Russia.
Millions of civilians
and soldiers died.
Soviet premier Josef Stalin
was demanding that the Allies
immediately open
a second front in the west
to relieve the pressure
on his beleaguered people.
But there was as yet
not a single Allied soldier
fighting in western Europe,
and there would not be
for a long time.
They simply weren't ready.
American planners
had a straightforward idea
of how to beat the Germans -
invade France
in the spring of 1943
and drive right for Berlin.
But the British were wary
of moving too fast.
"A defeat on the French coast,"
Winston Churchill warned,
was, "the only way in which we
could possibly lose this war."
Instead, he favoured attacking
German and Italian forces
in North Africa.
American commanders
thought invading Africa
would be a dangerous
and wasteful diversion...
...but Congressional elections
were coming up.
American voters were eager
for more offensive action
against the Axis.
President Roosevelt
overruled his generals.
The invasion of occupied France
would be delayed.
Instead, preparations were made
for American troops
to land in North Africa
at the end of 1942.
A bitter General George C.
Marshall, army chief of staff,
wrote privately that he
and his fellow commanders
had "failed to see
that the leader in a democracy
"has to keep
the people entertained."
('AMERICAN PATROL'
BY GLENN MILLER PLAYS)
SIDNEY PHILLIPS:
I did notice repeatedly
during the war that there would be
a sense of pride
in what you were a part of.
You would feel
the power of the military.
You would feel the power
of the convoy you were in,
the warships that
were surrounding you,
the weapons that you
were responsible for.
It was a strange feeling.
You knew you were
in great danger,
but you somehow felt safe
in that you were a part
of this great, powerful group.
NARRATOR:
In early August of 1942,
Private Sidney Phillips
of Mobile, Alabama,
and the 19,000 men
of the First Marine Division
steamed out
of Wellington, New Zealand
in a large convoy,
including all three
of America's carriers
in the South Pacific.
Their target was
so remote, so obscure,
that some of their officers
had trouble saying its name.
But that summer, Guadalcanal,
a 90-mile-long island
at the eastern end
of the Solomon chain,
covered with dense jungle
and coconut plantations,
had suddenly become one of the
most strategically important
spots in the Pacific.
Two separate commands
had the task of pushing
back the Japanese.
General Douglas MacArthur
was in command
of the South-western Pacific,
assigned to drive
from New Guinea
toward the Philippines
and Formosa.
Admiral Chester W. Nimitz
would use the marines
to climb a longer ladder
up the Solomons, the Gilberts,
the Marshalls, the Marianas,
the Volcano Islands,
the Ryukus.
He would begin
in the Solomons.
The Japanese had made landings
there, and construction crews
were hard at work
on an airstrip on Guadalcanal.
If they were allowed
to complete it,
Japanese warplanes
could choke off shipping lanes
between the United States
and Australia
and make the Allied
campaign impossible.
The marines, including
17-year-old Sid Phillips,
now a mortarman,
had been sent to stop them.
Their commander had assumed
his green troops would receive
another six months of training
before they saw combat.
They were armed with old
single-shot,
bolt-action rifles.
They had only 10 days
worth of ammunition,
and in order to get them into
the fight as fast as possible
their supply stocks had been
reduced from 90 days to 60.
The men called it
'Operation Shoestring'.
At dawn on August 7, 1942,
American land forces
went on the offensive
for the first time
in the Second World War.
No-one had any idea how long,
how bloody
and how consequential the battle
for Guadalcanal would be.
Sid Phillips's platoon
was part of the second wave
of marines to go ashore.
"We had been repeatedly told
"this would be the first
"ship-to-shore landing," he remembered,
"and nobody could more
than guess if such an idea
"would be successful.
"We braced ourselves, and
the craft slid up on the beach.
"We charged out, ready
to do or die," Phillips said,
"and there was the first wave
sitting, laughing at us."
There was virtually
no opposition.
The first American casualty
on Guadalcanal was a marine
who cut his hand
with a machete,
trying to open a coconut.
Americans seized
the unfinished airstrip
with little trouble
and renamed it Henderson Field
after a marine pilot
who was killed
during the Battle of Midway.
They began to prepare it
for American planes
with signs that read,
"Under new management."
Their orders were
to hold the field at all cost.
The enemy couldn't
be allowed to retake it.
Then... the Japanese attacked.
The American fleet offshore
was their first target.
PHILLIPS: The Japanese Navy came in
and sank all of our escorts.
NARRATOR: Four heavy cruisers
were lost, along with more than
1,800 American sailors.
PHILLIPS: They could have sunk
our supply ships, too,
but they didn't - it was at night,
and they didn't know
how successful they had been.
But the next day,
all of our supplies left,
and we were... we were there
without ever unloading
even our 10 days of supplies
that we had brought in with us.
We would have starved to death
if there hadn't have been
a big supply
of Japanese rice there.
NARRATOR: The marines
found themselves alone
and began to wonder if they,
like the men on Bataán,
had simply been abandoned.
With no support
from the sea or the air,
the men were strafed
and bombed daily...
...pounded by shells
from Japanese ships offshore
and under attack
from enemy troops
hidden in the jungle.
PHILLIPS: We understood that
we might be expendable.
It had become
sort of the established thing,
and, uh, we knew our country
was not yet, uh, heavily armed.
And yes, we did, uh, feel
that we might be expendable.
We really did.
NARRATOR: Phillips was among
those sent out to help recover
the bodies of marines
killed in an enemy ambush.
PHILLIPS: And it was about five miles
out to the ambush site
where all the American bodies
had been mutilated.
They had been beheaded and, uh,
had their genitals, uh,
stuffed in their mouths, and...
Uh... our battalion
never took a prisoner
that I know of after that.
I really...
I really don't remember
that we ever took a prisoner.
NARRATOR:
On the late afternoon of August 20,
after 13 harrowing days
on the island,
Phillips heard the sound
of approaching aircraft
and took cover as usual.
But this time,
the planes were American.
The marines cheered.
They were no longer alone.
PHILLIPS: It looked like Uncle Sam
was going to fight
for that miserable place,
after all.
NARRATOR: But at 2am
the next morning,
just hours after the first
American planes arrived,
a Japanese commander
sent 900 fresh troops
against marine positions
along the western bank
of a twisting jungle creek.
Its name was the llu River,
but because the maps
the marines had been issued
had it wrong,
the fierce firefight
that followed
would be remembered
as the Battle of the Tenaru.
PHILLIPS: At that time
on Guadalcanal,
almost every night
there would be some event
that would arouse everyone,
would keep everyone awake.
But this night it was different.
The whole world erupted,
and, uh... the lines became
just a wall of fire.
We knew it was the real event.
NARRATOR: The Japanese commander
was so certain
he could destroy the marines
that in his diary he had
filled in the entry for the day -
"21 August.
"Enjoyed the fruits of victory."
The Japanese kept coming
all night.
"Banzai," they screamed.
"Marine, you die!"
The marines just kept shooting.
PHILLIPS: We killed, I think,
over 900 Japanese
and lost something like
34 marines.
So it did our morale
a great deal of good.
NARRATOR: For the first time,
the supposedly invincible
lmperial Army had been stopped.
The humiliated commander,
who had predicted victory,
shot himself.
But the Battle of the Tenaru
settled nothing on Guadalcanal.
Japanese reinforcements
poured onto the island,
and the fighting
just went on and on.
A confusing,
vicious war of ambush
and counterattack.
A terrifying world
where random Japanese shells
would explode
among the entrenched
and embattled Americans.
PHILLIPS:
Some men could take it,
and, uh, some just physically
could not take it.
The sheer terror of knowing
that the next one
is going to have
your name on it -
when that goes on
and on and on and on,
you... you-you get
a strange feeling
in which you seem
to become detached,
and you just think,
"Well, maybe this will end
"and maybe it won't,
and maybe we'll all be blown up
"and maybe we won't,
but who cares?"
And you... you learn
to sort of live with it.
It is just a matter of fate.
You will either survive
if the Lord is willing
or you will not.
So there's really nothing
you can do.
And you just take it.
NARRATOR: Private Sid Phillips
turned 18 on September 2.
The next day, he got
his first letter from home
since he'd sailed
for Guadalcanal.
It was, he wrote back,
"the best birthday present
possible for me".
In late September,
some American reinforcements
finally made it through.
But nightly visits
by fast-moving Japanese ships
the marines called
the Tokyo Express
kept the enemy on the island
supplied and reinforced
as well.
Twice, the Japanese,
determined
to retake Henderson Field,
mounted full-scale assaults
on the airstrip.
Twice, the marines
beat them back.
Thousands of Japanese were
shot dead or blown to pieces.
Week after week,
the battle for Guadalcanal
ground on.
On November 12,
the Japanese Navy mounted
one last major offensive,
aimed at reinforcing
their forces
and dislodging the Americans
on Guadalcanal.
A much smaller number
of American ships steamed in
to try to stop them.
The naval battle that followed
went on for three days
and three nights.
PHILLIPS: You could see
the salvos of the ships,
and you could see
the naval shells
going through the air
like lightning bugs.
And you could see ships explode.
We didn't know if they
were American or Japanese.
We didn't know who was winning
or who was losing.
Sometimes when a ship
would explode, it would...
the concussion would actually
flap your clothes
miles and miles away.
But we did know that
our fate was being decided
and we would, uh, we would...
sit there sort of mystified
and horrified
by what was going on,
because we knew
thousands of sailors were
dying on one side or the other.
NARRATOR: Some 5,000
American sailors lost their lives
in the fighting
off Guadalcanal -
so many...
that the casualty figures
were again kept from the public.
Among those who died
were five brothers
from Fredericksburg, lowa,
who all served
on the cruiser 'Juneau' -
Joseph, Francis, Albert,
Madison and George Sullivan.
But Japan lost two battleships,
23 other warships,
600 aircraft,
and thousands
of sailors and airmen.
And most important
to Sid Phillips
and the men on Guadalcanal,
the enemy was no longer able
to resupply its forces
on the island.
The Japanese continued to fight,
but it was clear the Americans
would eventually prevail.
The last starving, desperate
Japanese troops on the island
would not be killed,
captured or evacuated
until February 1943.
21,000 Japanese soldiers
were lost.
Guadalcanal would prove
a crucial victory.
After six long months,
the Americans were beginning
to learn how to beat
the Japanese -
not only in the air
and on the sea,
but in the jungles,
where, over the next
three years,
the fighting would
only get worse.
Allied shipping lanes
to Australia remained open.
And there was more good news.
American and Australian forces
had also taken
the most important Japanese
strongholds on New Guinea.
Japan's expansion
had been stopped.
PHILLIPS: By the time
we left Guadalcanal,
which was December 22 of 1942,
we had been there
since August 7 -
everybody had lost
at least 25 pounds.
Our clothes were in rags.
We were covered with sores.
And we had nearly starved
to death two or three times.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
We did not realise
how desperate the marines
were on Guadalcanal
because the news never told us.
In fact, it was not till years
later when Sidney came home
that we found that their food
was down to fish heads and rice.
And that he was down
to 125 pounds
when they took him off
of Guadalcanal.
NARRATOR: More than 1,700
Americans had died on Guadalcanal.
Another 4,700 were wounded,
and thousands more
were seriously ill.
Sid Phillips had survived.
But his Uncle Charles Tucker,
a navy pilot
who had flown in and out
of Henderson Field, had not.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS: When we lost
Charlie, it made it very real to all of us.
And by that time, we had started
losing boys in the neighbourhood.
The boy up here on the corner
was a navy pilot
and he was killed.
The boy down the street
was an air force pilot
and he was missing in action.
We just... they started
disappearing all around us.
And my mother spent her time
going to visit the other
mothers, consoling them.
And it was a very,
very fearful time.
It really was.
You don't expect death
among people your age.
Old people die.
And then, you begin to see
that it's your contemporaries
are dying.
And therefore,
it is just conceivable
that you might die, too.
('AMERICAN ANTHEM' PLAYS)
NARRATOR: Luverne, Minnesota,
had been lucky so far.
No local family had lost
a son in the war.
But in Sacramento,
Mrs Lillian Cole had
received news
that her son David had perished
on the USS 'Arizona'
at Pearl Harbor.
She had been asked
by the government
"to keep secret for the present
"the name of the ship
on which he served."
Another Sacramento native,
airman Tom Burke,
died on a training mission
in Puerto Rico,
devastating
his younger brother, Earl.
In Waterbury, the family of
marine private Albert Boulanger
learned that he had been killed
on Guadalcanal,
not far from where Sid Phillips
of Mobile had been fighting.
Glenn Frazier was still
a prisoner of the Japanese,
but the girl he loved back
in Alabama had changed her mind
and was now waiting for him
to come home to her.