(BIRDS SCREECH IN DISTANCE)
(HORN HONKS)
NARRATOR: Early in 1943, an envelope
from the War Department arrived
at 1032 North Main Street
in Waterbury, Connecticut,
the home of the Ciarlo family.
They knew it was coming.
There were three boys
in the family.
Two were exempt from the draft -
Dom, married with one child
and another on the way,
and Tom, just 16
and still too young to go.
But the middle son, Corado,
was 19 and single,
working at Waterbury Steel Ball,
a perfect candidate
for the army.
His family and friends
called him 'Babe'.
OLGA CIARLO:
And he was the one to go.
Course, it was a shock
to all of us,
and my mother cried forever.
Forever.
But that's the way the war was.
So... it was a tough time.
And not only that,
but my father had passed away
in, uh, 1937.
My mother was
very, very heartbroken
at that time already.
My mother would take the bus
and go up to the cemetery
all by herself.
She couldn't speak
a word of English.
And all she could tell the man
on the bus was, "Cemetery."
And then to know that my brother
was going off to war,
she was scared.
She didn't want to go through
this all over again, so...
It was hard times,
very hard times.
(HARP PLAYS ARPEGGIOS)
(BIG BAND PLAYS
'LET'S GET LOST' INTRO)
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
Here's number six,
a song by Frank Sinatra.
(Sinatra sings) # Let's get lost... #
MAN: "May 9, 1943.
"Dearest Mom and family,
"We are listening
to the Lucky Strike program,
"and Frank Sinatra is singing
'Let's Get Lost',
"and what a voice he's got.
"Tell Mom not to worry about me,
'cause I'll be home
soon enough.
"I am calling Mom to give her
Mother's Day greetings.
"I will have to wait
five or six hours
"for the call to go through,
but it is worth it."
# Let's defrost... #
"From now until I get through
with my basic training,
"I will be pretty busy,
"so if Mom doesn't hear from me
for a few days,
"you explain to her
that I am alright,
"but just busy.
"Love, Babe."
(Sinatra scats softly)
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
NARRATOR:
By January of 1943,
Americans had been at war
for more than a year.
US Navy warplanes had stopped
the Japanese advance
at the Battle of Midway,
destroying four enemy carriers
and inflicting the first defeat
on the lmperial Navy in 350 years.
The marines
had taken Guadalcanal
in the Solomon Islands...
...and American
and Australian forces
had defeated the Japanese
at Buna
on the island
of Papua New Guinea.
But the 4,000-mile march
toward the Japanese home islands
was just beginning.
And thousands of Americans
were still held prisoner
by the Japanese,
including 9-year-old
Sascha Weinzheimer,
whose family came
from the Sacramento Valley,
and Corporal Glenn Frazier,
from Ft Deposit, Alabama.
Meanwhile,
in the snows around Stalingrad,
Hitler's dream of expanding his
empire eastward across Russia
was ending in catastrophe
as the Red Army annihilated
his surrounding armies.
But the Germans,
with their vast war machine,
still occupied
most of western Europe,
and the Allies had not yet
been able to agree on a plan
or a timetable to dislodge them.
For the time being,
they would have to be content
to nip at the edges
of Hitler's enormous domain.
American troops were now ashore
in North Africa,
ready to test themselves
for the first time
against the German
and Italian armies.
For the people
of Mobile, Alabama,
Luverne, Minnesota,
Sacramento, California,
Waterbury, Connecticut,
and every other town in America,
the war would dictate
the rhythm and pace of life
in ways they could not have
imagined a year before.
And the sense
of national purpose
Franklin Roosevelt's New Deal
had brought to the battle
against the Great Depression
was now fully focused
on winning this war.
PRESIDENT ROOSEVELT:
I do not prophesy
when this war will end.
But I do believe
that this year of 1943...
will give to the United Nations
a very substantial advance
along the roads
that lead to Berlin
and Rome and Tokyo.
(APPLAUSE)
A tremendous, costly,
long enduring task,
in peace as well as in war,
is still ahead of us.
But as we face
that continuing task,
we may know that the state
of this nation is good,
the heart of this nation
is sound,
the spirit of this nation
is strong,
the faith of this nation
is eternal.
(APPLAUSE)
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
Roosevelt carried
a real message
of confidence with his voice.
He gave us all the confidence
that we could do
anything he asked us to do,
and certainly the boys could do
anything he asked 'em to do.
And he was the powerful,
driving force.
Now, England had Churchill...
...but we had Roosevelt.
And from the time
he announced Pearl Harbor,
and announced
that we would go to war,
we were all behind him.
(BENNY GOODMAN'S BAND PLAYS
'IN A SENTIMENTAL MOOD')
WARD CHAMBERLIN:
The lucky thing was that...
the American Army didn't get
its first taste of battle
going across the Channel, the
way some people wanted us to.
They had to go through that...
that North African thing,
which was a learning experience
and a very expensive one.
Our army got to be goddamn good,
but at the beginning
they were like anybody else -
they weren't too good at it.
NARRATOR: At an Allied conference
in Casablanca in January, 1943,
everything went well
for the cameras,
and President Roosevelt
and British prime minister
Winston Churchill
announced they would accept
nothing less
than unconditional surrender
from the enemy.
NEWSREEL:
...unconditional surrender.
NARRATOR: But behind the scenes,
both men were concerned.
The Allies were still trying
to find ways to work together.
The previous November,
Allied troops
under General Dwight Eisenhower
had made coordinated landings
in Morocco and Algeria
without meeting much resistance.
But Hitler strengthened his
forces in neighbouring Tunisia.
Eisenhower's troops
were meant to race east
to engage the enemy,
while British general
Bernard Montgomery
and his Eighth Army
pursued German general
Erwin Rommel's Afrika Korps
westward from Egypt.
NEWSREEL: Tunisia,
next door to Italian Libya,
is at the rear of the Axis Army.
It's the next objective
for the American half
of the nutcracker campaign,
closing in on Rommel
from the west as the British
smash from the east.
The aim is to chase the Axis
out of North Africa,
threaten Italy
and other Nazi-dominated
territories in Europe,
and open shorter supply lines
to Russia.
That's the meaning
of the American drive to Tunis.
(WIND WHISTLES)
NARRATOR: After two months
of sporadic fighting,
the battle for North Africa
suddenly intensified.
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
(MEN SHOUT, EXPLOSIONS)
On February 14, Rommel sent
his seasoned veterans
against the untested, poorly
led, and ill-equipped Americans.
His goal, he said,
was to instil in them
"an inferiority complex
of no mean order".
And for a time,
he succeeded.
With the American forces
was Private Charles Mann,
a farmer's son
from Luverne, Minnesota.
CHARLES MANN: It was good,
I guess, that you were afraid,
but it did not interfere with
what your real thinking was
because you had one idea
and that was that you
was gonna make it.
NARRATOR: Rommel's forces
quickly overwhelmed the Americans
whose armour proved no match
for German Panzers.
Some soldiers called
the Allied tanks Ronsons,
after the cigarette lighter,
for their propensity
to burst instantly
into flame when hit.
(HEART BEATS RHYTHMICALLY)
Stuka dive-bombers screamed
down upon the Americans.
Some men held,
others panicked.
Survivors fled westward
across the open plain.
They would not stop
for 50 miles.
CHAMBERLIN: They didn't know
what the hell they were doing.
Guys never been
under fire before,
and, uh, when they got hit,
they didn't know what to do,
and they retreated,
and they had terrible
leadership.
It was chaos.
And war's always chaos.
The commander
of the American troops there
was a visible coward.
He built a... a, uh...
headquarters for himself
in a rock chamber
some 20 miles back
from the line
with the argument that he could
communicate better from there.
So, he was appalling.
NARRATOR: After beating back
two American counterattacks,
the Germans poured westward
through the Kasserine Pass,
gateway to Algeria,
threatening the Allies' main
supply base at Tébessa.
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
(EXPLOSIONS, MEN SHOUT)
(AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE)
(MEN SHOUT)
In two weeks of fighting,
6,000 Americans were lost.
45 soldiers from the little town
of Red Oak, lowa,
were killed
or reported missing.
A third of those who lived
were victims
of neuropsychiatric disorders
brought on by the first
experience of battle
for which they were totally
unprepared.
2,400 surrendered.
The Americans simply didn't
know how to fight,
a British commander said,
and if they didn't
learn quickly,
they "will play no useful
part whatsoever"
in the invasion of Europe.
General Eisenhower agreed.
"Our operations to date,"
he confided grimly to a friend,
"will be condemned,
in their entirety,
"by all war college classes
for the next 25 years."
The correspondent Ernie Pyle
was with the troops
and struggled to make sense
of what he'd seen.
MAN: "You folks at home
must be disappointed
"at what happened to our
American troops in Tunisia.
"Personally, I feel that some
such setback as this -
"tragic though it is
for many Americans,
"for whom it is now too late -
"is not entirely
a bad thing for us.
"It's alright to have
a good opinion of yourself,
"but we Americans
are so smug with our cockiness
"we somehow feel that just
because we're Americans
"we can whip our weight
in wildcats."
FUSSELL: But I think every ground war
has to begin that way
because what's going to happen
to people is so unthinkable.
So it's only after you've been
in a little while
that you're capable
of understanding
what's happening well
enough to do well at it.
And you have to do well at it.
NARRATOR: The Americans
pulled themselves together.
Air strikes staggered
the German advance.
American artillery
moved in to hammer
German tank columns
with howitzer shells.
The enemy was running out
of ammunition, food, gasoline,
while the Allies
were well-supplied
with everything they needed
to keep fighting.
Fearing a counterattack,
Rommel pulled back
through the Kasserine Pass.
Eisenhower replaced
his inept commander
with a major general
named George S. Patton,
who would transform
the beleaguered 2nd Corps
into a determined,
capable force.
MANN:
It was purely a matter of Patton
using different tactics
to beat them suckers.
That's what it amounted to.
We'd done so poorly towards,
uh, Rommel's forces,
but next time around
we'd done it right.
NARRATOR:
Now the Allies pushed forward,
surrounding the German
and Italian armies
on Cape Bon in northern Tunisia.
(LOUD EXPLOSIONS AND GUNFIRE)
On May 12, after three more
months of fighting,
the last Axis troops
in North Africa surrendered -
a quarter of a million men.
(BENNY GOODMAN'S BAND PLAYS
'IN A SENTIMENTAL MOOD')
The lessons the Allies had
learned had come hard -
76,000 men had been lost,
including
Captain Richards Aldridge,
a flyer from Mobile,
who was reported missing,
and Private Charles Mann
from Luverne,
who had been wounded
in the neck by shrapnel.
MANN:
It bled like a stuck hog.
If that had been
an inch higher or lower,
I'd have had it.
NARRATOR: The prolonged
6-month campaign in North Africa
had forced the Allies to
postpone the planned invasion
of France once again -
from August until
spring of the following year.
But the Allies had proven
that they could work together
toward victory.
And the inexperienced Americans
were beginning
to learn how to fight.
MAN: "The most vivid change
in our men
"is the casual
and workshop manner
"in which they now talk
about killing.
"They have made
the psychological transition
"from the normal belief that
taking human life is sinful
"over to a new,
professional outlook
"where killing is a craft.
"To them, now, there is nothing
morally wrong about killing.
"In fact,
it is an admirable thing.
"So you at home need never
be ashamed
"of our American fighters.
"The greatest disservice
you folks at home can do
"for our men over here
"is to believe we are at last
over the hump.
"For actually -
and over here we all know it -
"the worst is yet to come."
Ernie Pyle.
NEWSREEL: An army of 150,000 men,
women and children
invaded an American city -
whites, Negroes, Indians,
Creoles, Cajuns.
They came from every corner
of the land,
their roots in every curve
of the globe -
Moscow, Indiana, Warsaw,
North Dakota, Hamburg, California,
Milan, Missouri,
Baghdad, Kentucky.
Some came out of patriotism,
some out of grim necessity,
some for a richer life.
All came to do a warjob.
This could be any one
of a hundred
great American war centres.
It happens
to be Mobile, Alabama,
but the story is the same
in every war town in America.
NARRATOR: The chronic
unemployment that had eaten at Mobile
and every other American town
for more than a decade
during the Depression
was over.
(DRUMS BEAT INTRO
TO 'SING, SING, SING')
Idle factories were back
in business.
(BENNY GOODMAN'S BAND PLAYS
'SING, SING, SING')
Mass production
was an American invention,
but now it reached levels
its inventors
could never have imagined.
Nearly all manufacturing
was converted to the war effort.
In 1941, more than 3 million
cars had been manufactured
in the United States.
Only 139 more were made
during the entire war.
Instead,
Chrysler made fuselages.
General Motors made
airplane engines,
guns, trucks and tanks.
And at its vast Willow Run Plant
in Ypsilanti, Michigan -
67 acres of assembly lines under
a single roof
that one observer called
"The Grand Canyon
of the mechanised world" -
the Ford Motor Company performed
something like a miracle
24 hours a day.
The average Ford car
had some 15,000 parts.
The B-24 Liberator
long-range bomber had
1,550,000 parts.
One came off the line
at Willow Run every 63 minutes.
If the American military
wasn't yet quite equal
to the Germans or the Japanese,
American workers would soon be
able to build ships and planes
faster than the enemy could sink
them or shoot them down.
By the end of the war,
more than one-half of
all the industrial production
in the world would take place
in the United States.
(COUNT BASIE'S
'THE BASIE BOOGIE' PLAYS)
Mobile was among
the fastest-growing
of all American war towns.
Even before the war began,
powerful Democratic congressman
Frank Boykin landed his city
a $26 million defence contract
that transformed
the Municipal Airport
into Brookley Field,
a major army air force
supply depot
and bomber modification centre
that provided
17,000 civilian jobs.
In 1940, Gulf Shipbuilding
had had 240 employees.
By 1943, it had 11,600.
In the same period,
Alabama Dry Dock went from 1,000
workers to almost 30,000.
They included Hank Williams,
the future country music star,
and the parents of future
home run hitter Hank Aaron.
CLYDE ODUM:
It was seven days a week.
And during the war
when it was so strong,
it was 12-hour days,
five days a week.
10 hours on Saturday,
8 hours on Sunday.
You felt like you've had a week off.
There was such
an influx of people
that they got
on each other's nerves.
And there wasn't enough,
uh, watering holes
to entertain everybody.
And so they'd get out
and have fights and drink
and all that kinda stuff.
NARRATOR: African-Americans
streamed into Mobile
from all over the South
in search of defence work
and a fresh start.
They found both.
But they also found
the same kind of discrimination
they had known at home.
JOHN GRAY: Mobile was
a pretty fair-minded city.
And before this time, whites and
blacks got along pretty good
as long as you had
the status quo.
Uh, but when blacks began
to get homes,
to buy homes and to ride
in big cars,
uh, it, it turned
some people off.
The policemen would stop you
and give you a ticket.
My cousin got a ticket
for driving 16 miles an hour in
a 15-mile zone.
NEWSREEL: 150,000 people,
10 full military divisions -
the civilian equivalent of
Rommel's entire African army -
bivouacked without warning
in the narrow confines
of one peaceful Southern city.
Less then three years ago,
you might have walked blocks
in Mobile without encountering
a person.
Today you stop to scratch
your head
and a line forms behind you.
No wonder there's such a chaos
and congestion of traffic.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
Mobile became so crowded
in six months
that people were living
in vacant lots.
They put up tents
People went
into the boarding houses,
and one room would hold
as many as four men.
They would sleep
for so many hours,
get up and leave the bed,
go to work and another man
would take the bed.
NEWSREEL: This was
a neighbourhood grocery store.
These girls - welders, checkers,
and machinists.
NARRATOR: Emma Belle Petcher was
from the tiny town of Millry, Alabama.
Most of her girlfriends had
taken secretarial jobs
once they'd gotten out
of high school,
but Emma Belle, like her father,
loved to take things apart.
PETCHER: I always fixed my own
appliances at home, growing up.
If the washing machine got
a nail in the pump
I took the pump apart
and took the nail out
of the housing of the pump
and, you know, run...
I didn't have the patience to
call in a repairman
who would be, maybe three days
later and he wouldn't tell you
morning or evening, so I'd empty
the washing machine,
turn it upside down,
take the screwdrivers
and, course I, I knew how
to do all this stuff.
('PISTOL PACKIN' MAMA' BY JIMMIE
LUNCEFORD & HIS ORCHESTRA
PLAYS)
So, I packed my little cardboard
suitcase and got on the bus
and went to Mobile.
So they put me in a school to
learn airplane accessories -
that was starters, generators,
alternators
and some other thing.
So we did those parts,
just those little instruments,
over and over and over
and over until graduation.
We had to almost put them
together blindfolded.
NARRATOR: Petcher breezed through
all her tests
and got a job working
on airplanes.
By 1943, 6 million women
had entered the work force,
and nearly half of them were
working in defence plants.
'Life' magazine paid tribute to
the mythical "Rosie the Riveter"
as "neither drudge nor slave,
but the heroine of a new order".
In Mobile, 2,500 women worked
at Alabama Dry Dock,
1,200 at Gulf Shipbuilding
and 750 at Brookley Field
where Emma Belle Petcher worked
her way up to inspector,
responsible for quality control.
PETCHER: You would be assigned
'X' number of planes
to be responsible for.
I was to inspect the torque
in the screws in the wings,
and go into the gas tanks,
and crawl up in the wings
with flashlights.
Well, I was so conscientious, I
just didn't make the mistakes.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS: I worked at
the government nursery school
which was downtown
in Christ Church Rectory,
and we had the children
of the women that worked
in the shipyards.
Rosie the Riveter would come
bring her child
in all of her headgear and her
togs that she did
her riveting in and drop her
precious little baby off
and go down and work all day
and come back at 5:00
and pick the child up.
NEWSREEL: And the story of Mobile
is the story
of every American war town.
MAN: "Dearest Mom and family,
"I am feeling fine
"and I hope to hear the same
from all of you, always.
"I am at Camp Patrick Henry,
Virginia.
"I would have called you up,
"but there are no public
telephones at the camp.
"I feel bad because
I didn't call Mom up,
"but I thought for sure
"that I would go to New York
or Massachusetts.
"I would have done anything
in the world
"to be home that weekend.
"From here I don't know where we
are going and when we are going,
"but I am almost positive
it is overseas.
"There is nothing
to worry about,
"because I will not see action
for a long time
"and the war will be over soon.
"Love, Babe."
MAN: "To the War Department,
Washington, DC,
"Can you furnish me with the
exact status of my two sons -
"Walter Weinzheimer
and Conrad Ludwig Weinzheimer -
"who were American citizens
but resided in the Philippines
"at the outbreak of the war?
"Stop.
"Are they military
or civilian prisoners,
"dead or alive or missing?
"Stop.
"Such information is
urgently needed.
"Ludwig Weinzheimer -
"Thornton Farms,
Thornton, California."
NARRATOR: Ludwig Weinzheimer
was a well-to-do farmer
in the Sacramento Valley.
Just before Pearl Harbor,
his daughter-in-law had written
to him from Manila,
asking if his sons
and their families,
including his grand-daughter
Sascha,
shouldn't come home
to California.
War seemed very close.
The old man told them
all to stay where they were.
The rumours of war were
exaggerated, he said.
Now, filled with guilt,
he was frantic to find out
what had happened to his two
sons and their families.
He wrote to everyone
he could think of -
old friends, the Red Cross,
the War Department,
the State Department.
In October,
the State Department told him
the family had been reported
to be in the Santo Tomas
internment camp in Manila,
but it could provide
no further information.
GIRL: "On February 15, 1943,
"a few days
after my 10th birthday,
"we moved into
the Santo Tomas camp.
"We left Nila, our amah,
crying loudly.
"After bowing to the sentry
on duty,
"we went through the gate,
where Daddy was waiting for us."
Sascha Weinzheimer.
NARRATOR: For almost 14 months
after Manila fell to the Japanese,
Sascha Weinzheimer, her mother,
her sister, Doris,
and her younger brother, Buddy,
had managed
to stay out of the camp
the Japanese had established
for foreign civilians on the
campus of Santo Tomas University
on the city's outskirts.
But after Sascha reported
having seen
Japanese soldiers drowning
a small Filipino boy,
her mother decided
they would be safer
in the prison than outside it.
Their father had been imprisoned
there for more than a year -
so long that his young son
no longer recognised him.
There were now some 4,000
prisoners at Santo Tomas -
American and British, Dutch and
Norwegian, Polish and French.
Immediately, the Japanese
didn't want to have anything
to do with us.
They weren't going to feed us.
They weren't going to follow
the Geneva Convention rules.
So you were left
to fend for yourself.
NARRATOR: The Philippine Red Cross
provided rice.
Filipino friends
of the internees
passed canned foods and fresh
vegetables through the fence.
Families were permitted to build
themselves bamboo shanties
with palm leaves for roofs
in which to spend the day.
At night, they were herded into
crowded dormitories
in the main building.
Everyone was assigned a job.
GIRL: "It was funny to see
bank presidents
"and other men like that
"cleaning toilets
and garbage cans.
"Mother had toilet duty
four times a week.
"There were all kinds
of people in camp.
"Some were hard workers,
like Daddy.
"Others were gripers
who liked to talk a lot
"and goldbricks who didn't
do anything at all."
NARRATOR: The prisoners organised
churches, schools, police,
even a 'morality patrol',
meant to keep teenagers from
disappearing together
into dark corners.
Your world becomes very small.
And you don't think beyond your
little environment,
because everything that's
important to you is right there.
It's not in the States.
It's not back at the plantation.
It's right there.
So you have to make do with what
you can in this small sphere.
GIRL: "We got our chow
from the lines in tin cans.
"Then we would
eat in our shanty,
"and Mother said that
no matter what happened
"we would eat off
our bridge table
"with a tablecloth
with our coloured dishes
"and a small bowl of flowers
so long as we could."
Sascha Weinzheimer.
(OFFICER SHOUTS IN JAPANESE)
(TROOPS SHOUT IN JAPANESE)
GLENN FRAZIER: We didn't know
anything about the Japanese
when we were captured,
and they didn't know anything
much about us.
We most certainly didn't know
their language.
(Speaks Japanese)
And to be able to be compelled
or, or made obey an order
that you didn't even know
what the order was -
a misunderstanding
or not any, any idea -
and this depending
on you maybe surviving...
NARRATOR: Glenn Frazier had
endured the Bataán Death March
and weeks of imprisonment
at Camp O'Donnell
in the Philippines,
where survival had seemed
so unlikely,
he had thrown one of his dog
tags into a mass grave
that held the bodies of many
of his fellow prisoners.
That way, he thought,
if they were ever recovered
his family back in Alabama
would find some comfort
in knowing
what had happened to him.
As the marines had struggled
to take Guadalcanal,
Frazier was shipped
all the way to Japan,
to a prisoner of war camp
near Osaka.
FRAZIER: The number
that the Japanese gave us
was like a serial number.
And mine was 6-32.
Roko naka san juni,
is the number in Japanese.
And they put it on your clothes.
You had a little button saying,
uh, 6-32.
And it was, uh,
it was part of your records,
and I kept that number all the
way through my days in Japan.
NARRATOR: The commandant told
Frazier and his fellow prisoners
they would be treated well,
as "guests of the Emperor".
They were not.
What little food they had
was rotten.
Barracks were unheated.
The prisoners were divided
into 10-man shooting squads.
If one member tried to escape,
he and all the others
would be shot.
Frazier developed double
pneumonia and nearly died.
All the prisoners were made
to work in Japanese foundries
or on the docks,
loading and unloading ships.
Small children jeered and cursed
as they walked to
and from the docks,
calling them cowards
for having surrendered,
rather than fight to the death.
Guards beat the prisoners
regularly,
and the smallest infraction
of rules could prove fatal.
One day I was walking, coming
back from a detail that day
on the streets of Osaka.
And the weather was cold.
And I put my hands
in my pocket,
and I'm walking along with
everybody else.
When we got to the camp
and they checked us in,
this guard pointed me out
and called me out.
And, uh, said, "Why did you have
your hands in your pocket?"
I said, "Because I was cold."
So they took me in the
commander's office
and the interpreter says,
"That's against
the military code.
"Soldiers do not walk
with hands in pockets."
And I said, "Well, I'm not a
soldier, I'm a prisoner of war."
So the commander banged his fist
on his desk, and -
he was a major -
and got up and he says,
uh, the interpreter said,
"He don't like your attitude."
So, he come up and he started
arguing with me,
and I couldn't... I couldn't
understand anything he said.
So he pulled his sabre out
and he said he was going to
"make an example of you,
"so that the other men will
understand
"they have to obey orders".
So he puts his sword
to my throat, here,
and nicked me a little bit,
and I could feel a little bit of
blood coming down.
So, he, the interpreter said,
"He's going to execute you."
So he asked me if I had
any last words to say.
And I looked him straight in the
eye and I said, "He can kill me,
"but he cannot kill my spirit.
"And my spirit's going
to lodge in his body
"and haunt him
until the day he dies."
And he had a frown
come over his face
and took three steps backward
and lowered his sword
and ordered me to be put
in a five-by-five-by-five
cubicle in the ground.
I had never seen
a Japanese back down
in front of any of his
subordinates
until that particular time.
Because once they
got to that point,
they went through with it,
regardless of the results.
(TYPEWRITER CLACKS)
MAN: "Luverne, Minnesota.
"All of us use the phrase
'after the war'
"so much it almost
becomes meaningless.
"The motorist uses it
when he thinks of new tyres,
"a new model car,
"and the right to drive as fast
and as far as he pleases.
"But for all of us, although
the words aren't often spoken,
"it means the day
when you boys come home.
"It means,
if you had witnessed it -
"a portion of a little drama
as we did this week -
"the ecstatic happiness
and the wild gladness
"of thousands
of family reunions.
"The other morning an unshaven,
weary uniformed man,
"with a string of gaily-coloured
ribbons on his breast,
"slipped off the morning train
and was driven to his home.
"Instead of going
in the front way,
"he went around the back,
unnoticed.
"Probably he just wanted
to feast his eyes on home.
"His children were watching
at the front,
"their noses almost boring holes
in the window panes,
"as they watched
for a sign of Daddy.
"Nobody needs to describe
their shrieks of joy
"when he walked in from
the back door to surprise them.
"If you could
have seen them later,
"hanging on to his hands
for dear life
"as though they could hold him
home forever,
"you couldn't have helped getting
a bit misty yourself."
Al Mclntosh,
'Rock County Star Herald'.
JIM SHERMAN: I think,
particularly in Luverne,
there was this general feeling
of we're in the right,
we're doing the right thing,
and all of the things
that we're doing, collectively,
sort of brought a lot of people
together.
It was in a totally
different feeling
that I don't think can ever
be duplicated, ever.
I just don't think that you
could have that sense of oneness
that, that we had
when we were growing up.
NARRATOR: At home and overseas
Americans were slowly,
sometimes painfully,
learning to work together.
But President Roosevelt warned
the country in the summer of 1943
"it's not too much to say
that we must pour into this war
"the entire strength and intelligence
and willpower of the United States"
before victory could be won.