NARRATOR: By the late summer
of 1943,
the United States had been at war
for more than 20 months.
Its factories and shipyards
were now performing miracles of
manufacturing around the clock.
But its armed forces
were still far from ready
to mount an assault on the Germans
occupying western Europe.
Meanwhile, along a thousand-mile front,
the Soviets were struggling
to hurl the Nazis from their soil.
The Americans and British
did what they could
to help relieve the pressure
on the Russians.
American airmen, including Earl Burke
of Sacramento, California,
would be called upon
to defy preposterous odds
and begin to bring the war
to the heart of Germany itself.
While Private 'Babe' Ciarlo,
an Italian immigrant's son
from Waterbury, Connecticut,
would find himself battling foul weather,
hostile terrain
and fierce enemy resistance
to liberate the land
where his parents had been born.
SAM HYNES:
Dying is different for pilots,
for aviation personnel.
On the ground, in the infantry,
there's a corpse.
It might be blown apart,
but there's a foot
or an arm or something.
And it's very close.
In aviation, the planes tend
to go away and not come back.
Even if someone dies
in the air with you
the plane explodes,
it falls to the ground
at a place you'll never see.
I had a number of friends
killed during the war...
...but I never saw
any of their bodies.
EARL BURKE:
The war came home to my family
on a very gut level.
Uh, my Uncle Earl,
who lived in Sacramento
called me one night and said,
"I want you to come over
to my house."
He was only a couple blocks
away, so I went over there.
And he showed me an article
in the newspaper that said
there was a crash
in Puerto Rico.
And my only brother I had,
older brother,
was listed as killed
in an airplane accident.
And we tried for 12 hours
on the telephone to try to get
to Puerto Rico to confirm that
this was, indeed, my brother.
And finally, somebody says,
"Yes, it was a Tom Burke
from Sacramento."
Well, five days later,
we got the telegram
telling that he had been killed.
So that's how my war came to us.
And there was no talking
about what had happened.
My parents were very stoic.
And I only heard
my mother cry once.
It was in her bedroom, since she
never cried in front of me.
So it was a tough thing
for those two people.
For me, I lost a brother.
"Yeah, damn it.
"We gonna do something about it."
Then I got the crazy idea
that I was going to enlist
and win the war.
(Chuckles)
It was kind of for Tommy...
in a way.
Not so consciously.
I didn't say,
"This is for you, Tom."
No, I never did that.
But, uh, I enlisted.
I'm glad I did.
(BENNY GOODMAN'S
'ON THE ALAMO' PLAYS)
NARRATOR:
Earl Burke joined the army
and trained first
at Fort Lewis in Seattle
where, he remembered, he learned
"how to pick up cigarette butts,
"paint anything that didn't move
"and salute anything that did".
Like his late brother,
he wanted to take part
in the air war.
After serving at a base
outside Reno, Nevada,
where he loaded bombs
onto heavy bombers,
he was sent across the country
to Camp Shanks, New Jersey,
and then on June 1, 1943,
boarded the 'Queen Mary',
part of the seemingly
endless stream of Gls now headed
for England to prepare
for the invasion of France.
Soon after he got there,
he happened upon
two old friends from Sacramento,
twin brothers named
Richard and Robert Egger.
BURKE: I was in
a Red Cross hut on a base.
It was kind of
a PX type of thing.
So as we were drinking the beer
and all that,
having a good time, they said,
"Well, why don't you
get with us?"
They were tail and ball turret
gunners on a B-17.
It sounded like fun.
What the heck, you know?
I was 19.
I could've had a lot of fun.
They seemed to be having
a lot of fun.
They were not scared at all.
So I says, "OK,"
so the next day I went down
and got an application
and filled out the application.
And at that time, they were
losing a lot of bombers.
They were losing 60 at a time.
They were losing
over 600 men in a raid.
So they were taking anybody.
They were taking cooks.
They were taking truck drivers,
mechanics - anybody that could
get into an airplane.
Nothing was going
to happen to me - no way.
I'm 19 years old.
I'm gonna conquer this world.
Nothing was going to happen
to me, you know... no.
NARRATOR: Until the Allies
were able to launch
their long-planned
invasion of Europe,
the only way to weaken
German power
on the Continent
was from the air.
Since bombing during the day
attracted anti-aircraft fire
and swarms of German fighters,
the British preferred
to fly their missions
at night.
But when aerial surveys showed
that only one in five
British bombs had fallen
within five miles of its
intended industrial target,
their policy shifted
to what was called
area bombing.
Relentless night-time raids
on German cities,
intended to destroy
not only factories,
but whole neighbourhoods
and "break the spirit
of the people".
While the British continued
to bomb German cities at night,
the Americans decided to take on
the much more dangerous task
of bombing defence industries
by day.
The Americans believed
the B-17 -
their big, 4-engine bomber -
superior to anything else
their Allies or the enemy had.
It was called
the Flying Fortress,
because it was armed
with as many as nine
.50-calibre machine guns,
and each plane was fitted out
with the revolutionary
Norden bombsight,
said to be so accurate
it made it possible to
"drop a bomb in a pickle barrel
"from 20,000 feet".
Around-the-clock bombing
took a fearful toll.
In late July, British bombs
set off a whirling firestorm
that burned
or asphyxiated at least
40,000 German civilians
in and around Hamburg,
taking almost as many lives
in one week
as the German Luftwaffe
had taken
in eight months
of bombing Britain.
But the German will to resist
only intensified,
just as the will of Londoners
had intensified
during the Blitz.
Hamburg's factories
were soon back in business.
Meanwhile, American airmen
were suffering terrible losses.
MAN: Keep your eyes open.
MAN 2: Three planes, 9:00.
MAN 3: I got my sights.
(ENGINE ROARS)
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
MAN: B-17 out of control at 3:00.
NARRATOR: Earl Burke's friends
from Sacramento,
the Egger twins,
would both be shot down
in the coming months.
BURKE: The number of missions
that you had to fly
before you were returned
to the States
and/or given a non-combat job
was 25 at that point.
The average number of missions
flown in 1943
for a combat person
was only 14.
If you got to 14,
you were usually dead.
NARRATOR:
Earl Burke was now a member
of the 854th Chemical Warfare
Company,
part of the 384th Bomb Group
in the US Army's
Eighth Air Force.
On September 16, 1943,
he clambered
into the ball turret
for the first time.
Their target was the German
submarine facilities at Nantes,
on the French coast.
BURKE: The ball turret
is underneath the aircraft.
You put your knees up against
your ears... almost.
Almost like a foetal position,
'cause you're up in there jammed
in that little thing,
and you got
these horrendous guns
in front of you, two of 'em.
Didn't pass my mind that I was
getting into trouble...
...till the first mission.
We're flying about 28,000 feet.
And, uh, the first time
I tried my turret
to see whether I could fire,
you know, possibly, uh...
do a reasonable job
of tracking a fighter plane,
I didn't know my right foot
from my left foot.
I thought I wanted
the gun to go that way,
and I'd press up my right foot,
it'd go that way.
And I didn't know
where it was going.
I was so scared.
I didn't know what I was doing.
And pretty soon,
you know, before we got
to the bombing area,
and the fighters
started to come out,
uh, I learned my right foot
from my left foot.
MAN: Two fighters, 6:00 up,
coming in, diving out, chief.
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
NARRATOR: Earl Burke
survived his first mission.
The raid and others like it
reduced French coastal towns
to rubble.
"Not a dog or a cat survived
in them," a German officer said,
but the concrete
submarine pens that had been
the Americans' target
remained intact.
BURKE: Well, the accuracy
of our bombing
left much to be desired.
They said you could drop a bomb
into a pickle barrel.
We couldn't drop
a bomb in France
that hit anything, any target,
in the beginning.
We just couldn't hit 'em.
NARRATOR:
In August,
376 B-17 s had conducted
a massive raid on Schweinfurt
and Regensburg, Germany,
hoping to smash
the heavily-defended factories
that supplied ball bearings
to the Nazi war machine.
MAN: Fighters, 10:00.
NARRATOR:
It had been a disaster.
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
60 Flying Fortresses
failed to return.
600 crewmen were lost.
The battered factories
were again
back working round the clock.
And so the Allied command
ordered a second strike
on Schweinfurt for October 14.
BURKE: We were briefed
that we were going to Schweinfurt.
And you could have heard all
the people groan
and moan... swear.
Nobody wanted to go
back to Schweinfurt.
NARRATOR: Burke's squadron
was ready before dawn.
BURKE: You were getting ready to go.
Those were the times you were
more nervous and scared
to get into that airplane.
You did not want to get
into that airplane.
But you did anyway.
You got in the airplane
because your friends were
getting in the aircraft.
You didn't want to let
your friends down.
Even though, you know...
didn't want to go.
NARRATOR:
283 B-17 s
took off into the fog
and headed for Schweinfurt.
Fighter escorts shielded them
across Belgium,
then turned back
before their fuel ran out.
Within minutes,
hundreds of German fighters
rose up to meet them.
(RAPID ARTILLERY FIRE)
BURKE:
They came in 10 abreast.
You see these
little things wink.
And, as they wink,
you know what's coming.
You're talking about
a quarter pound of lead
each time you saw
one of those winks.
Then they would stay off
a fair thousand yards,
and they would lob...
Iob rockets at you.
You couldn't reach them
because your.50-calibre
machine gun couldn't touch them.
That's why we needed
the fighter escorts.
We were sitting ducks.
MAN: B-17 in trouble.
BURKE:
When the bogeys were coming in,
you're up there, you're pressing
the little red button here.
And, uh, hope that
he flies into it.
And I was up there flying two
.50-calibre machine guns.
Shooting rounds of shells about
half an inch in diameter.
Lots of lead in the air.
MAN: Going up... and down.
Take the shot, you guys.
One shot.
NARRATOR: As Earl Burke's battered
formation approached its target,
the German fighters withdrew,
and American crews braced
for yet another terror -
anti-aircraft fire,
exploding shells that filled the air
with thousands of metal shards.
The Germans called it flak.
MAN: B-17 out of control at 3:00.
NARRATOR:
Many more planes were hit
and never reached their target.
BURKE: And over Schweinfurt...
...bang.
Plexiglas on my right-hand side
exploded.
My left-hand side exploded.
And a 20-millimetre shell had
come up through my turret,
hitting me in the left arm.
Not breaking the arm,
but smashing the bone...
tearing my jacket off,
and went up
into the waist window
on the left-hand side,
hit the stanchion
of the.50-calibre gun,
and blew up.
Killed the waist gunner.
And here I was down
in this ball turret
trying to figure out
what I was supposed to do.
And, I have to say this,
my training as an Eagle Scout
in the Boy Scouts of America
saved my arm that day.
Because I put a tourniquet
around it, knew how to do that.
Knew how to stop
the flow of blood.
And, uh, everything
hunky-dory then.
And continued on flying
in the ball turret.
So it's, about 35,
40 degrees below zero.
And when blood flows out,
it freezes and drops down
and rolls around on the bottom.
So the idea is to make sure that
when you're at altitude,
you pick your blood up
and throw it out.
Because if you didn't,
you'd have to mop it up
when you got down. (Chuckles)
But I fly... I flew that way
for around four,
four and a half hours.
When I got hit,
immediately I says,
"Oh, my goodness... my parents.
"My parents will get
another telegram
"telling either I was
wounded or dead."
At that point,
I didn't know which.
That was the first time
I ever thought
what my being in the service
did to my parents.
And I had second thoughts then.
But it was too late.
MAN: 1:00 high... coming around.
NARRATOR:
German fighters returned
and attacked the bombers
in Earl Burke's group
again and again,
all the way back
to the English Channel.
The survivors landed
wherever they could,
at airfields scattered
all across England.
The second Schweinfurt raid was
just as disastrous as the first.
60 more Fortresses
had been shot down.
600 more men were lost
and hundreds more were wounded.
Surviving airmen
remembered that day
as Black Thursday.
We, uh, first were sent
to a bomber base
to meet the B-17 s
coming in shooting off
red flares,
which meant there
were wounded aboard.
The first one came in just right
over the treetops.
We thought it was
going to crash.
It skidded on the runway.
And I was in the ambulance.
We ran over there and ran in...
You had to crawl.
There was no way to get back
to a B-17 standing up.
The tail gunner was dead.
He'd been, you know, just
shot right through the head.
The, uh, copilot and the pilot
had been in a fire.
The belly gunner was hurt.
They were all injured.
I guess that the, uh,
plane that, uh...
the German plane
that fired on 'em
just riddled the whole plane.
NARRATOR: Earl Burke's injury
kept him out of action for weeks.
But each time he -
or anyone else -
returned to the air,
their odds of surviving the war
grew longer.
BURKE:
I kept away from making friends.
I did not make friends.
The reason is,
if you met a guy at the...
at the PX and bought him a beer,
tomorrow he would be gone.
You know, and you kept saying
"I'm losing people."
So you locked yourself up.
NEWSREEL: Hollywood's
most famous movie stars
leave the film capital to help
the government sell war bonds.
The country has asked the people
to invest a billion dollars
in one month to help pay
for the war.
And here's the start
of the drive.
They'll tour 300
cities from coast to coast.
This is the people's way
of saying,
"From the home front
to the battle front,
"from movie stars
to sales clerks,
"America's 130 million citizens
are in the war."
NARRATOR: The war -
the single greatest
coordinated effort in American history -
would eventually cost
the United States
$304 billion dollars.
More than $3 trillion
in today's terms.
Taxes alone could
never pay for it all.
That required a series
of annual war bond drives.
The whole country
got involved.
In Mobile, John Cottingham,
a worker at Brookley Field,
invested all but eight cents
of his pay cheque each month
in war bonds.
The Black Bears, the local Negro
league baseball team,
staged a double-header
that raised $100,000.
The citizens
of Sacramento were asked
to buy $16 million
worth of bonds
during one particular drive.
They were told it would pay
for 96 minutes of the war.
In Waterbury, bonds were sold
from 'Liberty House',
set up in the middle
of the town green
on the site where similar bonds
had been sold
to help defeat Germany
during the First World War.
People turned out to gaze
at a giant barrage balloon,
to see a German plane
that had been shot from the sky
and ride a tank.
MAN: "Luverne, Minnesota.
"They can send all
the movie stars they want
"on countrywide
war bond sales drives,
"but for our part,
we'll take Maude Jochims
"as the best bond salesman -
or saleswoman - of them all.
"We stopped in at the Palace
Wednesday afternoon,
"and they were going
to fall $8,000 short.
"Then Maude,
as a 1 -woman campaign,
"waded in to canvass
Rock County patrons.
"The bond orders poured in
"and the total was boosted
over $48,000."
Al Mclntosh,
'Rock County Star Herald'.
MAN: "Dear Mom and family,
"I know you didn't receive mail
from me for over a week,
"but circumstances prevented me
from writing to you.
"Yes, that's right,
"I took a little boat ride
and I didn't even get seasick.
"Well, I suppose you're
wondering where I am.
"I think if I wouldn't tell you,
you would never guess it.
"OK, I'll tell you,
"because I know you will want to
know in the worst way.
"I'm somewhere in North Africa.
"Surprised?
"Well, I am, too,
"but I am very safe,
so don't worry.
"Love, Babe."
NARRATOR: At the
Casablanca Conference
back in January,
the Allies had publicly called
for the unconditional surrender
of the Axis,
and privately decided upon an
invasion of the island of Sicily
and then the Italian mainland,
what Churchill called
"the soft underbelly of the Axis".
American commanders had
impatiently insisted
on a cross-Channel
invasion of France,
but the British were wary,
still haunted by the memory of
the losses
they had suffered there
during the First World War.
They got their way.
Sicily would be first.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
NEWSREEL: American troops
of General Patton's Seventh Army
move swiftly through western
Sicily, taking town after town
as they drive to join
General Montgomery's
British Eighth Army.
(EXPLOSIONS AND RAPID GUNFIRE)
DWAIN LUCE: And Patton came
to see us and talk to us.
We all loved Patton.
We loved lke, too.
But I mean, we loved Patton.
And then, he was something.
He says, "Now, some troops can
move and some troops can shoot.
"But when you can move and shoot
at the same time,
"then you and Napoleon are
pissing through the same straw."
NARRATOR: It took the Allies
just 38 days to capture Sicily,
pushing the enemy
from one town to another.
Thousands of civilians died,
and 25,000 Allied soldiers
were dead or out of action.
The Axis lost 167,000 men,
the overwhelming majority
of them Italian.
Tens of thousands
of crack German troops
had managed to escape.
In Rome, Mussolini
had been deposed
by his own generals
and counsellors.
The new Italian government
surrendered on September 8,
and declared war
on Germany soon thereafter.
But there were now more than
132,000 German troops
waiting on the Italian mainland,
another 460,000
were on their way to join them.
And a daring Nazi commando raid
rescued Mussolini from captivity
and set him up in northern Italy
as head of a puppet regime.
It was clear to the Allies
that the Germans were resolved
to hold Italy
at all costs.
NARRATOR: "ltaly is like a boot,"
Napoleon once said.
"You must enter it, like
Hannibal, from the top."
The Allies planned to attack it
from the bottom.
(ALARMS BLARE)
(RAPID GUNFIRE AND EXPLOSIONS)
At first, everything seemed
to go according to plan.
The Fifth Army landed at Salerno
on September 9.
(MEN SHOUT)
The British Eighth Army
seized the important
airfields at Foggia.
And Naples fell to the Americans
on October 1.
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
Despite fierce resistance,
in three months
the Allies managed
to achieve two key goals -
they had forced Italy
out of the war
and onto their side,
and they were keeping thousands
of German troops busy
who might otherwise
have been fighting in Russia
or preparing to defend France
against the invasion
both sides knew was coming.
The Allies' target now was Rome,
only 150 miles away.
Getting there would prove harder
than anyone could have imagined.
With the Allied forces
was Private Babe Ciarlo
of Waterbury, Connecticut,
now a member of Company G,
2nd Battalion, 15th Regiment,
3rd Infantry Division,
Fifth Allied Army,
under the command
of General Mark Clark.
On September 18, nine days
after the first elements
of the Fifth Army had landed
at Salerno,
the 3rd Division had gone
ashore to join them.
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
MAN: "October 20, 1943.
"Dear family,
"I know I haven't written
to you for a long time,
"and I hope you understand
"the army has been keeping me
pretty busy.
"I suppose you've been keeping
up with the news lately,
"and by the way
we're beating the Germans,
"this war won't last
much longer.
(DISTANT EXPLOSION)
"Eddie and I are dying
for some nice raviolis
"and I don't think it'll be long
before we get them.
"Will you please send me
Mom's brother's address
"in your next letter?
(EXPLOSION)
"Love, Babe."
NARRATOR: Babe was careful always
to keep the details of what he was doing
from his family
so as not to alarm his mother.
But her brother lived in Rome,
and Babe clearly wanted
everybody back home
to know he'd made it to Italy.
As the Allies tried
to move north,
the weather turned bad,
and the terrain grew more
and more forbidding.
Crags, deep-cut valleys,
twisting mountain roads,
blown bridges -
all under constant German fire
from hidden hillside
strongholds.
(MACHINE GUN FIRES)
Bill Mauldin,
from Mountain Park, New Mexico,
was a cartoonist for
'Stars and Stripes', the army newspaper.
Week after week,
he managed to find laughs
in the lives
of ordinary infantrymen,
even when, as he said,
"You don't think life could be
any more miserable."
MAN: "Dig a hole in your backyard
while it is raining.
"Sit in the hole while the water
climbs up around your ankles.
"Pour cold mud
down your shirt collar.
"Sit there for 48 hours...
"...and so there is no danger
of your dozing off,
"imagine that a guy is sneaking
around waiting for a chance
"to club you on the head
or set your house on fire.
"Get out of the hole,
fill a suitcase full of rocks,
"pick it up, put a shotgun
in your other hand,
"and walk on the muddiest road
you can find.
"Fall flat on your face
every few minutes,
"as you imagine big meteors
streaking down
"to sock you.
"If you repeat this performance
every three days
"for several months,
you may begin to understand
"why an infantryman gets
out of breath...
"...but you still won't
understand
"how he feels
when things get tough."
NARRATOR: The men learned
to sleep while marching -
it was "a kind of coma",
one remembered -
and when they got a chance
to lie down,
preferred to sleep on rocks
rather than bare ground
because rocks were
relatively dry.
Hundreds of mules were used
to carry up supplies...
...and to carry back the dead.
Boulder by boulder,
hill by hill,
the Allies battered their way
through the German defences -
the Volturno Line...
the Barbara Line...
the Reinhard Line...
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
On November 17,
Babe Ciarlo's
3rd Infantry Division
was pulled back to rest.
In 58 straight days of combat
since the landing at Salerno,
they had lost 3,265 men
and moved less than 50 miles.
The 3rd Division
would cycle through 76,000 men
before the war was over.
MAN: "November 17, 1943.
"The reason why I didn't write
"is because I don't have much
to say and I am a little lazy.
"I hope you have a good time
over the holidays,
"and I hope you eat
up at Mom's house for Christmas
"so that Mom might be happier.
"Your loving brother,
always, Babe."
(EXPLOSIONS, GUNFIRE)
(ENGINES HUM)
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
NARRATOR:
The terrible losses suffered
during the second assault on
Schweinfurt in October of 1943,
and other raids that week
in which 88 more American
bombers had been shot down,
helped persuade
the Allies to cut back
on daytime raids over Germany
until they could design
and produce enough fighters
capable of escorting bombers
all the way to their
targets and back again.
The targets themselves
were changed, as well.
Bombers continued to bomb
cities, including Berlin,
and to batter war industries,
but the destruction of the
German air force on the ground,
as well as in the air,
now took top priority.
MAN: Right to your left.
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
MAN: I got my sights on him.
NARRATOR: The Allies were
determined to dominate the skies
before the planned
invasion of France.
Before D-day.
EARL BURKE: Of course,
being an enlisted man,
we didn't think the officers
knew what they were doing.
We could have fought it a little
bit better than they did.
(CHEERING)
But, occasionally,
the missions came off proper.
We finally realised that these guys knew
what they were doing.
That we're fighting
the right war.
It was not an economical thing
to do in terms of life.
You'd lose 10 bombers,
you'd lose 100 men.
NARRATOR:
Earl Burke was no longer flying.
He had been wounded again,
this time by shrapnel
from a bomb that exploded
while he was on the ground.
BURKE:
They put me in a hospital.
And there they told me
that I had
to have my arm removed.
But fortunately,
there was the chief of surgery
came upon me in a hallway
as I was going
into the operating room.
Says, what was I doing in there?
I says, "Well, I'm...
"guess I'm going to have
a little problem with my arm."
"What's wrong with your arm?"
"L-I... I got wounded,
"and I got
what they call osteomyelitis."
And that was the scourge
of World War I.
If you got wounded in the bone,
that's what happened.
He says, "That... No, but...
not going to do it.
"Back in the ward."
They put me back in the ward,
bring me back in a cast,
cut a hole in the cast,
put a little wire net across it.
I said, "What are you doing?"
He says, "I'm making
a little home for somebody."
I said, "What is that
little home going to do?"
He says, "I'm going to keep
these little guys in on your arm
"so they can eat all that stuff
out of your bone."
And I said, "Well, what-what
kind of things are they?"
He says, "They're little
white things,
"you know, like-like this."
Had a handful of maggots,
flipped them in there,
and put the wire cage
back on it.
Says, "Now, those little guys
are going
"to eat that stuff out of you,
"'cause we can't get it
out of you.
"No way we can get that
out of you."
So, there I was with this
little thing over there,
and watching those guys
having a meal.
I was in the hospital 15 months.
NARRATOR:
Earl Burke's air war was over.
He returned to California,
helped rescue pilots lost at sea
on training missions,
and finally, went home
to his parents in Sacramento.
Despite the all-out
Allied raids,
German aircraft production
would actually increase.
"We are virtually drowning
in aircraft,"
wrote one German flyer.
But the Luftwaffe was now losing
trained crews far faster
than they could be replaced.
And Allied bombing
had also denied the Germans
the precious fuel
they needed to train new ones.
"The time has come,"
the chief of the German
fighter wing told his superiors,
"when our force is within sight
of collapse."
When the time finally came
to invade France,
the Allies would own the skies.
MAN: "Luverne, Minnesota.
"For our Rock County boys.
"Dear gang,
"Who'd have thought
four years ago
"that you'd be reading this
in all the states of the Union,
"maybe in Africa, India,
"Iceland, England,
"Alaska, New Guinea,
"Australia, Caledonia, Hawaii,
"New Zealand
"and a score of other places
with funny names?
"Up until late Monday,
"it didn't look much
like winter,
"and then the white flakes
began to fall silently,
"swirling in white clouds,
"almost blotting out
the street lights at night.
"But it didn't last very long,
"just enough to throw
a little mantle of white
"in patches over the dark,
bare, dirty-looking ground.
"Tuesday morning,
the snapping cold came,
"and by Wednesday morning,
"the smoke from the chimneys
was hanging like white plumes
"in the clear,
quiet, frosty air."
Al Mclntosh,
'Rock County Star Herald'.
NARRATOR:
Americans could now look back
on some real progress
in the war against the Axis.
In the Pacific Theatre
of Operations,
Americans had recaptured Attu
in the Aleutian Islands
and were fighting
on Bougainville and New Guinea.
But the Japanese were still
on the march in Burma,
intent on invading
north-eastern India.
And the long campaign
to take the Gilberts,
the Marshalls
and the Carolines,
to liberate the Philippines
and eventually attack
the Japanese home islands,
had only just begun.
In the European Theatre,
improved radar,
new, long-range Allied aircraft
and ever-growing numbers
of escort ships
sailing from American shipyards
reduced the threat
from German U-boats.
More and more weapons
and equipment were now reaching
the embattled Soviet Union.
When the Red Army began to sweep
the enemy from the Ukraine,
thousands of newly-manufactured
American trucks
helped make possible
their deadly pursuit.
The Axis had been driven
from North Africa, too,
and Sicily was now
in Allied hands.
But the Germans were
fighting back hard in Italy.
And in secret,
they had already begun
to implement a policy
of systematised murder
that would one day persuade
even the most cynical GI
that the war had to be fought.
As Allied leaders drew up plans
for the long-delayed invasion
of the Continent,
Hitler put tens of thousands
of labourers to work
strengthening
his coastal defences.
For the men of Luverne,
Sacramento,
Mobile, Waterbury,
and every other American town,
things were bound
to get still tougher.