MAN: Luverne, Minnesota.
'Rock County Star-Herald.'
"The four grim lead lines
of the newspaper seemed
"so tragically cold and bare.
"Staff Sergeant Richard E. Mueller
is reported missing
"with seven others following
the crash of a medium bomber
"in the Atlantic near Columbia,
South Carolina Saturday.
"All are believed dead.
"Four grim lines
of newspaper type
"that tell so much
and yet so little.
"For us and thousands
of other friends,
"none of the usual information,
or even a picture, is needed
"to help us remember
Red of the A&P,
"because that is the way
he will be remembered here,
"not as Staff Sergeant
Richard E. Mueller.
"With hair as vivid as a June carrot
"and a grin that had the power
of a locomotive headlight,
"this boy never walked
down the street
"or round the aisles of the store.
"He fairly danced or ran
"and you knew
that here was a chap
"that was going places."
Al Mclntosh.
NARRATOR: By January of 1944,
Americans all over the country
had already become accustomed
to scanning their newspaper
every morning...
...hoping not to see the names
of young men they knew
listed as missing or wounded or dead.
Men and materiel
were streaming into England
in preparation for the invasion of France.
US forces were about the assault the
Marshall Islands in the central Pacific.
American and British troops in Italy
remained mired behind
the German Gustav Line at Cassino,
unable to batter
their way through to Rome.
It was clear to everyone
that the newspaper casualty lists
would soon be growing longer.
SHERMAN: I delivered papers.
And all of the mothers
who had somebody in the army
would have a blue star in the window
on the little flag.
And then if the son or husband
or whatever died
they'd change that to a gold star.
The gold star mothers were those
who had lost a family member
in the war.
And it was the fact
that the star had changed.
But I was too young
to really understand
the consequences of death.
NEWSREEL: Now, taking the
Nazis completely by surprise,
the Allies hurl their fleet
upon Nettuno and Anzio,
points behind the German line
south of Rome.
At dawn, landing ships and barges
stand offshore.
Small boats begin to pour in.
The initial landing
meets with no opposition.
NARRATOR: On January 22, Allied
forces landed behind the German lines
at Anzio, hoping to break the stalemate
in Italy.
Babe Ciarlo, of Waterbury,
was with them,
part of the 3rd Infantry Division.
The Allies had caught the enemy
totally unprepared.
But the Allied commander,
General John P. Lucas,
was a cautious man.
His orders were to move inland 20 miles,
seize the Alban hills
that overlooked Rome
and cut off the railroad line and two roads
that supplied the enemy.
Lucas wanted to be certain he had
enough men and enough firepower
to be successful.
He took nine days
to consolidate his position,
more than enough time for the Germans
to build up their defences.
By the time the Allies began to move
forward toward the Alban Hills,
the better part of eight enemy divisions -
100,000 men -
held the high ground
along the Allied perimeter,
ready for any attack.
Fire!
(GUNFIRE, EXPLOSIONS)
Babe Ciarlo's division tried
to fight its way through the German lines
near the town of Cisterno...
...only to be hurled back toward the beach.
Unable to advance, Americans and
Britons dug in as best they could
on the Anzio plain.
15 miles long, 10 miles deep,
and totally exposed to enemy fire.
They would remain pinned down there
for four miserable months.
The secret landing meant
to stun the enemy had stalled,
just as the assault on the Gustav Line it
had been meant to aid had also stalled.
As Churchill said about that Anzio thing,
he said, "I thought I was
putting a wildcat ashore.
"It turned out to be a bloated whale."
Because we just sat there.
Meanwhile, the Allied armies back at
Monte Cassino were faring no better.
In February,
New Zealand and Indian troops
were ordered to take Cassino.
They failed.
Their commander insisted
the Germans were using the abbey
as an observation post to direct
fire on the huddled men below.
Waves of American warplanes
dropped 586 tons of bombs,
turning the abbey into rubble.
The men below stood and cheered.
Some wept with joy.
But German resistance
was actually strengthened.
Having promised the church
not to disturb the sanctuary,
the Nazis had never
actually used the abbey
as an observation post.
But they quickly turned
its ruins into a new stronghold
from which they directed fire
to destroy the men
that were again sent against them.
In March, the Indians and
New Zealanders attacked once more.
The battle seesawed back and forth
for two days and two nights
before the Allies fell back
to where they'd started.
4,000 men were lost.
The Germans held.
In the mud and snow and bitter cold,
the killing went on.
(GUNFIRE)
CHAMBERLIN: You'd get a guy in
and he looked OK,
but a little further on,
there'd be a medical guy
and he'd say, you know,
"This guy's going."
And I said, "Should I stop?"
He said, "Yeah, why don't
you stop for a minute?"
So I went back and held his hand and...
...you know, he just looked up
and kind of gave a sign of recognition
and then he was gone.
It was quick, quick.
It's hard to describe what it's really like.
You can remember
the moments, but...
You see some guy leaving this world,
it's not a lot of fun.
NEWSREEL: At Fort Bragg,
North Carolina,
in the largest training camp
of its kind in the world,
800 coloured rookies get
their basic physical build-up
for eventful days to come.
Ten weeks ago they were
coalminers, steel workers,
mechanics, professional boxers -
in fact, most everything
from college teachers
to Pullman porters.
A few weeks more
of this intensive drill
and they'll become
the field artillery replacements
of the famed 16th Battalion,
a compact fighting force
of cannoneers,
radio and signal men,
an all-Negro group assembled
from all over the nation -
a well-trained unit ready
and eager to join the fight
for survival of the great
democracy that gave them birth.
Man: Alright, men.
On behalf of the United States Army,
and the reception centre
here at this camp,
we're glad to welcome you
here to today,
and into the United States Army.
We're glad to see all
of your happy, smiling faces.
You'll be converted
from a civilian
into a full-fledged soldier.
GRAY: When I went in they, uh,
had a pad.
And "Eyes - negro.
"Hair - negro.
"Colour - negro.
"Complexion - negro.
"Race - negro."
Everything was "negro"
except height and weight.
NARRATOR: Despite the bravery
of African-Americans in all
of America's previous wars,
despite the argument made
by the NAACP and others
that "a Jim Crow army cannot
fight for a free world,"
the armed forces
of the United States
remained strictly segregated.
Growing protest
by African-Americans
would force the military
to make a few changes.
An Army Air Corps training camp
was set up at Tuskegee Institute
in Alabama.
A single ship, the USS 'Mason',
was manned entirely by blacks -
except for her commander.
The 761 st Tank Battalion
would eventually fight in Europe,
sent to the front
by George Patton
with the admonition - "I don't
care what colour you are,
"so long as you go
up there and kill
"those Kraut sons of bitches."
The Marine Corps had refused
to accept any blacks at all,
but after 1942, as casualties
in the Pacific mounted,
and pressure from civil rights
groups intensified,
John Gray and others
were finally allowed
to sign on and serve...
...in segregated units.
GRAY: They did not intend
to have blacks as fighting units.
They intended to have them,
if at all, as support units.
Look like you ought
to appreciate the fact
that you're not up front.
But they didn't want you
to get that kind of a glory.
NARRATOR: John Gray was sent
to Camp Lejeune, North Carolina,
where he joined
the 51 st Defense Battalion,
one of only two black units
being trained for combat
in the Marine Corps.
Its commander was
Lt. Colonel Floyd Stephenson,
a veteran of the attack
on Pearl Harbor
who won his men's loyalty
by declaring,
"There is nothing that black
troops cannot be taught."
He was a far cry
from the officers
John Gray was used to.
GRAY: And that was different
from Major Larsen
who said he had been out
in the jungles
and he had fought this
and he had done that
and he came back
to find women Marines
and dog Marines
and then "you people."
We didn't like for people
to say "you people."
So instead of referring
to troops as "troops,"
they would always refer
to black troops as "you people."
And we resented that.
NARRATOR: John Gray and his unit
were eventually
sent to the South Pacific.
They had been trained
as expert gunners
on 90mm and 150mm guns,
and were so skilled,
Gray remembered,
"We could shoot
the sting off a bee."
But their white commanders
did not see fit
to send them into battle.
The men took to calling
themselves "the lost battalion"
because they had so little to do,
and white Marines
resented their presence -
especially when Samoan women
were involved.
GRAY: And when they got a chance
to dance or something...
...and those girls were told
that we had tails.
So when a girl
would dance with you,
she would reach down and try
to see if you had a tail.
But those girls would be so glad
to have the treatment.
So they extended, uh,
"separate, but equal,"
so to speak,
into the armed services.
(EDGAR MEYER'S 'CONCERT DUO
MOVEMENT ONE' PLAYS)
AANENSON: I wanted to fly fighters.
And by the luck of the draw,
I was sent to Harding Field
at Baton Rouge, Louisiana.
That's where they had
the P-47 Thunderbolt.
And that was the plane
I wanted to fly.
NARRATOR: The war offered Quentin
Aanenson, of Luverne, Minnesota,
a chance to realise
his boyhood dream of flying.
Colour blindness had kept him
out of the Army Air Corps
until he took the test
enough times to memorise it.
In early 1944, he was one
of hundreds of thousands of men
being trained to play their part
in the coming invasion of France.
The P-47 Thunderbolt was
a powerful airplane.
We could carry two 500-pound bombs
under the wings
or we could carry two 1,000-pound
bombs under the wings.
We carried up to ten rockets.
We had eight.50 calibre
machine-guns
mounted in the wings
that had a rate of fire
of 600 rounds a minute per gun.
So we, in a second,
we could throw a hundred shells
on a target
and just devastate anything
that was in front of us.
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
NARRATOR: Fighter training
in Baton Rouge was exhilarating,
but dangerous.
(EXPLOSION)
Five members of Aanenson's group
of 40 trainees
died before they got
a chance to go overseas.
(MILLS BROTHERS'
'PAPER DOLL' PLAYS)
SONG: # I'm gonna buy a paper doll
# That I can call my own... #
AANENSON: And I had been there
only about ten days or two weeks
when I met Jackie.
I went to a dance
that was put on
by a girls' club that
she belonged to.
And this absolutely
darling girl came up.
JACKIE GREER: And
that particular night,
I had a darling Valentine dress,
you know, the red and the white
stripes and all.
There was a song called
'Paper Doll'
that was so famous at that time.
And as I took her
to dance with her, I said,
"Hello, paper doll."
GREER: We did have our dance,
and we danced
for about five minutes,
the music stopped to let
the band rest, and I went home.
And when I got home that night,
my sister was already
in bed asleep.
We slept together,
and I woke her up
and I said, "Nelwin,
"tonight I met the man
I'm going to marry."
AANENSON: Well, we had 90 days
to work with from the time I met her
until the time I shipped out
to go overseas.
We would go to parties,
and we saw each other
almost every night.
And we knew within a matter
of just a short time
that this was something serious
and everything was...
...it's sort of like
on fast forward.
You live your life
realising that, uh,
you don't have a lot of time.
NARRATOR: Before he left for England,
Aanenson laid down some
ground rules for Jackie.
AANENSON: So I said that
"I'd like to make
a deal with you.
"I will come back
and survive this war
"if you will agree
that while I'm gone
"that you will not date
any one guy
"more than three times."
I don't know where in the world
he came up with that.
I never did understand it.
But the rule was,
I couldn't have over three dates
with any one fella.
And he explained it
that I wouldn't get
too familiar with them
in three dates,
and if I couldn't have any more,
it couldn't go any further.
And it surely worked.
(COUNT BASIE PLAYING
'FOR THE GOOD OF THE COUNTRY')
TOM CIARLO: Waterbury at that time,
during the war,
was like, uh, you could almost compare it
to a miniature Times Square.
It was never quiet
because there were
so many factories
and each factory
had three shifts
so they're going
around the clock.
So we had buses running up and
down from the centre of town
to different streets all over
the city going constantly.
NARRATOR: Like Mobile and countless
other American towns,
Babe Ciarlo's hometown
of Waterbury, Connecticut
was booming.
Its peace-time industries had
all switched over to defence
and were working 24 hours a day,
seven days a week,
365 days a year.
Workers came to Waterbury
from everywhere.
LEO GOLDBERG: While looking for
work, there was one memorable morning
when I got on a bus,
sat down next to a stra... somebody
who turned to me and said,
"Good morning."
And I looked at him as if to say,
"Who are you to say
good morning to me?"
After all, I'm from Brooklyn, New York.
But any rate,
the impact was very great.
The friendliness that I found in Waterbury
was something I was not
accustomed to.
NARRATOR: 23-year-old Leo Goldberg
quickly got a job as a saw sharpener
at the Scovill Manufacturing Company.
Scovill produced so many
different military items,
the 'Waterbury Republican'
reported,
"That there wasn't an American
or British fighting man
"who wasn't dependent
on the company
"for some part of the food, clothing,
"shelter and equipment
"that sustained him
through the struggle."
GOLDBERG: Having a job and no
attachments, it gives you a freedom.
You don't have to answer
to anybody.
"Hey, Mom, I'm gonna stay
out until 10:00,"
or "You gotta
to be home by noon,"
or whatever it was.
So, it was a burst of freedom.
So couple that with
the friendliness.
I got to know people.
I went horseback riding for
the first time in my life.
I never knew what a horse
looked like.
And uh... it was just great.
NARRATOR: Waterbury also sent group
after group of draftees to the war,
12,000 of them.
The mayor saw them all off
at the railroad station.
Each man received a prayer book
and a carton of cigarettes,
courtesy of the Shriners.
Meanwhile, young Waterbury women
did their best
to keep in touch with
the men overseas.
ANNE DEVICO: We wrote letters
to all the boys we knew.
And they loved
getting the letters
because they said at roll call
they wanted their name
to be called over and over
because they said
it was so wonderful.
They loved these letters
because we told them
where we went last night.
We went for a hot dog
or something.
You know, it wasn't
anything big,
or we went to the USO dance
and we saw so-and-so there.
And at Christmastime,
they got boxes galore.
My whole kitchen table,
my mother used to help,
everybody helped.
And we sent boxes
to all of them.
(CREAKING)
NARRATOR: From guns hidden
in the Alban Hills...
...the Germans continued
to hurl artillery shells
at the Allied troops
pinned down at Anzio.
For more than eight weeks,
since the end of January, 1944,
they had been stuck there.
With the American forces
was Private Bill Mauldin,
a cartoonist
for 'Stars and Stripes'.
MAN: "There wasn't any rear.
"There was no place in the entire
beachhead where enemy shells
"couldn't seek you out.
"Wounded men got oak leaf
clusters on their Purple Hearts
"when shell fragments riddled them
as they lay on hospital beds."
(EXPLOSION)
"Nurses died.
"Planes crash-landed
on the single airstrip.
"You couldn't stand up
in the swamps
"without being cut down,
"and you couldn't sleep
if you sat down."
(EXPLOSION)
"Guys stayed in those swamps
for days and weeks."
(MEN SHOUT)
(EXPLOSIONS)
NARRATOR: After one massive shelling,
a mess sergeant fell to his
knees and began loudly to pray.
"God, help us," he said.
"You come yourself.
"Don't send Jesus.
"This is no place for children."
Some 7,000 Allied personnel
were killed
during the Anzio campaign.
36,000 more were
wounded or missing.
And another 44,000
were classified as
"non-battle casualties",
victims of frostbite
and trench foot,
shell shock and madness.
Axis Sally,
the Nazi radio propagandist,
began calling Anzio
"the largest self-supporting
"prisoner of war camp
in the world."
And German aircraft littered
the beach with leaflets,
urging Allied solders
to surrender.
"The beachhead," they said,
"has become a death's head."
On the front line
with the 3rd Infantry Division,
Babe Ciarlo saw all of it,
took part in some of it,
but never said a word about
any of it in his letters home.
MAN: "March 27, 1944.
"I just got through with chow.
"We are having
beautiful weather here,
"and I hope
it's the same way there,
"so you could take
the babies out every afternoon."
TOM CIARLO: He never mentioned
a word
about what he was doing,
where he was.
You couldn't say much about
where you were anyway,
but it was always the upside.
"I could only write a few lines
right now because I'm...
'... l'm going to chow,
and I don't have time."
This is in the heat
of the battle,
and he's going to chow line.
I mean, there's no such thing
as a chow line when you're in...
But you don't realise it
at the time, until years later,
you get a little smarter
and you go, geez, you know,
uh, how could he be going
to a chow line when you're in
the middle of a battle or you're
in a foxhole or someplace?
But he always had
that upbeat outlook about him.
MAN: "April 14, 1944.
"I am in the very best
of health, and I hope to hear
"the same from
all of you always.
"Well, things here
are moving pretty smooth
"and the only thing I do
is eat and sleep.
"And if I keep it up much
longer, I'll be like a barrel.
"Well, take care of yourselves
and keep those stoves roaring,
"because I'll be doing a lot
of eating when I get home."
NARRATOR: By the end of April,
the Allied command
was determined
to break the stalemate
and resume its drive
toward Rome.
Babe's division had finally
been pulled back to rest,
and to get ready
for the big battle to come.
MAN: "April 30, 1944.
"Dear Mom and family,
"This afternoon, I might go
swimming in the Tyrrhenian Sea.
"The salt water will do me good.
"Well, I had my dinner
and guess what I had -
"pork chops,
about a dozen of them.
"I'm getting to be a chow hound.
"Love, Babe."
NEWSREEL: The Allies
are stalled at Anzio,
but patrol clashes are frequent.
Here's a German outpost.
(GUNFIRE, EXPLOSIONS)
TOM CIARLO: You see, probably,
on the newsreel
or you read about it
in the paper
about different battles.
But you don't actually
put Babe in that position,
because he's always telling you
how everything is fine,
everything is no problem.
At one point, as a matter
of fact, my mother had my aunt
write a letter in Italian
that she had sent to Babe.
"When you get to Rome,
when you get to Italy,
"we have relatives over there.
"When you get there,
"show them these letters
and they'll treat you well,"
and everything else, you know.
And at the time, you think,
well, yeah, he's going to Italy.
He's going to go to Rome and
he's going to see his relatives.
Can you imagine that?
It's so unreal.
MAN: "May 9, 1944.
"I'm glad that you're going down
to the beach with the babies,
"and I hope Mom goes down
with you,
"because it'll do all
of you good.
"I won't be with you this year,
"but I'll guarantee you
I'll be there next summer.
"That's a date.
"I'm alright.
"Nothing ever happens here.
"I guess it's like Waterbury - dead.
"Love, Babe."
(BENNY GOODMAN'S
'MEMORIES OF YOU' PLAYS)
(CANNON FIRE)
NARRATOR: By the middle of May,
American artillery had managed
to target German guns,
and things at Anzio
had calmed down a good deal.
The rain of shells that had once
fallen day and night
was reduced to sporadic,
harassing fire.
(LAUGHTER)
In one sector, German gunners
held their fire each afternoon
while Gls played a game
of baseball.
In a ceremony on the beach,
37 foreign-born members
of Babe's division were sworn in
as American citizens.
300 men from his outfit
attended a wedding
between a first lieutenant
and an army nurse.
The bride cut the cake
with a trench knife.
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
MAN: "I figured out just what
"I'm going to do after the war
when I get home.
"I'm going to loaf for a while,
and then I'm going to work,
"and the next spring,
"I'm going to get a car.
"Not bad, huh?
"May 19.
"I am in the very best
of health,
"and I hope to hear the same
from all of you always.
"Today we had a little rain,
but it wasn't bad at all,
"'cause it cooled us off.
"We had beer again today,
"and I gave my share
to the fellas.
"Mom, how are you getting along?
"Fine, I hope,
and keeping happy always.
"I'm doing good,
"and always happy,
'cause I know you're OK.
"Love, Babe."
(MAN SCREAMS)
NEWSREEL: The heaviest Allied
barrage of the war
precedes a dawn attack
in the final battle for Cassino.
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
(PLANES HUM)
(WEAPONS FIRE, RUMBLING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
NARRATOR: On May 11, Allied troops
had begun still another assault
on Monte Cassino.
(GUNFIRE, DISTANT SHOUTING)
French forces from North Africa
battled their way behind Cassino
and began
to choke off German supplies.
(DISTANT SHOUTING)
(GUNFIRE AND SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
(EXPLOSION)
(GUNFIRE AND SHOUTING)
(RAPID GUNFIRE
AND EXPLOSIONS)
(DISTANT RAPID GUNFIRE)
Polish troops,
eager to avenge the Nazi
invasion of their country,
finally took
the ruined monastery
and the positions around it.
(EXPLOSION)
The Gustav Line had broken.
The Germans began falling back.
Monte Cassino was
in Allied hands.
Meanwhile, at Anzio,
General Mark Clark
ordered his forces there
to begin their own offensive
on May 23.
He was determined
to break out of the beachhead
and link up
with the Allied armies
coming up from Cassino
to trap the enemy
now retreating northward.
Babe's regiment helped
lead the way,
finally taking the fiercely
defended village of Cisterna
they had tried
to take months earlier.
(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
(EXPLOSION, MAN SHOUTS)
But when his men broke through,
General Clark astonished
his own staff
and his British Allies
by racing toward Rome
rather than trapping
and destroying
the retreating German army,
which had been
the original plan.
CHAMBERLIN: And when we finally
did break through there,
we didn't even beat
the German army then.
So there wasn't a lot to show
for all that.
All those casualties,
all those terrible things.
The only thing we did
from a larger perspective
was to keep a number of German
divisions occupied there
that otherwise could have
gone to France,
or could have gone
to Russia or somewhere else.
But there wasn't a lot
to show for it.
It was horrible.
(RADIO STATIC, RADIO CHANGING
STATIONS QUICKLY)
RADIO: This is Douglas Edwards
reporting
that the 5th Army, tanks and
motorised infantry has roared on
through Rome today
in relentless pursuit
of two battered German armies.
That's the picture in Italy
as Allied planes continue
hammering German-held Europe
from the west.
Now, General Electric takes you
direct to Rome,
Winston Burdett reporting.
BURDETT: The people of this ancient
and still splendid capital
have seldom celebrated
such a riotous holiday
as they did today...
NARRATOR: On June 4, 1944,
units of the 5th Army
marched into Rome.
BURDETT: A tremendous shout went up
in the square...
NARRATOR: It was Babe Ciarlo's
21 st birthday.
BURDETT: We are bringing
some 3,000 carabiniere into the city.
NARRATOR: Back in Waterbury,
his sister Olga sat down
to write him a letter.
OLGA: "Dearest Babe..."
('THE AMERICAN ANTHEM' PLAYS)
"It is now about 3:15
in the afternoon,
"and it's a beautiful day.
"We are all in the best of health
"and always hope
to hear the same from you.
"We just had news
a little while ago,
"and our American forces
are in Rome.
"The Allies have passed
the city limits in Rome,
"but they're not doing
any fighting.
"Gee, I don't have
to tell you anything.
"You know everything
from beginning to end.
"Babe, try to tell us
a little more about you.
"Where you are
and what you are doing.
"We do hope everything
is alright with you.
"Remember always
to take good care of yourself.
"Well, Babe,
today is your birthday,
"and we do wish you a happy one.
"May all your wishes
and dreams come true.
(Voice breaks) "Let's hope that you'll be
home for your next birthday.
"I'm sure you will be.
"It won't be long now.
"We'll have the biggest party
you've ever seen.
"Just keep your chin up.
"You're 21 years old,
and what a man.
"We're all so proud of you,
"especially Mom.
"There's not a minute
that goes by
"that she doesn't think of you.
"We all miss you
and pray so hard
"for this war to end
so you can come home.
"You said you sent home $30.00.
"We didn't receive it yet,
but it will get here soon.
"Mom is going to put it
in the bank for you, Babe,
"so that when you come home..."
(Sobs) "...you can have
everything you want.
"You can buy your car
and all your new clothes.
"Well, Babe, I guess
I've said enough for now.
"Love from all.
"Take good care of yourself
"and write as often as you can.
"May God bless you
and keep you safe.
"Our thoughts are
always with you.
"Your loving sister, Olga."
NARRATOR: 22 days later,
on June 26, 1944,
a telegram arrived
at the Ciarlo home.
Babe was dead.
He may have been wounded
as early as May 23,
as his battalion struggled
to take Cisterna
during the first few hours
of the Anzio breakout.
995 men from his division
were lost that day,
perhaps the largest number
suffered in a single day
by any American army division
during the entire war.
Hundreds more were killed
or wounded
during the next few days,
some of them hit
by American fighter planes
whose pilots mistook
their advancing countrymen
for retreating Germans.
Whenever Babe was hit,
however he was wounded,
he died on May 27,
eight days before his birthday.
Among the belongings in
his pockets were two rosaries,
his driver's licence,
a wallet with 16 photographs
of family and friends,
a blood-stained letter,
and $1.61.
OLGA CIARLO: Well, I was out that night
with the girls.
We had a sewing club.
I came home
and after I got off the bus,
I see all these lights lit,
which is very unusual
that my mother would have
all these lights lit,
and the closer I got to my house,
lights were all over the place
and I can hear people talking,
and as I went up the front stairs,
I can hear my mother screaming, crying.
My aunts, uncles, everybody was there,
and I didn't know what had happened,
so my aunt called me aside
and told me what had happened.
Well, it was a terrible night.
When I got upstairs
and found out what happened,
of course... a complete shock to all of us
because we thought
everything was fine.
Babe said everything was fine.
He's coming home soon
and it would be great...
So to tell you the truth,
I just went to my room,
I closed the door,
and that's where I stayed.
('EXILES' BY AMY BEACH PLAYS)
NARRATOR: The news of Babe's death
spread throughout the neighbourhood.
ANNE DEVICO: And my girlfriend called
me up.
She's crying.
I said, "What happened?"
"Babe Ciarlo was killed."
You know, we couldn't do a thing
for days after that.
We didn't because
all we could think of was him.
He was always so happy and jolly
and always so fun-loving,
and then I'm thinking,
"He's not coming back."
And it was terrible
'cause you started to realise
that this isn't just going
over there and...
They're not coming back.
Some of them aren't.
NARRATOR: Babe's mother refused
to believe her son was gone.
There had been some mistake,
she was sure of it.
OLGA CIARLO: My mother, of course,
was... well, how can I explain it?
She was a disaster.
We would be getting the newspaper
and my mother would look at pictures
and she'd say to me, "There's Babe.
That's Babe."
And I'd say, "Gee, no, Mom."
"No! You have to write.
You have to write."
I don't know how many newspaper
offices I would write to,
magazine places I would write to,
questioning the name of that boy
that was in that picture
because my mother always thought
it was Babe.
But it never came to be.
It was so bad in our house
that nobody ever knows.
I used to play the piano
ever since I was a young girl.
When my father passed away
and my brother Babe died,
my mother had no music
in the house.
I never played the piano again.
('TWO PIECES FOR STRINGS'
BY WILLIAM WALTON PLAYS)
NARRATOR: By the late spring of 1944,
events were accelerating at last.
In the Pacific,
the Americans were on the move
and a large force was steaming
toward the Marianas -
the islands of Guam,
Tinian, and Saipan.
(BOMB EXPLODES)
On the Eastern front,
the Soviets had triumphed
at Leningrad,
then destroyed or captured
some 250,000 German troops
in the Crimea.
But the basic fact remained,
that until the Nazi grip
on Western Europe was broken,
Allied victory was impossible.
The German army had taken up
new positions
on the Adolf Hitler Line
north of Rome
and the greatest test
for the Western Allies -
the long-delayed invasion
of France -
was now just days away.
Back in Baton Rouge, Quentin
Aanenson from Luverne
had to say goodbye to Jackie
and prepare for war.
AANENSON: We were very much aware
of the fact that it was a...
...deadly calling.
And we knew that the loss rates
were extremely high,
and so it was the, uh,
Judge Advocate General's Office
that put this program in place
that all of us should have
our wills drawn up.
And, of course, we knew
the reality of our situation,
and so we tried
to make light of it,
but, nevertheless, we...
...we all signed our wills,
drew up our wills -
they were standard-type wills -
and there had to be three pilots
that would witness
the other pilot's will.
The three pilots
that witnessed my will...
...were all dead in six months.
('UNTIL I'M IN YOUR ARMS AGAIN'
PLAYS)