(GUNFIRE)
(PLANE ENGINES ROAR)
QUENTIN AANENSON: It was on
one of my very early missions
that I first knew I had...
I had killed men.
We caught a group of Germans
that were on a road
in an area where
there were no trees,
and so there was no place
for them...
to... to run and hide.
And we caught them before they
could really get off the roads
and run toward the ditches.
(GUNFIRE)
And I remember
the impact it had on me
when I could see my bullets
just tearing into them,
and... and, uh,
we had so much firepower
that the...
the bodies would fly,
uh, some yards, and, uh,
as I... as I was doing this,
I was doing it knowing
I had to do it, that it was my job.
This is what
I'd been trained to do,
and I dealt with it fine.
But when I got back home
to the base in Normandy
and landed...
I got sick.
I had to think
about what I had done.
Now, that didn't change
my resolve for the next day.
I went out and did it again.
(GUNFIRE)
And again and again and again.
The Allies were on the offensive now
in western Europe as well as the Pacific.
But the enemy was
making them pay dearly
for every inch of territory
they tried to take.
Quentin Aanenson, of Luverne,
for whom flying had once seemed the
carefree symbol of freedom and escape,
would find himself confronting death
daily in the skies over France.
While Ray Pittman, of Mobile,
would witness the unimaginable
on the Japanese-held island of Saipan.
MAN: "June 6, 1944,
the Philippine Sea.
"At 6:30pm this evening
"the announcement came over
the loudspeaker,
"that the Allies
landed in France.
"Everyone gave a big cheer
when they heard this.
"I won 40 bucks from the boys
because some time ago,
"I bet the invasion would come
off about the middle of June."
James A. Fahey.
NARRATOR: Seaman First Class
James A. Fahey
of Waltham, Massachusetts
was the youngest
of four orphaned children.
His brothers, John and Joe, had
been in the navy at Pearl Harbor
when the Japanese attacked,
and had been spared.
James had signed on
the following year,
assigned to the light
cruiser 'Montpelier'.
Against navy regulations,
he would record what happened
every day he spent aboard
in a little diary.
MAN: "It was a great feeling
as I staggered up the gangway
"to the ship with my sea bag
in one hand
"and the mattress cover loaded
with blankets, mattresses, etc,
"over my shoulder.
"At last I have a home,
"and a warship at that."
NARRATOR: Fahey went to sea
in hopes of seeing action,
and he saw plenty of it
as a member of a gun crew.
The 'Montpelier' shot down
Japanese planes
and sank Japanese ships
off Guadalcanal,
bombarded Japanese defences
at Munda,
and survived an enemy bomb
and two torpedo hits
off Bougainville.
A week or so after hearing
the news of D-day,
Fahey and the men
of the 'Montpelier'
prepared again for battle.
She was now a part
of an 800-ship fleet,
steaming toward the next
American objective
in the Pacific - the Marianas,
a chain of volcanic islands
from which the US
B-29 Superfortress bombers
could begin to attack
the Japanese homeland.
The fleet's three most important
targets in the Marianas
were Guam, Tinian, and Saipan,
where the marines
would land first.
MAN: "June 13.
"In about 14 hours now,
we will start bombarding Saipan.
"We are only about
1,200 miles from Tokyo.
"I guess I will go down
and buy some candy.
"The candy has been
our old stand-by
"when we have nothing to eat
"at battle stations,
for long hours."
NARRATOR: Saipan was unlike
many of the tiny, flat coral atolls
the marines had
taken previously.
It was 14 miles long,
featured all kinds of terrain
and was defended by more
than 30,000 Japanese troops.
It was also home
to somewhere between
16,000 and 20,000
Japanese civilians.
(ALARM BLARES)
(BOSUN'S WHISTLE SHRILLS)
The shelling of Saipan
went on for two days.
Among the marines
of the 4th Division
waiting to go ashore
was Corporal Alvy Ray Pittman
of Mobile, Alabama.
He'd been working as a carpenter
alongside his father
when he decided to join
the marines.
RAY PITTMAN:
I'd made up my mind
I want to get in
the toughest outfit they had.
And I was afraid the war
was going to get over
before I got over there.
So, I joined the Marine Corps.
Course, they sent me
to Parris Island for boot camp.
And I remember going in,
all these guys
standing out on the grass.
They said, "You'll be sorry.
You'll be sorry."
NARRATOR: Ray Pittman
was in the first wave,
part of a 16-man
demolition team,
assigned to destroy enemy strong
points wherever they were found,
using explosives, grenades,
and flamethrowers.
PITTMAN: You never think about
getting hurt yourself.
You think about maybe some
of your buddies
are going to get hurt.
And you wonder
who it's going to be.
I mean, I, I really didn't ever
think about getting hurt myself.
Of course, when you, when you...
slugs start bouncing off
your amtrack going in,
you know it could happen.
NARRATOR: The naval bombardment
had failed.
Concentrated Japanese mortar
and artillery fire
rained down among the amtracks
and on the men fighting
for a toehold on the beach.
All four commanders
of the assault battalions
were hit within minutes.
By evening, 20,000 marines
had made it ashore,
but they could go no further.
The Japanese planned to keep
the Americans pinned down
until their own fleet
could steam in
from the Philippines
and destroy them.
Despite the rain of shells,
the marines began slowly to
fight their way off the beach.
PITTMAN: I know I was scared a lot...
...and losing a lot of friends
really hurts you.
It's, it's really hard
for me to describe,
really, just how
I felt the whole time
'cause there's something
happening every day
and you're so tired and you
can't lift your eyelids hardly.
And something happens,
you get a call to blow a pillbox here,
blow a pillbox there.
I mean, you wake up
and go and do your job.
But it's hard for me to tell
just how bad it was -
how I felt.
NARRATOR: The battle for Saipan
had just begun.
MAN: "June 23, 1944.
"This Norman countryside
"looks exactly like
the rich, gentle land
"of eastern Pennsylvania.
"It is too wonderfully beautiful
to be the scene of war.
(BIRDS CHIRP)
"Some day, I would like
to cover a war in a country
"that is as ugly as war itself."
Ernie Pyle.
NARRATOR: Normandy's beauty
was deceptive.
Allied planners had failed
to understand the landscape
through which their men
would have to fight
before they could begin to drive
the enemy out of France.
(GUNFIRE)
Normandy was quilted with small,
irregularly shaped fields,
walled from one another
by hedgerows,
earthen ramparts four feet high,
topped with dense hedges
whose tangled roots turned them
into natural fortifications
and made it impossible
to see into
from one field to the next.
In one area that measured
just two miles by four,
there were 4,000 such fields.
Here and there,
ancient sunken wagon tracks
twisted between the hedgerows,
ideal for ambushes
and often concealed
from air attack
by overarching trees.
The Germans took
full advantage of all of it.
American Sherman tanks could not
break through the hedgerows,
and when they tried
to roll over them,
exposed their unprotected
underbellies to deadly fire.
(GUNFIRE)
Each field became what the
newspaperman Ernie Pyle called
"a separate little war",
fought mostly
by companies of riflemen.
DWAIN LUCE:
The Germans were good troops.
They did not
give up ground easily,
there or any other place
I saw them.
You had to respect them
for the fact
they were excellent troops.
(Chuckles) They were
too damn good, and...
or they wouldn't have
caused us so much trouble.
(EXPLOSION)
NARRATOR: Progress was measured
in yards.
Now the pace was far slower
than the Allied commanders
had anticipated,
and the cost in dead and wounded
was far higher.
Unarmed C-47 s,
cargo planes stripped down
so that as many litters as
possible could be lifted aboard,
carried the worst hit
to hospitals
in England,
just 20 minutes away...
...then turned around
and came back for more.
Emily Lewis was
one of hundreds of nurses
who did all they could
for the wounded.
LEWIS: All those wounded soldiers,
they were scared to death.
Really frightened
half out of their minds.
I hugged 'em, I was teary-eyed.
It makes me cry to think of it.
(GROANS)
Got 'em on my plane,
talked to them.
Some of them were...
so unnerved...
that I-I just had to put my arms
around them and hold 'em.
I was 23,
and they were 22, 21,
24, 18, you know.
It was...
it was just... terrible.
But it had to be done, you know?
NARRATOR: By July 1,
hundreds of thousands of troops
were onshore.
The Cotentin Peninsula
and the port of Cherbourg
had been taken,
and the beachhead stretched
for some 70 miles.
But after three weeks of combat,
it remained, at most,
20 miles deep.
The plan to liberate France
was stalled.
General Bradley feared
that unless something drastic
were done,
the Allies would face the same
sort of ghastly stalemate
they had endured
during the First World War.
To avoid disaster, his men had
to get out of the hedgerows
and find the kind
of wide-open countryside
American armour needed
to make real progress.
The region just beyond
the town of St-Lô
was what Bradley had in mind.
It was just 15 miles away...
...but to his exhausted men,
it seemed as distant
as their ultimate target -
Germany.
(PIANO PLAYS 'IF I COULD BE
WITH YOU (ONE HOUR TONIGHT)')
SONG: # If I could be with you
one hour tonight
# If I were free
to do the things I might
# I want you to know
that I wouldn't go
# Till I told you, honey,
that I love you so
# If I could be with you,
I'd love you long
I'd love you strong
# I'm telling you, too,
I'd be anything but blue
# If I could be with you
for an hour
# If I could be with you... #
KATHARINE PHILLIPS: During the war,
you just kept thinking
that life cannot begin
until this is over.
You just had to see again
all the boys
that you had known
and been fond of,
and know they were home safely.
Especially for me.
I was not married,
so I was still anticipating
my life ahead of me,
but I didn't know who
it would be spent with.
But I felt, if I could just
get my brother Sidney
back home again...
In fact, I talked to one
of my old boyfriends
two years ago,
and I said,
"Why didn't you propose to me?"
He said, "You wouldn't
have listened to me.
"Till you got Sidney home,
"you wouldn't have
listened to anybody."
And he said,
"By the time that occurred,
"I had lost all my nerve."
# I'd be anything but blue
# If I could be with you
for one hour
# If I could be with you. #
(ALARM BLARES)
MAN: "Sunday, June 18, off Saipan.
"All hands got up at 4:45am.
"I had a swell sleep last night
"even if it was only
for about six hours.
"We had church services
topside this morning,
"even though we are so close
to Japan,
"and the Jap fleet
might be close by."
James A. Fahey.
NARRATOR: The Japanese fleet
was close by.
Vice-Admiral Jizaburo Ozawa
had formulated a new plan
to destroy both
the American land forces,
still struggling their way
inland on Saipan,
and the American fleet offshore.
He would send waves
of carrier-based warplanes
against the fleet,
then reinforce the Japanese
garrison on the island.
"The fate of our empire rests
on this one battle," he said.
"Everyone must give all he has."
(ALARM BLARES)
But the Americans
had intercepted coded messages,
and knew they were coming.
Hundreds of planes took off
to engage the Japanese.
The Battle
of the Philippine Sea
would be the greatest carrier
battle of the Pacific War,
nearly four times
as big as Midway.
It was clear the Americans
now had an edge.
Their pilots were better
trained than the enemy's.
Their planes were better, too.
And they had twice
as many of them.
Maurice Bell,
who had been working
in a Mobile shipyard
when he was drafted,
and joined the navy
rather than the army
because, he said,
he didn't want to sleep
in a hole in the ground,
was serving as a gunner
aboard the heavy cruiser
USS 'lndianapolis',
now the flagship
of the 5th Fleet.
MAURICE BELL: I was sitting up there
with the binoculars
and, all of a sudden,
I saw a torpedo plane
diving in on the ship
right behind us.
And, just as he launched
his torpedoes,
or was ready to launch them,
they hit him with fire.
They was firing at him.
And the plane tumbled over
and crashed.
Five seconds behind him
was another one.
They hit him and he crashed.
About five more seconds,
there's a third one come in,
and they hit him,
and it throwed that plane
in a twist, and the torpedoes
fell end over end,
and hit the water,
and the plane crashed.
I was watching all that
with my binoculars.
NARRATOR: The Americans lost
29 planes that day,
but they shot down
at least 273.
American submarines sank
two Japanese carriers, as well.
Those who took part
in the one-sided contest
remembered it as the
'Great Marianas Turkey Shoot'.
(GUNFIRE)
MAN: "Today is the Fourth of July
"and a good way to celebrate it
is by killing Japs.
"We fired star shells
all last night and all morning
"until daylight today.
"It rained for a while
this morning.
"Yesterday and today
our artillery on the beach
"gave the Japs
an awful pounding.
"The press news said that
in the first couple of weeks
"of fighting on Saipan
over 6,500 Japs were killed.
"There is a very strong odour
from the beach.
"It smells like burnt flesh."
PITTMAN: Well, your Japanese soldier
is probably the toughest soldier
that fought in World War II
other than the marines.
And I mean, they were tough.
And you surround one,
he's going to keep fighting.
In Germany, you surround 50,000
Germans and they'd surrender.
Or Italians, they'd surrender.
But you surround one Japanese,
he's going to keep fighting
right on.
He's going to keep firing
until you kill him.
And they had one thing
in mind - it's killing you.
NARRATOR: The Japanese troops
on Saipan, now without hope
of rescue or reinforcement
from their shattered fleet,
were resolved to die
rather than surrender.
American forces had cleared
the airfield
and begun a slow, agonising
march toward the north,
trying to keep from killing
Japanese civilians
while flushing Japanese troops
from their hiding places.
(GUNSHOT)
Again and again, Japanese
soldiers threw themselves
at the American guns,
shouting "Banzai!"
Apparently willing, even eager,
to die for the Emperor.
PITTMAN: We'd hear the Japanese
talking and drinking
and clanking bottles
and everything.
And we knew there
was one coming.
But they'd come at us
and, and, uh...
we had machine guns set up
doing crossfires every way.
They'd have to get through
the crossfire
before we started shooting,
but then some
of them would get through.
I had one that came at me
with a bayonet
and I shot him in the face
and he fell
in the foxhole with me,
and bled all over my pants
and the bayonet went down
between my arm and my, my chest.
Nearly got me and him dead.
NARRATOR: Before dawn on July 7,
the Japanese launched
a final banzai charge.
3,000 men, some forced
from their hospital beds
and barely able to walk,
many armed only with clubs
and rocks and shovels,
charged into the American lines.
Bulldozers buried all
but a handful of them
the next morning.
It was the largest banzai
charge of the Pacific War.
SAM HYNES: We thought
of the Japanese
as... mysteriously unlike us.
We knew that they would
fight to the death
where, probably, we would
have surrendered.
We began to learn,
though I don't think we...
gathered a lot of information
about the prison camps,
but we had some and we knew
that they were capable of,
of a cruelty and,
and sadism in a way
that we hoped
our people weren't,
though I've never been quite
sure what Americans would do
in the...
exactly the same situation.
NARRATOR: On July 10,
Saipan was officially declared 'secured'.
In almost four weeks
of fighting,
16,525 Americans had been
killed, wounded
or reported missing,
the costliest battle
in the Pacific to date.
Among them
were several black marines
who had finally
been permitted to fight.
"The Negro marines are
no longer on trial,"
the marine commandant said,
"they are marines, period."
Almost 30,000 Japanese soldiers
were dead, as well.
In the final days of the battle,
some 4,000 terrified
Japanese civilians,
mostly women and children,
had fled
to the island's northern tip,
a high plateau called Marpi Point.
Their government had
convinced many of them
that it was their duty
to kill themselves
rather than fall into the hands
of the cruel Americans -
and the handful of Japanese
soldiers who had survived
were prepared to shoot them
if they hesitated.
Some marines risked their lives
to halt the madness,
Japanese American interpreters
with bullhorns
pleaded with civilians
to give up.
But more than a thousand were
either killed by Japanese troops
or chose suicide.
PITTMAN: When we got down
to the end of the island,
they were jumping off the cliff
at Marpi Point.
They thought we'd eat them.
They thought we'd kill them
and eat them.
Stuff like that.
It's just the Japanese
mentality -
they don't want to get captured.
I never did go down to look
at the bottom of the cliff,
but it must have been
a mess down there.
NARRATOR: A few Japanese soldiers
decided to swim out to sea,
rather than surrender.
PITTMAN: So we decided, well,
they're going to die anyway,
we might as well shoot them.
So we set up there
shooting at them.
We'd hear the slugs
hitting around them
and sometimes somebody
would hit one.
But it was a long shot,
trying to hit their head.
MAN: "Sunday, July 16.
"It was a warm, sunny day
"although it rained
during church services.
"It was the first time
I ever went to church
"and saw dead bodies
floating by.
"It is nothing to see men,
women and children floating.
"There must be thousands of Japs
in the waters near Saipan.
"The ships just run over them."
NARRATOR: The Americans went on
to take Tinian and then Guam,
the first US possession
to be recaptured.
The fall of the Marianas
and the damage done
to the Japanese fleet
in the Philippine Sea
forced Hideki Tojo to resign
as the Japanese premier.
His successors -
first a general,
then an admiral,
vowed to fight on.
The Japanese had succeeded
at one thing -
the willingness of their
soldiers and civilians
to die rather than surrender
had made Allied planners
painfully conscious
of the bloodshed
that would surely accompany
the invasion
of the Japanese homeland.
BARBARA PERKINS:
During the war,
it was hard to keep track
of your loved ones.
Mail was very slow.
And even the news media,
if you knew
what-what company and troop
and all that was in,
those things weren't published
in any detail at all
as to pinpoint
just where they were.
Well, you just never know.
We lived with that.
That was part of our part
we had to play.
MAN: "Luverne, Minnesota.
"July 20, 1944.
"Somehow,
the gossip grapevine
"had heard that
there was a telegram
"coming through
after 6:00pm last Friday
"for Mr and Mrs Ray Lester
of Magnolia.
"Ray Lester heard about it,
and his heart was heavy.
"He started walking
down the street.
"On the way he met
Scotty Dewar, the depot agent.
"'Which one is it? '
Asked Lester,
"because there were four boys
to worry about in that family.
"After being told,
he went sorrowfully home
"to break the news to his wife.
"And it was a gracious gesture
"that was made at the dance
in Magnolia that night.
"When the crowd heard the news,
the dance was halted immediately
"out of respect to the memory
of that fighting marine
"who died on Saipan."
Al Mclntosh,
'Rock County Star Herald'.
FRANK SINATRA ON RADIO:
Gentlemen of the armed forces,
this is the 'Hoodlum from Hoboken'.
I'd like to sing
a tune for you.
My name's Sinatra
and I hope youse like it, hey.
(Sinatra sings) # Long ago and far away
# I dreamed a dream one day
# And now that dream
# Is here beside me... #
AANENSON: We would be, uh,
sitting around our tent area
in the apple orchard
in Normandy
and we would discuss what
they would have to pay us
to really do what we had
just done that day.
We agreed first
that we might do it
for $1,000 a mission,
but less than 10 days later -
our losses had
gone up heavily -
we decided that we
wouldn't consider doing it
for less than $10,000 a mission.
And I think that it went
off the radar screen in value
before the end of July,
because there's no way
that you can be
a mercenary enough,
they could pay you enough,
to do what we were doing
on a volunteer basis.
(PLANE FLIES OVER)
NARRATOR: In the weeks after D-day,
American pilots,
including Quentin Aanenson,
continued to fly their missions
over the fields and hedgerows
of Normandy every day,
trying to focus on the help
they were giving
to the men on the ground,
and to avoid thinking too hard
about the losses
in their own ranks.
NEWSREEL: Dashing to a hedgerow
to clear Nazis out
of another line of hedge
across a meadow.
(EXPLOSIONS AND GUNFIRE)
The enemy position's blasted
and the Germans occupying
it have enough,
so out comes the white flag
of surrender,
more prisoners taken
in the drive
to the important city of St-Lô.
As the infantry pushes forward,
the way is cleared
by the smashing power
of tanks and heavy artillery.
NARRATOR: On July 18, St-Lô -
or what was left of it after
six weeks of Allied bombing -
fell to the Americans.
General Bradley's forces
had finally reached the line
Allied planners had
expected his men to reach
just a few days after D-day,
And he was now ready
to send his armour
roaring through the German
lines beyond the city.
But first, Allied warplanes
were called in
to blast an opening.
The operation
was called Cobra.
The correspondent
Ernie Pyle was down below,
watching from a battered
French farmhouse
with officers from
the 4th Infantry Division.
MAN: "The first planes
"of the mass onslaught came over
a little before 10:00am.
"They were the fighters
and dive-bombers.
"We stood in the barnyard of
a French farm and watched them
"barrel nearly straight down
out of the sky.
"And then a new sound gradually
droned into our ears,
"a sound deep,
all-encompassing,
"with no notes in it,
"just a gigantic, faraway
surge of doom-like sound.
"It was the heavies,
"coming on
with a terrible slowness
"in flights of 12,
three flights to a group
"and in groups stretched
out across the sky.
"I thought it would never end.
"And then the bombs came.
"It began up ahead
as the crackle of popcorn
"and almost instantly swelled
into a monstrous fury of noise
"that seemed surely to destroy
all the world around us."
NARRATOR: The bombs continued
falling for an hour and a half.
The bright day
grew dark with smoke,
Pyle remembered,
and the steady roar
seemed to fill "all the space
for noise on earth".
Two days later,
on July 27, the first army
poured through the newly opened
gap in the German lines,
out into the countryside
beyond the hedgerows.
For weeks,
the Americans on the ground
had felt fortunate
to gain 1,000 yards a day.
Soon they would be
covering up to 40 miles
in the same amount of time.
The Germans were reeling.
On August 7, the Americans
stopped a counterattack
cold at Mortain,
and after five days of battle,
forced the Germans to retreat.
Then, on August 15,
in the south of France,
American
and Free French Forces landed,
fanned out
in all directions
and began driving northward.
The following day,
Hitler reluctantly agreed
to pull his battered
Seventh Army
out of Normandy.
It began a desperate
retreat toward Germany.
The Allies caught them
near the town of Falaise.
For three days,
the Allies poured fire
into the fleeing men...
...from the ground
and from the air.
80,000 Germans ran
the terrible gauntlet.
At least 10,000 died,
so many that the pilots
of the Allied spotter planes
hundreds of feet
above the battlefield
were nauseated by the stench.
So many that after
the shooting had stopped,
General Eisenhower
remembered,
"it was literally possible
"to walk for hundreds
of yards at a time,
"stepping on nothing
but dead and decaying flesh".
AANENSON: I had caught
a bunch of Germans
in... in double tandem trucks,
and they were just
massed in there.
There was so much, uh,
firing into that
and I was the only one
that was firing.
My wingman... his guns
had been jammed, and, uh...
the effect on me was that
my right hand quit working
and I was on the way home
and I couldn't
grip with that hand.
So I had to put my left hand
over on top of the stick
to maintain it and go
and land with that.
When I'd have
these nightmares
in years after the war,
many years after the war,
if it was one relating
to that mission
or missions like that,
when I'd get up in the morning,
go out to the kitchen,
Jackie would be there
and she would have had
the coffee made,
and she could tell
when I walked in
that my right hand
wasn't functioning right.
She'd pour a cup
of coffee, not say a word.
She'd hand it
to my left hand.
Never a word said.
We just went on.
NARRATOR: All across France,
the Germans were in full retreat.
Since D-day,
they had lost some 240,000 men...
...another 200,000 had surrendered.
Allied casualties
were terrible, too.
256,000 soldiers and airmen
had been killed,
wounded, captured,
or reported
as missing in action.
At least 19,000 French civilians
had died as well.
Countless French villages
had been pounded into dust.
But most of France was free.
On August 25, 1944,
after four years of Nazi occupation...
...Paris, the City of Light,
was liberated.
MAN: "I, Ollie Stewart, of sound mind
"and fairly sober character,
do solemnly give my word
"that I have never been kissed
so much in all my life.
"Almost every woman I meet
on the street stops
"and kisses me on both cheeks.
"It is a beautiful custom."
AANENSON: We were flying
a mission near Paris
and as I pulled off
my strafing run
and I turned back over the city
and as I looked down,
there were just thousands
of people jamming the streets
of the Champs Élysées
and around the Eiffel Tower
and the Arc de Triomphe
and I realised
that I was seeing something
that was basically
the culmination
of why we were there.
We are winning this war.
The good guys are going
to come out ahead.