MAN ON RADIO:
It's seven o'clock in the morning
and we're steaming along
the western coast of Peleliu Island.
In just about an hour and a half,
the marines will hit the beaches there.
Before that,
the warships of this task force,
which have been pounding the island
for three days,
will give it a final, terrific softening up.
WOMAN: Everybody had
a radio during the war. No TVs.
And three times a day
you got the national news,
and three times a day you did not
be far from that radio.
And, of course, my mother had
about a four-by-four map.
I really don't know where she got it.
It was a map of all of Europe.
And she had a big, long rule stick,
and that map hung right there
and it covered that little wall
where the, um, buffet is.
And when news time came,
she followed all the battles
with the rule stick on the map.
She would have been a great historian.
She would have been.
NARRATOR: Before the Japanese
attacked on December 7, 1941,
most Americans could not have
found Pearl Harbor on a map.
In the two and a half years that followed,
they had had to learn
a host of new names
of the places their sons were fighting.
Kasserine Pass
and Monte Cassino and Anzio.
Utah Beach and Omaha Beach.
Sainte-Mère-Église
and Saint-Lô and the Falaise Gap.
And on the other side of the world,
Guam and Bataán and Guadalcanal.
Midway and Saipan
and the Philippine Sea.
Before the war could end,
the citizens of Mobile, Alabama
and Sacramento, California,
Luverne, Minnesota
and Waterbury, Connecticut,
and every other town in America,
would be forced to learn
still more names.
Arnhem and Aachen
and the Hurtgen Forest.
The Vosges mountains
and the Ardennes and Remagen,
Peleliu and Luzon and lwo Jima,
and more.
And young men from those towns would
learn lessons as old as war itself...
...that generals make plans,
plans go wrong, and soldiers die.
MAN: "To the noncombatants
and those on the periphery of action,
"the war meant only boredom
or occasional excitement.
"But to those who entered
the meat grinder itself,
"the war was a netherworld of horror
"from which escape seemed
less and less likely
"as casualties mounted
and the fighting dragged on and on."
(FLAMES CRACKLE)
"Time had no meaning.
Life had no meaning.
"The fierce struggle eroded the veneer of
civilization and made savages of us all."
Eugene Sledge.
(EXPLOSION)
The men coined names for the chaos
in which they often found themselves
and the ineptitude of some
of the officers who sent them there,
employing language
they would never have used
in front of their mothers or their wives
back home.
'SNAFU' - 'situation normal,
all fucked up'.
And 'FUBAR' - 'fucked up
beyond all recognition'.
MAN: General Patton
is a very wise person,
despite his personal eccentricities.
He said a number of memorable things
about war that only real soldiers know.
He said, "All plans last only
until the time of the first shot."
Then they're set aside.
Then you just have to go
on sheer invention and guts
and not running away
and various other things
that are never, never mentioned.
By September of 1944,
the Allies seemed to be moving steadily
toward victory in Europe.
On the eastern front,
the Russians had taken parts
of Estonia, Latvia, Lithuania and Poland,
and inflicted 700,000 more casualties
on the retreating Germans.
And in the 11 weeks since D-day,
American, British and Canadian forces
had freed most of France and Belgium
and parts of Holland
and were arrayed along the 350-mile belt
of concrete fortifications
the Germans called the 'Westwall'.
Beyond it lay the heart of Germany itself.
Allied planners had not expected
their forces to get that far
for another eight months.
George Patton's Third Army
had set the pace,
covering 400 miles in less than 30 days,
though he had outrun his supplies
and was desperately short of fuel.
His armoured columns alone required
some 600,000 gallons of gasoline
every 50 miles.
On September 11,
an armoured unit of the US First Army
crossed the German frontier.
"Militarily", General Dwight Eisenhower's
chief of staff told the press,
"this war is over."
Post exchanges were ordered
to halt all holiday packages
for the men on the European front.
Nearly everyone was certain
the war would be over by Christmas.
There was no room in the supply trucks
for winter clothing either.
Besides, the men wouldn't need it.
Meanwhile, the British had taken
the important Belgian port of Antwerp,
but no fuel or supplies
could be landed there
because the Germans
still held the estuary
that lay between the city
and the North Sea.
Eisenhower ordered British General
Bernard Montgomery to clear them out.
That would have taken weeks,
and Montgomery proposed
a daring alternative
designed to speed the Allied advance
into Germany -
Operation Market Garden.
First, American and British
airborne troops
would be dropped behind German lines
to seize bridges along a 65-mile highway
from Belgium, through Holland,
to Arnhem.
Then the British Second Army
would race along that highway,
cross the Rhine at Arnhem,
go around the northern end
of the Westwall
and drive into the Ruhr Valley,
the centre of German industrial might.
For the risky plan to succeed,
everything had to go perfectly
and quickly.
Eisenhower thought
the gamble was worth it.
If it did succeed,
the war could end in weeks.
"I not only approved of Market Garden,"
he said later, "I insisted on it."
On Sunday, September 17,
1,481 C-47 transports took off
in broad daylight from 24 British airfields
with 20,000 paratroopers on board.
Towed behind the transports
were hundreds of CG-4A gliders
carrying men and matériel.
Let's talk about the combat glider -
the CG-4A.
An 85-foot wingspan.
It would carry a ton and a half -
3,000 pounds -
plus the two pilots up front.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
But they were flying coffins. (Laughs)
There was no return.
So, the idea was to get your
people down or get your load down,
whatever it is,
and then become an infantryman,
which is what we became.
Harry Schmid, of Sacramento,
had been studying accounting
when he was drafted in 1942,
and first planned to become a medic.
But then, he said, he didn't want to
change bedpans for the whole war,
and volunteered to become a pilot.
When his weak eyes
kept him out of a fighter cockpit,
he settled for flying a glider
with the 82nd Airborne instead,
and found himself part
of Operation Market Garden.
Captain Dwain Luce, of Mobile,
was also on his way to Holland
aboard a glider.
The father of two small children,
he had left his family's cannery business
to join the 82nd Airborne
when the war started,
and had survived Sicily and Italy
and 33 days of fighting in Normandy.
MAN: I got out over the North Sea there,
and that pilot had a parachute on.
I told him, I said, "Look, you might
as well take that parachute off
"because you're not
leaving here without me."
And I said, "Now, you get your ass shot,
who's going to land this thing?"
He says, "You are."
SCHMID: Too fast a speed
with a CG-4A will kill you,
because you're talking about
a fabric airplane
with nothing but little aluminum struts.
And these guys come in at
90 miles an hour
and crash into something,
and, boy, they just disintegrate.
In all my combat missions,
I never came in at more
than 50 miles an hour.
I took the chance of getting hit
by ground fire and flak,
but I wanted to get my people down
and get down on the ground.
MAN ON RADIO:
This is Edward R. Murrow.
In just about 30 seconds now,
these 19 men will walk out
onto Dutch soil.
There he goes! Do you hear them shout?
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen.
(ENGINE ROARS OVERHEAD)
There they go. Every man out.
I can see their chutes going down now.
Every man clear,
hanging there very gracefully,
like nothing so much as khaki dolls
hanging beneath a green lampshade.
The whole sky is filled with parachutes.
They're all going down so slowly.
It seems as though they should
get to the ground much faster...
Things went well at first.
Dutch citizens poured into the streets
to greet the Americans.
The 82nd Airborne,
including Harry Schmid and Dwain Luce,
seized three bridges near Nijmegen,
then dug in
and waited for the British armour to
race up from Belgium and relieve them.
The 101 st Airborne took
four bridges near Eindhoven,
and when the Germans blew up a fifth,
managed to rebuild it overnight.
They too waited to be relieved.
But when the 10,000 men
of the British 1 st Airborne
came down seven miles from Arnhem,
the Dutch crowds that turned out
to greet them slowed their advance.
Only 500 of the soldiers
managed to reach the
all-important bridge across the Rhine.
Meanwhile, word of the Allied plan
had fallen into enemy hands,
and by the end of the day,
German panzers had surrounded
the outnumbered British at Arnhem.
(GUNFIRE)
Bad weather delayed airborne
reinforcements for several days,
and when a parachute brigade
of Free Poles was finally dropped in
it was shot to pieces.
The British armour
that was meant to meet up with
the paratroopers on the ground
and then spearhead
the advance into Germany
soon found itself under attack
from enemy artillery.
Smashed tanks and vehicles
caused massive traffic jams
that took hours to clear.
SCHMID: The idea of the whole mission,
of course, was to control the bridges
while Montgomery came up
with his tanks.
Well, they shot him all up, and he didn't
get there for seven days. (Chuckles)
So we were in the front lines
all that time.
We were not attacking the enemy,
but we were defending perimeters.
This was not the way
it was supposed to go.
Harry Schmid, Dwain Luce
and the men of the 82nd Airborne
found themselves struggling
just to hold on,
with no tanks and no heavy weapons.
SCHMID: And they had two ways
of going after you.
They'd either do shells that exploded on
the ground or they used air bursts.
(EXPLOSIONS)
You worried about those air bursts,
because they would... they would burst
about 20 feet above you,
and there was just shrapnel everywhere.
And just a little piece of shrapnel could
hit you, you know, and you're gone.
LUCE: They had better weapons,
in many cases, than we did.
You're talking about their 88s.
They were great weapons.
Very high velocity.
They were so damn fast that the bullet
got there before the sound did.
It was "Zip, bang!" you know?
Man, it just...
It was a terrible weapon to...
We all dreaded the 88s, I guess.
SCHMID: And when you're in a mission
where you're behind enemy lines,
you worry because
nobody knows anything.
You don't know whether the Germans
are coming or they aren't coming.
And that's probably the thing
that mentally bothers you,
is that you don't know what's going on.
As the Americans held their ground
near Nijmegen and Eindhoven,
the surrounded British at Arnhem
were being slaughtered.
(GUNFIRE)
Finally, after nine long days,
Montgomery abandoned his plan,
and ordered the survivors
to withdraw by boat.
Market Garden had been the largest
Allied airborne operation of the war...
...and the most disastrous.
17,000 Britons and Canadians,
Americans and Poles
were killed or wounded or captured
before the operation was abandoned...
...more casualties than the Allies
had suffered on D-day.
LUCE: You don't like
to see what you see. No.
You don't like to see what you see.
I mean, it's very disquieting to...
have your friends... gone
and some of them
pretty terribly mauled and things.
And... but that's part of it.
War is not a pleasant activity.
And you kind of need to keep
your sense of humour a little bit
to get through it.
The Allies had won themselves a
narrow 65-mile corridor across Holland,
but the rest of the British
and American troops,
including Dwain Luce and Harry Schmid,
had to stay where they were to hold it,
battling the deepening cold as well as
the relentless German shelling.
They would be left there for weeks.
LUCE: As a boy, I spent
a good time in the woods,
and I think my experiences with that
helped me survive,
and I think the little man upstairs
had his hand on my shoulder.
And I got hit once, across the helmet.
And it didn't penetrate my helmet,
but it'll make you change
your underwear, if you have any.
But that's the only time I got hit.
No, it's... it's kind of like
a bad dream, I guess.
Wouldn't want to do it again.
Nope. Couldn't do it again, I don't guess.
It was clear now that the war in Europe
would not end before winter.
(DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL FANFARE
PLAYS)
MAN: We couldn't wait for
the next war film to come out,
because it was filled with heroism
and everybody sacrificing for the war,
and everybody who died
died for a cause.
The biggest audience response
came, like, from a movie
'Flying Tigers' with John Wayne.
And when he shot down
Japanese planes
and the Japanese pilot
would hold his hands to his face
and the blood would come
out of his fingers,
we would jump up and cheer
because the good guys were winning.
(Speaks Japanese)
(BIC YCLE BELL RINGS)
WILSON: The big change
that the war brought for me
was I was a businessman
at the age of 10.
I was a 'Bee' carrier managing my
own money, managing my own route.
And what did I do
with my first pay cheque?
I went and bought a cardboard replica
of a.30 calibre machine gun
and went home and put it up in a tree
in the backyard
and made believe I was
mowing down the enemy like that.
That was my contribution
to the war effort.
And we all played war to a certain extent,
but it's interesting the way we
played war, because nobody ever died.
If you got shot, somebody
came to your aid and fixed you up,
and then you could rise up
and shoot again.
In Waterbury, Connecticut,
just before Pearl Harbor,
Miss Virginia Fleming had married
Staff Sergeant John Soden,
who had worked at
the US Rubber Company in Naugatuck.
They had a daughter,
born while Soden was in training,
and he had been home to see her
just once
before leaving for France
in the summer of 1944.
On September 10, after volunteering
to lead a patrol across the Moselle River,
he was hit in the leg.
(GUNFIRE)
He had his 'million-dollar wound',
his ticket home, he told a friend,
and was carried to a barn
where he was to receive treatment.
(EXPLOSION)
Then, a German shell hit the barn.
A few days later,
Virginia Soden got a telegram
regretting to inform her
that John was missing in action.
She wrote to him right away.
WOMAN: "To my dearest
husband and daddy.
"I pray to God you will be OK
and be back soon,
"as I don't know what I'd ever do.
"But you're coming home, darling.
"And we'll enjoy life
like we're supposed to be entitled to.
"Well, sweets, your daughter is OK.
"I still kiss her every night for her daddy.
"But the poor little dear
doesn't know what it's all about.
"She's so like you, darling,
in every respect.
"The cheque you sent for $40 came.
"Thanks a million, darling.
"Every little bit will help
for our future, right?
"Well, John, I can't seem
to write any more,
"except I still love you more than ever.
"I pray you'll be safe and home soon.
"Your wife, Virginia."
A month later,
a second telegram arrived.
John Soden would not be
coming home to Waterbury.
The shell that had exploded in the
makeshift hospital had killed him.
Virginia's younger brother
would always remember
that after she read the telegram
his sister let out "an unearthly howl".
MAN: War is mostly boredom,
telling lies,
stealing from some other outfit
if they've got something better to eat
than you have,
and just making the best
of a thousand bad situations.
It's going to rain. You're going to get wet.
It's going to get too hot.
It's going to get too cold.
I mean, you're always uncomfortable
in the service, it seemed like to me.
By the spring of 1944,
Sid Phillips, of Mobile,
had been stationed in the Pacific
for more than two years.
He had survived the fighting on
Guadalcanal and at Cape Gloucester
and hoped to be sent to Australia,
with its plentiful beer and friendly girls,
until he got his orders to go home.
Instead, his 1 st Marine Division
was sent to Pavuvu,
a remote island so small
that when the men drilled,
one outfit had to march clockwise
and the next counterclockwise
to keep from blocking the only road.
Sitting on his cot one hot afternoon,
Phillips was surprised to see
a familiar figure -
his best friend from Mobile,
Eugene Sledge.
PHILLIPS: I saw him coming down
the company street, looking intense.
I recognised him and ran out,
screamed his name.
And we ran and beat on each other
and embraced
and rolled around on the ground.
People thought we were fighting
and a big crowd gathered.
But then I introduced him around,
and it was just a great day.
20-year-old Eugene B. Sledge
was the grandson
of Confederate officers.
Bookish and frail as a child,
he had been taught to fish and hunt
by his physician father
and was a freshman
at the Marion Military Institute,
studying to become an officer,
when he decided to sign on
as a private in the Marines instead.
He told his anxious parents
that if he waited for graduation,
he might not get a chance at combat.
WOMAN: Eugene Sledge was just
an ordinary young man.
He was full of pranks and full of tricks,
and he and my brother Sidney
pulled every one of them
that they possibly could.
But they were such great friends
that what one did,
the other one followed suit.
He was a very gentle man,
as my brother Sidney was,
to be thrown into
the middle of a fight like that.
Not long after Sledge
got to the Pacific,
he began keeping
an unauthorised journal,
slipping tiny sheets of notes
between the pages
of the small New Testament he carried
so that no-one else would know
what he was doing.
Years later, those uncensored notes
would form the basis
of a harrowing memoir
of his experiences in the Pacific.
MAN: "The awesome reality that
we were training to be cannon fodder
"in a global war that had already
snuffed out millions of lives
"never seemed to occur to us.
"The fact that our own lives
might end violently
"or that we might be crippled
while we were still boys
"didn't seem to register.
"The only thing that we seemed
to be truly concerned about
"was that we might be too afraid
to do our jobs under fire.
"An apprehension nagged at each of us
"that he might appear to be yellow
if he were afraid."
Eugene Sledge.
PHILLIPS: He had come in
as a replacement,
and I was being rotated home because
I had been overseas over two years.
I certainly did think about what
he was facing, because it was all bad.
Every campaign was bad.
Some were a little quicker
and a little worse than others,
some were under worse conditions
than others,
but they were all bad, and I knew
he was going to face some hard times.
In late August of 1944,
Sledge and 16,458 other men
of the 1 st Marine Division
left Pavuvu for the Palau Islands,
more than 2,000 miles away.
The marines were headed
for the tiny island of Peleliu,
where the Japanese
had constructed an airfield.
It was only 550 miles east of Mindanao,
which was to be the first stop in
General Douglas MacArthur's campaign
to recapture the Philippines.
MacArthur wanted Peleliu
put out of action to protect his flank.
But as Eugene Sledge and his fellow
marines steamed toward their target,
playing poker and sunbathing
on the deck to fill the time,
Allied plans changed.
After the decisive American victory
in the Battle of the Philippine Sea
the previous June,
Admiral William Halsey
no longer considered the
Japanese air force a serious threat.
The Peleliu airfield
had become largely irrelevant.
But no-one cancelled the invasion
of the island.
Halsey was sure it would take
only four days to secure it.
For three days,
the navy bombarded Peleliu.
(EXPLOSIONS)
The foliage that blanketed
its jagged coral hills was burned away.
The coral itself was bleached white
by phosphorus.
Finally, the officer in charge told his
superiors, "We have run out of targets."
It was time to send in the marines.
MAN: "It was hard to sleep
that night before the invasion.
"I thought of home,
my parents, my friends,
"and whether I would do my duty,
be wounded or disabled, or be killed.
"I concluded that it was impossible for
me to be killed, because God loved me.
"And then I told myself
that God loved us all
"and that many would die
"or be ruined physically or mentally
or both
"in the days following.
"My heart pounded,
and I broke out in a cold sweat.
"Finally, I called myself
a damned coward
"and eventually fell asleep
saying the Lord's Prayer to myself."
(EXPLOSIONS, GUNFIRE)
The invasion of Peleliu began at dawn
on September 15, 1944.
At 6:30 in the morning,
Sledge and his comrades
clambered into their amtracs
and started for the island.
"The world was a nightmare of flashes,
violent explosions, snapping bullets.
"Up and down the beach,
a number of amtracs were burning.
"Japanese machine-gun bursts
made long splashes on the water,
"as though flaying it
with some giant whip."
Three marine regiments -
more than 5,000 men -
went ashore side by side
and quickly discovered that the
bombardment had done little damage
to the carefully prepared warren
of 500 fortified caves
and concealed gun emplacements,
some equipped with sliding doors
of armoured steel,
that honeycombed the coral ridges
running up the centre of the island.
The Japanese poured fire down upon
Eugene Sledge and his fellow marines.
"I turned my face away
and wished that I were imagining it all.
"I had tasted the bitterest
essence of war,
"the sight of helpless comrades
being slaughtered,
"and it filled me with disgust."
Willie Rushton, also from Mobile,
was on the beach too,
now a member
of the 11th Depot Company.
And then the first day
we went in there,
those people they just...
they slaughtered us marines
like we were just a bunch of hogs
coming in the slaughter pen.
The Japanese were some
tough customers.
They really could fight. They come
at you with everything they had.
So, we marines, we were just as tough
or tougher than they were,
so we always - well, almost -
came out on top.
The Americans lost 1,200 men,
but they clung to the beach and some
began fighting their way inland.
Eugene Sledge was a mortarman.
He fired round after round
into the enemy
while riflemen advanced ahead of him.
He and his regiment managed to make it
all the way across the narrow island,
then dug in for the night.
No-one slept, for fear that Japanese
infiltrators would slip into their lines
and slit their throats.
"It was the darkest night I ever saw.
"The overcast sky was as black as the
dripping mangroves that walled us in.
"I had the sensation
of being in a great black hole
"and reaching out to touch the sides
of the gun pit to orient myself.
"Slowly, the reality of it all
formed in my mind -
"we were expendable.
"It was difficult to accept.
"We come from a nation and a culture
that values life and the individual.
"To find oneself in a situation
where your life seems of little value
"is the ultimate in loneliness."
The next morning, the marines were
ordered to assault Japanese positions
in the cliffs that overlooked the airfield.
Tanks and artillery would go first,
then the infantry and Sledge
would follow,
charging across the exposed
gravel airstrip to attack the high ground.
The temperature neared 100 degrees.
There was no shade.
The only water available, hauled up
from the beach in 5-gallon cans,
turned out to be fouled by diesel oil.
Scores of men collapsed
from heat exhaustion
before the signal was given.
As the marines - four battalions
and 1,800 men - moved forward,
the enemy opened up
with everything they had.
"I clenched my teeth,
squeezed my carbine stock,
"recited over and over to myself, 'The
Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want.
"'Yea, though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death,
"'I will fear no evil, for thou art with me.'
"The further we went, the worse it got.
"It seemed impossible that any of us
would make it across.
"To be shelled by massed artillery
and mortars is absolutely terrifying,
"but to be shelled in the open
is terror compounded."
Sledge somehow made it
across the airstrip safely,
and took what shelter he could
beneath a bush.
He was "shaking like a leaf", he wrote,
but took comfort from the fact
that a veteran of the fighting
on Guadalcanal, crouching nearby,
was shaking too.
Japanese tactics had changed
since the beginning of the war.
Suicidal banzai charges,
like those on Guadalcanal
and Tarawa and Saipan,
were largely a thing of the past.
Instead, Peleliu's 10,500 defenders
would contest every inch of the island
from their hillside strongholds.
They would have to be blasted
or burned out of them, one at a time.
(GUNSHOT)
"Even before the dust had settled,
"I saw a Japanese soldier appear
at the blasted opening.
"He drew back his arm
to throw a grenade at us.
"My carbine was already up.
"When he appeared,
I lined up my sights on his chest
"and began squeezing off shots."
(GUNFIRE)
"As the first bullet hit him,
his face contorted in agony.
"His knees buckled.
"The grenade slipped from his grasp.
"I had just killed a man at close range.
"That I had seen clearly the pain
on his face when my bullets hit him
"came as a jolt.
"It suddenly made the war
a very personal affair."
Willie Rushton was in the thick of it too.
He wasn't supposed to be -
his outfit was assigned to just
unload supplies and ammunition.
But when the fighting started,
he and some of his friends volunteered
for front-line duty.
RUSHTON: But we were right there
where the fighting was going on,
you know.
They was just knocking us off
as we came forward.
That's what they were doing -
knocking us off.
They didn't make no... whether
you was black or white or whatever -
they didn't care
when you got into combat.
15 members of Rushton's
depot company were hit.
He was one of them,
wounded in the leg by shrapnel.
He was carried to a hospital ship
offshore,
the only wounded black man aboard.
After his wounds were treated
he asked if he could have a haircut.
The ship's barber refused.
When I got up there, he told me,
he said, "I can't cut your hair."
And so then a couple of white marines
asked him, "Why can't you cut his hair?"
Said, "You don't have to give him
no style, just cut his hair off.
"All he wants is some
of that hair off his head."
So he said, "No, I can't.
I can't cut his hair."
Then the captain intervened.
The captain of the Red Cross ship
came down there and told that barber,
"I'm telling you for the first
and the last time -
"I don't care who comes on this ship,
if he's an American soldier,
"whether he's black or white
or whatever,
"I want you to cut his hair, you know,
just cut his hair.
"Don't ever make a remark like that
anymore."
Private Rushton got his haircut.
For Eugene Sledge and the other
marines still fighting on Peleliu,
one day, one firefight,
one terror-filled night
now seemed just like the next.
"During a lull, the men stripped the
packs and pockets of the enemy dead
"for souvenirs.
"The men gloated over, compared,
and often swapped their prizes.
"It was a brutal, ghastly ritual
"the likes of which have occurred
since ancient times
"on battlefields where
the antagonists have possessed
"a profound mutual hatred.
"It was uncivilised, as is all war,
and was carried out with savagery.
"It wasn't simply souvenir hunting
or looting the enemy dead -
"it was more like Indian warriors
taking scalps.
"While I was removing a bayonet
and scabbard from a dead Japanese,
"I noticed a marine dragging
what I assumed to be a corpse.
"But the Japanese wasn't dead.
"He had been wounded severely
in the back and couldn't move his arms.
"The Japanese's mouth glowed
with huge, gold-crowned teeth,
"and his captor wanted them.
"He put the point of his KA-BAR knife
on the base of a tooth
"and hit the handle
with the palm of his hand.
"Because the Japanese was
kicking his feet and thrashing about,
"the knifepoint glanced off the tooth
and sank deeply into the victim's mouth.
"The marine cursed him, and with
a slash, cut his cheeks open ear to ear.
"I shouted,
'Put that man out of his misery.'
"All I got for an answer
was a cussing out.
"Another marine ran up and put a bullet
in the enemy soldier's brain
"and ended his agony.
"The scavenger grumbled and continued
extracting his prizes undisturbed."
"There were certain areas
we moved into and out of several times
"as the campaign dragged
along its weary, bloody course.
"I became quite familiar with the sight
of some particular enemy corpse,
"as if it were a landmark.
"It was gruesome
to see the stages of decay proceed
"from just killed, to bloated,
"to maggot-infested rotting,
to partially exposed bones,
"like some biological clock
marking the inexorable passage of time.
"On each occasion my company
passed such a landmark,
"we were fewer in number."
"The opposing forces on Peleliu
were like two scorpions in a bottle,"
Eugene Sledge wrote.
"One was annihilated,
the other nearly so."
After six weeks of combat,
Sledge and the rest
of the 1 st Marine Division
were finally taken off the island.
It would be another month
before the Japanese commander
finally radioed his superiors
that "All is over on Peleliu"
and then committed suicide.
A handful of Japanese would go on
fighting there until February of 1945.
Securing Peleliu was supposed
to take four days.
It took more than two months.
10,000 Japanese were killed - nearly
every man who had defended the island.
More than 1,200 Americans perished,
including Private John D. New,
who had grown up in Mobile
just across town from Eugene Sledge.
He hurled himself
onto a Japanese grenade,
saving the lives of two friends
but losing his own.
For his heroism, he received
a posthumous Medal of Honor.
5,274 more Americans
were maimed or missing.
Out of the 235 men
in Eugene Sledge's company,
only 85 left the island
without physical wounds.
And in the end, there had been
no tactical need for the little airfield
for which so many
of Sledge's friends had died.
"As I struggled upward onto the boat
with my load of equipment,
"I felt like a weary insect climbing a vine.
"But at last I was crawling up
out of the abyss of Peleliu.
"I stowed my gear on my rack
and went topside.
"The salt air was delicious to breathe.
"What a luxury to inhale
long, deep breaths of fresh, clean air.
"But something in me died at Peleliu.
"Perhaps it was a childish innocence
that accepted as faith
"the claim that man is basically good.
"Possibly I lost faith
that politicians in high places,
"who do not have
to endure war's savagery,
"will ever stop blundering
and sending others to endure it."
Eugene Sledge.
Over the coming weeks,
on both sides of the world,
Allied force would continue
to be undercut by Allied folly.