NARRATOR: On August 3, 1944,
in the skies over the town of Vire,
in France...
...the law of averages caught up
with fighter pilot Quentin Aanenson
of Luverne, Minnesota.
MAN: I was flying
the 'tail-end charlie' position,
which means the last one
in the line of flight,
which is the most vulnerable position
because that's the one
they'll start with first.
And suddenly the 88s and 20mm
started coming up in heavy amounts,
and just "Brmm!"
I heard this roar through my airplane
and fire came into the cockpit,
just all in an instant.
My airplane was shaking.
I thought, "I'm gone."
So I tried to bale out.
I tried to move the canopy back,
and a piece of flak had come up
through the glide
and so I couldn't get the canopy open.
Couldn't get it open.
The fire was still coming at me,
and so I put the plane in a dive,
because we'd always discussed
that we didn't want to die by burns.
And so I put the plane in a dive -
I was only at 4,000 feet,
so I could hit the ground fast -
and that move literally saved my life
because the air pressure changed
and so the flames were sucked out
through that opening in the canopy
and that fire died out.
I got back to the base.
I would stall if my speed
dropped below 160 miles an hour
so I landed at 170 miles an hour,
and I didn't know that one of the 20mm
had come up through my left wheel well,
and I had a flat tyre there.
So when the landing gear
collapsed on one side,
I was still going
about 100 miles an hour,
and I was spun around by the force.
My shoulder harness on the right
broke loose.
The left one held.
I was spun around, and the back
of my head hit the gunsight.
So I was unconscious.
Then a couple of enlisted men
had pulled me out
and pulled me away from there.
After medics tended to his dislocated
shoulder and the burns on his legs,
a British photographer
from 'Picture Post' magazine
asked Aanenson to pose with his plane.
MAN: Al Mclntosh,
'Rock County Star Herald'.
"Lieutenant John Stavenger,
bomber pilot now in England,
"has decided it's
a mighty small world after all.
"He hadn't hardly landed
"before he bumped into
Lieutenant Howard James, of Luverne.
"Then he leisurely settled back
and read an English magazine.
"He looked at one big picture
of a wrecked plane.
"The picture carried the caption,
'The man who was lost returns to base.'
"The pilot in question was none other
"than Lieutenant Quentin Aanenson,
of Luverne.
"His family knew nothing of the incident.
"And the picture showed
the Luverne youngster walking away
"from his wrecked plane
"as blithely unconcerned as if he'd
just bought a nickel's worth of candy."
A week after his close call,
Aanenson was back in the air,
providing ground cover for the
Americans advancing toward Germany.
By the autumn of 1944,
the Allied advance
across western Europe had stalled,
crippled by continuing problems
with supplies,
confusion among commanders
and stubborn German defence
of the fatherland.
The people of Mobile, Alabama
and Sacramento, California,
Luverne, Minnesota
and Waterbury, Connecticut,
who had hoped the D-day invasion
and capture of Paris
would bring a swift victory,
remained anxious
about their sons and brothers,
husbands and fathers overseas.
A strategic mistake
would put Tom Galloway,
a college student from Mobile,
in an unwinnable battle where
the only victory to be had was survival.
Robert Kashiwagi, of Sacramento,
who had had everything taken from him
by his country,
would be asked to give even more.
And Quentin Aanenson, of Luverne,
who had lost so many friends
and seen so much death,
would endure still more horror
and nearly lose all hope.
Meanwhile, for those held captive
by the Japanese in the Pacific theatre,
rescue still seemed a long way off.
GIRL: "Santo Tomas Camp, Manila.
"Daddy is now out of tobacco.
"He dries papaya leaves on the roof
and smokes that.
"People use anything
to roll their cigarettes.
"Some even use pages from the Bible
because the paper is so fine.
"Every day I hear of some person
doing strange things.
"A Catholic priest did a mortal sin
by going around with a lady,
"then falling in love with her,
"acting so mushy in front of everybody
that he was kicked out of the church.
"I heard a husband and wife
fighting loudly.
"She yelled at him, 'lf I hadn't married
you, I wouldn't be in this camp now."'
Sascha Weinzheimer.
11 -year-old Sascha Weinzheimer
and her family were still imprisoned,
along with 4,000 other civilians
rounded up by the Japanese,
on the grounds
of the Santo Tomas University in Manila,
on the island of Luzon.
As the war went on,
conditions had steadily deteriorated.
WOMAN: Once the food started
going down, everything went down.
And toward the end,
my mother was 73 pounds.
And she nursed my brother
until he was three.
So if you see a picture of him
during that time, he is chubby.
And that's because of mother's milk.
But that depleted her.
(AIRPLANE ENGINES BUZZ)
GIRL: "September 21, 1944.
"This morning, about 9:30,
"there were seven Nip planes above us
practising diving.
"It was a bright, sunshiny day.
"Then we heard the sound
of many planes in the distance
"but didn't pay much attention.
"Mother said, 'That's a different sound.
Can't you hear it?"'
(ENGINES DRONE)
"Mother ran outside
and we heard her yell, 'Look, look!
"'There are hundreds of them! '
"We all ran out, and right over our heads
were planes, planes, planes!
"Everyone was screaming
and pointing up at them."
WEINZHEIMER:
That was absolutely fantastic.
First of all, the engines
were not Mitsubishi engines,
they were American -
different-sounding, strong engines.
(GUNFIRE)
Waves of American planes
launched from aircraft carriers
roared in over Manila,
bombing and strafing
Japanese positions,
attacking Japanese warships
anchored in the bay.
"Everyone was so excited.
"Of course, it was very dangerous for us
"because of the shrapnel falling
all over the camp from the ack-ack guns,
"but everyone seemed to feel that our
boys and our bombs couldn't hurt us."
('PENNIES FROM HEAVEN' PLAYS)
The Japanese were still in control
of the Philippines,
but the American assault had begun,
and the next morning,
the prisoner who played music
over the camp's loudspeaker
put on 'Pennies from Heaven'.
(Billie Holiday sings) #... the things
you love, you must have showers
# So when you hear it thunder
# Don't run under a tree
# There'll be pennies from heaven
# For you and me... #
One month later, on October 20,
General Douglas MacArthur's forces
landed on the island of Leyte...
...the first foothold in the struggle
to win back the Philippines.
MacArthur's own landing craft
got stuck 75 yards offshore
and he had no choice
but to wade to the beach.
His publicity machine
made the most of it.
NEWSREEL: When General MacArthur
left his command of Bataán
by presidential order,
he gave the solemn promise,
"I will return."
Now he tells the Philippine people,
"I have returned."
WOMAN: So when he came wading
through the water up on the beach,
there were great cheers
in the movie theatre.
Because that's, of course,
how we saw MacArthur returning.
I realise now it was staged, a lot of it,
but, man, it was good
to see him walking back.
MacArthur's return thrilled
Americans and Filipinos alike.
As his men began to fight their way
across the islands of the Philippines,
what remained of the once-mighty
Japanese fleet would be shattered
in the largest naval engagement
in history -
the Battle of Leyte Gulf.
But 24 volunteer enemy pilots offered
fresh evidence of Japan's resolve
to keep fighting, no matter the odds.
They deliberately crashed their planes
into the decks of American carriers
in hopes of setting them ablaze.
They were called Kamikazes -
Japanese for 'divine wind'.
(GUNFIRE)
Despite the victory at sea,
months of bloody fighting lay ahead...
...before the Philippine islands,
and the people imprisoned on them,
could be liberated.
MAN: Everybody was scared to death
all the time.
And yet, you never said so, you never
gave any signals that you were.
You just were, and you knew
the other people were too.
You don't run away,
because every alternative is impossible.
There's no way out of it,
there's no way to change it,
and you are there
until you get killed or wounded.
Or until you flee
and, you know, allow everybody
to exercise their instinct for contempt,
which is unthinkable to most people.
So there's no way out,
and that puts you in a situation
that you're never in, I think,
in civilian life.
Back in Europe,
the Allies were still stalled in the north,
suffering from supply problems,
the disaster
of Operation Market Garden,
and intensified German resistance.
The American Seventh Army's drive
northward from the south of France
had run into trouble as well.
They had landed at Marseilles
in mid-August,
and at first things had gone better
than anyone had anticipated.
Within a month,
they had pushed almost 400 miles,
taken 89,000 German prisoners
and linked up with elements
of Patton's Third Army
to finally complete the continuous line
Eisenhower now believed essential
to the Allied cause.
But thousands of Germans had
retreated into the Vosges mountains -
steep, thickly forested with evergreens,
shrouded in fog
and drenched with cold autumn rains.
There they dug in, ordered to halt
the Allied advance into Germany.
American units that had already fought
in the mountains of Italy
were sent to France and ordered
to battle their way through the Vosges.
One was the 36th Texas Division,
the same outfit
that had nearly been destroyed
at Monte Cassino the previous winter.
Another, attached to it,
especially requested by headquarters,
was the 100th/442nd Combat Team -
Japanese-American troops,
most of them recruited from
internment camps in the United States.
They had once been considered
a problem by the army.
Now they were problem-solvers,
called in when others failed.
MAN: It was bitterly cold.
That's when the 'lost battalion' campaign
happened,
because our general was very,
you might say, ambitious.
You say "blood and guts". Why was it
our blood and his guts, you know?
Major General John E. Dahlquist,
commander of the Texas Division,
was relatively new to combat
and had nearly lost his command twice
during the drive north from the Riviera
for allowing his men to lag behind.
But he was convinced he was a better
tactician than more seasoned soldiers.
And he would prove willing
to use his detachment
of Japanese-American veterans
to correct his own mistakes.
The village of Bruyères
was their first target.
Dahlquist assured them the surrounding
hills were only lightly defended.
In fact, they were filled with
well-dug-in Germans.
The 442nd cleared them off in four days,
despite the terrain, the steady icy
downpour that filled their foxholes,
and the rain of artillery shells
bursting among the treetops.
MAN: General Dahlquist was, uh...
...a very strict general.
And especially, it seems to me,
that he was trying to push
the 442nd too hard, too far.
Telling us to "advance, advance",
you know.
So he was hard in that way.
And I really didn't have
any respect for him.
Meanwhile, General Dahlquist
had sent a battalion of his Texans
along a densely forested ridge
toward the important town of Saint-Dié.
Again, veteran officers warned him
the woods were full of Germans.
Again, Dahlquist insisted
there were none.
Within an hour,
the Texans were under attack.
275 of them were cut off
and surrounded by the Germans,
who zeroed in on them from three sides.
For two days,
shells blasted their positions.
The Texans began to run out
of food and ammunition.
Two attempts
to break through to them failed.
Finally, on October 26,
Dahlquist ordered the exhausted men
of the 442nd
to return to the wooded slopes,
rescue the 'lost battalion' -
as the Texans would come to be called -
and restore his reputation.
MAN: One time, our regimental
commander, Colonel Pence,
pleaded with the division commander,
you know,
that we could pull back
'cause our men were so depleted.
But the division general said,
"No, we need to get those boys out,
because every day counts.
"You get in there and get them out
"if it takes every damn last one of you
to do it."
For five days,
fighting from tree to tree in heavy fog,
they tried to get to the trapped men.
On the morning of October 30,
they were just 1,000 yards
from the survivors
but pinned to the slope
by artillery and machine-gun fire.
KASHIWAGl: We were stuck,
because it's a terrain that was steep,
and so we were on our own,
like a cowboy-and-lndian type of battle,
and so the other people couldn't help us.
Finally, they had had enough.
I Company
and Robert Kashiwagi's K Company
rose to their feet
and charged up the hillside,
hurling grenades
into German machine-gun nests
and firing from the waist
as they climbed.
KASHIWAGl: We just went
hog-wild crazy.
We were mad at everybody
and ready to kill anything that there was.
And finally we made contact
with the lost battalion,
and we found only 230 or so surviving.
But we lost 400 men
trying to rescue those 230.
What a terrible price we paid.
TOKUNO: After we rescued the outfit,
why, the first Caucasian fellow
that came out
said, "I was never so glad
to see a Jap in my life."
Ha!
That's the first thing he said.
I Company had started into the forest
with 185 men.
Just 8 walked out unhurt.
Robert Kashiwagi's K Company
had begun with 186 men.
Only 17 emerged on foot.
All the rest were dead
or wounded or missing.
Kashiwagi had himself
been hit by shrapnel
for a third and then a fourth time
in the fighting.
A few days later,
Mr and Mrs Kametaro Takeuchi,
formerly of Sacramento,
now living behind barbed wire
at the Granada Relocation Center,
received a telegram.
Their son, Tadashi,
had been among those killed
in the struggle to rescue
the lost battalion.
On November 12,
General Dahlquist announced
he wanted to review the 442nd
to thank them for what they had done.
KASHIWAGl: The general decided,
"Well, now, we want to award
you people, recognise your deed."
And so he said, "We want
the whole regiment in formation."
And when the general got there
and looked at the formation,
he was so disgusted.
He said, "I asked you to get
the whole regiment out there!"
And our colonel, with tears in his eyes,
says, "General", he says,
"that's all that's left
of that particular regiment.
"That's exactly what you did to us."
MAN: In the schools, we always talked
about what was happening in the war
in all the grades that I remember.
Once in a while, we would have
somebody come home, you know,
who had been overseas,
who would come up to the school
and talk about where
they had been or...
You really... you know, again,
you know, between 6 and 10 years old,
I wasn't into the geopolitical aspects
of the war.
I was more impressed to see the guy.
(LIVELY JAZZ MUSIC)
MAN: I think every man that was
in the service was well aware of the fact
that when you came home on furlough,
it was a very good chance
that you would lapse
into a release of bad language, so...
It was dominant in your thinking.
It made you speak slowly
and deliberately
and almost repeat in your own mind
what you were going to say
before you said it,
because, you know, in the service,
you just don't use any adjectives -
you forget all your adjectives
and just use one or two.
WOMAN: Like?
Like I'm not going say.
(Chuckles)
My wife would come down from heaven
and hit me on the head.
FUSSELL: When you come on the line,
you are very brave
because you know nothing
about what's happening.
And it's easy for you to perform
pseudo-brave gestures and procedures,
because you don't know yet.
And gradually -
this is because you have
a reservoir of courage when you arrive -
and each time you get badly frightened,
a little of it diminishes
until you don't have any left.
And that is the worst moment.
As the lost battalion was being rescued,
Paul Fussell, a newly minted second
lieutenant in the 103rd Infantry Division,
was bivouacked at Épinal,
at the foot of the Vosges mountains.
He was 20 years old,
from Pasadena, California,
fresh from 19 months of training
and filled with excitement.
He had told his parents he felt
"very confident and safe"
as he went off to war.
The reception he and his fellow soldiers
had received
during their first few days
in southern France
only added to his buoyancy.
As the division moved northward,
up the Rhône Valley,
young women appeared along the road,
waving and passing out bottles of wine.
FUSSELL: We brought in good health -
very important -
youth, optimism...
That's why these 18-year-olds
could pursue war at all.
They were kids. They were optimistic.
And they really thought that
if you did well, you'd be rewarded.
I mean, they were that innocent.
They had no idea about life's accidents.
On the night of November 10,
he and the rest of the men
of Company F
were ordered up to the front,
to a thickly forested hillside
overlooking Saint-Dié,
the town toward which
the lost battalion had been heading
when it was surrounded
by the Germans.
They were to replace a weary company
that had been engaged with the enemy
for weeks.
FUSSELL: I came across
two German kids,
dead, lying on their backs.
They'd been killed the day before
by the unit we were replacing.
And they were so young,
I couldn't believe it.
I thought they were between
maybe 12 and 14 years old.
And at the end of the war, of course,
the Germans were absolutely
scraping the barrel of everybody -
old men who could hardly walk...
...and little kids
from late grammar school.
These kids had little uniforms on.
They were wearing caps, not helmets.
And each had been shot
through the head.
And the blue... bluish-red brains of one
were coming out his nostrils.
They had their eyes open too.
And the other one, his bluish-red brain
was coming out just from under his cap,
and sort of displacing his cap
as he wore it.
And that really gave me a jolt.
I seldom refer to it.
But it was my introduction to some
painful facts - that this war is serious.
We are going to kill people,
regardless of their age,
as long as they're wearing
German uniforms,
and they are going to try to kill us.
MAN: I often wondered
why the Germans didn't quit.
I wondered why they didn't quit
after Normandy.
Once we successfully landed
on the Continent,
to me it was obvious
we're going to win the war -
it was just how long, or how soon.
And all that we went through
and the people that were killed.
But what's your alternative?
The Allied command in Europe
had not waited to see how
Operation Market Garden turned out
before mounting four more or less
simultaneous assaults on the Westwall,
which the Allies called the Siegfried line.
Each had fallen short.
The Seventh Army overran Strasbourg
but was halted on the Rhine's
west bank.
Patton's Third Army took Metz
and secured three bridgeheads
across the Saar,
but could proceed no further
until it could get enough fuel to go on.
In the north, two attacks were launched
by the American First Army.
One was aimed at the German city
of Aachen.
The other intended to sweep the enemy
from the 50 wooded square miles
just south of that city
called the Hurtgen Forest.
MAN: The Hurtgen Forest
was the worst.
And you haven't heard much about it
because... it was just a mess-up.
There was no reason
to go through the forest,
but the generals kept wanting to
go through the forest.
And you'd put a division in there
and chew it up,
and they'd pull it out and
put another division in and chew it up.
It was a nightmarish place to fight...
...with 100-foot fir trees that
in some places grew just 4 feet apart.
"It was so dense and dark
and shrouded in dank fog,"
one general remembered,
"that upon entering it, you want
to drop things behind to mark your path,
"as Hansel and Gretel did
with their breadcrumbs."
Two parallel lines of German pillboxes
and log-and-dirt bunkers
were hidden among the trees,
several miles apart.
The pine needles that blanketed
the forest floor disguised trip-wires
and mines the Americans called
'Bouncing Betties'
that sprang into the air
and went off at groin height.
The commanders who planned the battle
knew almost nothing about the terrain
and never came to see it for themselves.
And no-one had been trained
to fight in such a place.
"We're taking three trees a day,"
one officer said,
"and they cost us
a hundred men apiece."
The first two divisions
to be ordered into the forest
would lose 4,500 men in three weeks
and move less than three miles.
On November 2,
the 28th Infantry Division followed.
With them was Second Lieutenant
Tom Galloway from Mobile, Alabama,
an acquaintance of Sid Phillips
and his sister Katharine.
He had been a senior
at Auburn University
and was now a replacement officer
on the front lines,
a forward observer scouting targets
for the 109th Field Artillery.
GALLOWAY:
The man I replaced got shot,
and it just wasn't too good to think
what happened to him,
but then you've replaced him.
Targets were almost impossible to spot
from the ground.
Dense growth and constant fog
hid them from the air as well.
Tanks could barely move
on the handful of narrow, muddy,
heavily mined logging trails.
Soldiers could not see one another,
let alone the enemy.
"If anyone said he knew where he was,"
one commander said,
"he was a damned liar."
Despite everything, Galloway's division
took its first objective -
the little town of Schmidt -
in just two days.
The Germans took it back
the following morning.
The battlelines became totally confused.
We were all mixed up.
Give you an example - the medics.
There was only one building
that I know about there
and both the German and American
medics were using it.
They were just bringing in
all the wounded
and both sides were using
that one building.
A steady, cold rain began to fall,
followed by sleet, then snow.
Thousands developed trench foot.
When it was too painful to stand,
men took turns kneeling in the icy water
that filled their foxholes.
German 88 shells burst
in the fir trees above them,
showering the men with shrapnel
and dagger-sharp shards of wood.
GALLOWAY: The artillery
would hit those trees
and you didn't know if you were hit
by artillery or flying wood.
There just was no place
to get protection.
The Germans had it,
they had it all mapped.
And you had to go down the firebreaks.
Of course, they would have guns
at those firebreaks.
And it made it bad.
I just recall one morning
I went in with the battalion,
and before nightfall
the sergeant major came to me
and told me I was
the only officer they had left.
And that's out of a battalion.
And it just chewed people up.
(EXPLOSIONS)
"The days were so terrible
that I would pray for darkness,"
one private recalled,
"and the nights were so bad
I would pray for daylight."
By November 13, the officers of every
single rifle company in the 28th Division
had been killed or wounded.
After a night
of continuous German shelling,
an entire company broke and ran.
Even officers with drawn revolvers
could not stop them.
Hundreds of men shot themselves
in the foot or hand
rather than endure any more.
Hundreds more collapsed
psychologically,
sat staring into the distance
as if no battle raged around them.
The reporter Ernie Pyle called it
"the accumulated blur,
the hurting vagueness
"of being too long in the lines."
In mid-November,
fresh troops replaced what was left
of Tom Galloway's division.
The fighting in the Hurtgen Forest
would go on for weeks.
More than 33,000 American soldiers
would be lost.
So many died,
and those who lived spent
so much time desperately digging
for their own protection,
that there were few burials.
When the snow melted
the following spring,
hundreds of bodies and parts of bodies
would still litter the forest floor.
GALLOWAY: The men were...
well, you were just all beat up.
You'd been in that mess.
You'd been under that strain.
You just were glad to get out of there.
I like to think that probably
the prettiest sight that I saw over there
was coming out of the forest,
up on a hill, and looking down.
It had snowed, and the whole -
these were big fir trees -
and they were all pretty,
with snow on and everything.
And I couldn't decide
whether the scene was pretty
or I was so glad to get out of there
that made it look so pretty.
But I do remember that.
Galloway and his comrades
were sent for rest and recovery
to the Ardennes Forest,
a quiet place where nothing much
was thought likely to happen.
November 23, 1944 was Thanksgiving.
Defense workers in Mobile, Alabama
and Waterbury, Connecticut
remained on the job
to help speed the day of victory.
At noon, servicemen at McClellan Field,
in Sacramento,
were serenaded by the glee club
of the 4909 Aviation Squadron.
And in Luverne, Minnesota,
the local Lutheran church
held separate Thanksgiving services
in English and in German.
Thanksgiving turkey was served
to the men
on the forested slopes
of the Vosges mountains,
though it was cold by the time
it got to Lieutenant Paul Fussell.
That same afternoon,
he found himself part of a 12-man squad
ordered forward
to scout the defences
of the German-held town of Nothalten.
(GUNSHOT)
A burst of rifle fire
forced them to find what cover
they could behind a small rise.
German snipers had them
in their sights.
No-one seemed to know what to do.
Then a second lieutenant
moved forward with his carbine.
"Let's get the sons of bitches," he said.
FUSSELL: His name was Abe Goldman.
And most of the people I fought with,
who were from the South and Texas,
Oklahoma and so on,
had never seen a Jew in their lives.
And the idea of this Jewish kid,
Abe Goldman,
who should have been - in the view
of most of the other soldiers -
should have been in
the dry goods business,
to see him on the front line,
and he was very enthusiastic.
He knew what had happened
to the Jews.
He was probably the bravest one
in the whole platoon of 40 men.
And that's why he got himself shot.
(GUNSHOT)
And the fact that out of, say, 12 people
he was the only one that
crawled forward to risk his life,
that sort of changed...
...l'd say it changed a lot of minds.
The fight for Nothalten would take
a terrible toll on Fussell's men.
Abe Goldman survived,
but by the time the battle was over,
the company had lost four
of its six officers.
Fussell's platoon lost 13 of its 40 men.
The average life expectancy for
a junior infantry officer on the front lines
was now just 17 days.
In the end, Lieutenant Paul Fussell
would beat those odds.
But they would haunt him
for the rest of his life.
AANENSON: Well, as we pushed the
Germans back and as they retreated...
...they were able to take
all of their flak guns
and most of their artillery with them.
So, as we would fly missions
into that area -
in the Hurtgen Forest
or into the Ruhr Valley -
we were facing a larger number
of flak guns than we had before.
So it was a terribly brutal time for us.
Fighter pilot Quentin Aanenson
of Luverne, Minnesota
had been helping provide air cover
for American troops on the ground
ever since D-day.
Through all that time,
his anchor to sanity had been the belief
that Jackie Greer, the girl he'd met
while in training in Louisiana,
would marry him if he survived the war.
WOMAN: Following that war
was the best history lesson I ever had.
I got a big map, and every day I'd get...
I had my crayons out.
Every day.
Certain colours meant this group is here,
certain colours are this.
And I kept up with that war.
I learned more about Europe
than I had ever learned in school.
It was very important that I stay with it.
Aanenson and Greer exchanged letters
every two or three days,
each trying to keep the other's spirits up
till they could be together again.
Aanenson had survived
a bad fire in his plane,
was haunted by the fear
that he had once mistakenly fired
on British or American troops,
nearly died when his plane hurtled
toward its target so fast,
his instruments froze.
When he managed to pull out of his dive
at 600 miles per hour,
blood vessels in his eyes burst
and blood trickled from his ears.
Meanwhile, his friends kept dying.
AANENSON: Two of the guys
that lived in my tent were killed.
There were just four of us in there,
and two of them were killed.
I had been listed as missing in action
because I had been so badly shot up
I had to land on a temporary airfield
closer to the front lines.
Johnny Bathurst and I,
who were the survivors
in Duffy's Tavern, our tent there,
decided that we couldn't
deal with that anymore.
So we quit making friends, new friends.
On December 5, 1944,
the impact of all that Aanenson had
seen and experienced overcame him...
...and he started writing Jackie
a very different kind of letter
from the ones he had sent before.
AANENSON: "Dear Jackie,
"For the past two hours,
I've been sitting here alone in my tent
"trying to figure out just what I should do
"and what I should say in this letter
"in response to your letters
and some questions you have asked.
"I have purposely not told you much
about my world over here
"because I thought it might upset you.
"Perhaps that has been a mistake,
so let me correct that right now.
"I still doubt if you will be able
to comprehend it.
"I don't think anyone can
who has not been through it.
"I live in a world of death.
"I have watched my friends die
in a variety of violent ways.
"Sometimes it's just an engine failure
on take-off,
"resulting in a violent explosion.
"There's not enough left to bury.
"Other times it's the deadly flak
that tears into a plane.
"If the pilot is lucky, the flak kills him.
"But usually he isn't, and he
burns to death as his plane spins in.
"Fire is the worst.
"In early September, one of my good
friends crashed on the edge of our field.
"As he was pulled from the burning
plane, the skin came off his arms.
"His face was almost burned away.
"He was still conscious and trying to talk.
"You can't imagine the horror.
"So far, I have done my duty in this war.
"I have never aborted a mission
or failed to dive on a target,
"no matter how intense the flak.
"I have lived for my dreams
for the future.
"But like everything else around me,
my dreams are dying too.
"In spite of everything, I may live through
this war and return to Baton Rouge,
"but I am not the same person
you said goodbye to on May 3.
"No-one could go though this
and not change.
"We are all casualties.
"In the meantime, we just go on.
"Some way, somehow,
this will all have an ending.
"Whatever it is, I am ready for it."
When he had finished his letter,
Aanenson folded it up
and put it away in his foot locker.
Mailing it home
would only have been cruel
to the woman he loved
and hoped to marry -
if he happened to make it through
what was still to come.