(DISTANT GUNFIRE)
MAN: In the process of this battle
we took about
18 or 19 German prisoners.
A young man approximately
24 years of age turned to me,
and in a voice completely accent-free,
he said, "Where are you from?"
I said, "I'm from the United States."
"Where in the United States?"
"The north-east," I said.
"Where north-east?"
I said, "I'm from Connecticut."
"Where in Connecticut?"
He was persisting.
I said, "Yes, I'm from
Waterbury, Connecticut."
"Ah, yes," he said. "Waterbury.
"At the junction
of the Naugatuck and Mad rivers."
Now, you have to know
a bit about the area.
The Naugatuck is
a fairly substantial river,
but the Mad River is a little stream
that you can jump across
without any trouble.
Anyone who knew this, um...
I was puzzled.
I said, "How did you possibly know that?"
He said, "I was in training
for the administration."
"The administration of what?" I said.
He said, "The administration
of the territories."
My blood ran cold.
I couldn't imagine that Hitler,
in his wildest imagination,
not only had figured
he practically had Europe in his grasp,
but he also figured that
he would control America too.
NARRATOR: By December of 1944,
Americans were growing weary
of the war
their young men had been fighting
for three long years.
In Europe, it was supposed
to be over by now.
The generals who had directed
the fighting from far behind the lines
had been predicting victory for months.
It had not happened.
In the Pacific, American progress
had been slow and costly.
The enemy showed no sign of giving up.
For the people of Luverne, Minnesota
and Waterbury, Connecticut,
Sacramento, California
and Mobile, Alabama,
and every other town
struggling to absorb it all,
the stream of telegrams
and newspaper headlines
telling of new losses
seemed endless and unendurable.
For their sons overseas
it was, of course, far worse.
(EXPLOSIONS, GUNFIRE)
For them, there was no option
but to fight on and try to stay alive.
Ray Leopold,
a mortgage broker from Waterbury,
who had been trained to kill people,
would find himself
trying to save them instead.
Glenn Frazier, from Alabama,
who had been a prisoner of war
for more than two years,
would begin to lose hope
of ever seeing his home again.
And Burnett Miller, the only child
of a prosperous Sacramento family,
would be caught up in the biggest
and least expected battle
on the western front.
MAN: Basically, getting shot at
or shelled is just plain scary.
You just hope that it misses you.
When the artillery's coming in,
you think, "Oh, God.
"It's covering such an area
and I hope it doesn't hit me."
We would wish they'd
just start using rifles, you know?
Well, when you get to where
a bullet whizzes by your head...
...you know that's personal. (Laughs)
You know?
You better get out of the way.
Since the summer of 1944,
Hitler had been secretly planning
a massive counterattack,
an all-out attempt to divide
and destroy the Allied armies
before they could move further
into Germany.
His target would be the Ardennes -
rolling, forested hills
in Belgium and Luxembourg
through which German troops had
advanced toward France twice before,
in 1914 and again in 1940.
It was now thinly defended.
His armies were to break through
the unsuspecting Americans,
race for Antwerp,
cut off the British Army in the north
and drive it into the sea.
Most of Hitler's commanders
thought it madness.
They had lost nearly 4 million men
since the war began.
They had too little fuel
for a major mechanised advance.
The once mighty Luftwaffe
had largely been destroyed.
But Hitler was implacable.
"The coming battle", he said, "would
decide whether we shall live or die."
Every able-bodied German male
between the ages of 16 and 60
was made eligible for service.
25 new divisions called
the People's Infantry were formed.
250,000 fresh troops -
convicts and the infirm,
old men and young boys,
and conscripts from occupied countries
who didn't speak a word of German.
Preparations for the attack would
take time and demanded utter secrecy.
Hitler would not launch it
until he was certain
winter weather and dense fog
would keep Allied aircraft on the ground.
Meanwhile, Lieutenant Tom Galloway,
of Mobile, and his division
were among the American troops
who happened to be stationed
in the Ardennes.
GALLOWAY: We were in Luxembourg,
rebuilding after Hurtgen Forest,
because the losses were kind of heavy.
There, like, we had a front - the division
had a front of some 20 miles.
Well, because it was a quiet area
and nothing was going to happen,
I fired 25 rounds a day.
I'd go up in the morning
and fire just one at the time...
(ARTILLERY FIRES)
...just to let them know we were there.
There were only four
US infantry divisions in the Ardennes -
80,000 men stretched out along a front
that ran some 80 miles
from north to south.
Two of the divisions
had seen little combat.
The other two -
the 4th and Galloway's 28th -
had been battered by weeks of
desperate fighting in the Hurtgen Forest
and had been sent to the Ardennes
to rest.
Ray Leopold, of Waterbury,
was serving with the 28th too.
He had been trained as a sniper.
LEOPOLD: We were in a place
called Malmedy-St Vith,
at a little place called Sevenig Hill.
You could put one foot in France, one
foot in Belgium, and spit into Germany
at this particular spot.
One frosty morning,
after several hours of guard duty,
Leopold stood up to stretch.
A German sniper shot him
in the left thigh.
(GUNSHOT)
As chance would have it,
I had picked up a German medic's kit
a couple of days before,
lying in the field,
and I doctored my own wound
because our own medic had been killed.
And with the German equipment,
I probed for the bullet.
I extracted it. I cleansed the wound.
I doctored it myself.
Two days later,
when I got to battalion aid station,
the captain looked at the wound and
said, "This is wonderful. Who did it?"
I told him that I had.
He then told me, "Leopold,
I have a proposition for you.
"I'm going to make you a medic."
I, thereafter, never carried a gun.
(SOFT THUD)
Man: Strike!
(Men cheer)
('LILI MARLENE' PLAYS)
For the most part, the war seemed
a long way away from the Ardennes,
and the men took full advantage
of the facilities for rest and recreation.
Life there was so quiet, so uneventful,
that some of the men
called it the 'ghost front'.
(Marlene Dietrich sings) # Outside
the barracks, by the corner light
# I'll always stand
and wait for you at night
# We will create a world for two
# I'll wait for you the whole night through
# For you, Lili Marlene
(ACCORDION SOLO)
# It's you
# Lili Marlene. #
But just a few miles to the east,
hidden beneath the trees,
Hitler's army was making the final
preparations for its surprise attack.
There were signs that
something was going on.
Civilians slipped through the lines
to report growing numbers
of German troops.
Spotter planes noted hospital trains
and massive Tiger tanks
loaded on flatcars.
At night, Gls heard
the distant rumble of motors.
GALLOWAY: I did know that the roads
would not have snow on them
in the morning,
which meant there was traffic
on those roads at night.
Report it, but I didn't
put any significance to it.
Allied headquarters paid little attention.
General Omar Bradley
remained convinced
the German Army had been wrecked.
(EXPLOSIONS)
Then, at 5:30am on December 16,
thousands of guns opened up.
The shells fell on and around
the American positions for an hour.
A few moments later,
the enemy began to emerge
out of the dense fog
that shrouded the forest.
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
And, of course,
the Bulge broke right there.
And, as I say, when they fired
the first round, it darn near hit me.
From then on, it got worse.
But they came barrelling over there,
and just right into us.
20 German infantry divisions were
moving forward along a 50-mile front -
a quarter of a million men.
Behind them roared 600 tanks.
On the adjoining ridge,
which was only a half-mile from us,
sitting up as bold as brass,
several German tanks in line,
with the driver sitting
in his black uniform,
were coming down paths
that could not, in our opinion,
possibly have taken a tank.
Footpaths.
But there it was.
These gigantic tanks,
with their 88mm guns,
were coming down this path
in single file.
GALLOWAY: You just had waves
of Germans coming at you.
We had one machine gun
just mowing them down.
They'd keep coming right down the road,
right into that machine gun.
But there were waves of them.
The Germans kept coming
at the Americans,
pushing them back
or flowing around them.
As Hitler had hoped,
thick clouds and ground fog
kept Allied warplanes out of the sky.
Some men simply fled.
Surrounded by the enemy,
cut off from one another,
out of ammunition
and unable to fight back,
others were forced to surrender -
more than 10,000 men.
Most struggled to hold on.
Clerks and truck drivers
who had never fired a carbine
found themselves in combat.
Some officers acted like traffic cops,
trying to restore order to the chaos
on the clogged roads.
GALLOWAY: At one point, I'm there
and I'm trying to figure out tactics.
And to be perfectly honest, I figured,
as a junior officer in the artillery,
I'd be a forward observer and I didn't
have to worry about tactics too much.
As it ended up, here I am in charge,
and trying to say,
"Why did you sleep through tactics?"
And... (Chuckles)... it makes you think.
The Germans continued to advance.
On December 17,
an SS panzer unit
ambushed an American convoy
near a tiny village called Malmedy,
captured and disarmed 150 men,
and then gunned down
at least 86 of them.
They also butchered
scores of Belgian civilians.
News of the killing spread fast
among the embattled Americans.
LEOPOLD: Archie Costran was
the first sergeant of our outfit.
Came up to me within the hour
with word of what had happened
at the Malmedy massacre
only two miles away from us.
He said, "If you are captured
and identified as Jewish,
"you will not live."
He said, "Ray, why don't you
do what I'm doing?
"Take your dog tags,
with its big letter 'H' on it,
"wrap it around your hand,
put your glove back on.
"Lf, by chance, you're ever
forced to surrender," he said,
"as you raise your hand, throw the glove,
together with the dog tag,
"into the snow and step on it."
For 12 days, my hand had
the dog tag wrapped around it.
The Germans succeeded
in smashing through the centre
and spreading out to create
a 50-mile salient,
a bulge in the Allied line.
The Americans managed to keep
the breakthrough from widening
by holding on to two villages -
St Vith to the north
and Bastogne in the south.
GALLOWAY:
The unit tightened up, and we held.
Until - we had about a day, two days -
and then we had to start dropping back.
So we'd drop back and fire,
drop back and fire.
At that time I didn't know it,
but apparently we were
trying to protect Bastogne.
I had never heard of Bastogne,
I didn't know there was such a place,
but we were trying to protect Bastogne.
The little town commanded
seven all-weather roads.
Keeping the Germans
from gaining control of those roads
was now the Allies' highest priority.
I was asked to go out and ride recon,
and that was a mistake.
And I reported that
German tanks were coming.
And I could hear them speaking,
"Sprechen Sie Deutsch?"
So I had to back up.
But it was too late.
Tom Galloway and his men
were surrounded.
They hid in a house.
They brought a tank up,
shot that house up pretty bad.
Left with no other option,
Galloway surrendered.
Well, you never think
you're going to get caught.
You think,
"It's not going to happen to me."
He and some of his fellow captives
were sent deep inside Germany
to a prison camp
40 miles east of Frankfurt.
Meanwhile, the 101 st Airborne
was ordered to hold Bastogne
until other reinforcements
could reach the Ardennes.
While elements of the First Army
drove south toward the forest,
General George Patton's Third Army
began a headlong rush north
to try to relieve Bastogne
before the enemy could take it.
The Germans encircled the town
and began to shell it.
The surrounded Americans
began running out
of ammunition, food, medicine.
On December 22,
German officers under a white flag
approached the American commander
at Bastogne,
General Anthony McAuliffe
of the 101 st Airborne.
The Americans' situation was hopeless,
they said. The town was surrounded.
They demanded
the Americans surrender.
McAuliffe had
a one-word answer - "Nuts!"
The Germans had
no idea what he meant,
but they returned to their lines
and the shelling started again.
But the next morning, the skies cleared
and were quickly filled with Allied planes,
bombing and strafing German armour
and dropping supplies and ammunition
to the besieged Americans.
They were still surrounded,
still cut off from help on the ground,
but now at least they had food to eat and
ammunition with which to shoot back.
And they were fast becoming a symbol
back home of American resistance.
WOMAN: The Battle of the Bulge
was publicised.
We knew they were
holding out in Bastogne
and we were all cheering them on.
Again, we know now
how dreadful it was,
but we were very conscious
of the Battle of the Bulge,
because we felt like we had just about
completed that campaign in Europe.
And when this counterattack came,
it came as a blow to the entire nation.
('SILENT NIGHT' PLAYS)
FRANKLIN ROOSEVELT:
It is not easy to say merry Christmas
to you, my fellow Americans,
in this time of destructive war.
Nor can I say merry Christmas lightly
tonight to our armed forces
at their battle stations all over the world.
General Eisenhower,
as surprised as anyone
by the success of the German advance,
nevertheless saw the opportunity
embedded in the crisis.
The Germans were on the offensive
for the first time since Normandy,
but that meant they were exposed
and could be themselves surrounded
and cut off.
On Christmas Day,
30 miles west of Bastogne,
the Americans stopped
the German advance.
The following day, American tanks
broke through the German lines
and linked up with
the 101 st Airborne inside Bastogne.
The men there celebrated
a belated Christmas,
despite the shells and bombs
that continued to fall around them
and the fighting that lay ahead.
('O HOLY NIGHT' PLAYS)
GIRL: "I am making a few
Christmas gifts for Buddy and Doris
"and bookmarks for all my friends.
"Mother said it was best
to forget it this year,
"but we can't,
on account of the little kids.
"She told them, because of the
anti-aircraft guns in Manila,
"Uncle Sam told Santa
to keep away this year
"and leave his gifts
for the kids in San Francisco."
(EXPLOSIONS)
"When you stop and think
how hard our boys are fighting for us,
"I guess we can take it too.
"But just a little more rice
would be all I can ask for.
"We always picture Opa and Oma
on their farm in California.
"If they only knew how hungry we are,
they would be very sad.
"I guess even when we tell them,
they will never, ever believe it."
Sascha Weinzheimer.
The grandparents Sascha Weinzheimer
called Opa and Oma
lived in the Sacramento Valley.
Her grandfather blamed himself for
his family's captivity in the Philippines.
When they'd asked to go home
in the weeks before Pearl Harbor,
he'd insisted they stay where they were,
certain there would be no war.
Once he knew they
had been imprisoned,
he had tried to get messages
and Red Cross packages to them
month after month.
His health began to fail.
My dad walked me
to the main building for my siesta
'cause the camp shut down
for three hours in the heat of the day.
So he stopped at the desk,
and they said, "Oh, we have
a Red Cross telegram for you."
It was from my grandmother.
And it said my grandfather,
he had passed eight months prior,
and we were just getting it.
He stood there and cried,
and then walked me up to my room.
Everybody told us that my grandfather
literally died of a broken heart.
That evening, the family did its best
to celebrate the holiday.
They made a tree out of a palm branch
stuck in a tin can filled with dirt,
and lined up at the canteen with the
other prisoners for a special treat -
two tablespoons of jam
and one bite of chocolate.
Sascha thought it all delicious,
even though there were
tiny white worms in the chocolate.
During the night, American planes
could be heard overhead again
and scores of leaflets fluttered
out of the dark sky -
Christmas greetings from the troops
fighting their way across the Philippines
toward Manila...
...toward them.
Back in the spring of 1944,
John and Glynnie Frazier,
of Fort Deposit, Alabama,
received a telegram
from the War Department.
Their son, Glenn, had been
missing in action in the Philippines
for two agonising years,
and since nothing had been
heard from him since May of 1942,
he was now officially presumed dead.
Frazier had joined the army in 1941,
in part because he believed
that the young woman he loved
loved someone else.
He was wrong.
She had remained loyal to him
all that time.
Now, with this latest news,
she began to give up hope
of ever seeing him again.
But Glenn Frazier was still alive,
a prisoner of the Japanese.
MAN: When I'd think about home,
I would think about the things
that I missed most,
like ice-cream and potato salad
and some ambrosia that my mother
used to make for Christmas,
and so forth.
And of course it was always a thought
of if we would get back home,
but it got a time that we were so weak,
it got a time with me, I was so weak
until I couldn't even remember
whether I had sisters or brothers,
and I couldn't even remember
their names.
And it comes to a time when you think,
"Did I have a home?
Did I have a family?"
Frazier had come close to death
several times.
He had endured
the Bataán Death March
and nightmarish conditions
at Camp O'Donnell
and Bilibid Prison in the Philippines.
And he had been forced to perform
slave labour
in prison camps in Japan itself,
where he had survived
double pneumonia,
torture, a week of isolation
in a covered pit,
and beatings so frequent
they became routine.
Once, when he failed to lift his feet
high enough while marching,
a guard drove a bayonet into his knee.
FRAZIER: It started getting infected
and it finally got gangrene,
and the doctor,
our American doctor in there,
had nothing to treat me with
except iodine.
I would hold a cup to catch all the blood
and he cut it open with a pocketknife,
and it would get to the point where
he would pour pure iodine in there
to cure the gangrene.
They were thinking about
taking my leg off.
So I told the doctor, "I'd just rather die
than have my leg taken off."
So he fought it and we won.
At one point, there was only a space
in the back of my leg
about an inch and a half across
that the flesh was like normal flesh.
The rest of it was decaying.
I could open that wound up
and see my bone.
Frazier's leg eventually healed
and he went back to work
on the waterfront,
where he and his friends
did all they could
to sabotage the Japanese war effort.
They risked their lives to drill holes
in the bottoms of oil barrels,
poured sand into gas tanks,
wrecked machinery,
destroyed a dock,
and loosened blocks
so that a submarine under repairs
slid into the bay upside down.
And through it all,
Frazier thought of home
and of the girl he still hoped, somehow,
to see again.
But the thing that really kept me going
is seeing if that girl was still there
and see if, you know, I still
in my heart was crazy about her,
and the fact that I wanted to live.
I did not want my body
pushing up Japanese daisies.
And I just felt that way,
and I thought, "They're going to have
a heck of a time getting me in a casket."
MAN: I became a 'Sacramento Bee'
news carrier at the age of 10,
and for me, the war was that
little square map on the front page
where it showed wavy lines
moving in some direction,
and then the next day you'd see them
move a little more,
and arrows pointed here and there
where different armies were going.
And then, all of a sudden,
there was this bulge in the map
that was going back the other way.
That was the Battle of the Bulge.
And, "My God, what's happening here?
"Are we losing
now that we're this close?"
We all took it seriously, because
the lines had moved the other way.
(DISTANT SHOUTING, EXPLOSIONS)
MAN: "This is being written
on the verge of the new year,
"when all along the western front
the outcome still remains in doubt.
"When German parachutists
were known
"to have been dropped behind
American lines
"dressed in American uniforms,
"it became necessary to demand
identification papers from everybody.
"But with coloured troops,
it was only a matter of form,
"since the Germans have
no known coloured soldiers.
"I was halted many times,
"but my face was my best identification."
Ollie Stewart,
the 'Baltimore Afro-American'.
MAN: I think that we went
to have a great experience.
And all of a sudden we were having
more of a great experience
than we really had reckoned for.
We were scared to death, of course.
Burnett Miller, of Sacramento,
who had been raised a few blocks
from where Burt Wilson lived,
was a private in the
21 st Armoured Infantry Battalion,
11th Armoured Division.
He was among the thousands
of American troops
ordered into the Ardennes
to relieve Bastogne
and drive the Germans back.
It would be Miller's first real taste of war.
We crossed France,
went through parts of Belgium
and hit the Bulge in a big snowstorm.
Our vehicles became almost inoperable.
And the tanks, one after another,
were blown up
and we could see dead tankers
and wounded tankers
running for cover all over the place.
That was not a pretty sight.
We baled out of these tracks
and started running through the snow
to get some kind of coverage...
...and actually retreated
back up onto a hill,
dug in, and spent that night
in a big snowstorm.
We were wet, and I thought,
"Boy, I don't think we can make it."
And that night there were
tracer bullets all over, lots of artillery -
very, very scary.
And you'd rationalise things,
like, "Nothing worse can happen
but getting killed."
But there were things worse
than being killed.
In the Ardennes,
the fighting and the dying went on.
It was the coldest winter in memory.
Many men were without
winter boots or winter coats.
Thousands lost fingers, toes or feet
to frostbite.
MILLER: Lots of our equipment
wasn't very good.
We always had frozen feet because
our shoes were really very, very poor.
Also, you know,
we went into combat in the Bulge
in the same overcoats
we went to London in,
and they were big, bulky,
miserable things that would get wet.
And pretty soon we were looking
for German prisoners or German dead.
They had nice, white, bunny-fur jackets
that were just terrific -
not only comfortable and warm,
but were white and camouflaged.
MAN: Morale, I thought,
kept up because you were with people.
That as long as you were with other Gls
in the snow and in the misery,
if you had somebody next to you,
you figured, "Well, they can handle it,
I can handle it."
You just keep moving ahead.
In the chaotic fighting that followed,
some towns changed hands four times.
Civilians hid in cellars as their homes
were destroyed above them.
Allied troops had to recapture the ground
they had lost inch by frozen inch,
sometimes reoccupying foxholes
they'd been forced from
just a few weeks earlier.
The Americans lost an average
of 1,600 men a day.
Among the dead were
Private John Tavera, of Sacramento,
Corporal Lester Bendt, of Luverne,
Private First Class Domenic Derosimo,
of Waterbury,
and Private First Class
Jesse Leon Hattenstein, of Mobile.
Those who were killed and wounded
were replaced
by thousands of green troops,
mostly high school boys,
who had been rushed through
basic training.
Many replacements died
before officers could learn their names
and were replaced
by still more frightened newcomers.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
I had a friend who claimed
he was sent into the Battle of the Bulge
with six weeks training and a new rifle.
He said if he had not been
shooting squirrels all his life,
he would have been completely lost.
But he shot the Germans like he would
squirrels, and that was it. (Chuckles)
Some officers ordered their men
to take no German prisoners.
The memory of the massacre
of American troops at Malmedy
remained fresh.
MILLER: We had been held up
at a little town.
We were supposed
to just walk through it,
and the Germans stopped us dead.
We just couldn't crack it.
Eventually, artillery came in.
Sort of levelled the houses.
They finally surrendered,
and they came out and sort of lined up,
and per usual,
no-one knew what was going on.
We had a new battalion commander,
just graduated from West Point,
and he lined them up and said,
"I want you to shoot 'em."
And I was horrified.
Quite a few of us were horrified.
And I went to him and told him,
you know,
that this was against
all international law and humanity.
My good buddy,
who I'd spent so much time with,
grabbed me and said,
"This nut will shoot you.
"You'd better quit. Knock this off."
And he got enough guys and they
shot these... about 25 prisoners.
It was a terrible thing to see,
and I talked to a lot of my buddies
who had shot these guys
and they were horrified too.
By January 30, 1945,
six weeks after the German offensive
in the Ardennes began,
six weeks after the start
of the Battle of the Bulge,
the Allies had finally managed to regain
all the ground they'd lost.
It had been the biggest battle of the war
on the western front.
More than a million men took part.
19,000 Americans died.
60,000 more had been wounded
or captured or listed as missing.
Hitler's enormous gamble
had ended in disaster.
He had lost some 100,000 men
and virtually all his tanks and aircraft,
and now had no way of replacing them.
And in the east,
the Russian army was blasting its way
closer to Berlin every day.
LEOPOLD: They had blown up
our chow truck.
So these big aluminum cans that
contained the variety of food they had
were spaced about 40, 50 feet apart.
If a shell came in,
it would only kill one or two men
instead of groups of us
if we were all blocked together.
We walked down the line slowly
and opened up our mess kits.
And in the big pan of your mess kit,
the first man placed two pieces of toast.
The second man put a nice
half-inch-thick piece
of magnificent roast beef,
covering most of the toast.
The third man, a ladle of gravy
over all of it. Everything was fine.
The next man gave us a scoopful
of reconstituted dried peas and carrots.
It was proper. It was good.
It was on one side.
And finally we came
to the end of the line.
And the end of the line,
the man reached in
and took a great big scoop
of chocolate pudding
and covered this magnificent roast beef
from one side to the other
with chocolate pudding.
I don't know how many of you have
ever had chocolate pudding roast beef,
but I can tell you, despite this fact -
despite the insult that must have come
to this beautiful piece of meat -
we loved every single bite.
I still remember
chocolate-flavoured roast beef.