NARRATOR: When the people
of Luverne, Minnesota
and Sacramento, California,
Waterbury, Connecticut
and Mobile, Alabama
went to the movies in March of 1945,
they saw and heard a sick and weary
President Franklin Roosevelt -
so sick and so weary
that, for the first time in his career,
he referred directly to the paralysis that
kept him from standing without braces.
ROOSEVELT: I hope
that you will pardon me
for an unusual posture of sitting down
during the presentation
of what I want to say,
but I know that you will realise
that it makes it a lot easier for me
in not having to carry about
10 pounds of steel
around on the bottom of my legs,
and also because of the fact that I have
just completed a 14,000-mile trip.
(People applaud)
Roosevelt's strength was waning,
but his message was undimmed.
The war was still to be won.
It's a long, tough road to Tokyo.
It is longer to go to Tokyo
than it is to Berlin,
in every sense of the word.
The defeat of Germany will not mean
the end of the war against Japan.
On the contrary, we must be prepared
for a long and costly struggle
in the Pacific.
Americans had been fighting
for more than three years now,
and the number of dead
and wounded and missing
had more than doubled just since D-day.
The Nazis seemed at last
to be on the verge of collapse,
but American men were still dying
in the struggle to eradicate them,
and Allied planners feared the final battle
with Japan would stretch on for years.
WOMAN: I remember
going to New York on the train.
In the station at St Louis, Missouri,
the platform was lined with caskets
with American flags.
I could cry now.
It was just as far as you could see them
on the platform at the train station.
And I went down reading the name
in brass plaque, all the names.
And I cried and cried.
How could you not cry?
MAN: The Pacific, as one
experienced it, began at San Diego.
And you got a sense of what
a huge space you were going into.
That this was not going to be
like Europe,
where there was land all around
and it had names.
This was going to be nameless,
empty space, almost all of it,
with little dots of land in between.
In March of 1945, marine pilot
Sam Hynes was 20 years old,
a former University of Minnesota student
who, like thousands of other young men,
had been made to grow up fast
during the war,
passing test after test
on the way to manhood.
He had learned to live on his own,
had married,
mastered the dangerous art
of flying torpedo bombers
and had now received his orders to
proceed 6,000 miles across the Pacific
to face his final trial - combat.
Hynes landed at Ulithi,
the sprawling coral atoll
the US Navy had turned into
the advanced staging area
for the assault that was about to begin
on the Japanese island of Okinawa.
HYNES: It was awesome. It was huge.
The anchorage was miles across,
and it was covered
with ships of all sizes -
carriers, battleships,
destroyers, cruisers.
I'd never seen so many ships.
It was like seeing
all the power in your corner.
And there wasn't any power
in the other corner.
Okinawa, 60 miles long and home
to almost half a million civilians,
was the gateway to Japan.
The Allies knew they had to take it
before they could move on
to the home islands,
and were gathering
the largest invasion force since D-day -
almost 1,500 ships
and more than half a million men.
(EXPLOSIONS)
Day after day in March of 1945,
American and British warships
fired shells and rockets at Okinawa.
There was little evidence
of the island's defenders.
Allied planners were not sure
just where they were dug in.
But they knew they were
somewhere on the island -
more than 100,000 of them,
well entrenched
and prepared to die for their emperor.
The Japanese Kamikaze pilots overhead
were willing to die for him too.
There were nearly
100 Japanese airfields
within flying distance of Okinawa,
and the pilots of some 5,000 warplanes
were preparing to sacrifice
their own lives
in order to take those of as many
American sailors as possible.
MAN: They was trained to fly
their planes one way and no return.
And when they went out
after a ship or something,
they had their funeral
before they actually left.
And they knew they was
never coming back.
They was under the impression
that if they gave their life that way
for their country,
they had a special place in heaven
for them, automatically.
Which wasn't true.
Seaman First Class Maurice Bell,
of Mobile, Alabama,
was serving as a gunner
aboard the heavy cruiser
USS 'lndianapolis' off Okinawa.
On March 31, Kamikazes targeted her
for destruction.
BELL: I looked up to my right
and there was one small cloud up there,
and just as I looked up,
I saw a plane come out of this cloud,
and it was a Japanese Kamikaze plane.
The very instant I saw him up there,
he must have spotted our ship,
because he turned into a dive, instantly,
and was coming straight down.
It looked like he was coming just straight
to the very spot where I was sitting.
Our men back there started firing at it
with the 20mm,
and you could see the tracers hit.
The plane actually bounced off the ship,
but the motor and the bomb
went through the deck,
went through number three mess hall,
and right down there was three or four
or five men sitting at the table eating.
It killed all of them.
The bomb went all the way
through the ship into the water
and then exploded back up through.
They said that hole all the way through
was large enough to drive
a 18-wheeler through.
9 sailors died. 29 were wounded.
The 'lndianapolis' was sent to Ulithi
to have its hull mended.
Meanwhile, the bombardment
of Okinawa continued.
The invasion began on April 1.
This was the night before
Easter Sunday, the 1 st of April.
And Tokyo Rose, who was the
spokesperson for the Japanese,
was on the radio.
WOMAN ON RADIO:
Japanese special attack planes
launched late Thursday night...
And having been through Normandy,
and they didn't know we were coming,
and here we are going into Okinawa,
and Tokyo Rose is telling us,
"OK, GI Joes, we know you're coming.
"We're going to give you
a Easter party when you land,
"and we'll be there waiting for you."
Well, that really sent shivers
up and down one's spine.
Navy Ensign Joseph Vaghi,
from Connecticut,
who had been wounded
on Omaha Beach,
was among the 60,000 soldiers
and marines
moving toward the island that morning.
He had volunteered to return to combat.
VAGHl: When we finally
began unloading, it was quiet.
As the landing crafts went in,
you just walked ashore.
Couldn't believe this.
The Japanese mostly held their fire.
Four divisions - 75,000 men -
would land that day.
The veterans couldn't believe their luck.
Marine Private Eugene Sledge,
of Mobile, and his outfit
were at the landing too,
and so relieved, they began to sing
the popular hit 'Little Brown Jug'
as they unloaded their gear
and started inland.
They had been warned
that they would be likely to lose
8 out of 10 men
before they could make it off the beach.
They lost none.
They were pleasantly surprised
by the terrain as well.
It was "Pastoral and handsomely
terraced," Sledge remembered,
"like a picture postcard
of an Oriental landscape."
MAN: "The weather was cool, and
there was the wonderful smell of pines,
"which reminded me of home.
"It was such a beautiful island.
"You really could not believe that
there was going to be a battle there."
American infantry and tanks
raced across the island, cutting it in two.
Then, as Sledge and the marines
moved north
to clear the central
and northern parts of the island,
the army turned south
toward the main Japanese defences...
...where they began to face
increasingly strong opposition.
Offshore, the navy continued
to have its hands full.
NEWSREEL: Sky full of flak
as the Japs attack warships
supporting the invasion of Okinawa.
Scenes of plunging planes,
and enemy bombs land perilously near.
A low-flying enemy speeds
toward a warship target.
Will the guns bring it down
before it gets to its mark?
(ARTILLERY FIRE)
Yes! It's hit, on fire, and crashes.
On April 6, Japan loosed a new tactic
against the Allied ships.
Not single Kamikazes now,
but flights of hundreds of them at a time,
dropping out of the sky
to attack the fleet.
The Japanese called these deadly flights
'floating chrysanthemums'.
(ALARM BLARES)
By the end of the day, they had
seriously damaged 17 American vessels
and killed 367 sailors.
We lost more ships, we lost
more sailors, we lost more men,
and it was a horror.
It was one of the worst battles
of the Pacific, really.
As the land battle for Okinawa
intensified,
the floating chrysanthemums
would return again and again,
taking a terrible toll
on the men and ships.
MAN: If we had an invasion of Japan,
we knew we were dead.
They issued orders later
that the minute American or
Allied forces landed on their homeland,
to shoot all prisoners of war.
So we had basically accepted our fate.
Glenn Frazier was one
of 168,000 Allied prisoners of war
still in Japanese hands.
He had been a captive
since the surrender on Bataán
in the spring of 1942.
He was now in his fourth
POW camp in Japan,
at Suruga, south-west of Tokyo,
on the Sea of Japan.
One day, their captors
permitted 50 prisoners
to wash their own filthy clothes
in the ocean.
They were sitting around
waiting for their clothes to dry
when carrier-based American bombers
roared in to attack the port.
FRAZIER: We run out of the warehouse
at the end of the dock,
and across the railroad tracks,
and was waving.
And we knew then that
the aircraft carrier planes were close.
And we knew that
the end was coming close.
But that did not help our feelings
as to what was about to happen.
Our lives were going to be sacrificed.
MAN ON RADIO:
We interrupt this program
to bring you a special news bulletin
from CBS World News.
A press association has just announced
that President Roosevelt is dead.
The President died
of a cerebral haemorrhage.
All we know so far is that the President
died at Warm Springs, in Georgia.
WOMAN: We can all tell you
where we were
when we heard that Roosevelt had died.
President Roosevelt was really
the binding force for the United States.
When he would come on
and give his fireside chats,
we all gathered around the radio
and everyone looked to him
for leadership.
He had led us out of the Depression,
so we felt that certainly
he could lead us through a war.
And when the news came in April
that he had died,
it was a terrible blow
to the entire country.
MAN: It was catastrophic, because
he was the only president we knew
for the first 12, 13 years of our life.
Now, the thing was, my parents were
Republicans and hated Roosevelt,
but I loved him
and most of us kids loved him too.
Because he was the face of America
that was saying,
"Hey, things are going to be OK."
HYNES: I was standing
outside a quonset hut
looking across the little strait between
Saipan and Tinian, the next island,
and I felt a great sense of loss.
More than that, I think -
"How will we go on fighting the war
when our commander-in-chief is dead?"
MAN: We were all very sad about it.
Less about his leaving
than about the irony of it.
If he'd died a few months later,
he could have seen the success
of what he had done.
The men of the
100th/442nd Combat Team,
the Japanese-American unit
that had already distinguished itself
in the fighting for Italy and France,
were back in the mountains
of northern Italy
when they got word
of Roosevelt's death.
He had signed the order
that sent to internment camps
the families from which
many of them had come,
but he had also provided them
with the opportunity
to prove their loyalty on the battlefield.
It was that FDR
they chose to remember.
MAN: I remember that day,
because when we got the word,
suddenly men in my platoon
took out their bayonets and put it on.
And I said, "What's happening here?"
He says, "Well, I think we've
got to do this one for the old man."
They just stood up and started attacking.
Radio calls coming in
from the company commander,
"What in the hell are you doing?"
You know.
"You're not supposed to be attacking."
I says, "Captain, you can't stop them."
And so they're all moving forward for
the old man, a man they had never met.
(LAST POST PLAYS)
Many Americans,
overseas as well as at home,
couldn't even remember
the name of the man
who was now
their commander-in-chief...
...Harry Truman.
MAN: All aboard!
SONG: # I guess I had
a million dolls or more
# I guess I've played the doll game
o'er and o'er... #
MAN: I had great difficulty adjusting
to the fact that I was going home.
# That's why I'm blue... #
Landed at Washington, DC,
was processed through
some paperwork there,
caught a train at Union Station
taking me down to Louisiana,
where Jackie was.
# To love a doll that's not your own
# I'm through with all of them
# I'll never fall again
# Say, boy
# Whatcha gonna do? #
Fighter pilot Quentin Aanenson,
of Luverne, Minnesota,
was home on leave that April.
He had been in more or less continuous
combat in Europe since D-day -
10 ghastly months, during which
he'd killed men and seen friends killed
and come very close
to collapsing from despair.
He expected soon to be ordered
into action again, in the Pacific this time,
and he desperately wanted
to see Jackie Greer,
the Louisiana girl with whom
he'd fallen in love before going overseas.
Her letters had been
Aanenson's anchor to sanity.
WOMAN: I prayed for him to come back,
and I just felt like my prayers
would be answered.
I was walking down the street
and I saw the wedding dress
in a window.
So I went right in and I bought that dress
and shipped it to my mother
and I said, "Have this ready for me.
I'm going to need it."
Now the two were to meet again.
AANENSON: And I had to adjust
to being away from the war.
The silence was difficult to get used to.
But it was such an exciting
and unbelievable moment.
I was alive, and this was Jackie.
GREER: The first night,
we were in the living room
and he formally proposed to me.
And for some reason I got shy
and I couldn't quite make myself
say yes.
I don't know why, because I'd been
saying yes for 11 months, you know.
And when I hesitated
and couldn't quite say yes,
he said, "Well, now,
just make up your mind."
The funny part was,
the door right near my chair was closed,
and on the other side of that door
was my bed
with that gorgeous wedding dress
spread out all over it.
AANENSON: I was going to be
going back to the war.
I didn't want to face the idea
that she could end up
being a widow in a couple of months.
But the more we talked about it,
the more we decided,
"Let's get married now."
So we got married on April 17,
two and a half weeks after I got home,
in the First Methodist Church
in Baton Rouge.
As I saw her coming down that aisle,
it was just a thrill beyond belief.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
NEWSREEL:
In their stupendous advances,
the Russian armies
feature massed artillery.
The kind of warfare the Russians wage
on the road to Berlin.
By the middle of April 1945,
Soviet troops were just
30 miles from Berlin
and bent on revenge
for the horrors the Nazis had inflicted
on their homeland.
General Dwight Eisenhower decreed
that the armies under his command
would not drive directly
toward the German capital.
The deadly task of capturing the city
would go to the Red Army.
Hitler called upon his people
to resist to the end.
"Every village and every town
will be defended and held
"by every possible man," he said.
For the Americans in Europe,
the fighting and the killing sputtered on.
INOUYE: And that's a horrible thing,
knowing that the war is going to end
and you have to keep
urging your men to go forward.
The 100th/442nd Combat Team
was still in the mountains
of northern Italy,
hammering away
at the last German positions there.
INOUYE: We had this objective,
a high mountain.
As I was going up, I suddenly felt
someone punching me on the side.
That's what I thought it was.
I fell down and I got up
and kept on moving.
I had a bullet go right through
my abdomen.
Came out just about
a quarter inch from my spine.
Three machine-gun nests
were firing down at Inouye
as he continued
to lead his men up the slope.
He hurled a grenade
to knock out the first one,
then killed its crew with his Tommy gun.
He silenced the next gun
with two more grenades.
As he pulled the pin on yet another
and got ready to throw it
into the third machine-gun nest,
German shrapnel nearly severed
Inouye's right arm.
Somehow, with his left hand,
he pried his dead fingers
from the live grenade and threw it,
then started up the hill again.
INOUYE: According to the men and
according to my company commander,
he says, "For a moment,
you went berserk.
"You picked up your gun."
I had a Thompson submachine gun,
and with my left hand,
started approaching
the last machine-gun nest,
just firing it,
with the blood splattering out.
It was a horrible sight, I think.
Finally, I got hit again on my leg,
and I kept rolling down the hill
and that was the end.
German prisoners of war
were pressed into service
to carry Inouye back down the hill.
He was given morphine
at the aid station -
so much morphine
that when surgeons at the field hospital
began to amputate his shattered arm,
he had to endure it without anaesthetic.
"The pain was so intense,"
he remembered,
"that dying didn't seem like
such an awful idea."
I ended up receiving
17 whole blood transfusions.
Before they gave you the blood,
they showed you the bottle,
and on that bottle was a label
that had the name, rank,
serial number and the unit.
And so here is someone with some
fancy name, Thomas Jefferson Lee,
serial number, 92nd Division.
Now, 92nd Division was a unit that
we were attached to in the last battle,
and they're all made up
of African Americans.
And all of the bottles I saw
were from the 92nd Division.
So I must have had 17 bottles
of good African American blood.
And so here I am.
For his heroism under fire,
Daniel Inouye would receive
the Medal of Honor.
It was granted to him 55 years later,
during his sixth term as
a United States senator from Hawaii.
Meanwhile, events in Europe
were moving so fast
it was hard for the people back home
to keep track.
NEWSREEL: On the final lap
of their drive on Berlin,
Russian troops
send the Germans reeling.
On April 25, American and Soviet forces
linked up at Torgau on the Elbe river.
Germany had been cut in half.
The next day, Soviet troops
began assaulting Berlin itself.
On the morning of April 30,
Russian troops fought their way
into the Reichstag,
the symbol of German power.
Less than half a mile away,
beneath the rubble,
Adolf Hitler and his closest aides
huddled in their bunker.
That afternoon, Hitler named
Admiral Karl Dönitz to succeed him,
then shot himself in the mouth.
Only his most fanatical followers
now continued to fight on.
FUSSELL: Eisenhower,
on D-day morning,
distributed to the troops a general order,
which is like a handbill,
and everybody read it
and he said, "We are about to
embark upon the great crusade,
"which we've been preparing for
for many months, etc."
Now, at first, none of us could believe
it was anything like a crusade
because we were playing dice and
we were thinking about girls all the time
and getting as drunk as possible
and so forth.
It wasn't like a crusade. There was
no religious dimension to it whatever.
When they finally got across
France and into Germany
and saw the German death camps...
...they realised... that they had...
...been engaged
in something like a crusade,
although none of them called it that.
And it all began to make
a kind of sense to us.
I'm not sure that made it any better -
it may have made it worse -
to see that it was actually conducted
in defence of some noble idea.
As the Red Army had moved through
eastern Europe the previous summer,
it had uncovered, at Majdanek in Poland,
the first evidence
of the Nazis' industrialised barbarism.
The ashes of thousands of human
beings were found in a crematorium.
The American and British press
played it down,
assuming the Soviets
were exaggerating.
Not even the Nazis
could be so murderous.
By the end of April 1945,
more than 100 camps and subcamps
would be liberated.
Auschwitz, Treblinka, Ravensbrück,
Ohrdruf, Buchenwald,
Bergen-Belsen, Nordhausen, Dachau.
On May 5, advance patrols
of the American 11th Armoured Division
came upon Mauthausen, in Austria.
There they found
more than 110,000 desperate
so-called "enemies of the Reich" -
men, women and children
confined behind barbed wire.
Many were too weak to stand.
Private Burnett Miller, of Sacramento,
was there and saw it all.
And they had put some signs out -
"Welcome, Americans.
You've saved us," and things like this.
And we surrounded the camp
and then there was a surge of people
who were in fairly good condition
begging for food.
And we were giving them
what food we had, concentrated food,
and in some cases it overwhelmed
their systems and actually killed them.
I'm sure we were responsible
for the deaths of several hundred people
just by feeding them concentrated food.
We went down in the basement
and there were these big furnaces,
and it looked like cordwood piled around,
and they were bodies in rigor mortis
that they had been preparing to burn
in these big furnaces.
And the fellows that went
into the other barracks
came away just shocked,
some of them very, very sick.
The hospital there, people dying,
just thick,
and people couldn't get
out of their bunks
and people in terrible condition.
And then later there was a big trench,
and it was filled with bodies.
Some were dying,
some were trying to steal food.
And the guards were dispersed all over,
and we actually saw a guard move
into a house, and we chased him in,
and he was an officer.
And the prisoners who were there
tore him apart,
just killed him right there.
We lived in Mauthausen, which was
an idyllic little Austrian town on the river,
but you could smell the camp in town.
And all the villagers of course said they
didn't know anything about the camp,
and the local priest said
he didn't know anything about the camp,
and I knew that was a lie
because you could smell the camp.
You could just smell death.
So it was a horrible, horrible experience.
And then we came...
at least I came to think,
"Well, you know,
this effort has been worthwhile.
"There was a real reason to do this.
"These were inhuman things
that were being done to people."
Other Americans were witnessing
similar horrors at other camps.
Ray Leopold, a medic from Waterbury,
and a Jew,
was with the 28th Infantry Division.
We were...
...near the Hadamar...
...concentration camp.
At the same time, we noticed that
up on the hill there was a building
that the burgomaster described
as an insane asylum.
We went up there and found that, true,
they did have an insane asylum there,
at least initially,
but it was a place where there was
medical experimentation going
on humans.
I really can't tell you what I saw there.
It affected me profoundly,
and I think all the men
who were with me at that time
were equally affected.
I, um... I felt that it was too bad
that I was forbidden
by the Geneva Convention to kill.
I... I felt that this was
the most horrible human experience
that had ever been visited
on the face of the earth.
I saw one of those terrible places
where they were...
...where they had the people
that were dying and dead
and bodies stacked like cordwood.
That was the little town of Ludwigslust.
And we made the German people
in that community go get those bodies,
and had a burial in the park
in front of the castle
so that they would never forget it again.
And we gave them a Christian
and Jewish burial.
But the people did it.
We made the German people do it.
These people in this country
who say it didn't happen - it happened.
I saw it. I know.
It happened.
In 1933, there were 9 million Jews
in Europe.
By 1945, two out of three of them
were dead.
Thousands of Jewish communities
were wiped from the face of the earth.
Hitler's regime also slaughtered
nearly 2 million non-Jewish Poles.
They murdered more than 4 million
Soviet prisoners of war,
as well as hundreds of thousands
of handicapped people
and political opponents,
homosexuals and Gypsies
and Jehovah's Witnesses
and slave labourers
from all the countries they'd conquered.
LEOPOLD: How bad it was,
how wide it was,
we never really knew how fully extensive
this horror that Hitler had visited
on Europe,
and in particular on the Jews,
how it was.
But here we began to see.
We had no idea
that there was going to be
6 million dead Jews as a result.
I think the horror is still with me.
I think there's no apology
that can ever atone for what I saw.
On May 8, three days after Burnett
Miller's unit reached Mauthausen,
Germany finally surrendered.
The war in Europe had come to an end.
The Reich that Hitler had promised
would endure for a thousand years
had lasted less than a dozen.
HARRY TRUMAN:
General Eisenhower informs me
that the flags of freedom
fly all over Europe.
This is a solemn but glorious hour.
I wish that Franklin D. Roosevelt
had lived to see this day.
MAN: Al Mclntosh,
'Rock County Star-Herald'.
"Unlike New Yorkers,
who whooped, hollered,
"and tore up tons of paper
to throw in the streets,
"the news here was greeted
with quiet dignity and reverent restraint.
"One by one, the flags blossomed
out on Main Street,
"and store by store
the employees quietly filed out
"and the business places
were locked up for the day.
"But there was no shouting,
no hilarious display of any kind.
"Most everybody went home.
"There was quiet exultation over the fact
that a great victory had been achieved,
"but that rejoicing was tempered
by the sobering knowledge
"that there was another great war
yet to be won."