NEWSREEL: An army of 150,000 men,
women and children
invaded an American city -
whites, Negroes, Indians,
Creoles, Cajuns.
They came from
every corner of the land.
Their roots
in every curve of the globe -
Moscow, Indiana,
Warsaw, North Dakota,
Hamburg, California,
Milan, Missouri,
Baghdad, Kentucky.
Some came out of patriotism,
some out of grim necessity,
some for a richer life.
All came to do a war job.
These are the people - a few of them.
Thousands more
storm through these gates
on the graveyard shift
and the swing shift.
These are the jobs they came to fill.
Just a few of them.
40,000 workers
in two great shipyards,
repairing and refitting the torpedoed
vessels of the Allied nations
in giant dry vessels for
the Battle of the Atlantic.
The shipyards are the main war job.
But while these men and women
weld and rivet and file and plate,
tens of thousands more
are working round the clock
in the steel mills, the paper mills,
the gypsum plant,
the aluminum plant,
the Army Air Corps repair field,
and countless machine shops,
foundries, lumber and textile mills.
This could be any one of
a hundred great American war centres.
It happens to be Mobile, Alabama.
But the story is the same
in every war town in America.
150,000 people,
10 full military divisions,
the civilian equivalent of
Rommel's entire African army,
bivouacked without warning
in the narrow confines
of one peaceful southern city.
Less than three years ago,
you might have walked blocks in
Mobile without encountering a person.
Today, you stop to scratch your head
and a line forms behind you.
No wonder there's such a chaos
and congestion of traffic.
And one has to butt one's way
into buses at the plants
and elbow through thick crowds again
in town.
Crowds everywhere.
Crowds at the pay windows.
Block-long lines of white-collar
workers outside restaurants.
Thirsty shipyard workers on payday
waiting their turn outside
the state-controlled liquor stores.
Overcrowded schools
staffed with weary teachers
working in double shifts.
And still 3,000 in-migrant workers'
children
had to stay at home this year
until accommodations to care for them
are rushed to completion.
Dingy cafes crowded to the doors.
And makeshift tent dance halls
in crammed amusement parks.
Old Mobile - sedate, grand old lady
in crinoline and iron lace -
thrust aside 240 years of history
and tradition,
rolled up her leg-of-mutton sleeves
and pitched in
to solve the complex problems
created by 150,000 strangers
dropped without warning,
and for the duration,
into the lap of a little city
of only 78,000.
Every available room
was canvassed, utilised.
Many an old magnolia-shaded mansion
is now the roost of
an orchestra leader-turned-expediter,
a bond salesman-turned-leaderman.
Old warehouses were reopened
and peopled with shipyard workers
and airplane mechanics.
This was
an upholstering establishment
converted into a dormitory
for women war workers.
This was a neighbourhood
grocery store.
These girls - welders, checkers
and machinists.
This was a garage, now a barracks -
emergency housing for war workers.
This man is one - a pipe fitter
just checking in from San Francisco.
Here, there, everywhere -
on vacant lots and fields
and creek banks,
trailer camps, tent colonies
and shantytowns -
all facilities were overloaded.
In outlying sections of the city,
housewives, to make sure
of water for their daily needs,
set their alarms
for two in the morning
to fill buckets and pans
for tomorrow's drinking
and washing and cooking.
Mobile's understaffed
Health Department
worked day and night
on what was really a national
rather than a local civic problem
to provide basic sanitation,
water supply and waste disposal.
But still they poured into Mobile
from every corner of the nation -
farmers, clerks
and little businessmen,
Indians, Okies, cowboys
and cotton pickers,
hillbillies, Tennessee horse traders
and South American gypsies -
answering the government's call
for more and more war workers.
Many of them accustomed to
better things.
Others just in from the brush
where they use possums for yard dogs.
In Mobile, as in
every other war town,
the same acute problem arose -
homes for workers,
housing for the in-migrant armies
of industry.
Mobile, as every American city
of any size,
had its slums before the war,
but when a nation is at war,
it becomes clear that
the health and welfare of each
affects the health and welfare
of all.
Lack of comfort, lack of rest,
illness breeding
in conditions like these
mean time lost from production.
Each citizen living poorly
weakens the fabric of the society
in which all of us live.
These people
and these conditions too
suddenly become a problem to be faced
in solving the health and housing
complexities of a congested war town.
The government stepped in.
Vast housing projects were initiated
and opened at low rentals
to war workers
certified by the personnel
and housing officers
operated by the plants
in which they worked.
By January 1 of this year,
Congress had appropriated
over $2 billion for emergency housing
in America's war boom towns.
Here's how some of it was spent
in Mobile.
These are the slums we have seen.
Slum clearance projects had been
the local private enterprise
of a few high-minded,
far-sighted individuals.
But in Mobile, such projects as these
have become one of the obligations of
good government.
They're being written off
as part of the cost of building
ships and planes and tanks and guns.
They are rented only to
certified coloured war workers,
and are equipped with auditoriums,
playgrounds and day nurseries
to take care of the children
while their parents
are working in the war plants.
Dormitory units for men and women,
accommodating from 400 to 1,200
single workers.
Equipped with recreational
facilities, barber shops, gymnasiums,
hospitals, community centres
and low-cost cafeterias -
whole towns in themselves.
Government-owned trailers
moved in to meet the emergency
for rent as low as $15 a month
per family.
1,700 units to accommodate
7,000 war workers and their families.
Modern, sanitary and scientific -
built by the Maritime Commission
and adjoining the shipyards in which
their occupants are employed.
These 2- and 4-family dwellings
are typical of many of
the smaller projects
that are being rushed to completion
on the outskirts of Mobile.
Day nurseries to care for
the children of women war workers
are another problem the government
is undertaking to solve.
Five small nurseries
to 150,000 people is inadequate.
But more are planned to counteract
an important contributing cause
of absenteeism and loss of
valuable production time.
For those that can afford them,
there are modern, permanent homes
like these,
built with the help of FHA loans
and put on the market
at rentals compatible with
government ceilings.
Decent housing, medical care,
adequate transportation -
as each of these problems is met,
the ratio of production increases.
In the shipyards alone,
this is already evident.
At the beginning, one ship
was launched every six weeks.
Today, cargo and combat vessels
slide down the ways one every week.
And the story of Mobile is the story
of every American war town.