Let's reminisce the
special times he had.
[Kim Hyun-joong's Story]
Kim Hyun-joong debuted in 2005
as the leader of SS501.
He shined on stage with his
good looks as a flower boy...
And became the center of
many of his fans' attention.
This flower boy rose to sudden prominence in
the gayo world, but he has an unusual past.
I never received allowances.
I worked for money ever
since I was young.
I delivered newspapers, pizza, and chicken,
and worked as a waiter. I worked hard.
- I didn't go to school.
- Since when?
I started chicken delivery
when I was in the 8th grade.
I got a raise around $2.50
because I did well.
- How much did you start at?
- I started at around $1.70.
- How much did you make?
- I made close to $100,000.
- By working part-time?
- I didn't go to school.
It was like a full-time job, but
how did you make $100,000?
- I didn't spend money...
- You didn't spend money?
I saved it up for a
couple of years...
I heard you made money
by starting a business.
There are those I worked with since
elementary, and we're still friends.
We said if any one of us becomes successful,
that person will start a chicken restaurant.
So I started one. It's doing
well and I made some cash.
- You own a chicken restaurant?
- You still manage it?
We never knew.
- I just found out today.
- Me too. What a surprise.
My friend recently wrote an
ad copy. He's an eccentric guy.
I asked what he was doing and he wrote
something strange on the flyer.
"If it doesn't taste good
then I'm your kid."
That's incredible!
So you...
Usually it would say "give a refund."
First time hearing something provocative.
We said if any one of us succeeds,
and I was the one to keep that promise.
We would think he grew without hardships,
but there's more to his sad past.
I ran away from home.
How old were you?
It's when I just
entered high school.
It's when Seo Taiji released
a song titled "Ultramania."
It drew out my defiance.
- Ultramania?
- I became one.
I ran away saying that
I'm sticking to music.
"School or music?" "Music. I'll make
money on my own and live well off."
But I was cold and hungry.
I almost died 3 times.
[Almost died 3 times?]
I ran away and ran out of money.
I thought I would die of starvation.
My friend told me to stay at his place,
but he was living with his father.
His father told me to get out saying that
he can't accept someone who ran away.
My friend allowed me to sleep in the
boiler room which was a storehouse.
I was hungry and was searching the
ground for food if there was any.
I went down, but the roads were twisted
and I couldn't find my way back.
I discovered a snack shop at 4 AM.
My first thought was
to eat and survive.
I ordered a lot of tteokbokki, odeng,
sundae, and twigim, and ate it all.
You ate first?
I felt the Heavens were on my side.
That shop doesn't do deliveries
but got a call for a delivery.
- At that moment?
- Yes.
The person who called always
ordered from that shop.
She said, "I'll make the delivery."
I thought, "I should run for it."
- I intentionally made another order.
- So she can go on the delivery?
She needs time to cook the ramen.
I ate a little and ran away at the same time
she left while grabbing some twigim.
[Better safe than sorry!]
- You grabbed some on the way?
- He needs something for tomorrow.
I ran about a mile through the alley and
entered a boiler room in a building.
But it was a boiler room of
a big Korean dry sauna.
- It must have been hot.
- It was really hot.
There's a ladder there. I climbed up
and opened the lid to the sauna.
I already ate the food.
I opened the lid of that underground
bunker and there were people walking.
- You found a passage.
- I thought I should stay here.
First, I took a hot shower, and used
someone else's disposable shaver.
Look at the things this
flower boy did.
I was caught the next morning and
was kicked out. So I almost died.
You almost died because you
were beaten to death?
- No, I almost starved to death.
- Nothing to eat after being kicked out.
Another time, I was almost
beaten to death.
My friend pitied me and bought me a bowl
of pork bone stew. I ate and left, but...
That alley was full of tattooed men.
Two drunk men picked a fight with us,
"Why are you young'uns here?"
They started beating my friend.
- For no particular reason?
- Because they were drunk.
I had no strength, but I ran head on
because I had to save my friend.
I held on saying, "Let him go!"
But there was an accident.
It was snowing. When I did that,
he slipped and hit his head.
I did that to a gangster.
- You made him slip?
- I made him pass out.
- I was afraid.
- There's one more.
My friend held on to the other guy
because we had to make it out alive.
That's when the boss and others came.
We thought we were going to die.
But the boss started beating the guy who passed
out. "How can you get beaten by some kids?"
I said, "Please stop!
We didn't mean to do this!"
He told me to shut up and
asked who did this to him.
- Who did this?
- Thought I was a goner.
My friend who wrote the strange ad copy
just came out after using the restroom.
I was taking care of the situation,
but he completely lost it.
- "What are you doing to my friends?"
- When things were starting to get quiet?
That was before he turned the corner.
He just saw that small group.
He saw a large group when
he turned the corner.
He always acted cool. He took out his phone
and told all of them to come at him at once.
I said, "What are you doing? Don't cause
any more trouble!" He called the police.
"Hurry and come! I'm going to die!"
We were saved because the
police came right away.
The last one is when
I really almost died.
And the one who passed out?
The police took us in their
car and we were saved.
- Did the guy wake up?
- Beats me.
I was afraid and left.
You said, "Please stop!"
He slipped and passed out.
He slipped on the snow.
Also that winter, I didn't
have a place to stay.
All the five story apartments until block 163
were being reconstructed in my neighborhood.
All the tenants were told to move out.
I thought of sleeping in those empty rooms.
I slept in block 125. I put a mattress in
the basement that someone threw away.
I was sleeping, but it was noisy. I woke up
and everything was demolished to block 124.
They were breaking it?
Yes. All the apartments were
destroyed except for block 125.
You must have fainted.
I went back home and decided
to go back to high school.
Such hardships in life weren't bad
since he gained a lot of things.
Winter break is the season when
you run away from home.
Winter break is the season
to run away from home?
Don't go through hardships but spend
a happy new year with your family.
Your goals are not achieved by running
away. Think of what your mother said.
You'll know it when you graduate
from high school like me.
Don't regret it later.
Unpack your bags...
He's not detailed.
Just stay still at home.
If any of you have such thoughts,
take what he said to heart.
He got over such a past and
became one of the best idols.
He became a singer he dreamt of and
showed various images on stage.
From his charisma to his liveliness,
he showed many different faces.
He unleashed his potential again
in the drama, "Boys over Flowers."
He played flower boy, Ji-hoo, and was the
originator of the "flower boy" syndrome.
Kim Hyun-joong's special keyword.
[Special Keyword 1]
[Flower Boy]
[Shortened form of "Boys over Flowers" and also
means a man who is beautiful like a flower]
Maiden Jung Joo-ri!
[Burden...]
We're a handsome couple.
It's just a nice-looking man.
Yup, just a nice-looking man.
Let's look at your word.
Please reveal your word!
I starved.
Fine!
["Fine" and "I starved"]
Bachelor Hyun-joong...
- Don't laugh.
- Why's he laughing?
- An old lady!
- Don't laugh.
Bachelor Hyun-joong?
Don't laugh.
How do you feel making
eye contact with me?
- Don't laugh.
- Bear with it.
Don't laugh.
- @#&!
- "I sneer"?
"I sneer"?
Fine!
Bachelor Joo-ri?
[What?]
Maiden Joo-ri?
You were digging through
the trash earlier. Why?
I starved.
Are you going out with
me starting this moment?
- Take your punishment.
- Bear with it.
We're against it.
Fine!
She has it!
[Cell phone?]
Does she have an ulterior
motive for coming today?
- Is she here for a date?
- After the broadcast...
- Is this a dating program?
- Don't give her my number.
It's his number!
Thank you.
Do you suggest another
word? What will it be?
"I'm ugly."
What do you think
of your looks?
[She can say anything after
getting his number]
I'm ugly.
- That's incredible.
- She's humble.
Should we get married in May?
[Butchered]
The bride of May.
Fine!
Things are moving quickly.
What's with your figure?
I'm ugly.
That attack doesn't work on her.
Bachelor Hyun-joong?
Follow me!
Do you still like me?
[Looking straight in the eye...]
I don't like that.
It ends with him
not liking you.
Jung Joo-ri wins!
- Off to the wheel with you.
- Shouldn't get "shampoo hair."
Spin the wheel!
[Spins the punishment wheel!]
He got "shampoo hair."
[He won the long-awaited
"shampoo hair"]
The president of my agency told
me to never slick back my hair.
I will do it exclusively
for this program.
Who slicks back their hair
exclusively for a program?
- This is the first time ever.
- Fine. Let's do it!
What's wrong Han-young?
- Can I try once?
- No, I'm doing it.
Please!
Pour water over his head.
Is she actually...
Even Hyun-bin?
You're going to empty it?
- Don't spill it!
- He's like a eunuch.
My first time washing
a man's hair.
[Shampoo finished!]
Why are you applauding for that?
She acts differently compared
to Bachelor Shin.
- This isn't punishment.
- Is he an emperor?
- Do we have to bow?
- He will show his hair.
[Finally...]
[Every girl's dream...]
[Here is...]
It's a punishment but not for him.
He doesn't even get a humiliating shot.
Is this the might of a flower boy?
We have evidence of that power.
I can endure pinches.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Honest.
Pinch him real hard.
Doesn't it hurt?
- Really?
- Pinch me.
Boom, come here.
I was always curious...
[Even though Ho-dong strains!]
Please stand here. People will
think it's fake if the cast does it.
Anyone from the audience?
Who wants to pinch him?
- Me! I want to!
- Hurry! Run!
[This look!]
[Moved]
[Only saw him in her dreams]
[Even tears!]
She lost her mind after seeing him.
Yes, we understand that feeling.
How can she pinch in that state?
I can pinch him.
I can do it.
Wait, wait, wait!
Just stay still!
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Oppa...
We have to go on
with the show...
I'm okay. Really.
We'll do a reenactment
of what you did.
Alright. Will you do it?
Hurry! Come up here!
[It's the same]
[Am I dreaming?]
[Boom reborn as an actor]
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- You're okay?
- Yes, I am.
Calm down. Can you do it?
Even this perfect flower
boy has a complex.
- I have a complex.
- What did you say?
What's with that voice?
Since it's night...
I'm getting facial hair.
This is normal, but I
used to think it wasn't.
I'm getting facial hair because I'm
growing old, but I can't accept that.
I'm an idol! Why am I
getting facial hair?
That's understandable. It's like
when kids first get armpit hair.
Every time I see that on dramas or
music programs, I can't accept it.
I have severe dark circles
when make up is removed.
Why do I have dark circles? Then I have
to quit drinking. I can't accept that.
Since I love playing soccer,
my face became darker.
Because you play ball outside.
My face is dark, but
it's white here.
When I see myself after a shower,
I look like a burnt matchstick.
Because you're like this
only up to here?
You're just dark here like
a burnt matchstick?
I hated that. So I watch male
actors and singers closely.
"Some of them are definitely
like matchsticks."
And Cha Seung-won is one.
Only here?
Since he films outside often,
I thought, "I'm okay then."
[Even Dokko Jin's a matchstick]
Are you jealous of other celebrities?
Of course! Yes, I am.
You're good-looking but jealous?
I get jealous too. When I watched
the movie, "The Man from Nowhere"...
When I watched it at the theatre, the
women went wild when he cuts his hair.
I also think it's cool, but I tell people,
"He cuts his hair that well by himself?"
[Every Korean man thinks that way]
"A killer can cut his hair that well?"
- As if you don't understand.
- I try to find faults.
When "Jeon Woo Chi" was popular...
He's very cool and a good actor.
When women say he's cool, I agree.
But isn't his dialect strange?
[Feels the same]
- Wow! He's really honest.
- Every man thinks the same.
I acknowledge it but jealous.
It's cute that a flower boy gets jealous,
but don't let it get to your head.
Why don't we take a glimpse
into his love life as well?
- When was your first love?
- I think in the 7th grade.
- 7th grade?
- Yes.
I suddenly remember you saying that
you couldn't talk to girls at school.
- Is it coming and going?
- What's going on?
Other girls were invisible because
there was this one girl I liked...
Then you should've
said it like that!
I only hung out with guys because I
didn't get a chance to speak to her.
How and where did you meet her?
After school at a
sundaeguk restaurant.
And you were in middle school?
Old people usually go there
to settle their stomach.
A middle school student went there?
What is going on here right now?
What's your story?
I happened to eat there with a friend
and a girl came in and ordered a bowl.
- A certain girl?
- Alone?
- In the 7th grade?
- Yes.
- She was with her friends.
- So she was with a group.
They would usually go to a
bakery or fast food restaurant.
So I ate there almost every
day for 2 1/2 years.
- Did she also come every day?
- No. She came only 2 or 3 times.
You ate there for 2 1/2 years
to see her those 2-3 times?
I would rotate my friends around since
they got sick of eating the same thing.
[All to see her...]
- You went with your friends to see her...
- He changed his friends and not the menu?
You must have really liked her.
"Can I get a bowl here?
Is she coming today?"
I know.
That's how I felt. She came
in when I was eating.
- You saw her when she came in?
- After I saw her, that was it.
- Did you talk to her?
- No, I just saw her.
You should've been cool and said, "A
platter of boiled beef for her, please."
If a man does something cool like that,
she would be like, "What is this?"
"He ordered this for you."
Then she would look at you.
And you could say something cool
like, "Enjoy" before you leave.
I couldn't do that because I had to
break my piggy bank to eat sundaeguk.
I ate there until the
restaurant closed down.
- What does that mean?
- Did you work there?
The owner was an old lady and she was
sick. So I helped her move meat.
You got close with her while
waiting for the girl.
- You became fond of her.
- Yes, I did.
So it ended with a crush?
At the sundaeguk restaurant?
I had a friend who liked a girl for 3 years
and we spoke our mind at that restaurant.
On December 31st past midnight before going
to high school, we decided to speak up.
We agreed to confess and congratulate the
one who hit it off since we're friends.
My friend confessed and it didn't work out,
but fortunately, it worked out for me.
How? What happened?
- She already...
- She knew?
I tried to get close to
her friends to get to her.
I tried to get information from
her blog, find out her birthday...
How did you confess?
At that restaurant?
- No, I called her.
- By phone?
You found out her number?
What did you say?
I made a collect call.
This is where it comes
crashing down.
- Why? Why?
- Huh?
- Students don't have money.
- I didn't have money.
He broke his piggy bank
to eat sundaeguk.
I made a collect call to confess.
Since you didn't know
what she would say?
What was her response?
First, she said, "Who is this?"
Women know but pretend
they didn't know.
She already knew and asked if I would
like to go to the movies with her.
- She did it first.
- That's how you made it.
We didn't date right away.
We started to know one another...
Did you have your first kiss?
Yes.
Sundaeguk led to love. His story on
his first love was extraordinary.
But this continued with
other celebrities.
Please make eye contact
with Mr. Ahn.
An expert is looking at you.
[Gazing]
What are your thoughts?
If he has dated?
Not right now, but
he did in the past.
[Is he right?]
- Is he right?
- Yes, he is.
[Mr. Ahn the fortune-teller]
[He's more surprised]
[It was a careless remark]
He just said it and
got surprised.
I can't lie, and that's
in the past.
- But weren't you surprised?
- You could date freely?
I don't like hiding things
so I dated out in the open.
- She's also famous?
- Yes.
How come we don't know?
Why aren't there rumors?
- Did you meet only 2 times?
- She's a ghost. A ghost.
[That's why it says ghost?]
- Maybe he's dating a ghost.
- If not, there should be rumors.
I wonder why?
- How long did you date?
- It was short.
- How long?
- A week?
It's not that short.
It was about 5 months.
- 5 months? That's not short.
- So within those 5 months...
5 months, huh?
- How many times did you meet?
- Not that many times.
Where did you go?
We went to the movies. I like
fishing so we went fishing.
- You drove there?
- Yes.
Where did you go that
had a lot of people?
Garak Market.
There's a lot of people there.
- We ate sashimi.
- Sashimi?
Did Jung-min and Hyung-jun know?
- We never knew.
- We're surprised.
- Who is she?
- We were discussing.
- He's a mysterious man.
- Did you date yourself?
[Going off on a tangent]
The girl is not dating him.
She just met him and he's the
one who's taking it seriously.
Was it?
- No kidding...
- He's not back yet.
We're curious.
What did you like about her?
I thought she was a Japanese doll.
[Japanese doll?]
I almost put a coin in her back.
You know this thing inside stores?
I almost put in 30,000 yen.
- In Japan...
- It's a maneki-neko.
Please answer us. What did
you like about her?
She's easy-going and cool.
Is she currently active?
Yes, she is.
Then it's that person I saw.
[Eun-ji knows?]
Really?
Excluding Hyun-joong, why don't
the three of you explain to us?
We want to know too.
We're curious, but let's
bury the past.
I heard you like Lee Hyori?
It's Hyori.
She's charming.
I like charming girls.
Are your feelings the same?
Since I was a trainee, she was in
the same agency so she's my senior.
She has a very cool personality.
She calls me to a get-together...
She calls me to her birthday party so I
don't feel sad that we didn't hit it off.
His unrestrained and off the wall remarks
about her is also one of his charms.
[Special Keyword 2]
[Oddball]
[One of his many characteristics in
which he thinks differently from others]
We burst out laughing at it.
- What was it?
- Gray cropped pants.
You bought 30 pairs.
- I only wear one pair.
- Just one pair?
- I wear what I'm fixed on.
- Just like Andre Kim.
Yes.
I had 30 more manufactured since
it was a discontinued brand.
- Manufactured?
- I went to a workshop.
I handed it out as gifts to people that
visited me and now I only have 4 pairs left.
- We're getting curious.
- You must really like it...
I just ordered another 150 pairs.
[Shocked]
He's a style icon so it would
have a different feel.
Are you wearing them?
I wore them today and I brought a
pair to give them to you, Seung-gi.
- For me?
- Lucky.
I'm curious. Are they jeans?
Are they going to censor it?
- It's sweat pants.
- Oh, sweat pants.
[Wear comfortably at home]
Give him the gift first.
I'm grateful.
Thank you. Giving me
this special clothes.
I didn't wash it after practice
yesterday to give it to you.
[A gift that includes
his body odor!]
I have to wear it on the spot.
You have to think
of his sincerity.
- You look good.
- It's nice.
Those pants make you look
good whatever you put on.
[How do I look?]
- Do I look good?
- You look good.
It's good but you look
like a shaolin monk.
[Shaolin Seung-gi]
I think he's warm-hearted.
What are you saying
all of a sudden?
He gives clothes that he thinks is
comfortable to people as a gift.
- Since he gives gifts?
- Yes.
The conversation is unique
since they're both unique.
Isn't it expensive to
manufacture them?
It's so strange right now.
Is it cheaper to order them
in bulk of 30s and 50s?
You have to find the right factory.
You actually go there
to place the order?
But no factory receives
orders for 50s or 80s.
There's another word to describe him other
than a "flower boy" and that's "oddball."
It wasn't intentional, but let's see the many
episodes his off the wall charm created.
[Living with ghosts]
I believe there are aliens and
ghosts other than earthlings.
Alright.
The five of us started
dorming for the first time.
We go to sleep and
hear such sounds.
We thought, "What's this noise."
But we kept on hearing it.
I was surprised because the glass falls
off and breaks once every night.
- In the house?
- Yes.
We're watching TV and, I saw this with
Kyu-jong, the glass falls off and breaks.
We were surprised. I come back
after work and remove my make up.
I'm naked as I dry my hair with the
towel. It's night and really dark.
I'm drying my hair, but I saw a guy
through the towel. I was surprised.
A guy was squatting by the shoe
shelf and looking up at me.
I thought, "Who's that guy?"
Within 2 seconds, I thought maybe it's
a ghost. It's my first time seeing one.
I screamed and ran naked
into the manager's room.
The manager was surprised,
"Why did you run in here naked?"
He was sleeping and
was surprised.
He could have gotten
the wrong idea.
I told him, "Hurry, there's
a ghost by the shoe shelf!"
Kyu-jong and I share a room and
this time we saw it together.
We're sleeping and the male ghost looks at
us from here and the female ghost from there.
We were scared at first,
but now we're used to it.
- Since you see it all the time?
- Yes, we see it all the time.
They're talking with each other, and
Kyu-jong would say, "Go to sleep already!"
When I come alone, they're noisy
and knock on the dining table.
Since I'm used to it,
I shout, "Be quiet!"
- Really?
- Yes.
And then I really
don't hear them.
Since we're used to it now,
we're not afraid anymore.
The manager was tired and went to sleep
and the ghost was lying next to him.
He pushed away the face
saying, "Go to sleep."
He's used to it now. The ghost
got up and went outside.
He felt uncomfortable and bought a
tailsman but stuck it only on his room.
We went to Japan and saw it again.
The door's over there, Kyu-jong and I are
sitting here and the others are here...
[The MCs have a weak heart]
[Seung-gi's startled]
That startled me.
I went on a trip with some friends.
We had sashimi and bbq in a cabin.
We decided to find a place
where we could sing and drink.
That's when I first found out.
Seogupyo... Seogupo... Seogyupo...
Seogwipo.
Seogyu... gyu... gwipo.
It was Seogwipo...
- Where are you from?
- Jamsil in Seoul.
[He speaks Jamsil dialect]
There's no such place in Seogwipo,
but in downtown Jeju...
There's a place with a room, food and
alcohol, and you can sing and dance.
- It was a nightclub.
- Ah! A ballroom.
We went. Our gang and another
gang went there together.
We drank and had fun.
We also sang.
When I'm drunk, I fall asleep.
I left to use the restroom and came
back, but I don't remember anything.
- You were drunk?
- Yes.
I opened my eyes to check my text
and saw I had 100 missed calls.
I put my phone on the floor after
seeing it and went back to sleep.
All of a sudden, I thought,
"What is this place?"
Of course.
I couldn't see my hands.
It was pitch black.
I tried to calm myself because
I could have been kidnapped.
- You must have been afraid.
- I was scared senseless.
I imagined all sorts of things.
"What if I was sold somewhere."
I turned on my cell phone to see, but it
ran out of battery. I only saw for a second.
I groped around for my shoes and
started feeling my surroundings.
I was feeling around the room
and felt several buttons.
Where is he?
It could be a cold storage.
You shouted, but
there was no one?
I shouted, "Is anyone there?"
But there was no answer.
I pressed the button
and it felt familiar.
Ah! It's the room
from yesterday.
The buttons were from
the karaoke machine?
Yes.
Two groups came together and you
were the only one trapped there?
I searched my memory. I slept in
the right room and not the left.
But they left me and
all the workers left.
I was alone in that
dark nightclub.
Think about it, it's dark...
- It really was like night.
- It's scary to be there alone.
- It is scary.
- What did you do?
I had to get out. The only light
I saw was from the exit sign.
I went towards it and discovered
a door, but it wouldn't open.
- Since it's locked?
- Yes, it was locked.
- They don't lock it from the inside.
- It's locked from the outside.
I found a phone and dialed 119,
but it rang from another room.
[It's an extension!]
- As soon as you pressed "1"...
- It was ringing from the kitchen.
"What do I do?"
A Korean Wave star trapped in a
nightclub with his hair in a mess.
If that was filmed,
it would go viral.
I was thinking and started touching
the door. I managed to get it open.
I opened the glass door, raised
the shutter, and went outside.
It was like the raining scene in
"The Shawshank Redemption."
My hair was caked and
my face was swollen.
I got out but didn't have money.
I couldn't go back to Seogwipo.
I made a collect call to my friends, but
they didn't pick up. They were sleeping.
Downtown Jeju to Seogwipo
was around 25 mi.
I thought walking would
be overdoing it.
That's like a marathon.
I sat on the street
like a beggar.
[A waste to call a
flower boy a beggar]
- A flower beggar.
- He sure is one.
I hung around for 1 1/2 hours
and finally made it back.
I found out later on why
I was in that room.
It says "Jaejoong" in front of the room.
I thought that was the waiter's name.
But it was on every room.
- Oh, it's occupied.
- There's people inside.
It means it's occupied.
So I entered the wrong room.
[This was the true nature of that
incident! He's an oddball star!]
Why did they leave you?
They looked for me but thought
I left because I was tired.
When you go drinking next time, sleep
at home even though you're tired.
That's why I call them
over to my place now.
I would go around the country
to find famous restaurants.
- Really?
- Yes.
I went around to find tteokbokki
that pleases my palate.
I sign up at a naengmyun bulletin board
and read reviews on famous restaurants.
That's how passionate you were?
There's over 20 tteokbokki restaurants
in Sindang-dong's Tteokbokki Alley.
I went and ate at each place
over a period of 3 months.
- Really?
- Yes.
You must have had
a lot of time.
- You weren't busy at all.
- We thought you were busy.
You should have come on
this show during that time.
Why eat tteokbokki
for 3 months?
- If we only knew.
- We thought you were busy.
We were waiting for you.
I guess I'll be busy now.
- What place is good?
- Any recommendations?
The best place is where the food
is salty, spicy, and sweet.
Huh? What?
Salty, spicy, and sweet. Why?
Stimulating food is the best.
Plus a lot of MSG...
[A devotee of MSG?]
People are avoiding that and
looking for green foods.
Well... umm... I'm taking
medication anyways.
He has unique values. We can find
such charm in the things he says.
- He must've been a rascal.
- I sure was.
I skipped school and played soccer.
Your parents are called for too many
absences and you could get expelled.
I stole the roll book and dropped
it between the apartment elevator.
The space between the door?
- That space?
- Yes.
How do you recover it?
When the apartment
is reconstructed.
[They suffered from H1N1]
- You know, right?
- Of course, I do.
It says in the article, "Celebrity No. 1."
It's not like we're Robot Taekwon V.
[Not regarding sick people's feelings]
- Seung-gi, were you No. 5?
- I was around No. 10.
[Accompanied by backup dancers!]
[He's cool]
[High-class dancing]
[A beautiful finish]
I was curious about something.
What?
Why is there no mic
on the mic stand?
I thought you gave your all.
- I took it off.
- Why?
It's heavy.
[No pretense! He's honest!]
I lost weight due to that while
filming the music video.
- Because you held something heavy?
- Well, it is a lump of metal.
I wanted to be a PR Ambassador.
Huh?
- You know... promoting things.
- Like the Pyeongchang Olympics?
- Like a public service announcement?
- To enhance national prestige.
I don't know about others, but doing
that is representing South Korea.
Then look at the camera and say something
for Visit Korea Year, also in English.
A Korean Wave star can do that.
In Japanese too if you can.
Please visit Korea on
Visit Korea Year.
With confidence.
Visit Anus...
[He was nervous]
Visit Anus Year?
It's not Visit Anus Year.
That's not really...
- That's like saying get an endoscope.
- That's the surgery department.
- I'm not confident.
- It's okay.
Please visit Korea on
Visit Korea Year. Thank you.
In English.
Kim Hyun-joong's shining
stage as a solo artist.
[Kim Hyun-joong's Shining Stage]
Kim Hyun-joong announces his
first solo album in 2011.
He presents himself as more mature
as a solo artist with the song, "Please."
[A sentimental pop R&B with a beautiful piano
melody, grand orchestra, and sad lyrics]
[The performance along the
sad song stands out]
[It was changed more than 10 times for him.
It was first made public before his album]
After that was the title
track, "Break Down."
The strong performance stood out
as it showed off masculinity.
He even reached the top
with this song.
[It's a south urban dance song with powerful
electronic brass and dynamic synth sounds]
[A powerful perfomance shows a lot of
thought was placed on the choreography]
[Ken Louis, sound engineer, worked on
the mixing to produce the perfect sound]
[His matured masculinity can be felt in
the title track of his first solo album]
He transformed into a romantic guy in
"Kiss Kiss", an exciting pop dance song.
[An acoustic guitar leads in
this exciting pop dance song]
[His sweet charm stands out different
from the title track with lovely lyrics]
This is when he forms a
special relationship.
It's his agency's CEO who helped with his
solo career, Bae Yong-joon, aka Yon-sama.
Kim Hyun-joong's special people.
[Special People]
What are your thoughts on being
called "Little Bae Yong-joon"?
People think I'll feel bad for being called
Little something or the 2nd something.
If I could only be half of
what Bae Yong-joon is...
It's good to be half of
him popularity wise.
Kim Hyun-joong and Bae Yong-joon
are very close like brothers.
Bae Yong-joon gave him advice on choosing
an agency when he was worrying about it.
Several months ago, people were
calling me "The 2nd Yon-sama."
Are you two close?
Yes.
Well, he is the CEO of
Kim Hyun-joong's agency.
Where did you meet him recently?
In Busan. He was there alone.
I called him that I'll be there tomorrow.
I got on the plane and we had fun.
What was he doing there?
Solitude.
Solitude?
He was doing mind control in front
of the ocean while sipping tea.
You mean self-control?
["Mind control" is a game term]
I played too many games.
We ate and I asked if
he wanted some beer.
He said, "Sure, buy some canned beer.
Let's drink while viewing the ocean."
But the spring winds are cold. After
2 minutes, he said, "Let's go inside."
He was cold after
experiencing solitude?
He said it's hard
to endure the cold.
Yon-sama can overcome
anything except the cold.
Tell us how you stabbed
him in the back.
I sang the theme song of the
Guangzhou 2010 Asian Games.
[Singing the theme song of the Guangzhou 2010
Asian Games as one of Asia's top artists]
I was waiting at the airport, but someone
asked me in Chinese for an autograph...
Handing me a photo of Bae Yong-joon.
- A Chinese person?
- Yes.
If it was a Japanese person, although not
fluent, I could say, "I'm not Yon-sama."
But this person was speaking in
Chinese and I didn't know what to say.
I kept on saying, "No! No! No,
Bae Yong-joon. No, Bae Yong-joon."
- That person said I was lying.
- Because you're Bae Yong-joon?
This person followed me around the
duty-free shops for 30 minutes.
I told that person that I'm not
him. I'm not Bae Yong-joon.
Later that person got angry.
A star should say he can't sign
an autograph. Why is he lying.
That person was offended.
That person said bad things about
Bae Yong-joon in the end and left.
- That Bae Yong-joon is bad?
- Yes, so he lost a fan.
[He sure is an oddball]
Bae Yong-joon got a bad
name for no reason.
You could have said that you're
singer Kim Hyun-joong.
It's a difference in education.
I made him lose a fan due to
me not being educated.
That person will still think you're
him and that he's unmannered...
- Doesn't even sign autographs...
- Doesn't say that he is Bae Yong-joon.
That person might watch this show
and think he's Bae Yong-joon.
[I'm Kim Hyun-joong]
You two seem close. Did you ask
if you could call him on the show?
The writers asked me if
a call was possible.
Of course!
This was my first request. I asked
him, "I have a favor to ask of you."
"I'm going to be a guest on this show.
Is it possible for me to call you?"
He said, "Sure, since this
is your first favor."
- You know "Sebaku"?
- You mean "Sebakwi"?
It's "Sebakwi."
He was confused and said,
"I'm nervous of quizzes."
[He barely appeared on variety
shows and was nervous]
I said, "Just be yourself." He texted he's
nervous on quizzes with a crying emoticon.
[This Korean Wave star
is actually a cutie]
Are we able to call
him on this show?
Should I try?
That's cool!
We're grateful but...
If he does pick up, we're doing
a 1 minute speed quiz.
[A clock's prepared!]
[Calling]
Hello?
Who's calling?
[It's him!]
Start!
You only have a minute.
- The group I started...
- SS501.
- National MC is...
- Kang Ho-dong.
- Huh?
Wrong.
What are you called in Japan?
Me? Yon-sama...
The most handsome
in Super Junior.
Umm... Shindong.
President to elementary
school students.
- Hyun-joong?
- Yes?
This isn't a quiz show, right?
[Stop pretending!]
Correct!
Hello, Bae Yong-joon?
Hello.
[A pleasure]
Please greet the viewers.
Sure. Hello, viewers.
I am Bae Yong-joon.
[Charisma can be felt
in his voice!]
It's the same voice you
hear on television.
Hyun-joong said you get
nervous on quizzes.
I thought I had to solve questions,
but I found out it wasn't.
Were you confused with "Sebakwi"?
Umm... well... yeah...
I think so.
[That can happen since he's busy]
What do you think of
Kim Hyun-joong?
He's talented. People with talent
don't make an effort, but he does.
He's always concerned, progresses,
and is always polite and humble.
Many people, including myself,
like that about him.
Why did you go to Busan alone?
- Busan?
- Yes.
I had no place to stay in Seoul.
You can stay at my place!
- Who are you?
- I'm Jung Joo-ri.
- Oh! Hello.
- You know me?
Stay at my place.
It's Hapjeong.
[What a fool]
I heard you get cold easily.
Yes... I do.
How did you know?
Hyun-joong told us a little.
You'll be surprised when
you watch this show.
During the quiz, you said Kang Ho-dong
was the national MC without hesitation.
Since he's there...
[He's considerate!]
During "Happy Together",
he'll say it's Yoo Jae-suk.
What were you doing?
- Me?
- Right now.
I was waiting for this call.
[Even Korean Wave stars get
nervous for getting a call]
- While studying for the quiz.
- His answer was one-dimensional.
We're having a talk battle
for the King of Kings.
Kim Hyun-joong and U-know Yunho
are battling in Round 1.
Could you tell us who you predict
is going to be the winner?
- Umm...
- Could you...
I think Hyun-joong is going to win,
but it's good to see him lose as well.
Why?
I think the viewers would enjoy
seeing him get stood up.
[Puts a lot of thought
into his answers]
Please greet before you go.
I was glad to meet the two MCs even
though it was by phone. I had a fun time.
I hope the viewers will take interest
in this show and always stay healthy.
[Thank you for answering the call
despite your busy schedule]
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Yong-joon, I love...
Did he hang up?
Thank you.
A phone connection for Kim Hyun-joong,
but there were others that pleased him.
It's the people at his agency.
I'm close to 4 types of people.
1st is dancers, 2nd is friends, 3rd is my
old trainees, and 4th is my agency people.
Except for the agency people, the
rest of the 3 types were all nice.
They're nice but not that nice
when nice people saw them.
- Huh?
- That's hard.
Then is Seung-gi nice or what?
He sulks easily.
[Holds a grudge?]
There was an opportunity for me to
get close with my agency people.
I've been there for 1 1/2 years, but I wasn't
close with them for a year and 3 months.
With the exception of the director, Mr. Shin.
You wouldn't know even if I told you.
No, we wouldn't know.
I recently came back from my Asia Tour.
I went to 9-10 countries without rest.
I never went outside this time.
Many fans were waiting in the lobby.
I felt there might be an accident if I leave
and the agency told me to stay in the hotel.
I have nothing to do,
so we drank wine.
We decided to do something to
the one who passed out first.
Do what?
I didn't know what that was.
I thought they were boring people
and the most they would do is tickle.
One person left around 3 AM.
- Back to the room?
- He was dead drunk.
He lost it...
- Don't you mean knocked out?
- Oh! Yeah, you're right.
[Made a mistake!]
Losing it and knocked out
is a big difference.
He was knocked out, but I didn't
know they were such fun people.
They started drawing on his face.
They told me it's okay for me to
reveal those pictures on this show.
Really?
- They said it was okay.
- But not you, right?
I never get drunk with them.
I might retire early.
[He might retire if such
pictures are taken!]
Anyways, I will show
those pictures.
They're not celebrities, right?
I'll reveal them.
- Such things at the agency...
- How shocking is it?
[First scapegoat!]
[What a sight!]
What is that on his body?
This is...
Wow!
- Is he sleeping?
- That is sick!
[Second shocking photo!]
[OMG!]
[As if special effects
make up was applied]
[Funny seeing it again]
And?
[Third and final photo!]
I thought he was Lee Juck.
Seems like he came
back from a war.
They have a sense of honor to throw
away their portrait rights for him.
They sure are a unique family with
strong ties to this oddball star.
It wasn't much...
Above all else, his family
is his greatest support.
It's been several months since I left, but
she prepared a meal as if I never left.
After six months you're like, "Mom, I'm home."
She says, "You hungry?" You're like, "Yes."
After you're done, she
says, "Sweet dreams."
It was awkward. It wasn't
what I was expecting.
You must have told your family
about these things.
I didn't.
Because they'll be worried?
As a global star are you affectionate
to your parents and give gifts?
I'm not affectionate. I received some
exposure and ran away from home...
My family were against
what I was doing.
I give them allowances, but...
I give it to my brother and
tell him to give it to them.
- You can't give it directly?
- No, I can't do that.
I have a lot of worries. I want to
buy my dad a nice foreign car...
If he drives that to Dongdaemun Market,
where he works, people might badmouth him.
I have a lot of stress because I want
to express my heart, but I can't.
That can turn to deep resentment
since parents are waiting for it.
My grandmother fell and broke her leg, and
was paralyzed during the leg operation.
She passed away last year during
the year-end awards ceremony.
After the ceremony, they changed
my bow tie to a black tie.
That's when I felt that I should express more
often because it's too late when that happens.
I had a lot of stress and couldn't call
them because of work on my solo album...
But I should call them more often
after listening to what Yunho said.
[Say, "I love you," to your
father in the morning]
Since we brought this up, why don't
you say something to your father?
Tell him you'll express more often.
I always respected you. I always
act cold and serious to you, but...
That's not my true heart. I apologize
for acting differently from how I feel.
I exist because of you. I'll do well
for you and the family. I love you.
Lucky guy, Kim Hyun-joong,
enjoys the stage.
[Lucky Guy, Kim Hyun-joong]
He releases his 2nd solo
album in October 2011.
He presented his special performance
through the title track, "Lucky Guy."
His interest in band music gave him the idea to
make this song so people can dance to the music.
[It's an American uptempo funky rock song with
rhythmical electric guitar and brass session]
[His interest in band music gave him the idea to
make this song so people can dance to the music]
[With Daybreak and Common Ground as
session members, it gave a fresh sound]
[The concept of a dandy and witty
gambler stood out as well]
"Do You Like That" is also
in the same album.
With his dandy and sexy charm, he
gives an exciting performance.
[A funky rock and roll with a memorable arrangement
of danceable beats and intense band instruments]
[He worked on the lyrics showing off his
exciting performance and sexy charms]
He must be a lucky guy to do a joint performance
with After School at the year-end gayo awards.
A special performance with pretty girls?
To me, he really is a lucky guy.
This is how he creates his
own special colors on stage.
His complete transformation on
stage isn't strange anymore.
Not only is he active in Korea but will solidify his
position as an artist by planning a world tour.
Many are taking interest in
how much he will grow.