Star Documentary KPOP Hero
[A Special Girl
- IU's Appearance]
IU is a cute girl like my boo because she is very sweet.
But she started out differently. Do you remember that?
She made her first appearance in 2008 at the ripe age of 16.
She was complimented by many musicians even before her debut.
She sang exceptionally well unlike a girl and presented "Lost Child" as her debut song.
[It's a hybrid pop song based on ballad but with hip-hop rhythm on electronic]
[It gave a unique feel balancing electronic sounds with strings]
[It describes a person wandering like a lost child after losing a loved one]
[Her captivating voice was praised despite being only 16 years old]
I sang at Dongdaemun when I was in junior high.
I lied that I was 17 when I was actually 14. There was a singing contest every week.
1-3 place were picked and given a gift certificate.
I went every week as a different kid to get those certificates.
Every week as a different kid?
- You changed your name?
- There were 3 stages.
I went around here and there.
She developed her dream of being a singer at my karaoke when she was in junior high.
She was a regular for Room 2.
She came more than 5 times a week and sang 2-3 hours when she came.
That was a long time.
I always went on days when I didn't have after school.
- He gave a lot of bonuses...
- He gave them?
She developed her dream of being a singer ever since she was young.
She was a rookie but did her best on stage.
She was one of a handful of skilled rookies but her start wasn't easy.
Everyone's the same but I usually don't bear any malice.
But if someone tries to step on me then I will try to step on them.
It's because everyone's the same.
- When you have an interview...
- You fight with the reporters?
I debuted when I was really young at the age of 16.
I was also alone. Most of the reporters are kind but...
There are those that make you feel discouraged now and then.
We'll be discouraged on our own since we were rookies but...
I didn't want to be discouraged since I was being made to feel that way.
This wasn't the only thing that gave this 16-year-old a hard time.
Let's say I get a question like "What music do you want to do?"
If I say that I want to do such and such music and also compose...
Then they'll say something like "You'll vanish without a trace."
"I saw many like you. You'll vanish if you do that."
They say that with a smile and it makes me upset.
I can avoid that now because of my interview skills but...
Since he said he saw many like me...
I said, "I've never seen a reporter like you."
[Firm confidence]
I asked, "Do you wish for me to vanish?"
He said, "I'm just concerned and said that so you'll do well."
I said, "I'll do well as you wish."
Then I got reprimanded at the agency for saying that.
I met the same reporter again after "Good Day" was a success.
He's always smiling as he makes cutting remarks.
He says, "I heard that you're busy nowadays."
I say, "I'm busy. I'm really busy."
"You should be proud that I did well as you wished."
Then what did he say?
He did this and left.
[IU KO'd him!]
I'm on close terms with that reporter.
- Male or female?
- Male.
He has affection for you but his way of speaking is like that.
I didn't have any amibition for popularity when I debuted.
I remember what I wrote in my diary after having an interview with him.
"I have to become popular."
- He planted that in you.
- You must feel thankful.
But such hardships are doing her good now.
They will say such things and closely watch if the rookies can overcome it.
He must have watched her after saying that.
This song created synergism as it met the cute IU.
"Boo" is the title track of her 1st album.
IU wore clothes befitting her age with this song.
She unleashed her cuteness which is completely different from her debut image.
[An uptempo song with 80s retro sound]
[A snobby girl falls in love with an unexpected guy]
[It shows her cuteness unlike her debut song]
["Boo" is the sound she made while warming up her lips]
[It was put in the intro and made the song even cuter]
"You Know" is included in the same album.
[It's about making an honest confession to one's boyfriend]
[Her cute charms stand out from her energetic voice]
[The song was remade into a rock version with a cheerleader concept]
She still sings well in this lively stage with a cheerleader concept.
She draws more attention with such performances as she creates her style.
Next is IU.
I combined several songs with "crush" as the theme.
Give her a hand.
[IU's impromptu crush medley]
Guitar playing IU covered an acoustic version of songs.
It used to be her trademark.
Her timbre that goes with the guitar is very nice.
["Meeting" is born into a new genre with a sweet guitar melody]
[It makes even the original "Nation's MC" satisfied]
[It's now the climax]
How was the Lee Deok-hwa Show seeing it again after a year?
It's because of us if this goes well, but Lee Deok-hwa's fault if it doesn't.
She can sing various genres.
Even songs from before her birth aren't an exception.
[She's thoroughly educated from the fundamentals]
[Joo Hyun-mi is a strict teacher when practicing]
[Intensive training to present variety]
Doing great.
She's an admirable junior who can sing her seniors' songs.
That could be the reason why they look at her kindly.
[Her Charming Potential]
["Marshmallow" has the retro sounds and trends of 60s rock & roll]
She released her second mini-album in 2009.
"Marshmallow" is a pop song based on 60s rock & roll.
Her cuteness was upgraded with this song.
[French pop style added to 60s rock & roll]
[Love felt for the first time is compared to soft marshmallow]
[Her upgraded cuteness can be met in this song]
We need a doll before this person comes in.
Even the character on stage is cute. Do you know who the marshmallow is?
[The marshmallow is her manager!]
Stay there since you can't go all the way there.
Marshmallows are good when roasted over fire.
A duet with the "Nation's Little Sister" will stir up jealousy in everyone.
IU made harmony with 2AM's Seulong for her digital single "Nagging."
[This song is about the sweet conversation between lovers]
[It's about a lovely nagging towards one's lover]
[The exciting and lively melody stands out]
[2AM's Seulong was strongly recommended by the staff]
[Their sweet harmony stood out in this duet]
He had to explain himself on air for the crime of hugging her.
Many must have nagged him about it but cheer up.
- With popular singer IYO...
- It's IU not IYO.
There's also a lucky guy who got to sing a duet with IU.
We're curious how you got to sing a duet with IU.
- I'm a VJ for an internet show.
- Really? You must be talented.
There are people like him who are VJs and send in clips while being a cabdriver.
He is such a person.
A pretty lady and handsome guy got in at Apgujeong in July.
I told them to sing IU's "Nagging" which was popular, but she laughed.
I asked what's wrong and she asked if I didn't know her.
I asked who she was and she said that she's IU.
I won the lottery.
[This came out on his internet show!]
[Singing passionately in the cab...]
[IU happened to hail a cab...]
[The driver didn't recognize her and asked her to sing her own song]
[Excited]
[Their friendly harmony]
He's pretty good.
[A special relationship and a special stage]
He has a question.
Do you still have my business card?
I always have it in my purse.
I'll get to you straight as a bullet whenever you call.
I hope I get the honor of taking you home or the station safely someday.
[Thank you]
A duet with IU always turns out like a picture.
We can see that in many songs.
[A duet with Sung Si-kyung on the sorrow of love and parting]
Let's rank the stages that were special because it was performed with her.
[Ranking! Together with IU]
Ranking
- Together with IU.
"Hawaiian Couple" is a special love song by Inkigayo's MC couple.
See goes beyond generations and meets with a female solo artist.
She sang "Jjalajajja" with Joo Hyun-mi.
IU and Yoseob sings a sweet harmony "If You Want a Lover."
I heard that everyone who sang with IU became stars.
Superstar chose Huh Gak and IU's version of "Nagging."
[Beautiful passionate singing soothing the fall evening...]
[She's good]
[Huh Gak's surging high notes]
[A cute harmony by Huh Gak and IU]
[Passionate singing...]
[A duet with IU congratulating the birth of a star!]
She sang "Moon River" with a world-renowned pop opera singer.
The meeting between Paul Potts and IU is ranked at No. 1.
[Paul Potts the dream icon is back after a year!]
[Together with IU!]
[Fall into their melody this fall!]
[The reason why he's back]
[And a meeting with crab fisherman Paul Potts!]
[See them all in a moment!]
[His singing will continue!]
[IU Syndrome
- Her Good Day]
A song she can't forget in her singing career is born in December 2010.
It's IU's "Good Day."
[An imposing and dynamic sound is on top of a funky brass rhythm]
[It's an uptempo song reminding one of a musical scene]
[IU's detailed sentiments can be felt in this song]
[It's about a girl pining for an oppa she likes but couldn't confess to]
[This caused an IU syndrome]
This song is about a girl pining for an oppa she likes.
This made many oppas to pine for IU.
This made IU into Korea's top female artist and she is the cause of the syndrome.
[IU's Keyword]
[Samchon]
[Means uncle or one of IU's many male fans]
We are IU's samchon fans!
We can't leave out IU's samchon fan cheering squad.
You might have been curious about the men shouting at female artists.
[IU is the it girl!]
[IU's good day! Our good day!]
[These voices can always be heard at IU's performances!]
These men are them.
- What do you do for a living?
- I'm a web designer.
Shouldn't you be at work?
I asked my supervisor for a day off today.
These people don't idle around.
- What do you do?
- I'm a college student.
- What's your major?
- Dental technology.
They're all normal.
And at the end... What... do you do?
I've been in the reserves for 5 years!
He's protecting our country and always ready to go when called.
I heard there's an IU fanatic here.
Please step forward.
His nickname is "IU Chaser." Why do you have that nickname?
I got that nickname for taking pictures at the same place in the same pose.
He went to the places IU went and took pictures there.
IU is getting a piggyback ride and he does the same with his friend.
IU is drinking at a cafe and he does the same.
He takes the same picture wherever she went.
The truck's the same.
Just like Japanese tourists going to where the Hallyu stars went...
he did the same thing.
How can the same truck be in his picture?
Even the same motorcycle.
Did you take the picture right after her?
I took it after a week or a month.
- If you follow right after...
- I would go to prison.
If he did, he would go to prison as a stalker.
I know him.
I've met him online.
He always comes to the celebrity signing or...
to the set when I was filming with him.
He came to our charity restaurant and bought food twice.
So I remember him and always feel grateful.
They prepared a fight song.
This will be the shouting men when a female artist is up.
You will experience what sort of men do that.
Get ready and start!
I saw them practicing. Good luck!
IU's good day.
IU's the it girl.
[The mood at Inkigayo]
[They shout with one voice!]
[Military discipline!]
[It's funny]
[Their cheer is cute]
[Good day!]
[He made the IU t-shirt]
We!
IU!
[Samchon fans send...]
[a heart of love!]
[The highlight!]
[Same dance differen feel]
[This is a samchon fan's love]
- You should be grateful.
- Yes, I truly am.
- How do you feel?
- I'm happy.
- You actually hear that?
- They always do that.
IU's good day, our good day.
[Lee Soo-geun joins the samchon fans!]
I can't sing this well but... I made a short "IU Song."
I have to look at her while singing this.
[A song by Lim Baek-chun an appa fan!]
[IU Song
- Lim Baek-chun]
[What?]
[What's next?]
[Wow!]
[IU! I love you!]
[His heart is conveyed with that short lyric]
You can't do nothing when you received a song as a gift.
Shouldn't you return the favor?
- Really?
- Of course.
What a surprise.
[He even knows buzzwords...]
"I like Baek-chun appa. What do I do?" I'm sorry.
Oh my.
[Appa fan is embarrassed...]
Bring the real IU!
I'm sorry. That's why I brought the real IU.
- She's here? Call her.
- Will the real IU come out?
Even celebrity samchon fans aren't the exception.
[OMG]
[It's Baek-chun U]
[Baek-chun U and Yoyo U!]
[Cross-dresser legend and cross-dresser idol!]
[Baek-chun U's solo dance!]
[The ending is modest like IU]
[Bravo]
Introduction?
I'm Halbae U.
[Halbae U = Grandfather IU]
Can you do IU's aegyo?
He could do it after seeing the original.
[That's cute]
[Halbae U's attempt!]
[He can't bear to do this...]
"Fame didn't get to my head."
There are many articles and fans' expectations.
IU is known for being close to her fans.
She did a fanservice for them and it was a special airport fashion.
When I go to the airport, they should be, "She's here!"
But they said that they didn't know if I came.
- Why isn't she coming?
- Some missed me and left.
- "She isn't pretty at all."
- Your fans said that?
My fans say such things to me.
I like chatting with them and I was doing that.
Someone asked, "How much did you pay for that straw mat yesterday?"
[Straw mat...]
We use that term when you put something over yourself.
I pay attention to what I wear when I go to the airport.
But it looked like a straw mat to him.
Suddenly, I refused to yield.
I was returning to Korea the next day. So I wrote, "I'll show you what a star is."
[A cute declaration of war!]
My fans had high expectations.
I just went out that night to a huge shopping mall.
I bought sunglasses and several items.
I went the next day, but many came because of what I wrote.
Because you said that you'll show them.
More than a hundred came and I was suddenly intimidated.
I wanted to pass this off as a fun and trivial thing with few people.
I was intimidated because many came but I thought I had to show them.
I put on my sunglasses and let my shirt fall slightly off my shoulder.
- I threw my hair back...
- Like this?
You know how actresses do that.
I put my hands to my hips and walked like this.
It was really fun but there were all these articles.
Someone even left a comment, "What? That's it?"
- That's it?
- That's it.
I put on a lot that day but I'm going to explain that.
- I saw that picture.
- Really?
I collect every female celebrity's airport fashion pictures.
When IU wore that, I thought she was filming a spy movie or drama.
I was really surprised. Leeteuk, will you please?
[IU's complacent airport fashion!]
[She throws her hair back]
Those sunglasses are really round.
She does look like a celebrity.
She has visors on them!
If you look at it carefully, there are visors on top.
The fan behind her is laughing.
You know how celebrities don't wear normal ones...
That's not normal.
I purposely bought the one that stood out the most.
I didn't know it would come out that funny.
[Ta-da!]
It didn't go according to plan but it was cute. Her fans must've liked it.
You did that on purpose for your fans, right?
[Ideal Type]
[A type of person one thinks to be perfect within the scope of their thoughts]
[Getting dolled up]
[Someone came?]
Hello?
There's an ideal man she had until now and that's g.o.d's Kim Tae-woo.
[Handhakes the teddy bear?]
- It's Kim Tae-woo.
- Hello.
The one I really wanted to meet out of all my ideal types is...
Kim Tae-woo!
- Thank you for coming.
- It's my pleasure.
IU said she really wanted to have a meal with you.
[I'm happy]
[Me too]
Why did it have to be him out of all your ideal types?
Why did you say that?
I knew this was going to happen.
He's cool but...
There were many like Yoo Ah-in, Taeyang, and Song Joong-ki.
Kim Tae-woo is the first celebrity I ever liked.
I was a big fan of g.o.d.
Did you like g.o.d or was it Kim Tae-woo?
Don't ask!
You're the same.
I liked Kim Tae-woo the most out of all the members.
- Since when were you a fan?
- Since the 2nd grade.
2nd grade?
That's when they were taking care of Jae-min.
The "Hello Baby" show?
Kim Tae-woo... oppa was... can I just call you oppa?
He always made Jae-min cry.
He lifted Jae-min up when they first met.
Since he's tall, Jae-min bumped his head on the ceiling when he did this.
He started crying and wouldn't even look at Kim Tae-woo.
He wore primary colors to cheer him up, right? Since babies like primary colors...
I remember how he wore such clothes and danced.
He was really... really... cute.
That's when I...
Did you know she liked you? How do you feel right now?
I saw on television when she said she likes Taeyang.
I thought, "What's with this young girl changing her mind?"
There was this article...
"Love for Taeyang Respect for Kim Tae-woo"
I saw that too.
You were sad, right?
I want to be loved and not respected since I'm a man.
Of course.
[They set the mood for this meeting by eating pasta]
[IU neatly takes a bite]
[While Tae-woo slurps]
[It's like a dream that I'm eating with you...]
When I first met you at the recording studio...
You didn't believe me when I said that I liked you.
I still can't believe it.
The first thing you said was, "You like me? Stop joking!"
["One Candlelight" from g.o.d's 3rd album (2000)]
[So you won't think that you're alone...]
[Dissonance!]
[Ji-eun is laughing out loud]
[He's the best but was off-key...]
[He was really nervous since IU is popular]
[It's too funny for her]
[They choose matching hats]
- It doesn't fit.
- Yes it does.
She's on a date and even sang. Is that what you call success?
But why do I envy the singer more than the fans?
[Everyone knows IU]
[Allows pictures to be taken]
Do this for IU. "I like you noona." Ready, start!
"I like you noona."
- Do "What do I do?"
- "What do I do?"
That was really cute.
It's over for us if it doesn't work but we will win if it does.
Since he's Taeyang.
- I'm getting nervous.
- Taeyang's a man.
Who's close with him?
[But we have 6 female celebrities here...]
Me!
My manager for the 1st album was also BIGBANG's manager...
- Are you really close now?
- No, not really.
I'm a big fan of his. He's my ideal man.
There it goes.
Please, please, please.
Hello?
Hello.
[Making a fuss]
- I'm In-na.
- Oh! Hello.
- Were you sleeping?
- I just woke up.
I love his voice.
We have a women's rugby team.
They really want to see you and IU is also a big fan.
I wanted to know if you can come.
Right now?
Whenever you can but today.
I just finished shooting a music video.
I don't know if I can make it.
It must be hard but I'll hand the phone over to IU.
Hello.
[She's flustered]
- Were you well?
- Yes, I was.
[Even IU's an ordinary high school girl]
I watch your performances and it'll be great if you can come.
I really want to see you.
[What's wrong with her?]
- I'm always cheering.
- Thank you.
Let me speak with him too.
- It's me, Noh Hong-chul.
- Oh! How are you?
It was nice talking with you.
I hope you can come later.
We'll be waiting. Bye.
Everyone knows her other ideal man is BIGBANG's Taeyang.
She's getting prettier and sings well too.
Yes, she does.
IU, why don't you sing one of his songs?
[What about preparations for the performance?]
[OMG]
This is good for the rugby team, us, IU, and even Taeyang.
Last of all, IU had waited four years for this.
[She didn't even touch him...]
The myth of this successful fan, IU, continues on.
[She'll be on the same stage as Taeyang that she dreamed of!]
Don't be nervous and do as practiced. You dance well and feeling is at top.
You'll be perfect if you do as practiced. The mood's really good right now.
I think you need to relax.
What do I do? I'm so nervous.
Stay calm, stay calm, stay calm.
[She nervously takes each step]
[This fan is on the same stage with the one she longed for]
[There's another fan here who can only look on]
[IU is still inexperienced but who does she vaguely long for?]
[She's excited!]
[They're like high school girls who never saw a celebrity]
[It was great]
What do I do?
I... I did it. What do I do?
[He's working with the audience]
[A great finish!]
IU put on a great performance with Taeyang.
I'm in trouble if this goes on air.
You're already in trouble.
You told me to do it.
A special performance with Taeyang. Keep this clip for a long time.
- What about me?
- Not you.
Your husband will be watching this.
It's ok.
[Takes Off as a Musician
- Her Growth]
IU returns in 2011 with her 3rd mini-album.
She used to be lovely but goes through another transformation.
It's a ballad by Yoon Sang.
Her sentiments matured another level with "Only I Didn't Know."
[Piano
- Yoon Sang]
[Lyrical melody of the session goes with IU's matured voice]
[Yoon Sang's participation in this minor ballad drew attention]
[He saw her sad eyes on television and wrote a song for that sad image]
[He regretted it because she was in high school and the song was too sad]
[He revealed his affection for her in an interview]
[Befitting the sadness of the song]
[She cried in the music video which she received favorable comments for]
IU takes on a new challenge later and that is being an MC on Inkigayo.
We introduce our new family on Inkigayo starting today.
We'll be taking care of your Sundays. I'm Gikwang.
I'm IU. It's our pleasure.
State your resolution to the viewers.
I'm nervous to do this live show every Sunday...
But we'll learn a lot from Jo Kwon and Sulli and do this perfectly.
Have you ever made mistakes?
It's my first time being an MC and people tell me, "You're MC."
So one time I said, "This is MC gayo live."
Taecyeon and Wooyoung on MC gayo...
- MC gayo...
- Inkigayo!
[Cute mistake by a rookie MC]
[Bouncy lines for MCs on a music program!]
She played the mascot well after getting back up from her mistake.
[1 min to the live show!]
[IU and Lee Jong-suk are Inkigayo's MCs!]
[As if they are actually MCs on Inkigayo!]
Jong-suk, do you know who's appearing today?
IU, what do you take me for?
- It's Lexa born to lead gayo.
- Nope, you're wrong.
- It's Nu Clear gayo's atomic storm.
- Nope, it isn't Nu Clear.
I know for sure this time. It's Key gayo's skeleton key.
I'm disappointed in you Jong-suk.
It's Get Ya Boom who's making a comeback after 10 years.
[He's making a comeback?]
Boom shakalaka still has lingering feelings.
Let's meet him. Music start!
[This is sad, please stop...]
[Lee Jong-suk the new Inkigayo MC]
IU's the best so far at acting in Inkigayo.
I fell hard one time and it still hurts.
Efforts don't matter. I need to do well.
I have to do well to look good because this is visual sports.
I can't do that.
It was big for her since she's clumsy.
I heard that you're not athletic.
Do you think you'll be fine?
I... I... will do it.
It's a difficult challenge but people took it the wrong way.
[After reading the article...]
Some people didn't receive it well and I'm pretty upset about it.
People said I didn't put any effort but I think I did put in effort.
People said such things because I was worse compared to others.
I think I have to do better in the next performance.
There's not that many steps so do just half of them.
[Can't get this particular move]
[She practiced every day for 4-5 hours despite her schedule]
Doing good!
IU's admirable for getting an applause for putting effort.
I'm your fan.
I knew skating would be hard but the reason I tried is...
because I can greet you from this distance.
I would like to sing the show's theme song with you if the opportunity arises.
IU and Yuna Kim revealed that they're both fans of each other.
The wish to sing together came true with the theme song "Ice Flower."
It's a heartwarming meeting between two "Nation's Little Sister."
IU releases her 2nd album after 2 years.
Corinne Bailey Rae, who she respects, wrote a song for her.
[IU's calm voice went well with Kim Kwang-jin's lyrical melody]
[He added his voice and appeared on a music program after 10 years]
The title track "You and I" was born amidst such great songs.
The song has a mysterious concept of a girl who went to the future.
She once again sang the special love of a girl.
[IU's unique sentiment and voice can be heard in this song]
[Instruments rarely heard in gayo such as harps and horns were used to create real sounds]
[She attempted various voices with a concept of traveling through space and time]
[Her singing skills have not waned and that's the charm of this song]
She felt this song will be a big hit since the recording.
People outside including myself didn't feel good about it.
Lee Min-soo composed this song who also composed "Nagging" and "Good Day."
He also composed "Abracadabra" for Brown Eyed Girls.
We started recording but I didn't agree with him from A to Z.
"You should sing like this!" "Shouldn't I sing like this?"
We got emotional so he said, "Then you compose the song!"
And I said, "Then you sing!"
[That's childish]
[They're really close]
He left and went to his room not the recording studio.
I was also upset because this recording is for the title track.
I said bye to leave and went back to the recording studio.
I told the people there that I'll be back tomorrow and left.
One of the engineers took hold of me and reasoned with me.
"Min-soo is older than you. You shouldn't act like that."
We were talking here and my manager was here.
He was nodding his head. Our eyes didn't meet...
but I know someone is there.
Since he was nodding his head, I thought, "I hate him."
Since he agrees.
He told me to apologize and do well tomorrow.
I said that I will and he told me to go now.
I said I will and my manager went inside the recording studio.
I thought, "Is he playing or did he leave something inside?"
I followed him inside but there was nobody.
[What?]
I asked the engineer, "Do you know where my manager went?"
"What's wrong with you?"
I said, "He went inside when we were talking here."
He said, "It was just us."
"No, he was here!"
I went outside and asked where he was.
"He's over there." I saw him coming out from over there.
It was a different place.
No one believed me.
People say it'll be a big hit if you see a ghost in the recording studio.
This is how "You and I" was born and it placed IU at the top.
The ghost of the recording studio jinx went well.
I'm getting the goosebumps.
IU is now 20 and releases a single filled with her sentiments.
She conveyed her sentiments with "Peach" her own song about the excitement of love.
She tweeted a picture of a peach she drew before the song was released.
She drew attention with that picture.
The peach that IU drew attracted attention.
I was told to draw one that will be included in the teaser.
I drew it in the shape of a heart.
I turned it upside down since that's obvious.
I gave it but they said they can't use it because it's erotic.
- Erotic?
- An erotic peach?
Then give it to Shin Dong-yup.
But it's a peach.
I couldn't throw it away since I drew it so I tweeted it.
- That's how it appeared in the articles.
- What did the articles say?
- It was called "erotic peach."
- Let's take a look at it.
This is how she first drew it.
But people like Shin Dong-yup could see this in an erotic way.
This is how it changed.
It's nicer.
The first one is attractive.
It looks like a butt.
The first one looks like a real peach.
"Every End of the Day" was released after "Peach."
Her uniquely clear voice stood out in this song.
She changed from a cute teen into one in her 20s with deeper feelings.
We look forward to the performances she will be giving in the future.
Subtitles by SBS International