Subtitles by SBS International
[Sentimental Time 2AM's Beginning]
2AM debuted on July 2008.
4 numbers stand out for this group.
It's 2567.
Jo Kwon of 2AM was selected from the Nurture the Gifted Project.
He is the owner of this number.
I will try hard and practice to be a great artist. Thank you.
[He's finally on stage today]
[This debut song is a sentimental ballad that accumulated everything they practiced]
[A sentimental ballad with subtle melody and sad lyrics]
[An ardent lyric that there is nothing to give but a song]
[Their debut song shined through their captivating voices]
2AM's Jo Kwon became a legend through his success of enduring 2,567 days as a trainee.
- We're proud.
- It's been 8 years?
When I'm on variety or talk shows...
People tell me to stop talking about my days as a trainee.
Many are sick of hearing it.
There's no other choice since I spent my teens as a trainee...
- That's a third of your life.
- That's all I have to say.
I have no memories of my school days.
I had my first audition in the 6th grade.
I never imagined it would take this long until I debuted.
You waited 8 years.
Now JYP tells you to get ready for your debut.
How did he tell you that?
He sent me a text.
Today is the 2,567th day you were a trainee.
He was a long-term JYP trainee that stayed the longest at 2,567 days.
He finally got to stand on the stage he dreamed of.
Jo Kwon silently overcame those 8 years.
He led 2AM as the leader with 3 other members.
Jo Kwon wasn't the only one who desperately wanted to be on stage.
They finished their first broadcast of their debut song "This Song" in tears.
They were moved to tears.
What can they exchange this feeling for?
The one who shed the most tears was Jo Kwon.
He can't believe this moment since he was a trainee for 8 long years.
This was the stage I dreamt and waited for until now.
Since I practiced under the burden and expectation of debuting.
Those 8 years seemed short when I was on stage.
I cried a lot because I was moved and felt proud.
"I have nothing to give but this song."
The voice and lyrics are sad.
It's a special song that only 2AM can present.
"This Song" is special as a collaborative stage.
He performed with Sunye, a fellow JYP trainee.
It must have been lovely to be in the spotlight with a friend.
[Jo Kwon spent time as a trainee for a long time]
[Sunye of Wonder Girls is a fellow labelmate and close friend]
[He wanted to show his gratitude to her through this song]
This heart-filled song gained much interest as it was released.
People paid attention to something else other than their song.
[Their Own Keyword]
[Kkap]
[A word describing Jo Kwon's one of a kind character]
He left a strong impression at a surprise performance.
This is how his "kkap" character was born and left a mark in idol history.
We did a special called "Wonder Boys" on Inkigayo's 500th episode.
There was a Jo Kwon crisis.
On the internet?
Many fans said that was the day "Kkap Kwon" was born.
There's this part in one of Wonder Girls' songs.
I expressed those emotions well.
[He sure is Kkap Kwon]
[Wonder Girls parody during Inkigayo's 500th special]
[This is how Kkap Kwon was born]
Only that part was made into an animated GIF and spread online.
JYP called me right away.
"Kwon, stop doing that."
"You shouldn't do that since you're a ballad singer."
The other members told me, "How can we sing ballads now because of you?"
You know Jo Kwon's Kkap Kwon dances on various programs...
I happened to watch that on television and was surprised.
There's an image when I create a group. The four of them are singing like this.
But he's doing such a dance with such expressions.
He didn't just dance but his expressions were...
I was really surprised and called him.
I scolded him, "What are you doing? You're a ballad singer."
- You did?
- Yes.
He didn't do it in one program but started doing it again.
Jo Kwon's instinct "kkap" goes against JYP's dislikes.
Didn't you sense anything when you casted him?
Not at all because he was in elementary school.
He was unique at the audition and did Lee Jung-hyun's "Come On."
But he went more crazy than the original artist.
We agreed that he can do such dances but behave himself inbetween.
Inbetween?
To be cautious inbetween when he does such dances.
We get hooked the more we see it. I guess JYP has given up on it.
[Jo Kwon is rising as a agitating woman!]
[Is my mascara okay?]
[What do we do with them...]
Kkap Kwon comes out anywhere. How can he not stand out?
[If you're going to shake, you should shake like this]
[My son's the best!]
He even made his own "Kkap" awards.
You prepared them?
[Kkap Kwon Best 3 Wonder Kkap Kwon!]
- It's this picture.
- When was that?
We parodied the Wonder Girls as Wonder Boys once.
I made this expression and this was the screen capture.
This is beyond "kkap" and close to horror.
Can you make that face?
[Red sun!]
[Kkap Kwon Best 2 Director Jo!]
JYP artists had a poster shoot for the year-end concert.
JYP was supposed to be here.
But I'm here and he's there.
JYP was hard on me at first.
"Why are you trying to be funny? You're a ballad singer."
He said a lot of things and I was scolded.
But now he goes around saying good things about me.
How did he change?
I'm known as Director Jo at the agency now.
Can you do a similar pose if a picture is taken now?
Another pose. One, two, three!
[His "kkap" instincts]
Let's stop.
The last is...
[Kkap Best 1]
We parodied Brown Eyed Girls as Dirty Eyed Girls...
This was during the filming of our music video.
I look similar to a character in a well-known Japanese comic.
- It's the same.
- It really is.
- It does look the same.
- It is similar.
I'll make a prediction. It's been a year since he rose as "Kkap Kwon."
This will last about 5 years.
What is your secret?
- I'll do a cam version.
- Alright. Make it cute.
That's a nice pose.
That's Jo Kwon for you.
He became big with "kkap." How did he hold this in for 2,567 days?
Let's wait and see this one of a kind character.
Now...
It's Go Hyun-jung and Jo Kwon's age.
[Ex-soldier idol]
[A male idol who finished his mandatory military service]
We can't leave out Changmin's voice from 2AM.
He drew attention not only with his excellent voice but also his nickname.
It's ex-soldier idol, an idol who finished his military service.
During the early days of my debut, I was known as ex-soldier idol.
You know those that completed their military service.
I qualified for the police marching band.
During my military service, MBC came to film.
I had a bad case of the flu and was sleeping upstairs.
I was resting when the commander came in.
"Changmin, I think you should go down and sing."
When I said I needed to rest...
He said, "Do you want a special leave?"
So... I did it.
[Vacations can make even sick soldiers to get up right away!]
Do all of you want to see Changmin singing at that time?
Yes!
This is being revealed for the first time.
- This is really...
- I'm getting curious.
Let's watch the clip.
Next is a music project that will please your ears.
The Police Symphony Orchestra in Yongin, Gyeonggi-do.
[This is the barrack Changmin used!]
[Where is he?]
[He fights against the flu with a red face to get a leave]
[Showing skills with a bug spray]
He shows off his showmanship by using the right props.
His talents were exceptional since his time in the military.
I was asked to go to an audition.
It was a JYP audition and I said I'll go since I like JYP's songs.
I went to the audition but I didn't get news of the results.
I was discharged from the military without knowing the audition results.
I hung out with my friends all night and received a call the next day.
I received a call saying, "Come to JYPE and sign the contract."
The day after my discharge, I went to JYPE and...
He went to the audition during his leave and signed the contract after discharge.
How he became a singer is also extraordinary.
He was also active in the group Homme with Lee Hyun of 8Eight.
What made you to be in a group together.
I put this song aside because there were some heavy parts for me to sing alone.
I was suggested to sing with Changmin and I thought that would be great.
But how he entered this group was different.
He heard the song first...
You're younger than him?
Yes, I'm 3 years younger.
What is this feeling?
I didn't say anything but I think we're thinking the same thing.
Changmin is younger than Lee Hyun who is currently in the military.
Don't be upset. I wasn't surprised.
He stood out since there weren't many ex-soldier idols at the time.
Good thing you served early on.
This is a bonus.
Including myself, we made a military version of this song.
[Disciplined moves!]
[A resounding voice!]
[They prepared a military version of a girl group's song!]
What's the MND's time?
[Tick tock, tick tock the time just flies]
[Radiating masculine appeal]
Hey, mister! What's your name?
Public service worker Kim Dong-wan!
He's a public service worker? Are you by any chance also...
- I'm not Pyo In-bong!
- I see you're not.
[1, 2, 3, 4! 1, 2, 3, 4!]
I was sleeping in the dorm and Seulong said we got a new member.
- I ran in with the notebook.
- But he was laughing.
His picture was posted!
It was a clip of him during the audition.
"We got a new member but I'm at a loss for words."
What's the reason?
I got up from bed and the two of us didn't say anything for 5 minutes.
"Is he a vocal trainer?"
His looks made us think that he'll sing well.
I mean, he is an idol.
We thought he would be skilled because he did sing well.
That's what we thought. He had spots on his face and was just discharged.
So he wouldn't have been picked if it wasn't for his singing?
Lookism needs to be eradicated from Korea.
What's your wish?
I want my mouth to go in!
Just live as you are.
He's at ease for being discharged but feels uncomfortable of his looks.
I thought he took my advice...
But recently his skills and looks were upgraded.
You were recognized for your singing in the group 2AM.
Is there something else you want to be known for?
- Be honest?
- Yes.
[Deep in thought]
For my looks...
He wants to be known for his looks. Guess he was a bright character.
I wonder what it feels like for people to say you look good.
You guys hear that.
[2AM's Music]
2AM drew attention with various activities along with their popular debut song.
They released their 2nd single in 2009 after their debut.
They presented their own ballad with "Confession of a Friend."
[A beautiful harmony stands out with powerful singing and masculine appeal]
[A ballad containing the regret of not becoming lovers from being friends]
[They're more stronger and masculine since their debut and their harmony stands out]
In 2010, their special ballad potential was unleashed in their 1st mini-album.
"Even If I Die I Can't Let You Go" was made by producer Bang Si-hyuk.
[This song was born from the meeting of 2AM and producer Bang Si-hyuk]
[It's a hybrid ballad with refined sounds and sentimental vocals]
[To keep the balance between the concept of ballads and idols...]
[Electronic sounds were used in this ballad]
[The static-like sound in the chorus is unique and made with a synthesizer]
[It was intentionally given such a sound]
[It topped various music charts with its release]
[Not only did they take first on broadcast...]
[They received the grand prize at the year-end awards]
- How do you feel?
- Yes, how do you feel?
First of all, I would like to thank my dad and our manager.
I thank JYP who's in the US right now and Young-kwon.
We also thank Mr. Yang.
Kwon is crying right now... Hey, say something.
Thank you. I thank God, my parents...
Thank you everyone. We'll do our best.
I love you mom and dad! Thank you God!
Not only did they get their first trophy with this song...
But they also received the grand prize at the 2010 Golden Disk Awards.
They reached the top they dreamed of with their own ballads.
They released their first full-length album in the second half of 2010.
They released double title tracks and showed strong as the best group in ballads.
[A ballad describing the pain and loneliness of breaking up]
[This song describes the pain and loneliness of breaking up]
[Their ardent sentiments on top of the lonely accompaniment stand out]
[When "Even If I Die I Can't Let You Go" was released, they worked on this song]
[It was decided a long time ago to be the title track of their 1st full-length album]
[Their looks also matured with suits that went with the song]
[The unique melody that's strongly attractive went with their voices]
[Due to the song's appeal...]
[Producer Bang Si-hyuk gave much thought on the title track and decided to go double]
[Before its release, a teaser of the members shedding tears attracted attention]
They didn't sing only quiet ballads.
They've also transformed with fast tempo songs.
[A dance song with a bright and catchy melody]
[It's completely different from the sad image of their debut song]
[They're lively and dance cute moves in this second single]
[A clip of this song performed at an awards ceremony was revealed]
[The fans' request and overwhelming support made this their 2nd single]
Their most shocking performance was when they danced in "I Was Wrong."
Their moves changed a lot in the past two years.
[A dance song with intense string melody, piano, and Eurobeat drum sounds in the intro]
[They wanted to present a sentiment that goes beyond a ballad]
[Their attempt on acting in the song's music drama also drew attention]
Before you see the dance, you need to compare our expressions.
The biggest change is our expressions in the song.
That freshness from our 1st album.
I'll go down and watch.
Let's see "I Was Wrong."
Expression is as important as the moves.
But be careful of getting screen captured.
We can't do anything about the ones that were already done.
We can't leave out the powerful Kkap Kwon dance for this song.
We'll excuse ourselves and become his shadow.
[Shadow]
Thank you.
It seemed we were successful in our image makeover but Jo Kwon...
We're curious of their special stage since they can sing various genres.
Let's find out more about their charms when they're together and alone.
[Ranking! 2AM's Special Stage]
2AM sings "Sunday Morning," a sweet pop song.
Seulong and IU's sweet harmony where they nagged each other.
"Woman of the Beach," an exciting song for summer sung by 2AM.
Another harmony on top of perfect harmony! A collaborative stage with Sweet Sorrow.
They can even sing JYP's songs well. Their version of g.o.d's song is No.1.
Clap your hands!
Sing along if you know it!
[What Do We Do? 2AM's Confession]
Seulong appeared on this show on August 3, 2010.
He said his ideal woman and only love is Shin Mina.
On a happy Christmas in 2011, where and what did you do?
December 25, 2011.
- We had a concert.
- A concert?
What did you do afterwards?
- We had a get-together.
- Where?
At a restaurant serving pork belly.
[What is that?]
What else do you want if you eat pork belly?
- Noodles.
- That's right.
In detail...
You want noodles if you eat pork belly?
There's a reason.
Boom? You always eat noodles after eating pork belly, right?
I do.
- And what noodles?
- Rice noodles.
You were with someone at a rice noodle restaurant around 3 AM.
And a lot of people know because of the articles.
Instead of denying it, it's now time for you to be honest.
Who did you meet at that restaurant at 3 AM?
It was Sohee, my labelmate.
[The one with Seulong was Wonder Girls' Sohee!]
- Park Ji-yoon?
- Yes?
If you meet someone at 3 AM... it's not 2 or 4 but 3 AM...
According to experience, what feelings might you have to meet at that time?
You have to like that person.
I heard that the birth of mankind is at 3 AM.
[What?]
[What's with that?]
[Boom was taken aback]
You're close with Sohee but that picture spread dating rumors.
It could have developed into a relationship or it did not.
What happened?
Nothing... happened.
Don't stutter.
Sohee was the one in Seulong's dating rumors.
But there's someone else that Seulong likes.
It's Shin Mina.
He has her ID picture.
[It's not like he'll get documents in her place...]
You're afraid of this one person in Korea?
Who is that?
That is Shin Mina.
[He fears her the most?]
You're afraid of her?
I get nervous.
It's been made public a few times that his ideal woman is Shin Mina.
Does your family know?
[She had heard about it]
[He can't look at her because his heart feels like exploding]
[This beast idol falls before love!]
Idols' ideal types are... Kyu-jong likes Oh Se-jung...
It's really big news that Seulong likes Shin Mina.
This is an unexpected competitor.
I beg you to not turn around.
Really?
I get the goosebumps all over my body.
What happens if she turns around?
[Eyes are tightly shut]
[Please... don't look...]
[Bashful nine-tailed fox]
[Singing "Nothing Better" for her]
[I'm nervous]
[Don't be nervous...]
[He was her fan for 10 years]
[He's actually singing before her...]
[He's so nervous he can't even look at her...]
[Seems like everyone's jealous]
[His dream was to be on television with her someday]
[Should I look or not?]
[He doesn't have the courage to look at her yet...]
Look at her at least once!
[He finally looked at her!]
[A dreamlike second...]
[His dream came true!]
[A pure heart of a fan who liked her for 10 years...]
That's it.
[A song of love that stirs the heart...]
We acknowledge his love for her.
Jinwoon also made a sudden confession.
Can you tell us who you like?
Of course.
It's Seohyun.
- Seohyun?
- Yes.
- Isn't she cute?
- I get nervous.
We met in the hall and I turned and ran away because I'm her fan.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're so innocent.
That's right!
My friend... Seohyun of Girls' Generation...
Something to eat?
Seohyun of Girls' Generation?
She asked to eat together before I left so we had breakfast.
She gave me vitamins after breakfast.
[She gave him vitamins as a gift?]
She gave me these.
[That's a letter by Seohyun!]
Seohyun of Girls' Generation?
Vitamins from Seohyun? That itself is vitamin.
But he has another room in his heart and that's for Lee Min-jung.
I really like Lee Min-jung.
- Lee Min-jung?
- I really like her.
You know the contact lens commercial she's in?
"Giving up for health." It drives me nuts. Her eyes are so pretty.
He wants poor vision just to put on those contacts.
Even when you see the ad poster?
I love it, but she came to our concert.
How?
We got acquainted after appearing in a one-act drama together.
I invited her and she was in the waiting room.
That's when he got really nervous.
I wanted to take a picture with her since she was there.
I was pacing up and down to get a picture taken...
But I couldn't ask her to take a picture with her.
I was so nervous that I hid in the dressing room.
I didn't do anything wrong but I was trembling as I hid.
I thought, "I should act like a man, greet her and get a picture taken."
But we could see him because he's tall.
That's even stranger.
Didn't Lee Seung-gi shoot many commercials with Lee Min-jung?
I took many pictures with her.
[I'm friends with her]
Jealous?
[Really jealous]
- I could make arrangements.
- You can do that?
I got acquainted with her and I meet her on the set so...
- It's okay.
- Why?
[He's holding on to his pride...]
Is Lee Min-jung the only one for you? Wasn't Kang So-ra...
He's currently shooting a drama with her.
Yes I am.
Leeteuk has a long face.
[Leeteuk and Kang So-ra are newlyweds]
Didn't you get a divorce?
The station is on a strike.
[They've been separated...]
[They want to see each other but can't]
You can't meet during a strike.
[Let us love each other again]
[That cracks us up]
It's a strike. We didn't break off our engagement.
Would you pick Kang So-ra over Lee Min-jung?
You're going on a trip.
- A trip.
- A trip?
- Planned?
- On impulse.
You pick them up in front of their house.
- Whose house is it?
- He's into it.
He just gets into it whatever it is.
The trunk is filled with food and you depart.
- Is there a mat?
- Of course.
- You call, "Come out."
- Come out?
Who steps out of the door?
- Whose house is it?
- Who is it?
I choose Lee Min-jung.
[Me?]
- I'll be straightforward.
- Alright, shoot it.
Are you close with Lee Min-jung?
- You like her, right?
- I'm jealous.
You should create an occasion for him if you know that.
I'm jealous.
I did during the concert but it was Jo Kwon who took pictures.
And Jinwoon was hiding in the dressing room.
I was embarassed.
Jinwoon was shy even though the members made an effort.
Does she know?
Yes, she does.
We acknowledge that he likes Lee Min-jung.
Let's listen to their hypothetical proposal song.
We always make idols do a hypothetical proposal.
Since I'm the youngest, I'll make it cute.
I'll always make this pretty smile if you'll go out with me. I'm sorry.
No, it was cute.
Can we change to a three member group?
Next?
I'll do a short song with some aegyo.
- Then go to the front...
- But I can't do it alone.
The members have to help.
- Are you going to do that?
- We play around like this.
I'll sing after speaking in a Busan dialect.
Fine.
Jung-eun?
- I have something to say.
- What is it?
Please have my child.
I would've regretted it if 2AM didn't do this.
[They Shine Alone and Together]
They are all exceptional singers and do well on their own as well.
They each went solo and had their own projects.
[Seulong]
Seulong went on stage first not as 2AM but as a duet.
He did a surprise colloboration with IU singing "Nagging."
[A song about nagging lovely to one's lover]
[IU and Seulong's sweet harmony stood out]
[Seulong was strongly recommended by the staff to be in a duet with IU]
[This is his first duet showing off a bright and cheerful voice]
But IU is interested in another 2AM member.
Who is your ideal type if you have to choose?
- Among the four?
- Yes.
Seulong looked cool when I didn't really meet them that much.
He's tall and like a model.
- His looks are not ordinary.
- He's really good-looking.
But after working together, Jinwoon looked cool.
- Me?
- You do it.
- Thank you.
- Take my place.
Seulong is sulking. What's cool about him?
When he smiles.
- Thank you.
- When his eyes disappear?
I feel uncomfortable being in the middle.
Jinwoon, did you create another space in your heart?
And Changmin? You lost if you feel jealous.
[Changmin]
Please introduce yourselves.
- I'm Lee Hyun of 8Eight.
- I'm Changmin of 2AM.
We have to introduce in our project name too.
Hi, we're Homme.
Changmin was part of Homme with Lee Hyun of 8Eight.
Songs with their unique voices were born as they are great vocalists.
[Two great vocalists, Changmin and Lee Hyun, gave birth to...]
[Bang Si-hyuk's first project (Homme by Hitman Bang)]
[This is Homme's first single]
[It's a hybrid rock with a cool guitar and drum sounds]
[The lyrics calmly describe the feeling after breaking up]
[Their uniquely cool voices were memorable]
He gave off a masculine appeal different from when he's in 2AM.
["Man Should Laugh" is the title track of their first mini-album for summer]
[A song mixing American style rock with sweet synthpop]
[This was released for summer like their first single]
[Their voices stand out and make us feel the coolness]
[Jo Kwon]
Jo Kwon released his first solo album in 2012 with a shocking performance.
He showed off his talents.
[His uniquely bright energy can be felt in this electronic dance song]
[Music, appearances, performance, and even the music video]
[Many different things were shown in the title track of his first solo album]
[His own bouncy electronic dance song was made collaborating with artists from abroad]
[The kitsch stage outfits and album jacket utilizing pop art were memorable]
He wore appalling high heels and did a performance only he can do.
[There's a wild feel to this song like the title]
[This song competed with the title track to the end]
[The vocal effect is as if it's echoing from a cave]
[The intense lyrics alluding himself to an animal stood out]
You gave a warning to your members?
It's been 4 years as I was a part of 2AM.
We didn't have any big fights, and if we did, we resolved it.
But I was really hurt by them this time and want to talk about it.
You have to let go of that.
You'll feel light if you do it in public.
I was filming my solo music video for about 3 days without sleep.
When a music video or album jacket is being shot...
Labelmates will sometimes come for support.
The other members come to support when one of them is doing a solo.
My members didn't come on the first day of filming.
On the second day, 2PM's Wooyoung was also filming a music video.
I asked him, "Did your members stop by?"
He said they already came and left.
[Suddenly we're starting to compare them to 2AM!]
I felt sad and went to the restroom to pick my nose...
These black things came out due to the dust and I was welling up with tears.
I don't know why but I felt really sad.
On the last day, filming ended at 9 in the morning.
Seulong texted me, "How's filming?"
I replied, "It's going well," thinking that he's coming.
He replied, "Good luck. I'm tired and going to sleep."
[Oh you poor thing]
I was really sad and didn't even want to send an emoticon.
So I texted "alright" with a tilde.
At first I didn't want to put in the tilde.
You might look timid without it.
There's a difference with and without a tilde.
He might think he's sulking without that tilde.
The feeling is different.
I was really sad and thought this feeling won't go away.
So I sent another text even to Changmin and Jinwoon.
I texted, "Today's the last day of filming. How's everyone?"
That's weird.
"Wooyoung is also filming today and all his members came and left."
- You were straightforward.
- That was around 5 AM.
Changmin wakes up at that time.
I got 5-6 texts from him.
I felt that they were going to come.
- Like a surprise?
- A surprise party?
- Something like a hidden camera.
- They're pretending not to know.
Thinking they will appear from somewhere but where?
That's right.
It felt they will walk out of there or wait in the waiting room.
They didn't come at all.
[Oh my!]
Do they know you're coming on this show?
Yes, but they don't know I'm talking about this.
They don't?
So we prepared...
[Prepared?]
Since this is Jo Kwon's first solo album and variety show appearance...
We have a special corner. Music please!
[I miss you to death]
[Explosive acting!]
Someone is here in the studio.
It's the one you want to see the most. Who is it?
My mom.
[Unexpected answer!]
[Do they call his mom?]
Anyone else?
2AM members!
You want to see them? Shout out to them!
- I miss 2AM!
- Louder!
I miss you!
[Surprise appearance by 2AM's Jinwoon!]
[The youngest member came in a heartbeat for Jo Kwon!]
Oh my! I'm about to cry!
[He cries as soon as he sees Jinwoon!]
[He's wailing!]
[He was really hurt]
[People might think a separated family reunited...]
[Don't cry!]
Jinwoon appeared for Jo Kwon who was feeling sad. He was touched.
[Jinwoon]
It's known that Jinwoon didn't have any solo activities unlike the other members.
Jo Kwon was busy in sitcoms and variety shows...
Seulong was in a duet with IU, something that I wanted to do.
I even believed in Changmin...
Why is it "even" for me?
It's okay because he was in a duet with Lee Hyun of 8Eight.
I'm the only one without a schedule.
But aren't you the busiest now?
Oh! Now?
Now...
This is about you!
[The one with the "top star" disease is Jinwoon?]
It's actually about me.
[The one with the "top star" disease is Jinwoon!]
I started off with a solo album releasing first and second albums.
I played the lead in "Dream High 2."
When I released my first solo album...
Many band members and musicians heard it and told me I was great.
He's a former rock band member and went solo at a Rock festival in 2011.
He's finally on his long-awaited dream stage. This suits him as well.
He's doing his part on "Law of the Jungle" with unique vigor and quick adaptability.
[Will he make physical contact today?]
[Come here]
[What is he doing?]
[He's trying to lure them by becoming a tall tree]
[Jinwoon lures them with a familiar sound]
[It climbed!]
[Lemurs are known to be sociable]
[Maybe since it's the second day, it became close to them]
[Awesome!]
[Made physical contact!]
[A concert on the spot for finding water?]
[How do I dig you?]
[If you dig me and try to dig...]
[Bring a shovel and dig]
[To not make this tiring...]
[To be able to take this water...]
[If it doesn't work, we can't take it]
[Even though I die, I can't dig it]
[He wrote his own song about his crush!]
I tried to hide her from my head and heart...
But I can't because she's so bright.
[You're So Bright
- Jeong Jinwoon]
[You're so bright]
[I hide under a shade that will block you]
[These two are absorbed]
[In his sweet voice]
[A sad song on unrequited love]
[In the middle of the desert]
[I draw you this time]
[Jeong Jinwoon the jungle's wandering minstrel]
That was really good!
Don't fall in love with me.
[Don't worry about that]
I should leave.
[Jung-chul feels left out]
They return in 2012 after a year and a half.
The quintessence of their ballad was felt again with a matured sentiment and voice.
[The calm piano and cello melody goes with their profound timbre]
[They convey a man's empty feeling after a breakup in a calm, heartrending voice]
[Its release was postponed 3 times for completion, but an LP was also made]
[This title track is nostalgic and worth possessing]
It'll be great if we could listen to more of 2AM's songs in the future.
[A soft piano melody and strings go well with their subtle timbre]
[Their voices are calm as if having a soliloquy]
[The plaintiveness is expressed dramatically as the melody gradually builds up]
[It was tough in the beginning due to the song's high level of difficulty]
[But they picked this as the title track after listening to the guide]
Subtitles by SBS International