[The Birth of T-ara and Secret!]
T-ara entered the gayo world
in the summer of 2009.
People were familiar with the
six members before their debut.
They debuted with their single "Lies."
[It's their catchy debut song with electronic
sounds in a retro style with a repeating chorus]
[The album also contains an acoustic version
of the song giving off a different charm]
[The music video that contained each
member's love story made the news]
One young man caught our
attention in their music video.
He's Yoo Seung-ho,
Korea's Little Brother.
Yoo Seung-ho transformed into a tough
guy. With different clothes and a girl...
He revealed his hidden toughness
as the main male character.
He had a kissing scene with Jiyeon
that surprised many women fans.
I didn't kiss at all.
Jiyeon, who was the envy of all,
was actually Seung-ho's fan.
There was a kissing scene.
He gets off his motorcycle and
pushes me to the wall...
Please calm down first.
[I like him]
I held on to my helmet with one hand
since it was slipping and he bent his head.
- It was as if I was covering the kiss.
- You were just holding the helmet.
People were saying, "What are they
doing? Separate them right now!"
- They thought you were actually kissing?
- Yes. I wouldn't feel wronged if I did it.
But I didn't do it.
They were making a fuss and later told us
to do it for real because they need to film.
They told us to do it
and we did it.
Was that your first kiss?
It was my first kiss.
Yoo Seung-ho gave your
very first kiss?
She debuted and had a kissing scene with
her ideal man. She must be very happy.
[She will never forget that kiss]
Four member group, Secret, appeared
after T-ara in October of that year.
They debuted with "I Want You Back"
and the beginning is a secret.
This is when they truly began. Their skills were
verified with a live video before their debut.
[It's a medium tempo pop R&B with
a lovely melody and hip-hop beats]
[Their skills were recognized through
various live videos before their debut]
[Their unique singing along the catchy
melody stands out in their debut song]
They're finally on stage but unleashed
their potential in the next album.
[Potential Unleashed - Their Dances!]
"Magic" is the title track of
Secret's first mini-album.
With flashy beats unlike their debut song,
they found favor in the eyes of the public.
[The flashy beats stood out
in this pop dance song]
[It's a completely different image
from when they debuted]
[This song garnered attention due to
their sexy and powerful performance]
The powerful dance gained much interest.
It contributed to getting this song known.
Just following these moves a little
bit will give you a workout.
It created many unforgettable stories.
After filming the "Magic"
music video for 24 hours...
We just fixed our makeup and went to
a music chart show without sleep.
I was half awake and said...
"I'm tired from filming all night, but I'll
do my best. Please understand."
I monitored myself after the
broadcast and that wasn't me.
I was slurring. People that didn't know might
think, "What is that drunk girl doing on air?"
People could get the wrong idea.
Even when I saw it, I looked
like a drunk person.
How bad was it? We have that
video clip in our possession.
While the weather was very cold,
I filmed a music video all night.
I came all the way here to *#@$
I'm not in a normal state right now.
Look at my pronunciation.
Please understand.
It's cold and I'm not in my right mind,
but spring is just around the corner.
I promise you a show as fresh as spring.
Once again, I'm not in a normal state.
Please understand just a little...
She was drunk with fatigue and not alcohol.
That could happen if you dance all night.
Their performance continued in the title
track of their 2nd mini-album "Madonna."
The four transformed into sexier
Madonnas showing off their dance.
With just two hits from "Magic" and "Madonna," their
sexy and powerful individuality are established.
[An electronic pop dance song with the message
of becoming this age's icon like Madonna]
[The mechanical synth sounds were
removed as much as possible]
[Actual instrument sounds can be heard and the
brass band, TST, participated in a session]
[With a sexy and energetic performance,
they gave off their unique charm]
A demonstration first.
At "don"...
You're really good!
You're the first that got
it on the first try.
- I like the "it's my way" part.
- Right. Many like this part.
Here we go. Ready, begin.
You have to move your
pelvis and chest.
I'll do it if you sing.
Should we do it together?
- You're better at this.
- You're really good.
You can lose weight with this.
Even a belly dance version, Secret's dance
makes losing weight easy. Let's dance!
["Madonna" goes well with belly dancing]
[Perfect transformation to Belly Madonna!]
When did they practice this?
[Han Sunhwa - belly dance goddess!]
T-ara also gave a clean hit
with their next song.
"Bo Peep Bo Peep" is the title track
of their first studio album.
They reached the top for the first time since
their debut with trendy melody and cute dance.
[As a dance music with a trendy, funky rhythm,
it's a hook song with a repetition of words]
[The cute dance is easy to follow and it
gave birth to many parodies and UCC]
[It put them on the top for the
first time since their debut]
The simple and addictive dance made it
a big hit. I bet many of you danced it.
[Cute cat dance!]
This dance was at the center.
Sergeant Noh is a witness.
[I want to sleep too!]
[Morning exercise will wake up T-ara]
Not only as a morning dance
that will wake you up...
[Disheveled Eunjung Half-shut eyes Jiyeon]
Even dogs are taking part.
Beast idols were turned
into cute pet idols.
A collaboration with substandard dancing was
a burden, but it does make everyone to dance.
[The aesthetics of substandard dancing!]
[Sorry for such dancing!]
Another thing catches our eyes.
It's the various stage costumes
as if they were doing a cosplay.
On our first broadcast, the CEO of our agency
told us to wear these gloves, ears, and tail.
- The CEO?
- Yes.
We learned the moves without these, but
he gave us these right before we went up.
We were taken aback since we
had to wear these baby things.
The one who told them to wear such
cute but difficult props was their CEO.
- The CEO himself?
- Yes.
- He bought them?
- Is it okay to reveal his name?
- He's going to like that.
- He likes that?
- Yes.
He's very meticulous. Just before we
go on air, he makes us stand in a line...
Our manager makes a
video call to the CEO.
"I did this and this" and
all the members talk to him.
"It's me, Eunjung..."
It passes quickly and after
hanging up, he sends a text.
"Eunjung take off the ears, Hyomin put on one
more glove, move the hairpin from left to right."
They would've said, "You're mean."
But he left a deep impression.
"Bo Beep Bo Beep" was also
their debut single in Japan.
It was No. 1 on the Oricon
daily and weekly charts.
They seduced both Korea
and Japan with this song.
They transform again with their
repackaged first album.
"I Go Crazy Because of You" is an
intense electronic dance song.
It gained attraction because
Wheesung wrote the lyrics.
[It's a dance song with electronic
sounds added on top of pop]
[They presented their strong charisma
shedding off their cute image]
[They took the top with a provocative and sexy
stage with the "temptation of the devil" concept]
[Wheesung heard their demo and wrote the
lyrics that went with the sensual mood]
They put on a contrasting mood with their
2nd mini-album with two title tracks.
First is "Why Are You Being like This?"
including new member, Hwayoung.
[A pop dance with strong beats and retro feel
with electric guitar and catchy bass sounds]
[Yangpa took part in composing
since she's close to them]
[They became a seven member group
with the addition of Hwayoung]
The other title track was "Yayaya."
They transformed into Indian girls with
the unique melody and arrangement.
[A pop dance with catchy melody and
lyrics, and a unique arrangement]
[The lyrics and moves were as if they
were chanting and it left an impression]
[They drew attention to their
cute Indian girl concept]
They were active without
rest throughout 2010.
They displayed their potential as
all their songs made the top.
Secret's "Magic" and "Madonna" garnered
interest, but they never made No. 1.
But the day they dreamed
of finally came.
They released their single
"Shy Boy" in 2011.
They transformed into lively girls
with a 1960s American retro style.
[A dance song in the swing genre
with bouncy rhythm and lyrics]
[They transformed into cute girls
with a 1960s American retro style]
[They presented a lot of spectacles
on stage as if it was a musical]
[With retro outfits and hairdo,
and the little bird dance...]
[They showed off their cute charms
of their complete transformation]
This song presented them with
an unforgettable moment.
They reached the top for the first time, and
were the only ones that shed the most tears.
They had a nickname during
their debut and that is...
[T-ara and Secret's Keyword]
[Basement Idols]
[Secret's nickname when they debuted. It also
shows their perseverance of reaching the top]
We dormed for two months
before we debuted.
The room was older than we thought.
We stuck foils because there were no
curtains and the walls were moldy.
The snow melted and
it kept on leaking.
- It was leaking from the ceiling?
- We placed a bucket all day long.
There was a completely
broken down kitchen.
And the bathroom?
We couldn't use it due to the
low pressure. Even the showers...
- All you did was sleep?
- That place is a jungle.
We only slept. If we need to use
the bathroom, we held it in...
Those who need to use the bathroom
raised their hand and we go to a cafe.
We can't just use the restroom so
we buy coffee and then use it.
Our dream was not to be No. 1
but to escape the basement.
So we gave our all...
Since they lived through the basement,
their nickname was basement idols.
They could feel upset, but this nickname
made them remember their original intent.
I heard you are hard workers.
It must have been tough.
I went to many auditions
and never passed at one try.
I went to auditions during vacation
from the 6th grade to the 12th grade.
It was tough. I thought
maybe this wasn't for me.
Did you feel you would make it
even though you failed?
They waited a long time until
they stood on stage as Secret.
That rankled in the heart
of one of their members.
My mom told me to go to Seoul,
but I didn't have the heart.
I eventually went and fell asleep,
but I fell into a deep sleep.
Someone woke me up. When I saw my
phone, I had more than 40 missed calls.
I went down to Chungju in haste.
That day was May 6th, my
younger sister's birthday.
On May 7th, the day after her birthday, my
dad removed his oxygen mask at 12:05 AM.
When I heard that... he held on because he
didn't want her to be sad on her birthday.
For my dreams,
I don't know why I...
[Regret and tears finally come]
I thought why I wasn't there
with him when he passed away.
When I arrived in Chungju...
When I saw his pale, cold body...
I thought I had to let him go.
I held his hand for the last time
and it was cold and hard.
Your father is watching
you with satisfaction.
I can't believe he passed away.
It's as if he's still in Chungju.
The four Madonnas that presented "Magic"
continued on with their transformation.
They made their bashful confession
"Starlight Moonlight" to shy boy.
[The heart of a shy girl is
contained in the lyrical melody]
[The lyrics sing of an innocent
love and it goes well with...]
[The retro feeling of the song and
they reached the top once more]
[Their dance gained interest again, and
this time it's a baby gorilla dance]
They reached the top again with this
song and made their foray into Japan.
This is amazing. It's like
when we first debuted.
Let's hold back our tears
because I'm getting emotional.
Let's just enjoy it.
One, two, three! Go!
[Even before the album went on sale,
their Japanese fans sing along]
We thank all of you today.
During our 3 1/2 years as trainees...
[Hyoseong became emotional as
she thought back to that time]
When we debuted in Korea and
when our hearts were broken...
We remember the time when we
used to live in the basement.
We won't forget you
that came here today.
Thank you very much.
Their Japanese fans were touched by
their heartfelt stage and cried together.
This is what's extraordinary
about the basement idols.
I feel great. It ended successfully.
[Even tears of joy...]
- I feel great.
- I'm excited.
I'm happy because I feel that
I'm loved when I meet my fans.
How do you feel?
- Our legs ache, but it was fun!
- We feel great!
- Our backs ache, but it was fun!
- Our legs hurt, but it was fun!
She was more realistic.
Act as if you're more hurt.
- Our legs hurt, but it was fun!
- My legs hurt for real now.
This is my cheat sheet.
This is a caldron lid hair.
We're a group that always changes,
but we will stay friendly.
They chose to change again.
They made a powerful return with an
intense pop dance song, "Love Is Move."
[A pop dance song with memorable
catchy chorus and intense beats]
[The exciting melody has a rock and roll
type of beat and it's sort of like a twist]
[Their style completely transformed
with flashy outfits and makeup]
[A stable live singing despite the intense
moves while wearing heels drew attention]
Secret time is fun because they never
lose their color despite the change.
Not only their shining stages, but
each member's story continues.
T-ara also revealed their own
unique song the same year.
They chose to go retro.
[Retro]
[T-ara showed their strong points in music,
fashion, dance, and so forth in this genre]
They initiated the "retro craze" with
their 1980s disco song, "Roly-Poly."
[A retro dance song with modern
elements on top of 1980s disco]
[Roly-Poly means to get up no
matter how many times one falls]
[The stage, style, and the hustle and diamond
dances of the 70s and 80s caused a retro craze]
[They conquered the music charts with its
release and was chosen as the song of 2011]
[They later performed in a
musical with the same name]
With fashion items and hairdo of the time,
they did a retro dance doing the disco point.
Their album, "John Travolta Wannabe,"
reminded people of Saturday Night Fever.
[We don't have time for this]
[This mission almost
became a dance lesson]
[This isn't the time for that]
[Holds the wall and dances]
T-ara's own Korean sentiment can be heard in
"Day by Day" including new member, Areum.
[The lyrical melody and string arrangement that
went with the flute in the first half stood out]
[It has the slowest tempo
out of all their songs]
[Their 16 minute fantasy music video
breaks away from existing conventions]
[They transform into an eight
member group with Areum]
They took moves from the
Bongsan Mask Dance.
The unique moves went well with their
song that has the slowest tempo.
"Cry Cry" uniquely conveys the sorrow
of parting in a Spanish melody.
[A Spanish style song with intense beats and
guitar sounds conveying the sorrow of parting]
[Showed both boyish sexiness and androgynous
charm with attractive singing and rapping]
They filled the stage with various
genres being loved around the world.
Joanna's from Peru. She's happy and excited
as if on stage. T-ara watches her warmly.
Even she looks satisfied.
I'm very happy because all
of you watched me dance.
Dancing is my favorite and something
I want to do for the rest of my life.
Joanna's desperate wish
is great and profound.
Even T-ara went through that process.
Thus, her challenge touched them.
One thing she respects about Korean culture
is the indomitable spirit of challenge.
She learns of the path of challenge
that K-pop artists walked for success.
They did a shuffle dance around stage and
changed to clubbers with "Lovey-Dovey."
They made everyone dance again.
[A club dance song with strong
beats and electronic sounds]
[They wore flashy outfits and props
and did a shuffle dance on stage]
[They became funky clubbers]
[She's tired and lies down]
[Tries to get up]
Everyone, are you having fun?
Things are heating up here.
We promise you a warm winter.
Their distinctness can be known
in their one-day pledge.
T-ara pledged to take the subway if
"Lovey-Dovey" gets the No. 1 spot.
Did they follow through?
It looks like they did.
As soon as they finished with Inkigayo,
they took the subway to their next spot.
They handed out their CD and
rice cakes to the passengers.
Both T-ara and the passengers won't
forget that day due to their pledge.
Now let's explore their charms.
[Exploring Members' Charms: Secret]
[Sunhwa, Jieun]
You're going to impersonate?
People say I sound like them
when I do it at the dorm.
She's doing it for the first time
on air, but I'm nervous.
First is Lena Park...
As the group's main vocalist,
impersonations are a given.
First time getting such a response.
Next, while things are good.
- Next is Lyn.
- Alright.
- I expected it to be like this.
- Okay, while things are good...
Last is Hwayobi.
I guess that's me.
It's her song time!
There was an article where Sunhwa
was first and I was second.
That's the official rank, but I was
first in the unofficial rank.
- Wait a minute...
- You have a side job?
This isn't a...
- Yes, I do.
- What is it?
Singers get royalties in
addition to their pay.
There's a royalty for voice and chorus.
Usually, singers don't do a chorus.
Our agency director made me the
chorus of our group from the start.
When "Shy Boy" and "Starlight Moonlight"
became hits, I made a lot for the chorus.
Secret's hidden chorus also
increased Jieun's income.
With a proven track record, she
released her first solo album.
She showed off her special voice in "Going Crazy"
about a woman who can't stand the obsession.
[The piano rhythm is memorable
in this R&B hip-hop song]
[It's about a woman who can't bear
a man's obsession towards her]
[She sang about it with her unique emotion
and B.A.P's Bang Yong Guk did the rapping]
[As Secret's main vocalist, this song
showed her potential as a solo artist]
But there was a twist to her.
- She never kissed before.
- No way! For real?
I gave a peck but never a kiss.
Then when you sing,
how do you...
The composers always point out that I sound
the same whether it's a sad or sexy song.
- Does Jieun have aegyo?
- She has a lot of it.
- Her daily life is aegyo.
- Really?
- What does she do the most?
- Show them your chair aegyo.
- What's that?
- She's 24, but...
Every time she sits, she goes...
- She's asking for a chair?
- She's exaggerating it.
I just say that when I sit.
Let's say you're in a restaurant
asking the manager for utensils.
What's wrong Jieun?
She'll meet someone one day who'll raise
her sensibility and watch her chair aegyo.
There's another Secret member
who went solo just like Jieun.
Sunhwa sang a love song "Everything Is Pretty"
with B.A.P's Young Jae in a surprise duet.
[It's a confession song sung by Sunhwa
and B.A.P's main vocalist, Young Jae]
[Fresh melody and lovely lyrics
fitting a love song stood out]
She was on stage before her debut as
a featured singer for another group.
But she has a past
that goes further back.
She was on "Super Star Survival."
- Let's study together.
- How are you going to teach me?
I'll teach you well like a friend.
We might get intimate,
but you're not my style.
Not your style? Should
I sing you a song?
Listen to me!
"Jae-yong. Hey, Jae-yong.
Why don't we study?"
There's a screen capture of me
that's going around online.
This video stirred things up again after her debut
and she was pestered with malicious comments.
Everyone thinks my past is strange.
I felt wronged and played out
a self-fabricated scenario.
There's a website where people
post old photos of celebrities.
I used my friend's login info
and started a topic.
I posted a few pictures of me that are pretty
but not too pretty because I can get caught.
I post a few strange pictures among them
and start a topic as if it wasn't me.
"I feel sad for singer Han Sunwha.
There's strange pictures of her online."
"But I searched and found a lot of pretty
ones." Then I post those pictures.
I think what I wrote was still
online so I brought it today.
- You wrote it yourself?
- Yes with the pictures.
That is long.
[A female idol's self-fabricated scenario!]
"There are many old pictures but
the ones online are all strange."
"There are faces that get prettier and
others that get uglier with age..."
"But my personal opinion is that
Han Sunwha is getting prettier."
I felt bad for her and am
posting some old pictures.
"For someone who's taking her
first step for her dreams..."
She dealt with it with a self-fabricated
scenario. It's something she would do.
Her charms can be seen in
other places as well.
[Powerful temptation]
[There she goes]
[Startled]
[Seungri's throbbing]
[What was that dance?]
[She just keeps on dancing]
[They've been scorched]
[Someone grab my hand...]
She does well alone. There's another
thing she dreams of doing alone.
[Lee Soo-hyuk and Han Sunhwa
reenacting "Closer to Heaven"]
I... can't let go of you.
Can't you stay with me a
little longer? Can't you?
Just one second! Only a second!
Please! Can't you do that?
Wake up now! I really have
something to tell you!
I'm awake.
With such passion, we might
see her acting someday.
[Exploring Members' Charms: T-ara]
[Hyomin, Jiyeon]
Like what Sunhwa said, a member from
T-ara went into acting and that's Hyomin.
I can't stand watching you
with that woman. Get out.
Good day.
Sometimes it sucks because
she's little miss perfect.
- How could he do that?
- I don't think he can tell...
She has an extraordinary past.
She was the model for Princess Mimi,
a doll every girl wanted at the time.
You didn't know?
- She looks so different.
- What? I look the same.
I was picked at the 1st
Princess Mimi Pageant.
[I'm Korea's Barbie!]
Your chin becomes this big if
you shoot from below, right?
You have to shoot from above
and follow the light like this.
- If this is okay...
- You just know it?
You can see your reflection on the
lens. You look at it and say...
"Who is the fairest one of all?"
"It's you, Hyomin."
- Show it to us!
- See, look.
She was well-known in the past.
She shows off her loser
charms on variety shows.
[This is hard!]
[Run!]
[With all her strength!]
[Stop!]
[Slam]
But she's different on stage.
Her secret weapon is
the sexy chair dance.
There's a T-ara member who holds a grudge
with this dance. It's the minor, Jiyeon.
You can't do it because you're
a minor. We'll get caught.
All she did was lie down.
A minor can do that too.
I want to age quickly
and lie down too.
You want to make that wish
come true on the show?
[Jiyeon fulfills her wish.
Give me my chair performance!]
[I can do it too!]
[Fulfills her wish]
[She's good]
- Do you feel good?
- I feel great.
She eases her grudge on variety shows as
well. She shows her charms on "Heroes."
I'm good at this.
Bring me some sugar and molasses.
[They do everything
the unni commands]
Just wait! It's not done yet!
Ordinary people eat that...
- But this is eaten at the palace.
- Jiyeon's just eating and doing nothing.
[All she's been doing is eating...]
Her character is an "eating dinosaur."
Where did all that food go, Jiyeon?
[You tattled on me?]
Feel sorry for eating
by yourself?
[Hardship and Another Beginning]
Every album by T-ara was a success,
but they faced a big hardship.
What they posted on social media became a
controversy and led to a break up rumor.
controversy and Hwayoung left the group.
T-ara was on a roll since their debut,
but this was their greatest hardship.
They hinted at their self-relection on air
that they were thoughtless in posting that.
They overcame that and
released "Sexy Love."
They gave their all on stage and
it was returning their fans' favor.
[An electronic synth pop with
a funky and refined melody]
[The robot dance made the
moves stand out in this song]
My concerns?
Since I'm in a girl group, there's so
many things I want to eat, but I can't.
Diet?
Secret overcame that temptation
and succeeded in losing weight.
They presented a provocative stage with
sexy outfits and performance in "Poison."
[It's a hip-hop song with a saxophone
playing throughout the song]
[They pursued real sounds]
[The catchy intense melody and their mature
and provocative performance stood out]
But the provocative moves of
"Poison" became a controversy.
They had to modify the moves
before going up on stage.
There was an unexpected variable.
I felt great from losing weight
so I took a picture and posted it.
I'm not good at taking pictures.
The next day, "Jun Hyoseong's cheeks
disappeared" came up on searches.
There were comments such as, "I used
to love you, but I'll let you go now."
"You're the first girl I
hated for losing weight."
- Hate for losing weight...
- Is it wrong to lose weight?
A mental breakdown.
I was tormented if I had
to gain weight again.
I didn't lose that much weight.
Yeah, she still has those cheeks.
- It's because I take the pictures...
- You have cheeks we can pinch?
Because I took it from above,
it came out thinner than usual.
Sunhwa, as a member of the same group,
are you envious of her body or what not?
Only her upper body.
I like my lower body.
They soon released "Talk That."
[It's a sad melody in the minor chord with dramatic
progression in French electronic style arrangement]
[It's been 3 years since the composer of "Magic"
worked with Shinsadong Tiger to create this]
[A melody that brought out their singing
and the mournful lyrics stood out]
They prepared very hard but got into
a car accident with their comeback.
- Didn't you have seatbelts on?
- No, we didn't have them on.
- Since they were in the backseat...
- It's the law to have seatbelts on.
Who was injured the most?
We thought Hana was unscathed because she
didn't say anything, but she was unconscious.
Her eyes were open, but she
couldn't remember what happened.
After a thorough checkup at the hospital,
she had a rib fracture and bruised lung.
It was hard for her to breathe.
Fortunately, nobody was seriously injured,
but it happened at the busiest time...
- First day of comeback.
- It must've been hard.
It happened during the first
week of our comeback.
We were all attached to the album.
We thought it was our chance to
plant a new image to the public.
We prepared a lot so we were
very disappointed at first.
But the sisterly love I felt was great.
I thought of many things as I rested.
I thank Hyoseong who helped me
even though her leg hurt...
And Sunwha for holding my
hand in the ambulance...
In 2013, they released "YooHoo" from their 4th
mini-album and returned to their cute image.
[It's an exciting synth pop dance
song with cute lyrics and melody...]
[Describing the pounding heart when
you see your friend as a man/woman]
[Their unique cute feel goes along
with the exciting rhythm and lyrics]
We look forward to their Secret Time that's like
conveying the feeling of someone in love.
T-ara returns in 2013 with a
sub-unit called T-ara N4.
"Countryside Life" is the title track.
T-ara showed their Korean sentiments again by
grafting Korean classical music to club music.
[It's an exciting club dance song
leavened with hip-hop elements]
[The lyrics are about breaking away
from the boring everyday life]
[The motif of this song is from the main
theme of the drama "Countryside Life"]
[Directed by Hwang Ho-joon, Korean traditional
instruments were grafted for a differentiated sound]
Many cheered them on for
taking such a challenge.
Even the legends of the drama
"Countryside Life" gathered.
Choi Bool-am and Kim Soo-mi are together
again after 10 years for the music video.
It's been 10 years since you
dressed up for "Countryside Life."
We finished it in 2003, right?
Then it's exactly 10 years.
Many celebrities are in it such as the
original sexy singer, Kim Wan-sun...
Your eyes are scarier...
Actor Jung Woon-taek...
Baseball god, Yang Joon-hyuk...
And Kang Minkyung of Davichi
made the music video enjoyable.
Why don't you also give a
congratulatory message?
- Are you in there?
- I come out a bit.
Then I have to see it.
After many hardships, they
dream of taking a new leap.
But they announced another sad
parting. Areum left the group.
Hello everyone. Even though
I didn't post much online...
I felt much love through the
few fan meetings we had.
I made many great memories and will
be seeing you soon as a solo artist.
Don't forget T-ara since they'll be active
and don't forget me and look forward to it.
Go me and T-ara!
Areum left the group to go solo, and
T-ara returned to a six member group.
Dani will take Areum's place
in the sub-unit T-ara N4.
T-ara went back and forth from
the top and hardships.
As they said, we hope to see a matured
and prudent T-ara shine on stage.