Star Documentary KPOP Hero
[The birth of 2NE1 and f(x)!]
Both YG and SM debuted new girl groups that showed off their colors in 2009.
They are 2NE1 and f(x).
YG's girl group that debuted in May of 2009 is 2NE1.
They were the talk of the town as soon as they debuted with their single "Fire".
It was a fresh group that gave a strong impact unlike the current girl groups.
[It's a mixture of reggae and hip-hop and the Indian sounding instruments were memorable]
[Their debut song strongly displayed each of their charms and talents]
[When a teaser of the first 20 secs of the song was put up on their official homepage...]
[200,000 visited the site in one day and there was much interest before they debuted]
They showed they have the potential to make the top and made their presence known.
f(x) debuted in September of that year after 2NE1.
They won over many fans with their lively pop dance song, "LA chA TA".
[The arrangment is memorable in that it has a hip-hop groove and electronic feel]
[The message of the song is to enjoy life]
["LA chA TA" is an interjection and a coined word that goes with the bright, cheeful song]
This song was more than enough to let everyone know the birth of a new groove.
2NE1 introduces themselves in a special way.
[I was influenced to be a singer as I listened to Mariah Carey and Beyonce when I studied in the US]
They showed they are skilled rookies.
They released their 1st mini-album in July two months after their debut.
The title track, "I Don't Care", is a catchy tune with a reggae melody.
Another one of their ambitious projects for summer.
[This is a mid-tempo R&B; pop with a soft reggae melody]
[It has a different feel from their usual songs to go along with summer]
[They topped various music charts and music programs once again]
They were at the top again and let all know they are a force to be reckoned with.
In November of that year, f(x) released their 1st physical single since their debut.
Their title track is "Chu".
[It's a europop dance song with a strong synth sound and bubbly charm]
[It's about the excitement of a girl filled with curiosity]
["Chu" is an onomatopoeia expressing the kissing sound]
[It hooks listeners as it repeats in the first half]
They made the name of f(x) known with sweet kisses.
[They have something special]
It wasn't just 2NE1's songs that received attention at the same time as their debut.
The never-before-seen unique styles were more than enough to draw attention.
The open box was filled with peculiar accessories.
The mood of every performance is changed with different accessories.
It's my first time putting on something colorful. Isn't it cute?
I always put on my airplane ring and Superman ring.
I always wear a swimsuit under my pants, but I wore a sleeveless shirt today.
- And... what do you call this?
- A bandana for the waist.
The color of the bandana always changes, and I have it on today.
I wore pants and boots today.
I think music and fashion are the same. They're connected.
We have to show you everything on the stage such as sights and sounds.
So our appearance is very important. Thus, fashion and music are one.
70-80% of what we're wearing right now is our own clothes.
- Really?
- Yes.
Everything's mine except for the belt.
You look classy.
- Your ring is...
- Scary, huh?
- It's pointy...
- There's more here!
- Oh, Bom has...
- Yes, we love studs.
- It's a bit scary, but...
- No, I covet them.
- Could CL introduce these?
- In "Can't Nobody" music video...
Minzy wore this, but we can't call it clothes.
It's like an armor.
- Like this?
- Yes.
That's right. Now work it.
Like this?
What's next? My head?
I see... like this?
It's similar to what football players wear...
You look funny, if you wear this.
- Really?
- Yes.
Take the challenge.
You look good!
Beauty, talent, and individuality.
f(x) is the girl group that has it all!
Hi, we're f(x)!
Nu ABO is very novel. Please explain it to us.
Nu ABO is a coined word for a new fifth blood type.
It expresses the lyrics of our unique love story in a fun way.
If 2NE1's specialty is their style, f(x)'s specialty is their lyrics.
The title track of f(x)'s first mini-album in 2010 is "NU ABO".
[It's a reverse beat dance song with a simple synth riff and intense drum compilation]
[NU is a homophone of "New"]
[It was combined with the blood types ABO to form a coined word]
[They don't follow the existing formula but develop their own way]
[They have something special that only they can convey through "NU ABO"]
NU and ABO combined to form a coined word. The lyrics were also memorable.
This could be said as f(x)'s own creative lyrics.
f(x)'s own unique lyrics can be found in their other songs.
The lyrics of their songs could also be searched online.
Their unique lyrics is one of the things used to describe them.
[It's an electronic pop dance song with intense synth sound and beat]
[It expresses in a fun way how to spend the hot summer]
[f(x)'s bouncy lyrics were memorable]
2NE1 releases their first full length album in 2010 showing off a new concept.
[The hip-hop rhythm was mostly percussion, but the intense rapping on top of it stood out]
[The strong chorus part and their styles gave off the same feel as the song]
They had 3 title tracks
- Clap Your Hands, Go Away, and Can't Nobody.
This was unprecedented in the gayo world.
Their triple title track strategy was much loved.
Confidence in their music hit it big for them.
[It has a strong tempo and shows off their flashy performance]
[2NE1 and f(x)'s keyword]
The youngest member of f(x) is the cute Sulli.
Sulli played a role in a period drama.
- When she was young...
- Really? What role?
It was Princess Seonhwa. I played Lee Bo-young's part as a child.
A princess?
[She's so cute!]
- Wasn't there a kissing scene?
- In a period drama?
- I know, right?
- A kissing scene?
I was young and embarrassed to kiss. So I told the director I can't do it.
- How old were you?
- I think I was 12.
- 12 years old?
- You were young.
- You sure were brazen.
- It was just acting.
- It was acting.
- It was a role.
Not as much as you, right Hong Suk-chun?
Yes, I am.
So you were 12 and told the director to remove the scene.
He said to kiss the nose...
He said no one would know so I kissed on the nose.
- With who?
- It was Kim Suk.
- Oh! Kim Suk!
- Do you know him?
No, but we'll see the video clip soon.
She acted as a child with a very beautiful face.
Seems like she listened to the saying, "Grow up as you are." She's still pretty.
I'm going to reveal something. It's about Sulli's atrocities.
3-4 years ago, she was in the 5th or 6th grade.
5th grade was 3-4 years ago?
Sulli was a trainee and I just entered the practice room.
Regardless of age, the date one enters the practice room determines seniority.
6th grader Sulli comes up to me one day and I think she was annoyed.
She said, "Oppa, since I'm your senior, fetch the keys from the 3rd floor."
- Sulli?
- Yes.
I have something that shows what her mind was like at the time.
- It's her diary.
- Diary?
- About Me by Choi Jinri.
- Could you read it?
"I know I'm beautiful, but I don't know why people adore me."
Aren't people like singers beautiful?
There are many in my church that are beautiful. Why do they only adore me?
I hate that about people.
I tell them my name, and they say even my name is beautiful. Am I that beautiful?
What should we do with her?
Her diary shows how immature she is.
This is something only the haves can do which is narcissism.
We can't refute her words.
Sulli's real name is Choi Jinri, and a well-known sentence was born.
[Sulli is Jinri]
[Using Sulli's real name, this is usually used to describe her superiority]
Yong!
Yong Hwa oppa!
Hwa!
Your makeup is heavier than mine!
Next is Jo Kwon!
Jo!
I thought you were quiet.
Kwon!
But you're cocky.
She got them both in an instant.
Hi, I'm Sulli and I'm the comedian of f(x).
Not only does she have good looks, but she can make jokes.
I have a joke for you.
A dried persimmon and tiger were friends...
A dried persimmon and tiger?
They lined up to have a race.
Shots were fired and the tiger started running.
But the dried persimmon stood still and didn't run.
The tiger ran but the dried persimmon didn't?
"How come you're not running?" What did the dried persimmon say?
Can you guess?
- Oh! I'll be there soon?
- I'll be there soon. Sorry.
It's corny but people laughed. This must be the power of Sulli.
Something like, "I'll be there soon."
If I told you this joke...
You would get angry.
"Samchons" love Sulli.
I heard that Sulli never met Yang Joon-hyuk privately.
Did you really invite her? What's going on here?
I was asked who I wanted to invite...
And Sulli was...
- You picked her?
- Yes, I did.
You're her fan?
I mean she looks like an angel.
I want her on my shoulder like Tinker Bell on Peter Pan.
[To that extent?]
You have many "samchon" fans...
- I'm an "oppa", not "samchon".
- Okay, you're an "oppa".
Aren't they your father's age?
- Well, my mom is...
- What about your mom?
My mom is 42.
- Your mother is 42?
- She's friends with me then.
He's an "oppa" who's the same age as your mother. He's a great "oppa".
Do you have anything prepared for your "oppa" fan?
- A dance.
- A dance?
Without music?
- There's music.
- Alright!
[f(x) is known for "NU ABO"]
[Cute like Tinker Bell!]
[Very pleased]
It's hard for young people to do that before older people.
She's not saying it, but she must be terrified.
She must've been nervous before she came here.
Tiffany asked, "Who's your favorite girl group?"
Tiffany asked that? My favorite is f(x).
Oh? You too?
Jinri? Yes, Sulli is Jinri.
What's charming about her?
Sulli's innocence is like Kang Suji of the 90s...
Both her names are correct. Sulli will always be Jinri.
2NE1 always put on a powerful performance with strong music.
But they showed off their matured charm with an ardent song.
[Their charming voices and polished beats stand out]
[Other than the title track of their 1st mini-album, this song was also loved]
They sing about love, but YG gave a special command
- dating ban.
[Dating Ban]
[Usually given to idols prohibiting dating while active as singers]
- I think he caught us.
- Guess he's a fisher.
The dating ban was for 3 years so it should be lifted on May 17th.
But he went back on his words.
He told us no even though the date passed. I don't know what to do.
- It was a promise.
- I know.
You should date if you're 29.
Because he ties them down, they could leave every night.
- You surprised me there.
- Because he ties them down.
That means they did go out.
Sometimes I didn't see them.
- We met up with each other.
- Yeah, we went out together.
I saw them together.
[The truth is getting lost...]
[I forgot how to date]
[I completely forgot how]
[YG... please let us go...]
As they said, "YG, you're mean!" At least, let go of the two oldest.
It's based on a true story.
Lonely Dara has a secret. Let's listen to the story told by her labelmate.
She's in her late 20s and how can she not have a guy when she's pretty?
I tried to ease her lonliness.
So I introduced her to her first man.
For real?
First means there wasn't only one?
Yes, there's more.
I introduced her to the first guy, and she really liked him.
I'm not sure if he introduced him to me or not because he called.
I asked what happened and he told me to wait and I'll get a call today.
I waited but didn't get any calls.
I heard nothing. I didn't hear anything about them calling each other.
I thought maybe he wasn't the one and introduced her to the 2nd guy.
- Guy No. 2.
- Yes.
He sways many women's hearts in Korea and is Lee Seung-gi style.
He must have forgotten, but he called me again.
I said hello and CL got a strange premonition.
She took the phone from me, spoke with him and hung up.
She took care of it.
- Why did she do that?
- I mean, then...
He called and everyone knows he has a loud voice. He was like, "Noona!"
I had a strange premonition and told him to hang up.
- He was going to introduce a man?
- Yes, I had that feeling.
Why did you do that?
- Umm...
- He didn't do it for you.
I introduced Guy No. 3.
He was really determined.
In front of Dara's house...
- In front of her house?
- This is it!
He waits in front of her house for her to come out.
Dara, is this true?
I haven't confirmed it but heard that's how it was.
He mustered up the courage and went on that cold day, but you trampled on his heart.
Why didn't you go out when he was waiting for you?
I was afraid. He was enthusiastic, but I didn't know if he knew me.
I'm bright and cute on air...
Her labelmates want her to be happy. Let's wait and see if the ban gets lifted.
[We Are the Best!]
2NE1 releases their 2nd mini-album in 2011. Starting with Bom's solo, "Don't Cry"...
They had a unique promotion by releasing each track in the album as singles.
[It's a fast tempo R&B; dance song with piano melody and house beats]
[3 weeks before promotion of their album, they released each track one by one]
[The first song released was Bom's solo, and her unique voice was charming]
Just one performance of "Lonely", released as a single, it became the mutizen song.
[This song shows off 2NE1's charming voices]
[It's a slow pop song that harmonizes their unique voices, guitar sounds, and strings]
[Unlike their other songs, an analog feel stands out in this]
[This song became the mutizen song with one performance after their comeback]
[Rappers CL and Minzy were able to show their charms with singing]
"I Am the Best" topped music charts as soon as it was released.
They solidified their place as the best girl group.
[It has a fast beat that's electronic and hip-hop]
[Main features are the uniquely strong sounds and suggestive title exuding confidence]
All of these songs were in their 2nd mini-album.
We can see in "Ugly", the title track, their charm in singing various genres.
[It's an uptempo song with electronic rock sounds]
[Contrasting that is the sad feeling within]
[The hurt they received due to their ugly looks and how people view them were expressed]
[It showed their rich emotions]
f(x) also has a song in 2011 that they can't forget.
It's "Pinocchio", the title track of their first studio album.
Not only did they top the music charts with this electronic pop dance song...
They were at the top in music programs for the first time since their debut.
[With a strong, restrained beat and unique guitar sounds...]
[This electronic pop dance song harmonizes with their bouncy voices]
[The process of getting to know love was alluded to the story of Pinocchio]
[It's fun as if watching a cartoon, and their styles were in that fashion]
The process of knowing love was alluded to Pinocchio...
They showed off their colors with unique styles and made it fun like watching a cartoon.
[The members' heated contest]
[2NE1's Minzy, f(x)'s Victoria]
Out of both male and female idols, Minzy gives a powerful performance.
As the great-granddaughter of Gong Ok-jin, her blood must be flowing in her as well.
Erotic Minzy!
I'm curious about that.
- This made a huge impact.
- Can you explain?
I participated in various contests and competitions since the 6th grade.
I won a set of ribs and many other prizes, but every time I performed...
Eroticism was hidden inside.
Eroticism in dancing?
Everyone agrees and says that there's something erotic inside of Minzy.
We are witnesses to that. We always see her.
Every time she dances, her looks, eyes and movements are sexy.
Before our debut, YG gave her a sexy ban.
He said, "Don't forget that you're the youngest."
- She's born in 1994.
- She's only 16.
Other than a powerful performance, she can make any dance look sexy.
[Cartoon theme song for Dooly]
[Erotic Dooly in an instant]
[There's eroticism in Dooly]
[This is Seung-gi's ballad, "Let's Break Up"]
[Now it's an ardent ballad dance?]
[There's Erotic Minzy even in ballads!]
[Even Seung-gi's voice sounds a little erotic]
[16-year-old innocent Minzy becomes erotic when she dances]
[Even a folk song?]
[There's eroticism even in folk songs!]
[Erotic Minzy shocked them all!]
- Can you split them today?
- Yes, I can.
Please show us.
Minzy can also do the splits. My legs hurt just watching.
If 2NE1 has Minzy, f(x) has Victoria.
She has an amazing form since she studied dancing. I'm amazed every time.
Go back.
Be careful.
One, two, three!
Is she human or a swan? Victoria showed off her flexibility.
She's drinking while doing the splits. Don't be shocked. She is human.
Since when were you flexible?
Since I was born.
- Do fingers count too?
- Of course, fingers count.
How is that possible?
Makes a living by doing splits. What do you mean by that?
I can do splits because I'm very flexible.
Yes, we saw.
How far down can you go?
I attended Beijing Dance Academy.
If she got into the best dance school in China...
- It's hard to get in.
- How old were you?
I was in the 5th grade. I told my mom I have to get into that school.
I went and the instructor told me to give my leg.
It's not give your hand but give your leg?
Raised my leg all the way here. I thought, "What's going on?"
My leg was now to the side and raised all the way up.
"That's it." Then I asked, "What were you doing?"
Next, I was told to bend backwards.
- So I bent backwards.
- You were flexible from birth?
I bent backwards.
Like a folder?
Not like this but like this?
When I sleep, I'm in a split position.
You sleep in that position?
That's hard to take. That means your leg is where our arm would be.
She could use her leg as a pillow.
When I first joined SM, I couldn't speak Korean well since I'm a foreigner.
I used honorifics to everyone including Sulli.
Sulli's the youngest.
I would say, "Good night," using honorifics.
Sulli must've been terrified because she's courteous but sleeps like this.
And then?
One day, I was sleeping comfortably since I was tired.
I was in a split position over the bed with my eyes open towards Sulli's direction.
I was sleeping with my eyes open, and Sulli came over, "'Unni', are you awake?"
With my eyes open, I replied, "Huh? What?"
Sulli said, "You scared me! I thought something happened."
Afterwards, we got close.
We don't need words. Just show it to us.
- Hello, Victoria.
- Hello.
We'll start the test. Give me your leg.
Raise it up.
Good.
To the side.
Backwards.
- Bend backwards?
- Yes, just go down.
Victoria, you pass!
[Sulli wakes up]
"Unni"? Are you sleeping?
"Unni"!
What's up, Sulli?
Are you awake or...?
- I was sleeping.
- Why were you...
Victoria's flexibility showed she's a human folder. That's some talent.
- He's from "Star King".
- Oh, no! We're late.
- Hello.
[That was Victoria's flexibility!]
[2NE1's CL, f(x)'s Amber]
CL is 2NE1's charismatic leader. Her presence shines on any stage.
She even shared a stage with an artist she respects. This is rapper CL's charm.
[CL explodes in rapping]
[A meeting of two girl groups with a 30-year difference!]
[Everybody together!]
[They're going wild]
[A great meeting between Korea's singer and idol!]
CL sings well as her rapping. She sure is versatile on stage.
[It has a very slow beat at 70 BPM using the latest sounds such as dougie and dubstep]
[It's a new type of hip-hop where her strong rapping goes well together]
[She wanted to sing of a woman who is dignified and fabulous]
[It's her first solo where her charisma shined]
Amber is f(x)'s rapper with an androgynous charm.
The rap she does in her special voice is also special.
Would Amber try?
- Me?
- Really?
[Can't see the lyrics!]
[To the front!]
[To the stage!]
[Can she sing like a woman?]
[Seems like she can!]
[Amber's rediscovery!]
[She's not used to Korean yet!]
She's actually feminine, and I have proof.
Ta-da!
Doesn't she look feminine?
Umm... I'm not sure...
It's the dress. Even this is a big change for her, right?
We have another one.
Unexpected for someone with boyish looks. Why don't she appear like that on stage?
[2NE1's Dara, f(x)'s Krystal]
Dara is very silly, but she's actually hiding something.
Bom and Dara are friends?
I'm friends with Dara?
Everyone's shocked at her age.
How come we're so different?
You look older than her.
I have a baby face.
They look like idols, but she looks like a middle age singer.
Her hairdo and clothes make her look like Lee Mi-ja.
[Solbi in a dinner show style?]
I was really surprised.
How come I'm not included with them?
Then Bom and Dara are older than Lee Seung-gi?
[Can't believe they're 26!]
- How old is he?
- I'm 23.
They're "noonas" then.
Call them "noona".
Hello, "noona"...
How is he to you?
He's a cute young guy.
Go in front of her and greet her politely.
On the other hand, there's an f(x) member who's mature despite her age.
She showed off professional skills and how mature she became on "Kiss & Cry".
[As the "Queen of Lifts", what was her final lift?]
[A beautiful rotational lift]
[Krystal and Dong-hoon's Paso Doble]
[They poured all their energy into it. The birth of a masterpiece program!]
Krystal was the winner of this show.
There's another reason why she can't forget this show.
Do you like Krystal as your partner the most?
Yes, I do.
Will she still be your partner in the next life?
Yes!
Before she became my partner, I thought she was older.
- I thought she was a "noona".
- She's only 18.
Krystal trains like a Spartan.
She should just be a figure...
[She has complete trust in her partner]
I was really tired. As I was making the landing, the blade...
Grazed his throat.
- With the blade?
- Yes, but...
The blade is like a knife.
Fortunately, he felt it and stepped back.
If I had put even a little bit of force into my leg, he would've been...
That's dreadful!
It was dangerous.
There were such dangerous incidents.
Was he okay?
I asked if he was okay, but he just smiled and didn't say anything.
He didn't say he was okay and just smiled.
He got a cut and such things happened often.
They have contrasting charms but have something in common. Did you figure it out?
They each have another celebrity sibling.
Everyone knows that Krystal's sister is Jessica of SNSD.
They're the superior Jung Sisters.
Congratulations! It's because I went to cheer you, right?
I got 2nd place that day.
[I'm proud of my sister, the figure skating queen!]
Do well!
[Dara is known for doting over her brother, Cheondung]
[2NE1's Bom, f(x)'s Luna & Sulli]
2NE1's main vocalist is Bom.
She's loved in her group and as a solo artist for her unique voice.
[Bom's extremely unique voice is charming in this R&B; hip-hop]
[It's her first solo track where one can feel her rich voice and emotions]
She's really funny; someone who'll appear once every 100 years.
But she freezes on air...
But she's completely different off stage. She's a cute oddball.
Her cute image off stage is also charming.
What are your nicknames?
I have several. Oddball Bom, Bread Bom, Dopey Bom...
- What else?
- Idiot Bom.
Oh! My head...
The man who covered my mouth.
[What does it mean?]
What did he cover it with?
Maybe it was with bread.
[Since she's Bread Bom!]
It's YG. He tells me to be silent and that I'm an A-bomb when I go on air.
Did you make a mistake?
When I debuted, I filmed a cell phone commercial with Hyori and Joon-gi.
There was a press preview and a reporter asked what kind of cell phone we used.
Hyori said she's using Any___ and Joon-ki said he's switching to Any___.
Everyone was laughing.
Since they're modeling for that cell phone.
I thought I should be funny too.
I was honest and said that I used a Cy__.
Hyori's face was like this and Joon-ki didn't know what to do.
I thought the reaction was great and I felt good.
- You thought the reaction was great?
- Yes because they were laughing.
Because Lee Hyori was like this?
I deluded myself. I thought YG would compliment me.
He said, "Idiot! You're clumsy and don't do anything right!"
He scolded my manager, "You should have bought her one in advance!"
But I got in trouble again that same day.
After the press preview, Hyori asked, "Bom, why don't we have dinner together?"
I was on a diet program and had to fit into a midriff by agency standards.
I said no to her.
I said I'm on a diet and left.
Joon-ki said to me, "Lee Hyori wants to eat with you. Are you joking?"
- I was proud of myself.
- Since you kept your promise.
I proudly told that to YG and he got angry.
- "You're an idiot!"
- Why was he angry?
"Do you think Hyori wanted to go yum-yum with you?"
"She just wanted to spend time." He got angry.
Why did Lee Hyori ask you? Was there something she liked?
Maybe she liked me after I caused that trouble.
When I exited, she patted me and said, "It's okay. It's because you were innocent".
Maybe it was to scold you.
What do you think, Dara?
She's doing very good.
But she's more fun at the dorm without cameras?
Yes, it's a hundred, thousand times more fun than this.
- She's more funny?
- Yes.
- Sometimes...
- It's okay.
I can't say it.
What is it?
It's so fun sometimes we think she's crazy.
f(x)'s voice is Luna, their main vocalist.
Luna is the "Queen of Reaction".
Luna is different off stage. She's the "Queen of Reaction".
[That's how it's done]
Now it's an emotional moment.
"Honey, I love you."
[Star King
- variety show academy!]
Not only is she the MC on SBS MTV's "THE SHOW"...
To all the female viewers, I'm sitting on top of Dong-joon.
It is I, Luna, vitamin MC of THE SHOW.
- Don't gauge my weight.
- Alright, I won't.
He's not shaking but doing well.
[Luna
- f(x)'s vitamin girl!]
What will you show us?
I'm in a musical, Legally Blonde...
She made a surprise transformation as an actress in "Legally Blonde".
[Solid skills from four months of performing]
[Now the acting begins!]
[Elle Woods' boyfriend left]
[A clear and cool musical voice]
[Luna's friends]
[Elle Woods grew up on her own to be acknowledged by her boyfriend]
[She grew up even more overcoming the pain of having an image as a muscular idol]
[Going beyond being an idol, she takes on variety shows and musicals]
[All will be well]
[An explosive voice!]
[This show is cooler than before because of vitamin girl Luna!]
There's another actress in f(x) and it's none other than Sulli.
In 2012, she cut her hair to play the role of a boy in the drama "To the Beautiful You".
- It's raining. Why are you here?
- Because it's raining.
Sulli of "To the Beautiful You".
She received the New Star Award in 2012 for her role in that drama.
We look forward to this new star's future both as a singer and actress.
Hi, I'm Sulli.
Thank you for this award.
I thank Director Jun Ki-sang and the staff of "To the Beautiful You".
I thank my family that's watching this on television right now.
I'll continue to try hard. I also thank my fans.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
[Their glorious stage goes on]
f(x) showed an energetic and rhythmical stage with an electronic pop dance song.
[It's an electronic pop dance song with an addictive chorus part]
[Starting off with drum beats, such energetic and rhythmical melody is memorable]
[The feeling of falling in love is compared to the electrifying feel of being electrocuted]
[They started each line of the word "electric shock" in Korean]
[They showed off their own special lyrics once more]
[They topped all music programs and this song solidified their place]
Now we expect something different when it's f(x).
We already look forward to their next stage to satisfy that expectation.
2NE1 makes another musical transformation with an electronic trot, "I Love You".
This song was born from their wish to spread Korean culture.
[Trot was exquisitely fused to electronic music]
[It's an experimental dance song also known as electropop]
[This song honestly portrays a woman's heart longing for love but is an amateur in love]
[They take on trot and a song on confession for the first time since their debut]
[It contains their wish of wanting to show their fans around the world the most Korean song]
2NE1 gives birth to their own music as they always worry over music.
We look forward to their ever- changing and evolving music.
Subtitles by SBS International