[The Birth of a Super Rookie - Rain]
A noticeable male solo
artist appeared in 2002.
He is Rain.
He gave a strong impression with
his debut song, "Bad Guy."
[A song with heavy emphasis on hip-hop with
orchestra mixed in the intense hip-hop rhythm]
[The introductory narration of a woman as if she
was crying out and Rain's powerful voice stood out]
[He left a strong impression by showing off his
acting and flashy performance in his music video]
He was in the spotlight
as soon as he debuted.
But he didn't reach
that spot overnight.
He meets an important person who will
change his life in a chance meeting.
And that person is...
JYP!
[JYP gave birth to the noticeable
rookie singer Rain in 2002]
Introduce yourself to JYP.
- Nice to meet you?
- Same here.
- I'm JYP.
- I'm your fan!
His dance is a work of art.
Really? Let's see some art.
Rain's 2nd key to success - do not miss
any opportunity even by chance.
He showed off his dancing skills
that he had honed to JYP that day.
It was simple. I danced after saying,
"Please watch. I am confident."
I said that I'm confident
once more and sang.
I said, "Pick me since I'm confident."
I said only those three things.
Before he debuted as Rain, he entered the
gayo world as a member of Fanclub in 1998.
But he experienced a bitter failure.
He's back on stage in 2000 as
Park Ji-yoon's backup dancer.
Your backup dancer used
to be global star Rain?
- Yes.
- Really?
[Here he is]
[He was cool even back then]
- Is that correct?
- Yes, you're right.
He's a great dancer and
good at choreography.
Yes, he is.
How do you know?
He was in the 12th grade and always did
that dance behind the school stage.
- Didn't it have such moves?
- Yes, yes. That's right.
He made all those moves.
That was after "Coming-of-Age Ceremony."
He taught me the dance when I was busy.
He was afraid of me at the time.
He was?
He felt uncomfortable because I was
known for "Coming-of-Age Ceremony."
It was difficult for him to approach
me because of my looks as well.
Each person was paired with the opposite
sex and there was a hugging move.
We had to be in perfect step, but
since he was nervous and afraid...
He tried to be as far as possible.
He told me all of that later on.
When I was a dancer, my skills weren't good
enough to be a singer. My singing was bad.
So I practiced singing in
tune for 1 1/2 years.
He went through intensive training since he
lacked in singing compared to choreography.
Do it again!
He would flick me on the
head if I didn't get it right.
It was bumper-to-bumper from
Chungcheong to Seoul.
He experienced bitter failure, silently kept
his place, and waited for his day on stage.
He fills the entire stage on his own,
and his thirst for it was quenched.
Rain was a hidden gem. Not only did he make
himself known on stage, but also on TV shows.
Aren't you chugging?
When did I say that?
You dance pretty well.
Yeah, I do. I think
I dance well too.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yeah, I do.
Is she pretty?
Pretty ones, ugly ones, and
funny ones... I have a lot.
Rain is very popular especially
with older women, right?
They do this to you once in
a while because you're cute.
Not like how I'm doing, but
you must have been upset.
I wasn't upset, but
you do that a lot.
We do a radio show together
where she is the host...
I never touched you directly.
But?
She's fun and tries to be friendly saying,
"Your body's great." In a welcoming way...
"You have strong thighs"
or "Your body's great."
I think she was trying to lobby
with that skit we just did.
Rain, you're great.
He even makes the MC act like that.
Is it really his devilishness?
- What a chatterbox!
- Your mouth is the problem.
You laughing?
This is the root of Jung Ji-hoon's acting.
This is how Rain was in sitcoms.
It's okay. I have another one.
You had another one?
It's because I was annoyed.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
What a flirt.
I can't believe this!
After people got their eyes on him, Rain
transformed in "Instead of Saying Goodbye."
It's fresh seeing the big gloves, visor, lively
dance, and his trademark smiling eyes again.
[This hip-hop with a funky beat showed a
cheerful image contrasting his debut song]
[The cute dance went well with the cheerful stage,
and the visor and hockey gloves were memorable]
He swept various awards ceremony in 2002
by receiving the New Artist award...
Confirming the birth of a big
rookie in the gayo world.
I'm grateful and the three
of us are happy to be here.
New Artist for the 2002 SBS
Music Awards goes to...
New Artist goes to Rain.
Yes, it's Rain.
He debuted online in April
with "Bad Guy."
Let's hear how he feels.
I first thank JYP, my parents, and
everyone at JYPE. Thank you.
All his efforts were for this moment.
Someone dear supported his dreams.
I made two promises with my mom.
She told me to always try and take
good care of my little sister.
The first part of my dream came true
and I kept that promise with her.
The other parts need to come
true now for me to show her.
She gave me this ring and I believe she's
always with me. So I have this on always.
I made a promise with
my mom in heaven...
That I'll win the grand prize
and dedicate it to her...
When he reached the top with the name "Rain,"
the first person he thought of was his mother.
She must be looking at
him with satisfaction.
I was determined to be a proud son when she
passed away. That goal is right before me.
I'm always trying hard to
keep my promise with her.
When do you miss her?
When I eat something good.
I visited her grave with her favorite food
wishing for the movie to be a success.
I miss her when I eat something good.
Unfortunately, I didn't play my part as
the son, and I regret it as I grow older.
I never bought her clothes or a meal.
That's why I treat my father well.
[Sang Doo! Let's Go to School - 2003]
His debut as an actor in 2003
was also a success.
He released his 2nd album with the
title track "How to Avoid the Sun."
[A hip-hop R&B song with a repeating
chord progression on a groovy rhythm]
[A mix and match of retro and modern hip-hop
fashion, aviator sunglasses, and so forth...]
[Made his upgraded stage to stand out]
I wanted to imitate those moves
whenever I put on big sunglasses.
It showed off his special charisma.
Even in his next song,
"Do You Love Me or My Fame."
[The unique lyrics resenting the girl who
returned when he became famous stood out]
[JYP wrote the lyrics in 5 minutes]
[His performance shined once more with his
unique voice along the storylike song]
One year after his debut, he goes even
higher as K-pop's top male solo artist.
He shouts to the world in 2004.
[It's Raining! He soaks the world]
Just listening to the opening makes you
remember him under the spotlight.
"It's Raining" is the title
track of his 3rd album.
[It's a song fusing energetic hip-hop
beats with intense techno sounds]
[The unique interjections in the introduction
and flashy performance were memorable]
["It's Raining" means he's performing and contains
the adrenaline and excitement he feels on stage]
The choreography he poured his heart and
soul into stood out with the intense beat.
It's also one of the hit songs
his fans remember.
He completely transforms into a beaming
young man just like in his debut album.
This is the twist to his charm.
[His sweet voice confessing his
love stands out in this love song]
[His complete transformation to a softer image
that contrasted with the title track was loved]
There's another reason why
he can't forget 2004.
He won the grand prize at the year-end
awards and stood at the top in tears.
[Full House - 2004]
[A Love to Kill - 2005]
Without doubt, he became
the top male artist.
He also consolidated his position
as actor Jung Ji-hoon in dramas.
This was his heyday.
[Lincoln Center, NY]
Rain is at a special place in 2006.
He was chosen as one of
the 2006 TIME 100.
He was shoulder to shoulder
with world-famous celebrities.
[Condoleezza Rice
US Secretary of State]
[Jim Yong Kim
Harvard Medical School]
Rain appeared with sounds of roaring.
I might get the world to know more about
music and other works if I try harder.
We met with Rain in New York
who was an attendee of the event.
I'll be starting the Asia Tour
traveling to 20 countries.
After it ends in success, I will make
a foray into the US next year.
Jerry Bruckheimer showed a
great interest in Rain.
ABC also proposed to make
a documentary on Rain.
They told me they wanted to work with me
because they think I'm going to be successful.
When filming begins, it will be decisive
in helping him make a foray into the US.
I'm burdened since this is the beginning,
but I'm happy because it's a good start.
We cheer Rain whose reach
is extending to the world.
With Yuna Kim...
He is chosen again for
the 2011 TIME 100.
He's among the 100.
[Yuna Kim is 3rd and Rain is 4th!]
Some of those candidates are US President
Barack Obama, Oprah Winfrey, and Beyonce.
And there are 2 Koreans
among the Top 5.
This is the first time ever.
You attend the awards ceremony
and a party afterwards, right?
There was Jennifer Lopez
at the table I was sitting...
- America's top female artist?
- And next to me was Puff Daddy.
If you go to such an event, everyone is
busy trying to get each other's number.
Because everyone's thinking, "Who is that
person to make it into the list of 100?"
If you and Yuna Kim gets in, it's the first
time that two from Korea were picked.
She has a high chance of getting picked, but
my chances are slim since I went in 2006.
But you're also influential.
Please send her a message that you'll
be on the red carpet together.
We have two good-looking people from Korea
among the most influential people in the world.
Even if I don't make it, you have
to and I believe you deserve it.
Please make it in and bring
honor to Korea. Thank you.
[Korea produced these global stars!]
Rain was the first Korean ever to
make it in the 2006 TIME 100.
He set a record for being nominated
as a candidate for 6 years after 2006.
This was the longest record
set by an Asian star.
There was a special press conference at 2 PM.
Many reporters across the nation gathered...
With such dignity, he held an exclusive concert in
New York in 2006. The first ever by a Korean artist.
He announced his World Tour and
the release of his 4th album.
The album title was "Rain's World." It's a
notice that the world will be soaked in rain.
Since I made a comeback after 2 years,
I have prepared many things.
He will begin his World Tour starting with
Korea this Friday until the first half of next year.
It will be held 35 times in 12 countries such
as the US, Japan, China, and so forth.
With an international staff, he will put on
the best show similar to US pop stars.
After I gain some experience and
a few more performances in Asia...
I decided on the Asia Tour since I want
to make a foray into the US next year.
You need to learn the language since it's
a world tour and I heard you studied.
[He makes an introduction in English]
That's how much I studied.
He spoke English fluently during
his US concert last February.
[He spoke English fluently in a certain
interview after his concert ended]
I don't know how high I'm going to set
my goals, but I'll gladly accept failures...
And I'll continue to challenge myself
when I succeed. Please take interest.
He who enticed the world made himself
known again with another song.
The title track "I'm Coming" showed
the return of an upgraded Rain.
["I'm Coming" is the title track of
Rain's 4th album "Rain's World"]
[The repeating electronic sounds and hip-hop
rhythm harmonizes with his upgraded voice]
[Epik High's Tablo makes Rain's stage even
more powerful and makes us look forward to it]
[This song combines hip-hop rhythm
with repeating electronic sounds]
[It sounds more hip-hop due to the
rapping by Epik High's Tablo]
[Richy and AJ, choreographers to Usher and
Madonna, presented this performance to Rain]
[Rain presented a powerful stage with a song
that contains his will for the stage and future]
[I'm a Cyborg, But That's OK - 2006]
He debuted on the silver screen
as actor Jung Ji-hoon in 2006.
"I'm a Cyborg, But That's OK" was
directed by Park Chan-wook.
Let's see his skills in stealing
another person's abilities.
"Sorry for being slow."
This considerate patient
was caught by Il-soon.
"Transfer."
Does that really transfer abilities?
"Hello everyone."
It worked.
"Did you have lunch? Hello."
Il-soon became affable after
stealing that man's abilities.
"I'm sorry."
- What should I do?
- I'm tired.
Hard worker Rain met a great master and was
recognized for his acting winning Best New Actor.
The Best New Actor for the 43rd
Baeksang Arts Awards goes to...
Jung Ji-hoon.
Congratulations.
He was Il-soon, a man who thought he could steal
other's abilities, in "I'm a Cyborg, But That's OK."
Unlike his charisma as an artist,
he acted well without hesitation.
He was evaluated as expanding his
spectrum as an actor. Congratulations.
Now his acceptance speech.
Thank you. I'm nervous right now.
First, there are people that helped me
in more ways than one in this film.
I see I don't need to bend.
I thank President Hong, Mr. Jung, JYP,
Mr. Cho, Chul-hoon, and Jun-ho.
It was my dream to star in a movie.
I thank director Park Chan-wook...
He dreams of another amazing
thing as actor Jung Ji-hoon.
Thank you.
[Rain's Keyword : Hollywood]
[Hollywood]
[Active in movie production and many
directors and actors dream of it]
Directed by The Wachowskis,
the main character is Speed.
But we're interested in the meeting
between The Wachowskis and Rain.
I think I got their trust
after they saw my acting.
I also took them out for meals
and did a lot of lobbying.
"Speed Racer" was directed
by The Wachowskis in 2008.
Rain created a new history by making his foray
into Hollywood by playing the supporting role.
I want to boast about myself here.
I was the main supporting actor.
I appeared for an hour
in the two hour film.
The Wachowskis casted Rain to
"Speed Racer" and "Ninja Assassin."
They took interest in him after
watching his performance.
After they watched Rain in
"I'm a Cyborg, But That's OK"...
They were fascinated with him to
the point of being carried away.
Why do I have to
go to Hollywood?
It looks like he was lucky and
moved up in the world, but...
He had to hold back the pain he
went through in harsh Hollywood.
[Rain - the world's most famous Korean man
makes it to Hollywood as Asia's top star!]
[As a supporting actor in the film,
it was a box office hit worldwide]
[Behind the splendor of success,
no one knew of his pain and tears]
[Rain exposes the truth
about Hollywood!]
[He's cool]
When I first went to the US
to film "Ninja Assassin"...
I had this big dream, "A great director will finally
build me up. I'm going to be like Brad Pitt."
I was very weak and was always beaten up
by the neighborhood kids when I was young.
I waged a war against myself and
wanted to overcome my weakness.
My greatest battle was against loneliness
and depression, and the diet of death.
- That was severe.
- 0% body fat.
I found out the truth about
Hollywood that it's cold.
It's cold?
They first see if the person
can make them money or not.
- "Will he/she make money?"
- Is that it?
They first discuss about that.
If not then they ruthlessly
look at the next candidate.
When I went to the audition, there were
many other Asian actors under my picture.
If I was not the one, they would rip
out my picture like a calendar page.
This is a secret, but even though I
signed the contract, I can't cancel it.
But they can cancel it even
in the middle of production.
It's the same for everyone
and not only me.
Gossip can destroy an actor's career.
Can you give us an example?
In my case, when we were filming
for "Speed Racer" in the past...
Usually, after 30 minutes of filming
inside the car, you take a break.
There's a doctor on the set because your
back and other areas can get injured.
But I filmed for 4 hours.
You didn't take a break?
"Want to rest?" "It's fine.
This isn't that hard."
Everyone heard about me. The faster the
filming ends, the more money you save.
When a new actor is on a high horse
because things are going great...
Then rumors go around to
not cast that actor.
That person is cast away.
Everyone is an expendable.
After 8 long months, filming for
"Ninja Assassin" finally began.
This allowed me to take
another leap in life.
His efforts weren't a waste.
Only one lead actor was produced by
Hollywood in "Ninja Assassin" in 2009.
A new face in Hollywood had to
fight a fierce and lonely battle.
It was hard to get that sculpted body.
He was praised for his all-out effort.
His fearless passion and masculine charm
exploded on screen in "Ninja Assassin."
But...
Why fight? I might die even though I might
be a good fighter. I'd rather run away.
We heard everything about "Ninja Assassin"
through our special meeting with him.
This was a fated battle that
Raizo couldn't avoid.
He survived countless life-or-death crises
for his final confrontation with Ozunu.
The main character who fought this brutal
and lonely battle is actor Jung Ji-hoon.
Forget pop star Rain and Jung Ji-hoon.
You are a fighter now and a killer!
With the training team that created
the sculpted warriors of "300"...
He started on his goal
to reach 0% body fat.
Just one picture confirmed his hard work.
This is what 0% body fat looks like.
Rain evolved both on the stage and
screen and continues to do so.
I used to have 0% body fat.
- Wait a minute...
- 0% body fat?
- Body fat...
- 0% body fat.
Kang Ho-dong, you're out.
After training was over,
my body fat was 0.x %
That must be bad for your health.
I felt like a human weapon.
Why did you do that?
There's just one scene in the movie
where I don't even wear underwear.
You're stark-naked?
I'm doing a handstand
but not like this.
I have to go up on my own
from a sitting position.
I trained for 8 months
just for that one scene.
- Just for one scene?
- Yes, just one scene.
I lift my legs and do this.
- And you go up?
- That's right.
- Wait, let's see it.
- How is that attractive?
[8 months for this!]
[0% body fat]
I can't eat any salt or sugar.
I taste a grain of salt once a month.
You know when vampires are
dripping blood in movies?
- You desired it.
- I get passionate.
- Just from eating it?
- Yes, just from that.
The saltiness reaches my brain
and I'm just feeling it.
How detailed is the contract?
For example, I can only get a
manicure from a certain place...
I eat steak once a week that has
a certain percentage of fat.
This is an eight pack.
Such a body does exist.
As he ate salt in tears to complete
this film, it gave him another gift.
I have another good news.
There's an MTV Movie Awards.
I've been nominated for an award.
If I'm lucky, I want to be there and
say that I'm Rain from Korea.
That dream came true.
He wins the Biggest Badass Star
at the 2010 MTV Movie Awards.
You must have mastered English.
I tried very hard and
took it head on.
I worried that they might despise
me for not speaking English.
I thought that I should just do it
since I'm starting it right now.
Does it matter that I don't speak
English well? I'm Korean after all.
I told Matthew Fox, "You speak English and
I speak Korean. Our level is similar."
"But I'm a cut above since I know
more English than you know Korean."
In the racing scene, only the handle
is real and everything else is CG.
I have to pretend to jump
when I'm told to jump.
You take off your suit and rest after 30-40
minutes because your back really hurts.
But I wanted to look good. They told me
to rest, but I smiled, "One more time."
Even though I feel like I'm going to die.
I'm wet with sweat and I have rashes.
I sat down for 5-6 hours straight.
What did the director say?
- "You're tenacious."
- Tenacious?
"I know Koreans are patient..."
He was born again as a Hollywood star.
But he's dreaming of bigger things.
[Only Rain]
Together with his 5th album, Rain made
a comeback in 2008 after 2 years.
It was his first album after
setting up his own company.
He worked on every aspect of the album, and
showed an upgraded image with "Rainism."
[The title track "Rainism" is a synthpop
with strong beats based on hip-hop]
["Rainism" is a coined term adding
the suffix -ism to his name, Rain]
[It's the title track of his first album
after setting up his own company]
[He wrote the lyrics, composed, and
produced for the first time in 7 years]
[He wore a suit and used a
cane in his performance]
[It emphasized his refined and natural
masculinity, and restrained sexiness]
I didn't know a neat suit
could look this sexy.
Even a performance with a cane.
A stage that only he can do goes on.
8 years after his debut, he releases a
new album in 2008 to return to the basics.
He stirred up talk with his
shocking album cover and teaser.
The title track "Love Song" met
everyone's expectations.
[This song harmonizes strings
with acoustic instruments]
[The sad melody on top of the
piano melody was memorable]
[The lyrics are about wanting to
hold on to his lover who left]
[This is his first ballad where
his mournful voice stood out]
[The shocking album cover and the teaser
of the kissing scene with Han Ye-seul...]
[Garnered attention before its release]
This was an exceptional performance.
The moves gave birth to many parodies.
I'll do Rain's "Love Song."
[Even today]
[Mud flat abs]
[That's cute]
[The one that can hold on
to you is Prince Jumong]
[G.O is on stage with Rain
for the first time!]
[Teacher and student]
Starting with the stage of his
students surpassing the teacher...
A special performance by Puffy Rain
showing off his belly and not abs.
[Puffy Rain vs Rain]
[Perfect reenactment]
[Charisma with weight]
[Puffy Rain is feeling it]
[OMG!]
[Wow]
[A sausage?]
[Puffy Rain needs a sausage
and not a magic stick!]
[Now to the climax]
[Rain's Rainism]
[Puffy Rain's Sausagism!]
[A bite for me and you!]
[Puffy Rain will keep
you on your seats]
[Takes on the abs dance!]
[Will he?]
[Is he?]
[OMG!]
[Obese compared to Rain]
[What about your belly?]
[Please...]
[Teuk Academy brings laughter]
[Standing ovation]
[Going wild]
Intense music and performance by Rain
continues in "Hip Song" as well.
[It's a song with intense beats
and a repeating synth rhythm]
[He presents another powerful performance
with a dance track mixing various genres]
Rain's performances reminds you
of his flashy choreography.
Out of all these choreographies,
which did he choose as the best?
Let's choose the best
three of your dances.
3rd is "How to Avoid the Sun."
Since this is the guitar melody,
I feel sleepy if I don't sing.
When I heard that's the title track,
I didn't know what to do with it.
I thought of finishing it off by singing
very well and with my appearances.
My moves were restrained as if I was going
to show something, and I ripped my clothes.
2nd is...
I once did a pop dance.
It's not from my album
but on a variety show.
- That choreography?
- Yes, it was 30 seconds.
The 30 seconds that introduced
dancing machine Rain to the world.
I made up that dance to go on the show.
I made it really intense but short.
It was called the three step dance
since it's divided into three beats.
That's when the opening of every
show started with a dance.
- It was.
- I know.
It was the most memorable.
And 1st is...
Rainism.
[He did everything on his own since 2007
and did everything alone on "Rainism"]
You know this dance?
I made it while goofing off.
I just put a wave in the clap
giving it some feel.
Just did it?
I made a fist to look wild and tough,
but I can't do this, right?
This is worthy to be one of the best.
But he didn't shine only in dances.
I remember Rainism and
its moves the most.
Another charming thing about his
voice is when he sings ballads.
Let's rank his ballads.
[Ranking - ballads that hold on to you]
Ballads that hold on
to you by Rain.
The sad lyrics stood out
in "Familiar Face."
"Only You" contains the musical
colors that he wanted to show.
"In My Bed" was memorable in that
it was like a scene from a musical.
[It's an R&B song with descriptive lyrics
portraying the sadness towards one's lover]
[The key here is his matured
voice and honest lyrics]
The twist to "Bad Guy" is "Handshake"
where his mournful voice stands out.
Rain can't forget that day. "Sep. 12th"
and "Love Story" are his No. 1 ballads.
[The Rain Story Continues]
Rain gives his fans a special gift in his
last concert before serving his country.
It's a unique single titled "Busan Woman"
named after the place he held his first concert.
["Busan Woman"]
[Rain's final nationwide tour
before going to the army]
[He released this single along
with "The Best Show"]
[This was titled after Busan, the first place
he held his concert in his nationwide tour]
[The title changed according to the city
and was only done during this concert]
With top actresses...
It doesn't have to be a Busan woman.
He's known for being blessed with women.
The top actresses that worked
with actor Jung Ji-hoon!
I remember Min-ah the most.
- Shin Min-ah?
- Yes.
We did many retakes because
it was very intense.
They were stopping you,
but you kept on going?
[How intense was it?]
It was really cold.
I didn't feel ashamed
because it was really cold.
I wanted to finish it quickly without
a retake and I think she did too.
They went, "Ready. Action!" I drove her
to a corner and made it really serious.
So...
The staff tried to separate you?
The one editing it told me, "You know
you made a lot of smooching sounds."
[OMG]
The sound was...
Should we do the ideal
woman World Cup?
[Starting at the quarterfinals!]
Whoever comes to mind, okay?
Song Hye-kyo or Han Ye-seul?
It can't be longer than
3 seconds. One, two...
But if you're silent, that
means you hate them both.
Song Hye-kyo or Han Ye-seul.
One, two, three!
Song Hye-kyo.
Wasn't Han Ye-seul in
your music video?
But you picked Song Hye-kyo. You
knew after you filmed with her?
[OMG!]
Shin Min-ah or Im Soo-jung?
- One, two, three!
- Im Soo-jung.
- You never worked with Shin...
- Yes, he did. In dramas.
He knows because he already did.
He got to know them, huh?
He did a music video
with Han Ye-seul.
He also filmed in dramas but
knows because he did it. Is it?
No, I...
Jeong Ga-eun or Park Kahi?
They're right here.
After School's leader Park Kahi
is 1980 and Jeong Ga-eun is 1978.
[A battle between noonas!]
Jeong or Park?
One, two, three!
Park Kahi.
Because she's a year younger?
Jung Joo-ri or Kim Hyo-jin?
This is going to be tough.
I don't want to lose.
[Me neither]
[He's troubled]
Kim Hyo-jin.
[She's touched]
Now the semifinals.
Song Hye-kyo or Im Soo-jung?
Im Soo-jung.
It's still the semifinals.
Park Kahi or Kim Hyo-jin?
Let's say that she's not married.
Park Kahi.
- You won't part yet.
- There was no tension.
Im Soo-jung or Park Kahi?
One, two, three!
Im Soo-jung.
Why is she your ideal woman?
How am I different from her?
- I'm dumbfounded.
- Yeah, you're twins.
You two look so alike.
Yeah, you look alike.
Thought you didn't know.
She's very considerate
and humorous.
She spreads this happy virus.
I had fun while working with her.
You know there are many
celebrities on our show.
Yes.
Uee said her ideal man is Rain.
Really?
Hold on.
[I'm nervous]
[He's now a matchmaker!]
Give it to me if
you're not doing it.
Hurry!
Hello?
- Hello.
- I'm Uee...
Glad to meet you. I'm
watching your group.
- What is he watching?
- Thank you.
Everyone's pretty and
your songs are great.
Do you know our songs?
I know "Diva."
I debuted with that song.
Congratulations for doing well and
I'll continue to listen to your songs.
Could you sing our...
I'm your fan.
He made Uee nervous with a phone call.
We acknowledge his blessing of women.
What's his charm for
captivating women?
[Global star's footwork]
His very existence emits an
aura that fills the entire stage.
[Brilliant]
His hidden talents as an entertainer
and human side are also his charms.
I can't do the recording.
Why can't you?
He has 3 stages of anger.
First stage is...
Don't look.
- Pretend he's not there.
- Wait! Hold on here.
Listen to my side later.
He has a characteristic. First,
he gives advice through allusion.
"You don't want to practice. You feel sleepy?
Do you know why the Red Hare runs straight?"
"It has blinders on!"
He gives advice through allusion.
Second, he loses his temper
and stamps his feet in rhythm.
"Why aren't you practicing?
Sleep only when you're dead!"
One famous saying after another.
Third, he's like, "Don't greet me."
- He gets cold.
- "Just leave."
That's it.
- He must have been really angry.
- But that happened recently.
- I can't really talk about it.
- You already said it all.
Are you afraid since you said it?
It's okay with you, Rain, right?
- It's okay.
- What he said.
But there's no 2nd album.
As you just saw, Ji-hoon isn't cool.
Rain's final concert before going to
the army was held on September 25th.
It's been a while. I'm Rain.
Rain left temporarily for
military duty in 2011.
He gave a special gift to his
fans by holding a unique concert.
I'm filled with emotion and only those
that didn't attend will feel slighted.
We won't leave you.
We love you Rain!
He sure is a global star with many
fans from around the world.
They won't leave him, right?
It's okay if you cheat on me
because I'm a cool guy.
But return in two years.
Even though you leave, return
in two years and all is well.
There was commotion right
before the concert started.
- It's because of the stars.
- Wow! It's MBLAQ.
The concert begins with
Rain's flashy entrance.
[Fans waited for this!]
[This is Rain God!]
He overwhelms the stage
with his entrance.
He sure made the fans go wild.
- Doing well?
- Yes.
- You want this?
- Throw it here!
He first thanked his fans. A buzz
cut on him seems a bit awkward.
Hello everyone.
Thank you for coming.
I feel sorry for causing all
this noise before leaving.
I'll be back soon. Thank you.
He showed his buzz cut to his fans
as a sign of gratitude for coming.
He's been on stage for 10 years,
but this must have been awkward.
It wasn't easy for him to speak
and ended it with a salute.
Thank you for coming and for
your love the past 10 years.
I'll be back.
Did he get emotional? He was teary-eyed and
didn't speak anymore. It made his fans sad.
His longtime friend Bbaek Ga finally showed
tears as well as the fans. It was a sea of tears.
Cheer up. I love you.
I'll wait for you.
Rain left amidst heartwarming
farewells from his fans.
The story of this man who promised to
return continues and will come soon.
People say if there's anything
else that you can do.
- There's so many things?
- What do you want to do?
I want to act in China and Japan
in their respective languages.
I want to be the supreme in the US
and go to the Grammy and The Oscars.