Star Documentary Kpop Hero
[The Birth of Young Artists]
U-KISS first made an appearance in
the gayo world in September 2008.
They stood on their first stage
with a boyish song "Not Young."
[This song is sending a message to people
around them that treat them like kids]
[Dirty South school of hip-hop was changed into a
Korean style with a piano line and catchy melody]
[They were the first idol group
to present such a genre]
[As a multinational idol group, this
debut song showed off their colors]
"I Like You" was released next.
They presented a unique stage with outfits
and hairstyle recalling 1990s boy bands.
[1990s old pop feel was
mixed in a new way]
[The repeating lyrics and melody on
top of the hip-hop rhythm made it catchy]
[In the style of the most popular
1990s boy band, NKOTB...]
[The retro outfits, hairstyle, and
accessories made it nostalgic]
They are a multinational group with members
from the US, Hong Kong, and China.
Hello. We're U-KISS.
Why are you called U-KISS?
Doesn't it mean "You kiss"?
- It's a bit long.
- Really? How?
Interpretation?
Did you get that? That's
what U-KISS stands for.
That's nothing for a multinational group.
Both Dongho and Soohyun did well.
B.A.P made themselves known on a reality show
with a unique concept on aliens invading Earth.
We are B.A.P! Yes, sir!
That was a rabble.
- One more time.
- Edit that.
One more time.
Look over there.
We are B.A.P... quietly.
We are B.A.P. Yes sir.
[What are you doing?]
Begin. We are B.A.P! Yes sir!
Wow! That was good.
Do what we just did.
One, two, three!
- We are B.A.P!
- That's a wrap.
The interview was a bit awkward...
[Many fans came...]
But many fans went wild
even before they debuted.
With all that interest, they successfully
finished a large-scale showcase.
How was the scale?
It was a big stadium with 3,000 seats
where we held our showcase.
It was huge.
What did you think of the
choreography for "Warrior"?
Umm... I felt it was intense.
Zelo too.
They made an impressive debut on January 2012
with a strong message in the song "Warrior."
[A new genre adding krumping and
rock to a strong hip-hop beat]
[With a strong message of changing the
conflicts that began with human nature...]
[B.A.P's leader, Bang Yong Gook, took part in
composing and showed their own intensity]
[Zelo's 16 syllable per second rapping in the
middle known as "LTE rapping" drew attention]
[The stage and outfits went with the strong mood
and they dyed their hair blonde for solidarity]
BTOB debuted in March of that year.
Formed by Cube Entertainment, producers
of B2ST and 4minute, they drew attention.
"Insane" is a dance song, but the lyrical
vocals and refined melody stood out.
[Magnificient strings and refined melody
on top of a sentimental piano line]
[Their lyrical vocals and rapping
stood out in this debut song]
[The song was custom-made to
maximize their vocal appeal]
[A 28 member orchestra and performance
that went with the mood stood out]
BTOB had something else that
differentiated them from others.
[They Have Something Special]
BTOB first presented a dance song,
but their dance song is special.
That distinction can also be seen in
"Irresistible Lips" from their special edition.
It's a dance song, but a
mournful voice can be felt.
Behind the fancy melody is
the members' singing.
[The lyrics of feeling gratitude for one's
family went with the lyrical melody]
[We could hear their captivating voice in
this special single made for Parents' Day]
[A cappella for the festive mood]
[Even the rapper's singing.
What's Peniel doing?]
[Conductor Peniel]
[Mood Change]
[You better watch out - Why?
You better not cry - Why?]
[Santa Claus Is Coming to Town]
[Santa Claus is coming to town]
[Why is he coming?]
[Their sweet Christmas melody]
[So be good for goodness sake]
[Really?]
[The power of cake
makes them to sing]
[The ending of this sweet song is?]
[One more time]
[Santa Claus is coming to town]
Not only their singing, but each
member also plays an instrument.
All-around entertainer Hyunsik plays
the bass guitar like a professional.
Since the planning stage,
BTOB started as a band.
Thus it's possible for them to switch
back and forth from dance to band.
Will we see a BTOB band
someday? I hope so.
[We finally meet]
[You changed a lot
since we last met]
[Are those Earthling clothes?]
Welcome to Earth.
B.A.P attracted with an alien concept before
their debut, but they have another symbol.
It's a masked rabbit called "Matoki"
appearing at showcases and music videos.
The cost is in the hundreds of thousands,
and it's very big and heavy.
Cute characters appear once in a while
and this is B.A.P's other face.
B.A.P is an unprecedented group that
debuted with a strong warrior image.
It reminds me of the time
when I was a warrior.
B.A.P's distinct features
continue in their next song.
"Power" contains a warning against
the irrationalities of society.
[It's a hardcore hip-hop mixing intense
hardcore rock with hip-hop sounds]
[Standing up to the strong that habitually
tyrannizes with power and money...]
[It contains a message for
the weak to fight back]
[A grand orchestra, chorus, and
B.A.P's intensity stood out]
[A unique performance utilizing
spray cans was memorable]
The performance was intense and unique
using spray cans in the choreography.
Powerful voices went with the mixture
of hardcore rock and hip-hop sounds.
It showed the real worth
of this peculiar rookie.
Even Soohyun recognizes
B.A.P's charms and so do I.
The same goes for U-KISS.
They started as a fresh boy band,
but one song made a huge impact.
"Man Man Ha Ni" is the title track
of their third mini-album.
It became one of their hit songs with strong
hip-hop sounds on top of electronica.
[It's a catchy song mixing the intense hip-hop
sounds of gangsta rap with electronica]
[Their masculine charms were made
prominent with a bad guy concept]
[Straightforward lyrics and restrained
performance were memorable]
[U-KISS had a bright image
since their debut but...]
[This became one of their most loved songs
where they succeeded in their transformation]
[Kiseop joined them with this song
turning them into a seven member group]
U-KISS returned as strong men.
The so-called Gangnam Dance, bending
the shoulders back, was impressive.
Everyone started dancing.
[Gangnam Dance!]
[Gets every move!]
["Man Man Ha Ni" in rasgueado]
[Naturally gets exciting...]
[They can dance to this...]
[Exciting!]
Lively boy band U-KISS undergoes
a complete metamorphosis.
Their next songs stress on powerful dances
and melody, but the voice is still appealing.
"Neverland" is the title track of their 2nd
album pursuing harmony and not auto-tune.
They showed their colors in every song
that seem the same but are always evolving.
[It's a fusion song with house
added to a disco driving beat]
[Instead of auto-tune, they did
it manually for vocal harmony]
[The vocal emotions stood out in
the strong melody and performance]
[They showed their colors again
while presenting a mysterious charm]
But U-KISS changes clothes in 2012.
[Their Perfect Transformation]
U-KISS returns with "0330"
a sad hip-hop with lyrical melody.
They that showed off strong masculinity,
returned as men singing of sad love.
Their voices were more stable
and rapping had beat.
[It's a sad hip-hop with a lyrical piano
melody reminding one of rain sounds]
[The sad heart of a man longing for
the woman he broke up with was...]
[Expressed well with a stable
voice and rapping that had beat]
[They presented an upgraded stage
with the addition of AJ and Hoon]
["0330" represents 3:30 AM and they released
a teaser at that same time on March 30th]
They changed into an autumn person
in "Someday" and "Stop Girl."
We can feel their charm in going
back and forth between genres.
B.A.P showed their power
as strong warriors.
They also transformed in
the summer of 2012.
"Crash" is a cute song comparing
a boy in love to an accident.
It was a big change
for these warriors.
[Based on British rock, it's leavened
with new colors leaning towards a band]
[The dist guitar and synth sounds
added to the excitement]
[The lively lyrics compared a boy
in love to a full-scale accident]
[B.A.P shed their strong image
and changed into cute boys]
They released "Stop It" in October.
They temporarily cast aside their warrior
image reinterpreting 1990s dances.
[A simple melody and lyrics full
of aegyo harmonized in this song]
[They reinterpreted popular 1990s dances]
[Using voice samples and melodies
used most often at the time...]
[They expressed it in detail and did a
wonderful reconstruction of 1990s sounds]
BTOB also chose a retro dance song.
They returned in the fall of 2012 with "Wow"
in new jack swing, popular in the 1990s.
[The popular new jack swing of the 1990s
was reinterpreted in a trendy fashion]
[The addictive melody and
bouncy lyrics stood out]
[World-renowned producer Teddy Riley
who spearheaded new jack swing...]
[Praised BTOB highly for their new jack swing
on his social media which drew attention]
["Wow" is the title of the song and
can be heard throughout the song]
[It was taken from the improvisation
Ilhoon made during the recording]
The extension of the retro sounds
of "Wow" is "I Only Know Love."
It wasn't exciting but was a special
dance song with nostalgic sounds.
[It's an extension of the 1990s retro
sound of the title track "Wow"]
[The sentimental lyrics of the time that
went with the retro sounds stood out]
[BTOB's transformation into
romantic guys was also charming]
[The title was made by Ilhoon]
Let's explore their charms.
[Exploring Group's Charm and Keyword]
Let well-proportioned Jessica try.
U-KISS took active roles on variety
shows and not only on stage.
And there's a member who
threw a strong punch.
What's your charm?
The real Jessica is here, but
I have more aegyo than her.
[Her aegyo dance!]
[They're suspicious!]
[Goes to Ho-dong!]
You're doing well.
Let's see who you are.
[Kevin - 20-year-old male]
Jessica... I mean Kevin, has
looks that can be deceiving.
Was his powerful dance
a twist to his charm?
[I'm Kevin from U-KISS]
- He looked pretty.
- He sure was.
Rookies are off the hook for
masquerading as a woman.
But everyone in BTOB did it.
[Woman No. 1 with an
hour glass figure]
[Time to depart to the
Love and Hate Village!]
[Women No. 1-3 get
their name tags]
[Joined forces to trick
their members]
Let's go to the Love and Hate Village.
[A sad reality]
Introduce yourselves.
I'm Gangnam Woman No. 1
from Cheongdam-dong.
You must've been surprised at the
size of my breasts, but they're natural.
I'm a pretty young woman
who developed quickly.
They're really pretty.
Hello, I'm from Chicago.
You must've been surprised at
my teeth, but it's due to Xylitol.
I'm 20 years old
with an open mind...
I'm strangely being drawn to them.
Which one caught my attention?
I'll personally call them.
[Contest to speak in a high tone]
[Towards a high note]
BTOB reveals their hidden charms and
artistic talents on their reality show.
Ready?
I'll see your ugly face.
Start!
Huh?
[Sungjae took 1 second!]
[How can he not look humiliating?]
[What happened?]
[He didn't break through the
plastic wrap, but the frame...]
[Broke into pieces]
[Rolling in laughter]
They have a bright future with such sacrifice.
They truly are prominent young people.
Follow me... to our room.
- What?
- Our room.
They showed they're straightforward
image on their reality show.
- We'll see him naked.
- Yup, naked.
- Let's go! Nude, nude, nude!
- Let's go! Let's go!
How are we going to
move in on Young Jae?
We are here to move
in on Young Jae.
[What are you doing?]
He isn't surprised.
It's down there.
[He's diligent]
[Emergency - his pants ripped
while he was into the acting]
We're going to a press conference
and he ripped his pants.
This is a big accident. Show us.
We're going to a press conference, but
he ripped his pants while goofing off.
- We're going in 5 minutes.
- This is no laughing matter.
It looks like we're laughing
and joking around, but...
He caused an accident
and is eating?
He ripped his pants after
saying, "Where is it?"
[His partner Jong Up is bright]
The day Him Chan can't forget.
We guess first?
[They begin without
choosing who goes first]
[Discord]
[Helter-skelter]
[Answer - Army]
[Chaos]
Salute? Salute?
Untouchable! The place
the Untouchable went.
We can't hear.
One, two, three!
Untouchable!
Army! Army!
[Untouchable went to the
army in August 2011]
One, two, three! #$@#@%$%
Steamed buns!
[How did they know?]
[Spider Man]
- Thwip, thwip.
- Spider Man
[Exhausted]
Victory!
- Sorry, you failed.
- Excuse me?
[Cold]
Why?
You have to get 20 right.
Since you failed, you move backwards
according to the number on the dice.
Get 1.
How can you just throw it?
[They have to get a low number]
[What is B.A.P's fate?]
[Fail]
[Punishment]
They fought against wind and fear
but are back to square one.
You have to complete the mission.
But if you make a deal with us...
We'll accept your deal if
you succeed in the mission.
- Wait! Let us discuss first.
- Come over here.
Choose three representatives.
The three of us will do it
since we didn't get a chance.
[Yong Gook, Young Jae, Zelo
against the production crew]
The game is roshambo.
[Confident]
We have the three most
beautiful women on MTV.
[Battle begins]
[Young Jae attacks]
[Counterattack]
[Tense and nervous]
[Safe]
[Attack successful]
[Cheer]
[Roshambo]
[Production crew attacks]
[Young Jae's speed attack]
[Production crew isn't easy]
[Change attack pattern]
[Slow attack]
[Festive mood]
- You're really good.
- I can't believe it.
[Will it end?]
[The production crew won't step back
and pulls out an ace from their sleeve]
[I'll win, right?]
[Roshambo]
[It's ominous]
[First attack decides it]
[Happy and sad]
[Yong Gook's turn]
[Passionate attack]
[Loud and no attack power]
[Disappointment]
[Two straight losses]
[Sweeping upturn]
[Zelo - their last hope]
[Tense]
[Will Zelo win?]
[It won't end like this]
[Attacks without difficulty]
[Loses without counterattacking]
Even with Young Jae,
they lost but did well.
This is their charm. Let's
look at their keyword.
[Investments]
[There are investment pros
hiding amongst U-KISS]
One celebrity is knitting modestly in
the waiting room. It's none other than...
Dongho of U-KISS that returned
as men with "Man Man Ha Ni" but...
This? It's fun.
He's been doing it for two years.
His hand movements are really something.
High school girls usually do this.
How did he get into it?
As we move by car, I used
to play games or read books.
But I got dizzy and car sick.
I thought of what to do and...
We asked a knitting expert
on his knitting skills.
He's good. He didn't master any
techniques yet but has good form.
His hobby is unusual. He's a master at
detailed needlework but has another hobby.
I first went to the bank.
- Bank?
- Yes.
I searched my name and up
came several accounts.
I withdrew every money
in all my accounts.
I sold all my stocks and ELS...
- Stocks?
- You had stocks?
I got it all in cash. The feeling
of freedom and all that cash...
I felt I had everything. I was happy
and regretted not lying low earlier.
I went to Seoul Station and booked a room for
a week at the most luxurious hotel in Busan.
Why Busan of all places?
I don't know. I wanted to see the ocean
and Busan was the only place I knew.
You know ELS but don't know
there's an ocean in Incheon?
ELS saved Dongho who
ran away from home.
I made that remark
because he's cute.
When money comes in...
There's another expert of
investments in U-KISS.
I put it in another account
to forget about it quickly.
I took 4-5 years to
purchase a house.
Kiseop's know-hows.
10% of $1,000 is allowances.
Then you have $900 left.
You divide the rest into 3 accounts.
$300 here, $300 here, and $250 here.
You'll save money with his info.
He sure is an investments idol.
[Dialect]
[B.A.P used dialect in one of their
songs receiving a positive response]
- What is this?
- Where are you from?
What are they doing?
Why are they hugging?
I guess it's an adult program.
[Belittling one of their member's acting,
Dae Hyun and Jong Up are having fun]
Maybe it's an adult film.
Dae Hyun's dialect was hidden by the mike.
B.A.P used dialects in one of their songs.
Him Chan gave the idea for "No Mercy,"
a crossover song with "samul nori."
They rapped in dialects also
known as a "man's rap."
Their leader, Yong Gook, partook
in composing and gave birth to it.
[A rock riff was grafted on to
the powerful hip-hop rhythm]
[With their uniquely strong message, the sounds
of drums, claps, and feet were memorable]
[Him Chan, a graduate of Gukak National High
School, gave the idea to crossover samul nori]
[As a crossover song, it drew attention when they
went on stage with an actual samul nori group]
[Traditional Korean instruments
were grafted into the moves]
[Jong Up's solo performance was
as if he was twirling a sangmo]
First is the Gyeongsang dialect.
Next is the Jeolla dialect.
The Korean dialects are a native language
of Korea, but it's not used as much.
We wanted to show how it's a cool language
depending on how we express it musically.
Having a member from
Gyeongsang Province helped.
"I'll kick your @$$" in
dialect would be...
That's unique. What about a
dialect from another region?
[Cutie]
[A BTOB member actually
started the cutie song]
1+1 is cutie. 2+2 is cutie.
3+3 is... cutie.
The aegyo Bible that swept
everyone is "1+1 is cutie."
But did you know that a BTOB member
gave birth to this Korean aegyo?
It's this member who was
featured in G.NA's song.
It's BTOB's Ilhoon.
1+1 is cutie and 2+2 is cutie.
What about 5+5?
Wait! There's also 3.
3+3 is cutie. 4+4 is cutie...
Cutie song by the creator. Let's
explore deeper into their charms.
[Exploring Members' Charms]
Soohyun is the main vocalist of U-KISS.
His talents, recognized even by the
originator, can also be seen in musicals.
There was 1st generation musical actor
Nam Kyung-eub, and idol singer Soohyun...
Even actress Lee Hyun-jung who is
talented in dance, singing, and acting.
Their passion, dance, and singing come
together to produce this fantastic stage.
I'm Soohyun of U-KISS playing the role of
Mark. It's my first time doing a musical.
First, I want to do
well in the chorus.
I want to do my best, and U-KISS
is also preparing our next album.
Our single will come out in October.
While active in Korea, we will hold concerts
and fan meetings in Southeast Asia...
With Soohyun making the first start, Kevin,
Hoon, and Kiseop also took roles in musicals.
We look forward to U-KISS
as musical actors too.
Kevin, Eli, and AJ formed
a sub-unit called uBEAT.
With Eli and AJ's low pitched rap and Kevin's
sweet voice, they gave a different charm.
[It's a slow tempo hip-hop
leavened with R&B]
[As a sub-unit, Eli and AJ's low pitched
rap went well with Kevin's sweet voice]
[It's about the sad heart of lovers
going through a breakup]
[They have a different
charm from U-KISS]
Don't you get a warning for
having your skirt that short?
- No, I don't.
- You don't?
- What's your name?
- It's Shin Dongsoon.
[Maybe Dongho passed out]
Not only in singing, but Dongho was also
active in variety shows and as an actor.
He's the youngest member of U-KISS.
- How old are you?
- I'm 18 years old.
You look mature now.
I haven't seen someone as mature
as him in the waiting room.
The day I've been waiting
for is almost here.
What day is it?
After this year's birthday,
I'm getting my ID card.
Oh, you don't have one.
He's now getting his ID card and
I talked with him about my problems.
I want to get a driver's license.
There's a place where you
drive to buy things.
- A drive-thru.
- Yes, a drive-thru.
But I always take the taxi...
He later told how he got his license.
Did you go to McDonalds first?
Zelo's the youngest
member of B.A.P.
That's so cute!
- One, two, three!
- That's mine!
One, two, three!
Zelo's a cute guy loved by his
fans and the other members.
He was on stage before his debut.
He was on stage with Yong Gook as
Bang and Zelo before debuting in B.A.P.
Bang and Zelo? They
had such a group?
[It's a song in a fresh genre
called gospel hip-hop]
[Bang Yong Gook's low pitched rap and
Zelo's high pitched rap went strangely well]
[It contains a message of hope]
[Korea's best Black gospel group, Heritage,
was featured with their impressive voices]
[Yong Gook and Zelo stood on
stage before their debut in B.A.P]
Singing and dancing well
isn't enough these days.
Him Chan was known as the MC for
MTV's "The Show" before his debut.
You don't need to pay attention to what
I'm saying but what I said here is right.
That's right.
The next MC of "The Show" after Him Chan
were Sungjae and Minhyuk of BTOB.
Eunkwang was also the MC
of "Studio C" on SBS MTV.
As people look forward
to Studio C...
He came here on horse.
His elaborate skills as former MC.
BTOB... umm...
Is... is good.
But his charm is his singing.
He's the leader and main vocalist,
and also took a role in a musical.
He's a really charming guy.
[Their Shining Stage Continues]
The powerful dances of U-KISS continues
in their 6th mini-album "DoraDora."
They presented their masculinity with a
funky beat and a right mix of dubsteps.
[A powerful dance song with a funky
beat and a right mix of dubsteps]
[The melodic progression of the song
went well with their unique voices]
[A constant relationship with composer
Kim Hyung-suk gave birth to this song]
[He found a concept and finalized
it after seeing them on stage]
[Not only their strong masculinity, but they
changed girl groups' wave into their style]
[They were appealing with sexy moves]
After 1 1/2 years, "Standing Still" was
the title track of their 3rd album in 2013.
By trying out progressive house for
the first time in Korean music...
They showed off their advanced style.
[With lyrical acoustic guitar sounds and
progressive house, it's a first in Korean music]
[It contains the cry of a man looking towards
the woman who closed her heart to him]
[After 1 1/2 years, you can find out how
their music advanced from their album]
U-KISS is growing and
their stage is changing.
We hope they will captivate more in an intense
and emotional way with their special stage.
As the rising stars of K-pop, they're raising
the status of K-pop all around the world.
They're especially popular in South America
and successfully ended their concert there.
They're the first Korean artists to form a
fan club that combines all of South America.
We can feel musical maturity
from B.A.P as well.
They released "Rain Sound"
from their mini-album in 2013.
This sentimental hip-hop
was pre-released.
But the music video that cost
hundreds of thousands drew attention.
[A sentimental hip-hop grafting hip-hop
on to a melancholy acoustic guitar riff]
[This song was pre-released before
their 2nd mini-album went on sale]
[They acted with emotion in their
blockbuster-level music video]
Next was their title track "One Shot."
They returned to their colors with
hip-hop containing their message.
[A song with an intense hip-hop beat
and a touch of orchestral sounds]
[It contains their colors with a message to
take chances that come and burn with passion]
[The song was more appealing due to
their powerful and original performance]
B.A.P swept the New Artist Award after
their debut and became rising stars.
We'll stand by until the day they
are born again as the best heroes.
After their debut, B.A.P won
every New Artist Award.
They successfully finished their concerts in
the US and Japan with more than 10,000 people.
They showed off their potential as
the next generation K-pop hero.
Today is a very important day.
I'm making my 2nd confession
to the same woman.
A year after their debut in 2013...
BTOB presented their single "2nd Confession"
which had a different feel from before.
They accented their song and put more
strength into singing and rapping.
[Wanting to return to the
woman he broke up with...]
[It's a confession song with
witty lyrics titled "2nd Confession"]
[The soft melody and narration
in the beginning was memorable]
[Danny Ahn of g.o.d is their role model
and he appears in their music video teaser]
[This single was prepared for their
fans a year after their debut]
[Following their concept of music to be heard,
they stressed on singing and rapping]
With skills and talents, we look to the day
they grow as a group different from the rest.
BTOB successfully had their
first fan meeting in Taiwan.
They had a fan meeting with 1,000 fans in
Cambodia where the Korean wave started.
We have expectations for them.
Subtitles by SBS International