Star Documentary Kpop Hero
[G-Dragon's Birth as a Solo Artist]
BIGBANG is k-pop's greatest hero.
Their stage has no equal and everyone
knows their leader, G-Dragon.
He's very talented with
an unusual past.
I like to dance anywhere...
When I go to amusement parks,
well-known ones in Korea...
There's always a dance festival and
my mom makes me to participate.
- I hated that when I was young.
- She did that because you were good.
"Anyone come up." Then several
of us go up and dance.
Must have been fun.
- You must have won many prizes.
- I used to do that too.
Okay... well, I went every week
and I won every time I went.
- Your mother was really...
- House must have been filled.
I think I was 7 when we
went to a ski resort.
The MC was Lee Soo-man.
- It must be a long time ago.
- Yes, he was the MC.
I won the festival and
went to his agency.
I first got into SM. After 5 years
of training, I switched to YG.
G-Dragon was recognized
by all the heads.
He's been building up his
own stage since he was young.
Unlike his age, his stage manners
and talents were different.
[Kwon Ji-yong, 19]
Hi, I'm G-Dragon.
I'll do my best.
[Kwon Ji-yong born in 1988]
[Skills: rap, dance, beatbox,
composition, English, Chinese]
[Favorite artists: Jay-Z, Omarion]
When it's absolutely perfect, I don't
know how many years it'll take but...
That is when I can show
something great to people.
Since I must do better before I debut,
I don't think 6 years is a waste.
Kwon Ji-yong will be the leader
of this group in this project.
He already signed up because
of his exceptional skills...
But looking at the mischief in his eyes,
he's the same when he came here 6 years ago.
When I see him, I can tell what
good dancing and singing is.
He has exceptional skills in singing,
rapping, and dancing that people envy.
His peers recognize that as well.
Since he prepared longer than others,
he thirsts to debut as a singer even more.
Since I was here longer
than others for 5-6 years...
If we debut together and
our album isn't a success...
If it becomes a dud, I would be
more disappointed than them.
The door of success opens
only to those that knock.
He doesn't sit and wait for
the day he dreamt to come.
He's a perfectionist
who's hard on himself.
He realized he had to push himself
harder the more desperate he is.
[Kwon Ji-yong born in 1988]
[Skills: rap, dance, beatbox,
composition, English, Chinese]
[Favorite artists: Jay-Z, Omarion]
[Debuted in Hip-Hop Flex 2001]
[Took part in "2001 KOREA",
Perry's "Storm"]
[YG Family's "Hip Hop Gentlemen"
and "YMCA Baseball Team"]
[Currently under YG Family]
After many years, he became a member
of one of the best groups, BIGBANG.
He didn't shine only with his group.
His long-awaited solo album
was finally released in 2009.
His first solo album had much
interest even before its birth.
"Heartbreaker" is the title track.
His song and stage gave a strong
impression and met their expectations.
[The strong beat and performance went
well with the intense intro narration]
[It was No. 1 on live music charts
20 minutes into its release]
[It took first on every site even before
its official television broadcast]
[He had a radical makeover with
blond hair and heavy makeup]
[It's the title track of his 1st solo album
released on August 18th, his birthday]
With his fans' fervent support,
he was welcomed as a solo artist.
The specialty that only he can convey
can be found throughout his song.
He swept various music charts as soon
as his first solo album was released.
The radical image as a blonde
and his charismatic stage...
Is a different image from
when he's with BIGBANG.
Many people say my rap
sounds chewy...
I thought the same!
That's right.
Instead of just saying it, I think
I brood over each word even more.
Please teach us.
I could say it like this...
But I say I like this.
It seems easy to follow, but it's
actually hard when you try it.
The origin of his moves is
the grasshopper dance?
[Grasshopper time!]
[Improvises to a twist dance!]
It's fun how he improvised.
As a trendsetter, his appearances
are unique attracting attention.
His blond hair was impressive.
But he was afflicted with
something because of that.
Ji-yong is considerate, well-mannered,
and takes good care of his juniors.
But, he...
He dyed his hair blonde
for "Heartbreaker."
[During his time on "Heartbreaker"]
[His refined masculinity
attracted women!]
He synchronized himself with that
and became more like a prince.
I met him at the salon...
He suddenly hugged
me from behind...
- And he whispered.
- What did he say?
Hey Minzy! Brag to your
friends that I hugged you.
[Cringe]
- Is that true?
- Did I do that?
He did. Bad guys always
pretend not to know.
[Bad guy! G-Dragon!]
Ji-yong? Why did you do that?
- I don't know... why did I?
- She heard it exactly.
- I really don't know...
- Do a reenactment.
Go to the front and
do a reenactment.
Think of me as the mirror.
[G-Dragon meets Minzy at the salon
when he was active with "Heartbreaker"]
[He approaches quietly and
hugs her from behind...]
This is the salon.
With Minzy's tip-off, we found out
G-Dragon has the prince sickness.
But there's a person who
surprises even Prince G-Dragon.
Idols ask idols questions.
This one's for Gyu-ri. Many male
idols asked this same question.
"Do you have a princess sickness
or is that just your concept?"
First of all, it's not a sickness.
When I look at myself...
why are you laughing?
Why are you laughing?
I never called myself a goddess.
The fans called me that.
I just cherish and love myself.
Isn't it? What do you think?
Well...
Do I have princess sickness?
No...
His eyes say otherwise.
Prince GD can't do much
before Goddess Gyu-ri.
He was on a roll as a solo artist
but went through an ordeal.
His title track "Heartbreaker"
was accused of plagiarism.
Your solo album "Heartbreaker"
Any words?
I never talked about that
on air or on another medium.
Since people hear, think,
and feel differently...
I can't say who's right or wrong.
This is something I need to
make better next time.
It actually spurred me to not
make such mistakes again.
I have to accept what I have to.
What I can do as a singer...
Instead of arguing the pros
and cons in writing...
I will show through music and the stage
with my next album or performance.
So I quietly prepared
for my next album.
- Any unbearable comments?
- Each comment hurt.
I avoided my parents' calls and
didn't pick up when friends called.
I didn't commit any crimes, but
I felt like that before people.
I was sort of depressed...
It's just their thoughts and it could
have ended with just listening to it...
- Since it's criticism?
- Yes, that's right.
But there were comments like,
"Why don't you go kill yourself?"
That was all of a sudden.
It made me think, "What did I do
for that person to think that way?"
I should overcome it instead of falling into it
if it's what I'm going to do and it's my dream.
When I was at ease and thought this
is something I need to put up with...
I received a lot of help from my members
and instead of being swayed by this...
There are many that will be at ease
and dream by listening to my music.
So I thought I shouldn't waver.
- That you should try harder?
- That's right.
GD was a guest at Flo Rida's concert in Korea,
the one he supposedly plagiarized.
He got over the controversy and
presented his best stage.
Flo Rida was also satisfied
with their joint performance.
He had such hardships, but his
first album received much love.
[The strong beats and repeating
lyrics were memorable]
[It's a double title track he presented on
his comeback stage with "Heartbreaker"]
Every song in the album was loved
and also appeared on the charts.
I was surprised at the online chart rankings.
The entire album was ranked at the top.
It's been 2-3 years since the
online charts revitalized...
This is unprecedented and I can see
the public has great interest.
He presented all the songs in his
first album through various stages.
The stage seems special when
he does it. Let's see the rankings.
[Ranking! GD's Special Stage]
Ranking! GD's special stage.
I have a song in return.
Songs are reborn when
passed through G-Dragon.
"Boom Up" moved Boom Dragon.
[G-Dragon sings Boom's "Boom Up"!]
[He's singing my song!]
[No one looks for this song]
[Am I dreaming?]
[Was this song this cool?]
[Boom's only best song released in 2006
that never made it into the gayo rankings]
[That's my song!]
[Boom's best day ever!]
[I'm going to revive
my song today!]
[G-Dragon revived "Boom Up"]
[A duet dance they
made on the spot]
[In perfect step]
["Boom Up" is reborn]
"Oh Yeah" made KPOP STAR
to shine even more.
And the best hip-hop collaboration
that made even his members dance.
[2NE1 and G-Dragon at
the ensemble room]
[G-Dragon writes the rap part for
the "I Don't Care" ensemble]
You can start whenever
you feel like it.
It's going to be strange.
What's it about?
Well... you're saying "I don't care"
from a woman's position...
But the man would have
something to say as well.
- So it's a response. A fight...
- You might think it's an excuse.
An impromptu rap revealed
another charm to this song.
This is the unplugged version
of 2NE1's "I Don't Care."
I'm a free spirit
Like you said
You're just a type of insurance
It's just a risk for me
Better put aside the thought
Of keeping me on a leash
Why don't care
This wasn't my plan
I just need a help
Because of my fault
It's all over
Guess I'm new to love
I just kept my pride as a man
I wasn't even able
To say sorry
Just understand me this time
This will be the last, please
I'll do better, uh
Number one is the stage with
guitar prodigy Sungha Jung.
[We Are GD's Family Family Family]
YG is GD's top mentor.
He's the one that made him
into G-Dragon and an artist.
He couldn't train hard
since he had the cold...
Ji-yong?
He had a bad cold that very day,
but he sang better than expected.
He strained his throat because
he didn't do much singing before.
He lost his voice after
recording 3 or 4 times.
Let's watch him singing.
After the project was announced,
the first test video was shown.
This is how YG periodically checks
and assesses the trainees.
That's why he recorded again even
though he went over his alloted time.
YG watched the clip of Ji-yong in
silence and then speaks his mind.
I don't expect much from Ji-yong.
Ji-yong and Young-bae have
the best expressions...
Ji-yong actually improved a lot
in singing here in this clip.
He hated singing, but
he's feeling it right now.
- I don't think singing suits him...
- No, I like that sweet voice.
I don't expect him to sing well
like singing R&B songs...
I just want him to sing melodies like rap.
Chris Brown's song he's singing suits him.
It's unprecedented for the agency head
to ask to meet the trainees first.
They're on pins and needles since
they made a mistake at the Japan concert.
They're all tense that he might say
something that will hurt them.
He's coming.
- Is this his seat?
- They want to avoid this time.
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
I'm thinking... Ji-yong and Young-bae,
you guys were here for 6 years, right?
They were here for 6 years, but
I treat them the same as you guys.
Just because they were here longer
doesn't mean I'm more friendly to them.
It's your skills that matter in the end.
I was dumbfounded when I saw Ji-yong and
Young-bae at Se7en's concert in Japan.
I thought if you guys are the ones
we're looking forward to.
That performance was barely 15 points.
I wanted to crawl under a rock.
6 years isn't short. What were you
doing there? Especially Young-bae.
What did you do for
the past 6 years?
I was really upset, but I'm not here
to scold or get angry at you guys.
If you guys are going to debut in August,
it will be decided at the end of May.
I don't know if one or four
will drop out of this group.
I'm going to call you again at
the end of May and tell you.
We can continue to see each other but can't
work together if you don't have the skills.
YG had a hardened look since what
he said was flat and heartless.
Then he saw Ji-yong smiling.
Ji-yong, want to go home
after 6 years of training?
Just like what you said,
YG is, I don't know, brusque?
- Even now?
- Not anymore.
He's more easygoing
now that he's married.
Even until 3 years ago, he never
smiled or treated us kindly.
I still fear him and can't
even step on his shadow.
Your juniors trained harder after he scolded
them that they'll become like Young-bae.
That's his method.
He makes you as embarrassed
as possible in front of others.
But it's not in front of other
agency people or the public...
What's the harshest thing he said
to you in front of your agency family?
For me...
It might seem like nothing, but I'm
getting emotional thinking about it.
Let's see...
For example, he would say I'm the
root of all evil in BIGBANG.
He would say such things.
- Then am I...
- Of no use?
I tried so hard but then I'll think
if what he said about me is true.
He first says the worst thing
possible to everyone.
So that we'll be able to overcome
anything we hear later on.
Since we're used to it now,
even if YG says something...
We think, "You just wait."
He loves that and we understand him.
That's how he trained us.
And now we're strong.
That's what he says to us, but he
compliments us when he's outside.
We hear that from others.
Then that...
- It strengthens you.
- Yes, it does.
He's happier than anyone.
Another thing is that he goes
around boasting that he made us.
Do you agree?
YG's a scary mentor, but he takes care of
G-Dragon more than anyone in YG Family.
He's the best partner
and family member.
Who is the best rapper?
Don't yield because if you do,
you'll be the worst rapper.
Will the handsome guy speak first?
Our styles are different...
They're different but...
He's serious and I'm free.
He's much better.
- So serious and free?
- Yes.
The standard for what's
good or bad rapping is...
There is a standard.
I think it depends.
Then I'm curious...
Does Park Myeong-su's comedy have
more quality or Tak Jae-hoon...
Tak Jae-hoon!
[Thanks]
[- You should be on my side!
- Actually, I'm on his side]
- It's Myeong-su!
- It's Tak Jae-hoon!
I said it's Myeong-su!
It's Myeong-su!
He's the best!
Daesung, your face?
[Unfortunately, they're
resembling each other...]
I think they're on par so...
- Let's see them rap.
- You can rap or...
[G-Dragon goes first!]
I'll go first.
You got the lead.
One, two, three!
[He stays centered!]
[He's free!]
[They have good teamwork for
being together for many years]
That's it.
They produce a synergistic effect when
together and form a unit later on.
Their first album as GD&TOP
was released in 2010.
They showed a refined music and stage based
on their musical background of hip-hop.
[Electronica and hip-hop were
combined in this song]
[The refrain that became
more intense stood out]
[They showed another beauty of hip-hop
which is their musical background]
[It has an exciting mood
as if having fun at a club]
It was a perfect meeting
of music and appearances.
[Rhythmical sounds stand out in this song
based on 1980s new wave and disco]
[T.O.P's uniquely serious rap goes
well with the rhythmical sounds]
[And GD completes it by giving it
a sweet mood with his singing]
[The tracks in the album are linked like a story,
and this song also tells a story through the lyrics]
This is another side to the
charismatic GD and T.O.P.
The kissing scene was the hardest
because I already did it twice.
T.O.P Joo Won loves G Ra-im.
I'm having an identity crisis
since I did it twice now.
Don't worry, but you two
look great together.
My name is Kwon Ji-yong...
The one who was with GD
the longest is Taeyang.
It's already been 10 years now.
[It's been 10 years since
they met as trainees]
We were the only trainees and
tried to do better than the other.
- We tried harder on stage.
- He has an unusual taste.
He was very cool on stage.
Your eyes became moist as you
talked about your trainee days.
It wasn't something sad,
but it was like a trainee's...
- Sorrow.
- That's right.
We had to be background dancers so we
practice the moves and the manager calls.
Ji-yong and Taeyang come in front
of SBS by such and such time.
We went but they didn't come.
We just wait there. We call
them but they don't pick up.
We wait 1, 2, 3, 4 hours.
We even waited 8-9 hours.
It's late at night and we know
the broadcast is already over.
We get a call around 10-11 PM. "Sorry, I was
busy, but someone filled in. You can leave."
- Trainees can't talk back.
- You're dispensable.
He told us to leave...
Really? Then let's go...
We leave feeling down.
- That happened many times...
- To both of you?
- We went through that a lot.
- You and Young-bae?
- You look at each other...
- We don't look at each other.
- We don't say a word...
- No comforting words?
Back then...
- Felt like crying?
- I think so.
We don't say anything. I get off first and
he walks to his home in Uijeongbu.
We come back the next day
after school and clean again...
- Did you cry at all?
- When I'm alone.
I never cried together or told anyone.
But I cried alone many times.
[Ji-yong and Young-bae dreamed of
becoming stars since elementary]
Ji-yong and Young-bae overcame the
hard times having the same dream.
We'll continue to watch GD and Taeyang's
stage filled with their dreamlike times.
[GD's Vocabulary List]
[Gaho]
[G-Dragon's dog is more popular than him, and
appeared on air, music videos, red carpet, etc.]
Gaho is as famous as
his owner, G-Dragon.
OMG!
Who's that?
It's my puppy.
I was filming a music video and
he used my head as a pillow.
It's so cute.
[It's this puppy!]
He's so cute it's driving me nuts.
[The puppy's young but the
wrinkles make it look old]
Bark into it.
He looks so adorable
it's driving me nuts.
- He really likes me.
- He's so cute.
You must wash between
all those wrinkles.
I wash between every wrinkle.
He went to a pet salon today
because he's coming on this show.
- He just snorted he went.
- He also has a name tag on.
Gaho... he's so cute.
Can I hold him?
He's sleepy right now.
- So he looks grouchy.
- Really? Well...
I love puppies.
He's grouchy because I woke
him up from his sleep.
I love dogs and I never saw
a dog as adorable as this one.
I was watching television one day and
saw that he came out more than me.
I'm thinking of starring him
in commercials later on.
When he gets popular?
That's a good idea.
- I'm thinking about it.
- He could be the next Herbie.
Look at his eyes! He looks
indifferent and sick of the world.
He has such presence. He does
take after his owner, right?
[G-Dragon learned ballet for
a while when he was young]
- My mom made me do ballet.
- Really? How old were you?
- I was 5 or 6.
- I see...
[Creates the stage!]
- I have bad memories...
- How long did you do it?
[He's excited]
I didn't learn for years.
It was 2 or 3 months.
Even though I was young,
I was still a boy.
I went to class and I wore the
same thing as the girls.
The thing that looks like a
swimsuit with tights on?
It was pink. I hated that!
I cried every time I went.
I could understand.
Especially at that time...
Boys wore black tights
with white on top.
Now that I think about it,
I think that school was wrong.
Do you remember any moves?
- Well...
- Let's see.
In front of the ballet master.
Well, when you do a turn, you do
this then stop and then do this...
That form is... there it is!
Kwon Ji-yong might have
turned out a ballerino.
I really liked those that
did ballet in dance.
I thought that if I have a daughter, I'll make
her do ballet because they look pretty.
The figure itself is different.
The back is straight.
The hair is always tied...
Shoulders are like this
and back is straight.
They walk like this.
- It shows confidence.
- They look confident...
Such a girl stands out in class.
- That looks pretty...
- But they have ugly feet.
No, not everyone...
He could have gone with ballet.
[Sandpaper]
[It's used to describe G-Dragon's
cold-heartedness and petulance]
The day is finally here, but
Ji-yong's group is in an uproar.
Spread it. Didn't I tell you to
do each move correctly, huh?
It doesn't matter if you do it
100 times if you do it like that.
You should think about it and
do it correctly if I told you.
Dae-sung and Hyun-seung
didn't memorize the moves.
You should have matched it together
yesterday when I was here.
How can you forget the moves?
Are you in your right mind?
How can you forget the moves
when we're on in 2 hours?
Ji-yong's on edge because
he feels frustrated.
Dae-sung, it doesn't seem
like you're turning.
Push it more Dae-sung.
Push it out all the way! Just turn
thinking you'll break your knee.
Why are you doing it softly?
It's because I'm frustrated.
You should get it into your
heads when I said it once.
With 2 hours remaining, you
should think about how I feel.
You think I feel good
saying this to you?
We have one day left
and you were sleeping?
All three had a long face.
This is how "Touchy Kwon" and
"Sandpaper Ji-yong" was born.
It's been a while since
they had a generous meal.
But his mother is not only
worried about his meals.
You do harm to others if you lose your temper
even though there's something bothering you.
Laugh and talk it out even though
you feel bad. I know you will do well.
You always say the same thing.
My son is a baby at home.
You know you're a handful.
I see I'm the concern of my family.
Mother and son showed their
affection for each other.
What caught his attention is the
10 Commandments of Laughter.
He would thoughtlessly pass this by, but
maybe he remembered his mother's request.
These are good words.
Laugh! Let's laugh!
Kwon Ji-yong's nicknames are Sandpaper
Ji-yong, Touchy Ji-yong, and Kwon...
[What is it?]
It's Kwon G-ral (BS).
[Pay attention to the pronunciation]
It's spelled with the capital "G"
making it Kwon G-ral.
With three nicknames, you
don't think you're touchy?
I think my fans made them and it's also
the cause of such misunderstanding...
How can they make such nicknames
if you weren't such a person?
It's due to my image on television.
I'm actually different inside.
How do we know that?
I'm very emotional and soft-hearted.
Alright. Can you show
some tears in 3 seconds?
Isn't that enough? You acted
so you should know, right?
That's not it! I'll plead for him.
Those are crocodile tears.
What do you mean?
If you shed tears in 3 seconds,
it's without feeling sad.
You can if you get into the sad feeling.
Isn't that right since you are acting?
No, it's not.
I'm going to defend my team
since we're on the same side.
This is different from
what you said.
My turn is next.
We will defend you.
That's right, cry.
If you're emotional, shouldn't your nicknames
be "Sad Ji-yong" or "Teary Ji-yong"?
As the leader of BIGBANG, I looked
strong on the outside but cried inside.
Did you show tears
to your members?
Did I?
No, he hasn't.
"Sandpaper Ji-yong" is
actually warmhearted.
[Dating Expert]
[People use this to describe
G-Dragon the dating expert]
I'm curious... I heard you
write and compose your songs...
Even songs on love, do you
write them upon experience?
People can relate to it if
it's natural and real.
I try to write based on my experiences
and it was best when I was truthful.
Where do you get those experiences?
We wonder if you actually dated.
- ... good at dating.
- Really?
Everyone is doing great.
Others?
We're asking you.
- Such time...
- As he said...
GD's a dating expert.
They'll do well and
will make time for it.
You wrote, "My name is
Hammered Dragon."
It was a friend's birthday and we went
to a bowling alley in Gangnam.
We had some beer as we bowled.
There were some strong drinks
since it was a birthday.
I started drinking but
drank too much.
All I remember was coming
home after having fun.
But my friend called
the next day.
- "Why did you do that?"
- What did I do?
"Try to remember!
You're in trouble!"
I was excited after a few drinks,
and there were a lot of people.
- He said I started dancing.
- At the bowling alley?
[Hammered Dragon]
I was dancing like this
because I was excited.
I started to go somewhere.
I was waving happily
to a group of women.
I drank the beverages there
and started dancing with them.
My friend was surprised to see them
and took me away from them.
In front of SNSD...
I danced.
Are you close with them?
I'm not close.
When I meet them at the station,
since I'm one year their senior...
I have to maintain my image.
So every time they greet me...
[Uh, hi]
- I always did that.
- An air of mystery.
Yes, I maintained that but
since I was drunk that day...
I think Yoona, Tiffany, Sooyoung,
and Hyoyeon were there.
They don't know why but
I started dancing.
After some time, I attended an
awards ceremony with them in Japan.
But their looks towards me...
[The shameful senior who
danced at the bowling alley]
They were doing that and
I was really embarrassed.
To clear up their misunderstanding, I said,
"I'm not such a person. I was drunk."
- He wasn't G-Dragon but Hammered Dragon.
- Three sheets in the wind.
You don't remember at all?
When people act unpredictably while drunk,
they do things they always had in mind.
So G-Dragon always wanted
to dance before SNSD.
Why did you do that?
So he expressed it
with his body?
If that came out, it must
mean it was on his mind.
Who was there?
[SOS, help me]
[He asks Seungri for help,
the talk show master!]
Out of Yoona, Tiffany, Sooyoung,
and Hyoyeon, who was it?
That's my Seungri!
[The truth of G-Dragon's dancing?]
The G-Dragon I know is clear-headed
no matter how drunk he is.
He's our team's leader so he always
thinks that he has to be clear-headed.
Maybe he wanted to
show off his charms.
[He has no way out!]
So who was it among them?
GD looks a little shy. Even this
dating expert has a cute side.
[Fashion]
[G-Dragon sets trends and
known as a fashionista]
Since I can't be naked...
We are convinced with what
he speaks of with confidence.
GD is fashion forward and the
king of fashion in gayo.
This man has no equal but
has a self-claimed rival.
Jung Hyung-don always
asks if I'm watching...
From this day forward,
I refuse his comparison.
I like your confidence.
But the overall dark color
makes you look like a burdock.
[Want to go at it?]
[GD vs Hyung-don]
[Breathtaking fashion battle!]
[This is how you scan]
[Not good]
[You look like a sausage]
Is that a scarf on your wrist?
I might look plain in this gray suit
so this color is the key to the look.
I have a habit of doing this when
I talk so this will come on screen.
That scarf is on fire.
Maybe it's because celebrities that
are into fashion are his fan.
Everyone recognizes G-Dragon
as a fashion leader.
Not only on stage, but whatever
he wears becomes an issue.
Even the boldness to wear a dress
made him a fashion icon.
Some time ago, he was pointed out
by Jung Hyung-don and humiliated.
- What do you think?
- We're not rivals.
He keeps on mentioning me,
but if I get the chance...
We look forward to their
fashion collaboration.
[KPA Kim?]
Doesn't look good?
Same hat, different feel.
The style only GD can make
also shines on the stage.
The shocking hairstyle made news.
His fantastic seaweed hair.
You know how you had
that long hair...
The seaweed hair.
There are pros and cons.
It looks fancy on stage...
But it was in my mouth
half the time.
When I move a little,
it gets in my mouth.
Now I know how.
How?
I go crazy when I rap.
Now I bend a little...
so my hair won't move.
[Walking while sticking
his stomach out]
For real? You really do that?
Yes. I look this way but,
I go back to doing this.
Looks like he has his share of problems.
Not anyone can be the king of fashion.
[Hardships and Another Determination]
GD returned to BIGBANG
after going solo.
He's been on a roll as the best star
but goes through a sudden hardship.
[BIGBANG's G-Dragon smokes pot]
We had a wrap-up party
after our concert...
Many people were at the party
and it was held abroad...
- It was abroad?
- Yes, we had a concert.
The trouble started when I got
a smoke from a stranger.
Many of my fans that looked at me
like sunflowers were disappointed.
And I actually experienced
them turning away from me.
I'm not that emotional, but I cried
a lot by myself during that time.
For the first time, I had time
to think due to that mistake.
I had 6 months of self-reflection
since I was banned from broadcasting.
I had time to look back because
I only looked ahead and ran.
That was one of my
biggest tasks.
GD had time to look back
through this hardship.
I realized I was nothing.
We can see how much he grew
in his music as well.
He released his second solo album
3 years after his first solo album.
"One of a Kind" is also the
title of his mini-album.
Just its release made news.
Just like the song title, he showed his
special and unique music without regrets.
[Just like the title, he went back
and forth from fast and slow rap]
[He tells his story
with candid lyrics]
[It's like an intro song for
his second solo album]
[He made a surprise announcement
on social media on his birthday]
He later released "That XX."
It was rated MA for its straightforward
lyrics and title but was first on the charts.
[Special appearance
Sungha Jung]
[Unlike the strong feel of the title]
[The lyrical melody of the
acoustic guitar stood out]
[A woman trusts her boyfriend
who is cheating on her]
[A man who has a crush on
her is hurt by this fact]
[The straightforward lyrics are
about how he feels about that]
[Before its release, to maintain
the purpose of this song...]
[He decided on his own
to get an MA rating]
[Yet it made news for taking
the top on music charts]
[The improper words were censored
with a beep allowing people to listen]
[He played both men
in his music video]
The title song "Crayon" is combined
from crazy and his name Ji-yong.
It means GD is going to get wrapped
up and absorbed in something.
[Hip-hop and electronic
were perfectly divided]
[It's an experimental form to
enjoy both genres in one song]
[The title means "Crazy On"
but at the same time...]
[It's a combination of
crazy and Ji-yong]
[It means G-Dragon is wrapped up
and absorbed in something]
[He put his motto of doing
everything with excitement]
["Why so serious?" from the "Dark Knight"
is heard here and there in this title song]
[He's saying this to the world and
also giving himself courage]
There's also something else
he shines at, and that is...
[GD the Producer]
He's responsible for the words and music
and is able to produce all on his own.
His talent as a producer
is one of his specialty.
At a young age...
I write the words and music...
And also produce.
And I make a lot from royalties.
[Jong Shin feels small]
It seems like he's joking but
he wrote many hit songs.
I'm over 40 but he
makes more than me!
I was able to do that with
help from many people.
He could be particular but...
I didn't say anything yet.
Of course, I envy him.
I don't know but I think
it's over a 100.
If it's a 100 songs, then
each month it's...
What are you calculating?
You succeeded at a young age.
[A capable guy!]
Where does that talent
come from?
I think it became a habit.
When we used to be trainees...
YG gave us an assignment of
writing a new song every week.
I started doing that and then
one became two then three...
His remarkable senses can also
be applied to the BIGBANG members.
It looks like you two are
goofing off in the waiting room.
It says here, "With Seungri.
Tom and Jerry."
Our fans call us
Tom and Jerry.
What song are the
members good at?
For each one?
Is it teuroteu for Daesung?
He sings teuroteu well
but he has a nice voice...
Korean classical music.
That's right!
His voice is open and
good at doing that.
Taeyang is... what do you
call that? Is it CCM?
When I go to church with him,
he looks cool when singing hymns.
I think he'll be serious.
He sings like he's on stage.
- Church hymns?
- Yes, in church.
So people next to him
look only at him.
They tell him he was cool
after church.
It must be fun. How would
he sing something like this?
Something like that.
[What about himself?]
- Children's songs.
- Really?
- What kind?
- My voice is thin...
My voice is like a child's.
You want him to sing?
[The best rapper singing
children's songs?]
You have to sing
with confidence.
Yes, and also clearly.
Like this.
"Look at Me, Gwisoon."
- That's right.
- Isn't that teuroteu?
Yes, it is.
Why only for Daesung?
He enjoys singing it
and sings it well.
I love it.
It seemed like a
loss not to.
Haven't you thought
of T.O.P doing it?
I wrote the song with Daesung
for the first time.
Many things happened last year
and as I talked with him...
There was something that
really hurt my heart.
He can get absorbed and sing
a really sad or happy song.
But when we sing a
medium tempo or an R&B...
He feels sorry and isn't confident
to sing while looking at his fans.
I don't know how to put this but
it made me sad when I heard that.
Since I like Daesung's voice and
he's good at hitting the high notes.
We worked to make that stand out
and that became his solo song.
I never knew how
awesome his voice was.
He memorized it while
writing the words.
Did he also...
Not only does he add their colors
to the song, he's also kindhearted.
He displayed his talents once more.
Everyone waited for this day.
It's GD's second album.
Not only did he write the words and music
but also produced creating this album.
[First world tour finale
Preparing for the Seoul concert]
His music doesn't disappoint.