[The Birth of Young Artists]
BOYFRIEND entered the
gayo world in 2011.
They presented their first stage
with their debut song "Boyfriend."
[The unique rhythm and touching melody
went well with the members' voices]
[This song is about a boy's confession and
the lively outfits and moves livened it up]
[This is their debut song conveying
the feel of a young boyfriend]
They seem like boyfriends out of a comic.
But isn't there a familiar face among them?
It's the twins - Youngmin and Kwangmin.
They had many fans due to their good looks.
- We are good-looking.
- Aren't we cool?
[Cute good-looking twins!]
Before his debut, he was K.Will's
flower boy backup dancer and...
IU's younger boyfriend in her
music video. It's Minwoo.
Their looks were verified
before their debut.
In "Don't Touch My Girl," their
2nd single, they sung of pure love.
[A synthpop harmonizing melodic bass
with guitar sounds giving off a rock feel]
[Their dynamic performance
contrasted the lyrics of pure love]
[They presented a matured stage and
styling apart from their cute image]
Seungyub is another one who appeared
on TV as a child actor before his debut.
Alright then.
You're talkative when feeling good
and play innocent when feeling bad?
I think all women
are like that, dad.
That boy became a member of A-JAX.
With dance performance and imposing sounds,
they debuted in June 2012 with "One 4 U."
[A visual-pop combining dance performance with
intense, imposing sounds of neo-classical metal]
[With pipe organ and harpsichord
not easily heard in idol music...]
[It harmonized with hardcore
electric guitar and drums]
[They drew attention as a boy band produced by
DSP in 5 years and this is their debut song]
There's a group that made themselves known
before their debut with a 100 day promotion.
It's the 12 member group, EXO.
The strategy they took for their
activities were unusual.
They released their prologue single
before their official debut and...
They were divided into EXO-K and EXO-M to be
active simultaneously in Korea and China.
[It's a song with a vintage sounding
electric guitar leading the song]
[The feel of the song stands out with
simple drums and soft synth sounds]
[The complicated feeling of falling in love
is expressed with the sensible voices]
[Teddy Riley and Yoo Young-jin collaborated
to produce this traditional R&B song]
EXO-K's first stage was held
in Korea on April 2012.
They presented their first stage with
their 2nd prologue single "History."
[The intense beat and catchy melody
stands out in this dance song]
[A contrasting charm from the 1st prologue
single with a dynamic performance]
[Thomas Troelsen took
part in composing]
[The fresh, bouncy percussion
beat was impressive]
"Mama" is the title track
of their 1st mini-album.
The lyrics, containing a special message,
and the magnificent sounds...
Go with the flashy performance
leaving a strong impression.
[The Gregorian chant and
imposing orchestral sounds...]
[Go with the guitar and intense
shouting in this debut song]
[The lack of communication
people feel in reality and...]
[The digital world is conveyed
with a strong melody]
[It's an SMP with flashy group dance
and the members' unique voices]
EXO-M is also successful in China
with a Chinese version of "Mama."
EXO-K and EXO-M combines
to present EXO's "Mama."
This stage is possible due
to their special strategy.
The concept of coming from Exoplanet with
supernatural powers is their uniqueness.
Earth, fire, wind, water, light,
and even teleportation...
I remember shouting out
these words as a child.
Sehun, blow some wind.
Sehun, master of wind, blows wind
for them in this sweltering heat.
Kai is mad at the warm wind.
He calls Sehun and begs for wind.
Maybe it fits only them. If I call
Suho, will he quench my thirst?
There's a group that combined such powers
into their song in May 2012 after EXO.
Their debut song "Super Hero" is about
protecting their lover with superhuman powers.
These 6 super heroes are VIXX!
[A catchy melody is added to the
unique synthpop chord pattern]
[An electronic with more pop quality
than intensity in the intense beats]
[The unique lyrics are about protecting
their lover with superhuman powers]
[It's their debut song with a higher
degree of perfection in sound]
The mascot that made their stage
even special is the robot ROVIXX.
It's a special work of art by
pop artist Charles Jang.
ROVIXX is composed of various characteristics
of heroes and sometimes called their 7th member.
Why don't you greet us?
- Hello.
- You're polite.
[Cute "Gangnam Style" Duo]
They were called "art-dol"
for such a strategy.
They made a surprise transformation into
artists by partaking in a Batman exhibition.
The size is 91 x 72.7 cm.
The "VIXX" here is the key.
Batman is saying, "VIXX."
Look at the eyes.
There's nothing in there.
- He is angry.
- You didn't finish his eyes.
He has dark circles like me.
Those are muscles.
- That's the shoulder...
- What muscle is that?
It's this muscle. I have them.
This is his nose.
These are wrinkles on his mouth.
- Since he's old?
- Yes, that's right.
This is around $50,000.
But I'll sell it to
you for $40,000.
- Thank you.
- How about it?
- Are you buying it?
- I'm not buying it.
You're not? Take this.
The title is... can you zoom in?
By Ravi, Stylish bat.
The title is "Stylish bat."
Since Batman is the theme here,
contrasting Batman's dark image...
Within the darkness,
I did some graffiti.
So I called it "Stylish bat."
As you came here...
This is the authority of "art-dols."
There's another reason why VIXX
drew attention before their debut.
It's their agency family.
Why don't we meet them?
[Keyword: Their Family]
[Family]
[Senior artists in the agency]
Princes of ballads like Sung Si-kyung,
Park Hyo-shin, Brian, and Seo In-guk...
Are under Jellyfish Entertainment which
produced its first idol group, VIXX.
With such outstanding seniors,
they received a lot of help.
Thanks to them, their skills
have become more exceptional.
- Who treats you the best?
- Park Hyo-shin does.
He was on vacation but came to check on our
dance, singing and expression for our comeback.
We love you.
That's why they love them.
Monitoring is the most basic.
Not only do they sing
their songs passionately...
We came to support Seo In-guk.
They're admirable juniors
coming out to give support.
- It's the suit senior!
- He's hip in a suit!
We are V! We are VIXX!
Pleased to meet you!
It drives me crazy every time
they do that. It's embarrassing.
We brought our gift to you
in the gift you gave us.
It's ROCK UR BODY.
N said to return
the car to you.
- Why did you say that?
- You don't like it?
- It's because it's old.
- Why did you say that?
I really hate you.
- What? Why me?
- I hate that especially.
We even know this.
It opens like this.
Engineer.
You know how he resembles me.
I'm boring, but he's boring too.
I guess that's what a relationship is.
They even resemble each other.
They're an amazing and
heartwarming family.
A-JAX also receives support from
DSP Media's KARA and RAINBOW.
Not only do they leave comments
cheering them on social media...
They showed off their strong affection for
them by appearing in their music video.
A-JAX showed off the advanced Backdown
dance of Sech Kies member Kim Jae-duc.
Even BOYFRIEND receives love and support
from their seniors like SISTAR and K.Will.
They have a special performance together...
Even a collaboration project
called "White Love."
It's not only on stage. SISTAR
came out for BOYFRIEND.
We hope you will develop your artistic
talents and whatnot through this show...
- We're always cheering you on.
- Let's cheer BOYFRIEND on that.
Count me in!
I envy them for getting such
a message from SISTAR.
We can't leave this group out.
It's SM Town, most famous by idols
and has the best k-pop heroes.
The youngest of this group is EXO.
2011 was covered by a veil.
They left a strong impression by performing
with senior artists at the year-end awards.
They're worthy of becoming
rising stars pre-debut.
They performed with senior artists.
Even I feel great watching this.
I see EXO were unique
since this time.
These young artists presented stages
showing their colors since their debut.
Let's discover their other charm
which is their hidden hit songs.
[Find Their Hidden Song]
This is a pop dance song
about desperate love.
An acoustic melody and subtle voices
stand out in BOYFRIEND's "Standing with U."
Their unique voices stand out
in this pop R&B song.
This ballad was prereleased
before A-JAX's debut.
The doll of Goo Ha-ra in their
music video was memorable.
This is "Never Let Go."
This song has a shocking title
and a contrasting acoustic feel.
VIXX's "Don't Want to Be an Idol"
contains an idol's honest confession.
A certain group had a 100 day promotion
with an online teaser before their debut.
They are the 12 member group EXO.
They showed a small teaser before their
debut but received a positive response.
You can get their feel in the teasers.
Why don't you listen to the full song?
[Another Charm]
To become heroes that captivate all...
They have to show off their talents
elsewhere and not only on stage.
Let's see what they have done.
BOYFRIEND and VIXX showed their hidden
talents on a reality show on SBS MTV.
To grow up into Korea's idol, "Wonder Boy"
is their project to unleash their potential.
Hyunseong is a 20-year-old
celebrity making big.
- Huh?
- Sing a song.
[Two women recognized BOYFRIEND!]
[Success]
- Do you know me?
- Yes.
Do you know my name?
[Hyun! Seong!]
[Trying to figure out]
[That's dirty!]
We can see your mouth.
They still don't know.
Hyun... Seong?
[Bingo]
Are the other members here?
Other members? No.
I'm the only one here.
[Trying to hog the limelight]
Ask if they know any names
of the other members.
Do you know the names of
anyone other than me?
- Youngmin!
- Donghyun!
[These two are known abroad]
Youngmin and Donghyun!
Want to take pictures?
This is Korea, but foreigners
recognize them more than Koreans.
Go again to a large crowd and say,
"Step aside! Celebrity coming through!"
- This is the last.
- Start moving.
Celebrity coming through.
Please step aside.
A mission to increase their awareness
is basic. You're doing great Hyunseong!
[Slapped with water]
[Slow motion]
[Can't miss this God-given chance]
[Does his best to roll]
[True as heard]
He overcame the pressures of slo-mo.
Screen captures and animated GIFs
may remain, but he did very well.
[We are Girl Friends!]
[I don't know]
[Passed out]
[Drenched in sweat]
Seeing that, it's a good thing
that BOYFRIEND is a boy band.
Another group was possessed by a girl group.
It's a good thing they're wearing masks.
All of VIXX's natural and exciting
images were shown on their show.
- You don't wear like that at home.
- You said to wear what I wear at home.
Want a beating?
Hyuk does his duty as an idol.
Let's just turn a blind eye.
[You look strange too...]
VIXX later became the
main of the show.
- I can do this well.
- I don't know what to do.
- Ready?
- Yes...
He laughed.
[Beams]
[Leo beams after drawing in N's breath]
[Bolts up!]
[They're fighting]
[Ravi goes to stop Leo]
Fight! Fight!
["Make Leo laugh"
caused this violence]
It ended with fists, but their
efforts are commendable.
They have a comical side to them.
A-JAX starred in their own
UCC to advertise themselves.
They showed their acting with a
clip that went with the song title.
Close your books!
Those two rows switch!
This row too!
What?
Another charm is the campaign song.
We're A-JAX
I look in the mirror
(put on a sweet smile)
Hey, be brave today
What strengthens me more is
Milk
A glass of milk after ramen
I'm all powered up
Song for you, milk
[Traffic safety song]
No drunk driving or falling asleep
No cell phones while driving
Observe the stop line
Obey the traffic signals
Drive slowly in school zones
All seats must have seat belts on
Turn off mobile TV while driving
Fall asleep and be in trouble
Drunk driving? No, No
Refrain from using cell phones
Seems like EXO can make even
karaoke into a flashy stage.
They're still rookies in variety shows,
but I think we can look forward to it.
[Their Song and Transformation]
Just like their group name,
BOYFRIEND's songs continued on.
Their 3rd single "I'll Be There" is a
love song with a unique melodic rap.
[It's a pop dance song
with an electronic feel]
[Their unique mood stands
out in this love song]
[An exciting melody and
romantic lyrics also stand out]
[The key to this song is their
group dance and melodic rap]
They confessed again with a song that's about
doing anything for the person they love.
"Love Style" is the title track
of their 1st mini-album.
[The dynamic form and fresh
melody were memorable]
[The uniqueness made by the guitar riff stands
out in this clear and cool dance number]
[The song is about doing anything for the
person they love, and it shows their colors]
[They drew attention with various looks such as unique
pastel suits with floral patterns and street fashion]
BOYFRIEND completely changed.
"JANUS" is the title track of their
first full-length album.
They completely transformed
like the title of the song.
We can see how they grew
up into men from boys.
[It's a fancy and lyrical
new wave pop song]
[It portrays the two contrasting sides of a man
who happily lets go of a woman but is sad]
[They had a pretty-boy image until now]
[But they completely transformed and
showed their strong charisma in this song]
[They presented a spectacular and disciplined
mirrored group dance with 6 other dancers]
[Youngmin and Kwangmin represented the
good and evil of Janus in the music video]
A-JAX also transformed.
"Hot Game" is their 2nd single
with a club music rhythm.
They presented a stage unique to rookies
casting aside their heavy debut image.
[The rhythmical and melodic harmony
goes exquisitely with the club rhythm]
[A man who fell in love at first sight
is expressed with witty lyrics]
[They debuted with a strong warrior image
but transformed to an image fit for summer]
A-JAX then returned as
a bad ex-boyfriend.
"2MYX" is about a "bad guy" who
threw a blow at his ex-girlfriend.
It's nostalgic of late 1990s boy band
and their performance also drew attention.
[A pop dance song with passionate beats
and an intense and catchy melody]
[Like their concept of returning to 1990s boy band,
the retro and modern feelings went well together]
[Kalle Engstrom, hit composer of 1990s
US boy bands, took part in composing]
[This is in response to composing
"Run Devil Run" for Girls' Generation]
[A "bad guy" throws a blow
at his obsessed girlfriend]
[The lyrics and musical elements are
in common with "Run Devil Run"]
They paid homage to Michael Jackson by
doing the moonwalk and such in their color.
VIXX's 2nd single dreaming of being
super heroes is "Rock Ur Body."
Like the lyrics comparing love to a video game,
it's a dance song with an exciting melody.
The pixel art and sound effects reminiscent
of video games at that time were memorable.
[The 8-bit sound effects of retro games and
exciting guitar riff in the intro were memorable]
[The fresh lyrics compare love felt for
the opposite sex to a video game]
[Going through with the retro concept of the album,
they stressed on pixel art completing their style]
SISTAR's Dasom, family to BOYFRIEND,
came to support these guys now.
[SISTAR's Dasom appears
in their music video]
[Formed a group for 20-year-olds]
VIXX created their color with an
exciting dance song after their debut.
But they chose to completely
transform in their next album.
They became vampires. It's a synth pop
with intense electric guitar sounds.
"I'm Ready to Get Hurt"
is their 3rd single.
These rookies were ready to transform
and their visuals were truly amazing.
[It's a synth pop with intense
electric guitar sounds]
[The intense sounds contrasted the sad lyrics of
a woman who hurts him even though he loves her]
[They showed off their sexy masculinity with
shocking visuals apart from their existing image]
They put on colored contacts for the
intense eyes and shocking makeup.
Their styling contributed to their
transformation into vampires.
They left a strong impression with this
song as a group making a great impact.
EXO made fans to wait making them say,
"EXO isn't making a comeback."
Compared to the others, they didn't
release another song since "Mama."
The wait finally ended in 2013.
[Their Stage Continues]
A year after their debut, EXO
released their 1st studio album.
All 12 members of EXO returned
in their title track "Wolf."
[A collaboration of dupstep and
hip-hop in this dance song]
[With wild, powerful beats and sounds...]
[Expresses the emotions of a wolf
falling in love with a pretty girl]
[The detailed and witty lyrics made the
unique mood of the song to stand out]
[The moves describing the wolf's cave and tree,
and the transformation into wolf boys...]
[Were a sophisticated performance
reminding one of a musical]
EXO transformed into wolf boys after
falling in love with a pretty girl.
They had a special performance to go with
the song that collaborates dubstep with hip-hop.
What are those?
They're name tags we use
during rehearsals.
[Name tag?]
Since we're rookies and there are 12 of us,
it's for the staff to know our names.
It takes a long time to read them
since they're a big group.
But it's great to know their names.
Now I know who's who.
Together with their comeback, EXO swept
music programs by taking 1st with "Wolf."
They became hot rookies
after a year since their debut.
Thank you for this award.
[It's a dance song based on
refined Urban R&B sounds]
[The feeling of not wanting to lose a
woman one loves to another man is...]
[Described in a fun way with a growl]
[World-renowned choreographer Nick Bass
was in charge of their choreography]
[The performance was dynamic and touching
on a grand scale with all 12 members]
[Their music video that was shot once
on a steadicam also garnered attention]
EXO seized the music charts in Asia and
rose as the most frightening rookies in k-pop.
We cheer their remarkable growth as heroes
and their stage that makes any place heavenly.
VIXX presented "Hyde" from their
1st mini-album a year after their debut.
Their concept after vampires
was Jekyll and Hyde.
They showed the contrasting sides of man
who was hurt by love and became a devil.
[The magnificent introduction and
tense development were memorable]
[The concept of Jekyll and Hyde
was used to portray...]
[A man's psyche that turned evil
after being hurt by love]
[An image of angels and devils
were portrayed with...]
[Smokey makeup, achromatic-colored clothes,
and a performance stressing their concept]
[They were successful in another
intense transformation]
They transformed again with "G.R.8.U."
Since the release of the teaser, it drew
attention with the unprecedented title.
[The fresh sounding guitar riff goes
well with the powerful synth sounds]
[They presented a clear and cool
melody that goes well with summer]
[Even before its release, online searches
were done due to the unique title]
[They took off their strong makeup
and revealed their pure charms]
[Their leader, N, took part in
creating exciting key moves]
VIXX were rookies in the spotlight but
grew up into a group with their own colors.
We look forward to their
ever-evolving stages.
BOYFRIEND's strong transformation
continued with "I Yah," an intense dance song.
Hmm? I'm hearing this title again.
It's very familiar to me.
There was a song with the same title
14 years ago. Thus it caught my eyes.
[This song presents a powerful
and masculine voice and rap]
[With a daring desire to conquer one's lover,
they transformed into romantic machos]
[The title track of H.O.T.'s 4th album
released in 1999 had the same title]
[It's been 14 years, but this
song has a different feel]
Just like H.O.T.'s "I Yah" that
they heard in their school days...
BOYFRIEND wants their "I Yah"
to be known far and wide.
We'll observe their songs that
are being heard here and there.
A-JAX returned after 7 months
with their 2nd mini-album.
"Insane" is the title track and
a hybrid electronic song.
They learned singing and dancing again
from the basics and honed their skills.
They presented a stage that is more
matured internally and externally.
[The nonstop intense and fancy
synth sound is leading the song]
[This is their first attempt on an original
electronic dance number since their debut]
[It expresses a man's heart that
has fallen for a certain woman]
[They expressed a new change in their
music with "insane" as the subtitle]
Like the lyrics of a man
falling for a certain woman...
We hope they become shining k-pop heroes via
their song and stage to make people fall for them.
Subtitles by SBS International