MAN:
Yeah!
NARRATOR:
On July 15, 1945,
the USS Indianapolis,
her repairs now complete
and ready to go back to war,
received orders
to pick up special cargo
at Hunters Point, California.
MAURICE BELL:
'Course, we had no idea
what the cargo was.
Well, there was
all kind of rumors went on
aboard ship, uh,
what we was delivering.
There was one rumor that's
very outstanding in my mind,
and this rumor
just flew all over the ship
was that we was delivering
scented toilet paper
to General MacArthur.
And they picked certain men
on the ship
to load and unload this,
and they picked me.
So I helped load it.
(music ends)
NARRATOR:
On July 26,
the Indianapolis
delivered its mysterious cargo
to the B-29 base on Tinian.
Then she set out
for the Philippines.
Four days later,
in the middle of the night,
disaster struck.
BELL:
A few minutes after midnight,
there was a loud explosion
on there.
It knocked me out of my bunk.
and the first thing that
passed... went through my mind
was that a...
a boiler had blown up.
(explosion)
NARRATOR:
A Japanese submarine
had sent two torpedoes
hissing into the hull
of the Indianapolis.
They cut it nearly in half.
1,196 men were aboard.
Within the first few minutes,
some 300 of them
were blown apart
or burned to death.
The captain ordered the rest--
nearly 900 men--
to abandon ship.
BELL:
I estimated I was about
25 to 30 feet up in the air
when I jumped.
I put my foot against
the side of the ship and pushed
and started swimming,
because I was told that, uh,
the best thing to do is
to get away from a ship--
as it went under, it would
create, uh, tremendous suction.
So as I pushed with my foot
and started swimming,
when I did,
the ship just shot away from me
as it was going under.
NARRATOR:
Within 12 minutes,
the Indianapolis
sank from sight.
The men were alone now,
scattered across miles
of dark, empty sea.
Many men were badly wounded.
Some had broken limbs.
Able-bodied survivors
did what they could in the dark
to fashion floats for them,
tying together life rafts
as floating beds.
Morning brought worse horrors.
BELL:
When daylight came,
you look around,
all you could see was just
the group that I was in.
There was probably
over a hundred men
in that group to start with.
Just shortly after daylight,
somebody yelled...
yelled out real loud, "Sharks!"
And sure enough, there were
sharks swimming all around us.
And, uh, those sharks
would swim around us,
and then, uh, all of a sudden,
they would dive in on us
and start attacking guys.
And, uh...
you'd see them attack somebody
over just a short...
just a few feet from you,
and, of course,
they'd grab them,
and down they'd go, and you'd
never see that... man again.
All you would see then
would be the water turning red
around them.
They attacked us every day,
several times a day.
Some of the sharks swimming
three or four feet of me,
but none ever touch me.
NARRATOR:
No one came to rescue them.
Distress signals
from the sinking ship
had been dismissed
as Japanese trickery.
BELL:
I stayed in the water
for four days and five nights--
a little over a hundred hours,
altogether--
with nothing to eat
or no fresh water to drink.
Some of the guys just went
completely out of their head.
Didn't even know
where they was at.
They would feel that fr...
cold water down at their feet,
and they'd dive down there
and drink it,
thinking they was
back aboard ship.
And they'd come back up
and describe...
that, uh, "Come on down below."
They thought
they was on the ship.
"Come on down--
at the officer's quarters,
there's water fountains up there
with ice water all the time."
NARRATOR:
When the Navy finally did
come upon them on August 2,
only 321 men remained alive.
Some 880 crewmen died.
BELL:
Some of the things
that I actually went through
out there,
it just seems more like
a dream... sometimes.
I wonder how I made it through.
I tell everybody now
that I was too sour
for the sharks to eat.
NARRATOR:
On August 5,
three days after the rescue
of the Indianapolis survivors,
the unknown object
they had delivered to Tinian
was placed aboard a B-29
named for the mother
of its pilot--
the Enola Gay.
It was an atomic bomb.
It had originally been intended
for use against the Germans,
who had been feverishly working
to make a bomb of their own,
but it had not been ready
for delivery
before they surrendered.
The American bomb
had been developed
under such strict secrecy
that the new president
had never heard of the project
before he assumed office.
But once he was told about it,
Truman approved the bomb's use
as soon as it was ready.
At 8:15 in the morning
on August 6, 1945,
the bomb tumbled
through the bomb-bay doors
of the Enola Gay.
43 seconds later,
six miles below
but still high above
the city of Hiroshima,
it detonated,
changing the world forever.
(explosion)
(rumbling continues)
(rumbling fading out slowly)
With a single bomb,
40,000 men, women and children
were obliterated in an instant.
100,000 more would die
within days
of burns and radiation.
Another hundred thousand
would succumb
to radiation poisoning
over the next five years.
More than half a century later,
citizens of Hiroshima
would still be dying
from the bomb's
long-delayed side effects.
Despite the devastation,
the Japanese still
would not accept
the Allied surrender terms.
Then on August 8,
the Soviet Union
declared war on Japan.
The islands now faced invasion
on two fronts.
At 11:02 the following morning,
an American plane
dropped a second atomic bomb
on the city of Nagasaki.
Some 40,000 more civilians
died instantly.
The Americans
had no more such bombs
and would be unable to produce
another for several months.
But the Japanese had no way
of knowing that.
In Tokyo, the Supreme Council
for the Direction of the War
remained split between those
still determined to fight on
and those willing,
finally, to give up.
That evening,
all six members of the council
called upon the emperor,
who broke the deadlock.
Japan would surrender.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
Everything was set
for the landings in Japan.
So when the atomic bomb
was dropped
and it ended it so quickly,
we were stunned
but rejoiced.
Our boys would come home!
There wouldn't be
any more of them killed.
You can never convince
anyone of my generation
that the atomic bomb
was not the greatest thing
(laughs):
that they ever came up with,
because we'll defy you.
It was just finally
the end of that horrible war.
RAY LEOPOLD:
I had very mixed feelings
about it.
That the atom bomb...
could be blasted
on fellow humans
whose blood is as red as mine,
whose skin blisters
as readily as mine does...
was something I had hoped
could be avoided.
Of course,
there is the mathematical odds
that by killing some...
quarter million... Japanese,
we may have saved
half a million American lives.
Mathematically,
that's a good thing.
But it's hard
to give up someone else's life.
NARRATOR:
After Japan gave up, the guards
at Glenn Frazier's prison camp
had simply walked away.
He and his comrades wandered out
among a dazed
civilian population...
and took the train to Tokyo
and freedom.
EUGENE SLEDGE (dramatized):
"We thought the Japanese
would never surrender.
"Many refused to believe it.
"Sitting in stunned silence,
we remembered our dead.
"So many dead.
"Except for a few widely
scattered shouts of joy,
"the survivors of the abyss
sat hollow-eyed and silent,
trying to comprehend
a world without war."
Eugene Sledge.
("Every Tub" playing)
(cheering)
EARL BURKE:
V-J Day-- I was in San Francisco
and it just blew up!
People come out of everywhere:
out of every window,
out of every door.
They came out of the sewer.
You could cop a feel
going down the street
and nobody would say a word.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
Well, my dad was so excited
that he ran in the room
and he got his pistol from
World War I and he filled it
and we went out
of the front door,
and if you go dig around
that azalea bush,
I know the bullets
are still in the azalea bush.
He fired six rounds
into the azalea bush,
brought the pistol back
in the house
and said to my brother and I,
"Come on, gang,"
and "We're going downtown."
And he threw mother in the car
and we drove down
to Admiral Semmes' statue.
And daddy circled it three or
four times honking his horn.
So by the time we left downtown,
people were climbing up
Admiral Semmes' statue
and the celebration had begun.
But I've always said
my daddy started
the celebration for V-J day.
NARRATOR:
In Waterbury, Connecticut,
newsboys peddling a special
"War's Over" edition
of the Waterbury American
were on the street
within 60 seconds of the
president's formal announcement.
Every firehouse siren
and factory whistle in town
began to blow.
ANNE DeVICO:
We didn't even know the people.
We didn't know who they were and
they didn't know who we were.
It was just a joyous time.
It was a happy, happy time
'cause we're thinking,
"Well, now all our boys
are going to come home."
(bell tolls)
NARRATOR:
That evening, special
services were held
at every Waterbury church
and synagogue.
As a sign of profound gratitude
for the good news,
some Italian-American women
climbed the hill
to Our Lady of Mount Carmel
Church on their knees.
OLGA CIARLO:
It was a happy time
for a lot of people.
It was a happy time for us, too,
to know that the war was over
for other boys, too,
that were there.
But it wasn't so happy for us
because we knew my brother
wasn't coming home.
NARRATOR:
Private Babe Ciarlo of Waterbury
had been killed in Italy
during the Anzio break-out
in late May of 1944.
His mother had refused
to believe it,
poring over newspaper
photographs
in hopes of glimpsing him,
insisting the Army
had made an error,
that somehow her son would still
be coming home to her.
Eventually,
long after the war, he did.
OLGA:
I think the worst day was when
they brought his body back.
And we went down
to the railroad station
and when they took his body off
the train and we were all there,
we all went to the cemetery,
when they handed
my mother the flag...
FRAZIER:
We sailed under
the Golden Gate Bridge
and into San Francisco Bay...
and as we approached the pier,
there-- I get
a little choked up--
there was the American flag
flying high in the breeze
over American soil,
and it was the most
gratifying thing
'cause we never dreamed
we would ever get back.
And there was a bunch
of prisoners of war on there.
couldn't even see anything--
with tears in our eyes.
And as we docked,
I was one of the...
I was the second one to get off.
And I get down on the ground,
I kissed the ground.
And every one of the prisoners
of war that was on that ship
got off the gangplank
and kissed the ground.
was just clapping their hands
every time
and welcomed us home.
And it was the greatest
feeling in the world.
NARRATOR:
Glenn Frazier's family back
in Fort Deposit, Alabama,
had officially been informed
that he had died
in the Philippines.
(phone ringing)
FRAZIER:
We were told we could make
a phone call home
at the expense
of the government.
So I made my phone call
to my home.
And the phone was answered
by my mother.
And I told her who it was,
and now I didn't know anything
about all these,
the... the letters
and the guy coming there,
you know,
telling them I was dead.
So she answered the phone
and then she fainted,
and the phone went dead.
And then her sister,
who was there visiting,
and she fainted
when I told her who it was.
And then my oldest sister came
to the phone and she fainted.
So then there was a long pause
and my daddy answered the phone.
He said, "Who in the world
is this?"
And so I told him
and I used my middle name
at home.
It was Dowling.
And he said, "Well," he said,
"I knew you weren't dead."
But he said, "Look like I've got
a bunch of dead women here."
He said, "I've got to get them
up off the floor."
So he said, "Now, you hold on.
Don't... don't go away now.
I'll be back in a minute."
So he goes
and gets a pitcher of water
and he's pouring some water
in their face.
Come back to the phone
and he said,
"I think they're waking up.
Their eyes are moving.
He said, "They'll be able to
talk to you in a little bit."
And that's when they knew
I was in San Francisco.
NARRATOR:
By the fall of 1945,
750,000 service personnel
were returning
to civilian life every month.
("It's Been a Long, Long Time"
playing)
BING CROSBY:
Kiss me once,
then kiss me twice
Then kiss me once again
It's been a long, long time
Haven't felt like this,
my dear
Since I can't remember when
It's been a long, long time
You'll never know
how many dreams
I dreamed about you
Or just how empty
they all seemed without you
So kiss me once,
then kiss me twice
Then kiss me once again
It's been a long,
long time...
Long, long time.
TOM GALLOWAY:
Certainly when you come home,
it, uh, it's an occasion.
I didn't know how to really
react to it because...
you'd seen a lot of things that,
that, uh, you didn't ever think
you'd see.
But in any event,
it, other than, uh,
I'll never forget my mother
wanted to see.
For instance, I was just sitting
there with my shoes on.
And she wanted to see that I had
all my limbs and everything.
(laughs)
That I still had my feet.
And, uh, yeah,
she stayed with me a good while
till I showed her that I had...
had all my parts on me.
LEOPOLD:
No matter how great,
no matter how small,
no matter how indifferent,
no matter how stupendous,
regardless of the facts,
home has a unique quality
that just cannot be exceeded.
Home is the ultimate value
that humans venerate.
NARRATOR:
The war had rescued
Waterbury, Connecticut,
and the industries
that had provided
its nickname: "Brass City."
And at first,
its workers returned
to making the screws and washers
and buttons,
showerheads and alarm clocks,
toy airplanes
and lipstick holders
and cocktail shakers they'd been
making before Pearl Harbor.
But as the years went by,
the brass industry declined.
So did Brass City.
Ray Leopold came home for
a time, then moved away,
went into business
and eventually became
a fund-raiser for charity.
LEOPOLD:
I ran into a young man who was
the brother of a young man
I had known reasonably well.
He said, "What outfit
were you with, Ray?"
And I told him that I was
with the 28th Infantry.
He said, "My brother was
with that outfit."
And I said,
"Where is your brother?"
He said, "Oh, he didn't make it.
"He's dead.
He was killed in action."
And then he turned, he says,
"You were with the 28th, too,
and you are home and he isn't."
He couldn't get over the idea
that someone so dear to him as
his brother couldn't make it...
and someone who is more or less
an indifferent third person
made it.
AANENSON:
There are casualties in war
that... they never show up
as casualties.
They're internal casualties.
We all changed.
We went out as a bunch of kids.
Wars are fought by kids.
And we came back--
looked maybe the same, but
inside we were so different.
They thought we were
just odd, I guess.
"What's happened to Quent?
And I was wondering, "Nobody
knows, nobody understands,"
and I am not
good enough with words
to be able to tell 'em.
NARRATOR:
Quentin and Jackie Aanenson
did not return
to his father's farm
south of Luverne.
He went to Louisiana State
University instead
and eventually entered
the insurance business.
AL McINTOSH (dramatized):
"Luverne, Minnesota.
"October 25, 1945.
"A lad who was one
of the 'living dead'
"has returned to his home--
very much alive
"and bubbling over
with high spirits.
"To look at Sergeant
Frank Lane with his 160 pounds,
"you'd never realize now
"that he was one of those
emaciated, tortured souls
"who survived by some miracle,
"the horror of that
'Death March' at Bataan.
"And in some ways, returning
to the States and to Luverne
"is like rising again
from the dead
"because he has to acquaint
himself with so many things
that have happened
in this changing world."
"He has a lot
of brushing up to do
because nearly four whole years
have gone out of his life..."
"Four years in which
he descended
"into a black hole of silence,
"knowing nothing about what
was going on in the world
"except that it was
a terrible struggle
to just barely survive."
Al McIntosh, Rock County
Star-Herald.
NARRATOR:
More than 1,000 citizens
of Rock County, Minnesota,
served in uniform
during the war.
32 of them lost their lives.
The names of all those who
served were carefully painted
on a wooden roll of honor in
front of city hall in Luverne.
As the years passed, Minnesota
winters wore away the names.
One year, the monument
was taken down
to be repainted and repaired.
Somehow, it was lost.
SASCHA WEINZHEIMER:
Our hope was we were going
to have a new life,
and I remember driving up
on the day
that we drove through
to the ranch.
And it was like being
in Alice in Wonderland.
It was absolutely amazing.
NARRATOR:
Sascha Weinzheimer
and her family,
who had nearly starved to death
as prisoners of the Japanese
in Manila, settled on their
late grandfather's farm
in the Sacramento Valley.
WEINZHEIMER:
It was some sort of, um,
cultural shock coming back,
because your body's here,
but your mind isn't.
And to have to put up
with the stupidity
of some of the Americans
that have been living here.
They'd walk into a room
and say, "Oh, tell us
about your experience."
And then immediately
they'd say,
"Um, we had these coupons
"that had to be, you know,
uh, rationed,
and then we couldn't go here
because of the gasoline."
And so we just sort
of avoided everything.
And when people were talking
to us about our experience,
because it... they didn't want
to hear it, anyway.
NARRATOR:
Sacramento's wartime
transformation
from small-town state capital to
big city would prove permanent.
State government grew, too.
So did the military bases
on Sacramento's outskirts
as the world war was eventually
supplanted by the cold war.
Among the Sacramentans
returning home
were thousands of
Japanese-Americans
newly freed from
the inland camps
in which they had been
imprisoned
for no other reason
than their ancestry.
They struggled to recover
their property
and rebuild their lives.
The men of the 100th 442nd
Combat Team came home, too.
Robert Kashiwagi, wounded
four times in Italy and France,
got a job with the California
Highway Department.
KASHIWAGI:
When I showed up in the shop,
this one fellow from the floor
went to his foreman,
"Look, if that Jap is gonna work
here," he says, "I'm quitting."
And this foreman told me that.
And I says, "Well, you know,
I passed my test
"and I served overseas
and I think I did
"what I was supposed to do, so
I'm going to hold my position
and I'm going to remain here,
you know?"
And so, as I remained
there, why, he quit.
And then everything turned
a little bit better
as time went on, and it got
easier and easier for me.
And so I was able to serve
32 years and retire.
EUGENE SLEDGE (dramatized):
"The train trip home was
a nostalgic one for me.
"I was a proud American,
of course,
but I was also a terribly
homesick Southerner."
"A porter came through our car
"calling, 'Next stop,
Mobile! Next stop, Mobile!'
"My buddies shouted,
'That's you, Sledgehammer.'
"A thrill ran through me.
"There were countless times
it looked as though
"I would never live to see
the next moment,
"much less live to make it.
"And now, here we were, rolling
into the L & N Station.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
When Eugene came back
from the war,
he came directly here to see us.
I remember him well,
coming in with his uniform
and all of his ribbons and all.
And I thought, my,
you certainly are handsome!
I do remember thinking that,
how he had grown up.
He was no longer
that little young friend
of my young brother Sidney.
I suddenly had these two men
in my presence,
and I had that feeling about
both of 'em.
Uh, it was written
on their faces.
Their faces changed.
They just no longer
looked like boys.
They looked like men,
which they were.
NARRATOR:
The war had made Mobile
into a boomtown.
But by the time
Eugene Sledge came home,
some 40,000 defense jobs
had already disappeared.
Some workers left the city
for the small towns
where they'd been living
when the war began.
Others moved north and west to
bigger cities in search of work.
Returning black veterans, who
had fought for freedom overseas,
found themselves facing
the same segregation
they had left behind.
JOHN GRAY:
It would be a matter of disgust
and distaste with you
when you found out
that the fruits of victory
were not yours.
I never did appreciate going
to work at night.
And the police officer would
stop you at night and say,
"Hey, boy, where you going?"
And you come up to, uh,
to answer him.
"You got your hat on.
Take your hat off
when you talk to a white man."
And that kind of stuff, uh...
And I'd worked all night,
just about, at the railroad.
And didn't have a car,
so I had to walk home.
I cried all the way home.
It was, it was hurt.
NARRATOR:
John Gray eventually went on
to college, became a teacher
and then a beloved school
principal and community leader
for 50 years in Mobile.
Katharine Phillips briefly
became an airline stewardess
and married a former Navy pilot.
Her younger brother Sid,
who had encountered
terrible suffering
while serving with
the First Marine Division
and vowed to find a way
to do something about it,
went on to medical school
and became a doctor.
But there was one person
for whom he could do nothing.
SID PHILLIPS:
My friend Eugene was probably
as good a friend
as I've ever had
in my whole life,
but, uh, he could not
throw off the war.
He could not forget it.
It seemed to, uh, uh,
to haunt him.
SLEDGE (dramatized):
"As I strolled the streets
of Mobile,
"civilian life
seemed so strange.
"People rushed around in a hurry
"about seemingly
insignificant things.
"Few seemed to realize how
blessed they were to be free
and untouched
by the horrors of war."
"To them, a veteran was
a veteran; all were the same,
"whether one man had survived
the deadliest combat
or another had pounded
a typewriter while in uniform."
NARRATOR:
Eugene Sledge had been
an enthusiastic hunter
before the war.
Now he found he no longer
had the heart for it.
In combat, he had felt the same
terror his targets felt
when he fired at them, he said,
and he couldn't bear it that
they could not shoot back.
Nightmares plagued him.
He earned a business degree
under the G.I. Bill,
tried the insurance business
and abandoned it,
eventually became a biologist
and teacher.
"Science was my salvation,"
he remembered.
"It helped keep at bay
the flashbacks
from Peleliu and Okinawa."
"Close, constant study
of nature," his wife said,
"kept him from going mad."
But the war remained
with him nonetheless.
He still had
the tiny sheets of paper
on which he'd kept a journal
in the Pacific,
and finally,
at his wife's urging,
he turned it into
a combat memoir called
With the Old Breed.
Describing the horrors
he had endured
eventually allowed him to begin
to put them behind him.
Eugene Sledge died in 2001.
SLEDGE (dramatized):
"Until the millennium arrives
"and countries cease to enslave
others, it will be necessary
"to accept
one's responsibility to,
to make sacrifices for, one's
country as my comrades did."
"War is brutish, inglorious
and a terrible waste.
"Combat leaves an indelible mark
"on those who are forced
to endure it.
"The only redeeming factors were
my comrades' incredible bravery
and their devotion
to each other."
Eugene Sledge.
FRAZIER:
My hometown just gave me
a hero's welcome.
Couldn't ask for anybody
to be any nicer to you.
But, uh, little did you know
what was ahead.
And, uh, I didn't until it
started happening to me.
NARRATOR:
Glenn Frazier and his brother
O'Vaughn, who had served
with the Army in North Africa
and Italy,
happened to arrive home in Fort
Deposit, Alabama, the same day.
Their mother, Frazier recalled,
seemed "dazed"
to have both her boys back,
but she remembered
to give each of them the little
pile of Christmas packages
she'd bought and wrapped
but had been unable to send them
during the war.
When the boys stepped out
into the street,
they were mobbed
by friends and neighbors
happy to have them home.
Before Frazier joined
the Army in 1941,
he had confessed
to a high-school classmate
that he loved her.
She had waited patiently for him
for over three years,
until the Army formally told
his family Glenn was dead.
Frazier now eagerly asked
after her.
Hope that he and she
would one day marry
had helped sustain him
in captivity.
"I hate to tell you this,"
a friend told him,
"but she's getting married
this coming Sunday."
That night,
the nightmares began.
FRAZIER:
It was just like
real life again.
It was just so real.
It sort of kept me
from sleeping.
I got to the point where I
didn't even want to go to sleep.
My nerves were bothering me.
You couldn't tell anybody.
In those days, if you were
seeing a psychiatrist,
it didn't make any difference
whether it was military or what,
nobody'd give you a job.
NARRATOR:
Psychiatrists working
for the Veterans Administration
were of little help.
"Just act normal and you'll feel
normal," they told him.
Frazier eventually married,
had two children,
ran his own trucking business.
But the war would not go away.
FRAZIER:
I hated the Japanese
as hard as anybody,
I believe,
could ever hate for so long.
And mine was as deep.
I think I was justified
in the hate that I had.
But it come a time
when it wasn't,
it wasn't affecting them.
They didn't even know I existed.
They were over there
and having their fun
and getting their things,
their country straightened out.
And here I am over here, I'm
hating and hating and hating
and having the nightmares
and so forth.
And it, it...
I had to get rid of it.
I had to throw it off
because it was just completely
destroying me.
And I prayed and...
and with the preacher's help,
I got to the point to where
I woke up one morning
and I felt a little bit of...
more rested.
But my war lasted actually
another 30 years.
PAUL FUSSELL:
To forget the war would be,
not just impossible,
it would be immoral.
It doesn't get to me very often
except when I talk about it
like this
and I seldom do that, actually.
It's just something,
it never goes away.
It's something you have
to endure
the way you endured
the war itself.
There's no alternative.
You can't wipe out
these memories.
You can't wipe out what
you felt at that time
It's just part of, it's part of
your whole possession of life.
And I suppose it does some good.
NARRATOR:
For all those Americans
who lived through
the terrible conflict,
for those whose fathers and sons
and brothers
were lost or maimed,
as well as for those
whose only contact with combat
was listening to the radio
and reading the local paper,
it remains to this day,
simply, "The War."
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
The young men that came home
from the war were my neighbors
when I was a young married
woman, and they lived the war.
They married,
they established homes.
We all lived in a wonderful
little neighborhood
where the homes were built
for the G.I.'s.
And every night after we would
get the children to bed,
we would all gather and the boys
would exchange stories.
That was the great way
of entertaining ourselves.
The boy next door to me
had ridden with Patton
across Europe.
The boy across the street
went in on D-Day plus four,
hanging on to a machine gun
on a half-track,
and he said
he was four miles inland
before he could pry his hands
off the half-track.
He was scared out of his wits.
The boy catty-cornered
had been a medic
and had survived
battles in Europe.
And we would just sit
and listen, we wives.
We learned more about our
husbands and what they did
by listening
to them exchange stories.
But I realize,
as I've gotten older,
this was a healing for them.
AANENSON:
The dynamics of war are
so absolutely intense,
the drama of war
is so absolutely,
emotionally spellbinding,
that it's hard for you to go on
with a normal life
without feeling
something is missing.
Now, I have had
a wonderful life.
I have a family
that just is ideal,
and, uh, I've enjoyed my life.
But I find there are times
when I am pulled back
into the whirlpool.
I find that
the intensity of that experience
was so overwhelming
and almost intimidating,
that you can't quite
let go of it.
AL McINTOSH (dramatized):
"Luverne, Minnesota.
"All week long,
with 'Silent Night'
"running through my head,
I've been groping
for a Christmas story."
"Somehow, the story
always eluded me."
"A lot of servicemen
have been in.
"They told us where they spent
last Christmas overseas.
But you didn't need to write
a story about them."
"The story of their happiness
about being home
was written all over their faces
for the world to see."
"And now comes the time
when it comes our turn
"to extend our Christmas
greetings
to each and every one of you."
"May the joy of Christmas,
and a big share of its peace
"and beauty, be with you all,
every single day
of the new year to come."
Al McIntosh,
Rock County Star-Herald.
NORAH JONES:
For those who think
they have nothing to share
Who fear in their hearts
there is no hero there
Know each quiet act
of dignity
Is that which fortifies
The soul of a nation
That will never die
Let them say of me
I was one who believed
In sharing the blessings
I received
Let me know in my heart
When my days are through
America, America
I gave my best to you...
America...
I gave my best to you.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
Ripped by stlc8tr!