¶ If I could be with you
one hour tonight ¶
¶ If I were free
to do the things I might ¶
¶ I want you to know
that I wouldn't go ¶
¶ Till I told you, honey,
that I love you so ¶
¶ If I could be with you,
I'd love you long ¶
I'd love you strong ¶
¶ I'm telling you, too,
I'd be anything but blue ¶
¶ If I could be with you
for an hour ¶
¶ If I could be with you... ¶
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
During the war,
you just kept thinking
that life cannot begin
until this is over.
You just had to see again
all the boys
that you had known
and been fond of,
and know they were home safely.
Especially for me.
so I was still anticipating
my life ahead of me,
but I didn't know who
it would be spent with.
But I felt, if I could just
get my brother Sidney
back home again...
In fact, I talked to one
of my old boyfriends
two years ago,
and I said,
"Why didn't you propose to me?"
He said, "You wouldn't
have listened to me.
"Till you got Sidney home,
you wouldn't have
listened to anybody."
And he said,
"By the time that occurred,
I had lost all my nerve."
¶ I'd be anything but blue ¶
¶ If I could be with you
for one hour ¶
¶ If I could be with you. ¶
(alarm blaring)
JAMES A. FAHEY (dramatized):
"Sunday, June 18, off Saipan.
"All hands got up at 4:45 a.m.
"I had a swell sleep last night,
"even if it was only
for about six hours.
"We had church services
topside this morning,
"even though we are so close
to Japan,
and the Jap fleet
might be close by."
James A. Fahey.
NARRATOR:
The Japanese fleet was close by.
Vice Admiral Jisaburo Ozawa
had formulated a new plan--
to destroy both
the American land forces,
still struggling their way
inland on Saipan,
and the American fleet offshore.
He would send waves
of carrier-based warplanes
against the fleet,
then reinforce the Japanese
garrison on the island.
"The fate of our Empire rests
on this one battle," he said.
"Everyone must give all he has."
(alarm blaring)
But the Americans
had intercepted coded messages
and knew they were coming.
Hundreds of planes took off
to engage the Japanese.
The Battle
of the Philippine Sea
would be the greatest carrier
battle of the Pacific war,
nearly four times
as big as Midway.
It was clear the Americans
now had an edge.
Their pilots were better
trained than the enemy's.
Their planes were better, too.
And they had twice
as many of them.
Maurice Bell,
who had been working
in a Mobile shipyard
when he was drafted,
and joined the Navy
rather than the Army
because, he said,
he didn't want to sleep
in a hole in the ground,
was serving as a gunner
aboard the heavy cruiser
USS Indianapolis,
now the flagship
of the 5th Fleet.
MAURICE BELL:
I was sitting up there
with the binoculars
and, all of a sudden,
I saw a torpedo plane
diving in on that ship
right behind us.
And, just as he launched
his torpedoes,
or was ready to launch them,
they hit him with fire.
They was firing at him.
And the plane tumbled over
and crashed.
Five seconds behind him
was another one.
They hit him and he crashed.
About five more seconds,
there's a third one come in,
and they hit him,
and it throwed that plane
in a twist, and the torpedoes
fell end over end
and hit the water,
and the plane crashed.
I was watching all that
with my binoculars.
NARRATOR:
The Americans lost
29 planes that day,
but they shot down
at least 273.
American submarines sank
two Japanese carriers, as well.
Those who took part
in the one-sided contest
remembered it as the
"Great Marianas Turkey Shoot."
FAHEY (dramatized):
"Tuesday, June 20.
"At 4:00 p.m. this afternoon,
"we got the good news
we have been waiting for.
"The Jap fleet
is running away from us
"and heading
for the Philippines.
We picked up speed
and are after them."
NARRATOR:
Late the following day,
American spotter planes
located the retreating
enemy fleet.
Within ten minutes,
216 U.S. warplanes
swarmed off the carrier
decks to attack it,
even though darkness
was falling
and fuel was likely to run out
before they could return.
(rapid gunfire)
(explosion)
The Americans sank
one carrier...
...and badly damaged
three others,
destroyed 65 more
Japanese planes
and then started for home.
(Duke Ellington's
"Echoes of Harlem" plays)
FAHEY (dramatized):
"The time dragged as we waited
to hear from our pilots."
"Everyone kept his fingers
crossed, hoping for the best.
It was like waiting in the death
house for a pardon."
"Then something never before
done in wartime happened.
"All the ships in this huge
fleet put their lights on,
and flares were dropped
into the water."
"This would make it easier
for our pilots to land
"and if they did hit the water,
they could be saved."
NARRATOR:
Only 20 American planes
failed to return,
but 80 were lost
within sight of the carriers,
sputtering into the sea
or crashing on the decks.
All but 49 pilots
and crewmen were recovered.
FAHEY (dramatized):
"A great job was done
by everyone
to save our pilots' lives."
"The Japs would never
do anything like this."
("Concerto for Clarinet,
Strings, Harp and Piano"
by Aaron Copland playing)
AL McINTOSH (dramatized):
"Luverne, Minnesota.
"We've had a couple of letters
"from boys out
in the South Pacific
"asking for more of those
columns describing
"how life 'goes on'
back in Rock County.
"Well, this is being written
"the evening
of the Fourth of July,
"the quietest Fourth
that Rock County has spent
"in many a decade.
"First, people hung out
their flags
"either at their home
or their place of business.
You never saw so many flags
being displayed in Luverne."
"Then about noon
they headed for the park
down by the river,
under the big trees."
"Some of the others,
with their elders,
"were busy in a softball game.
"The old-timers drifted over
"to the horseshoe pitching
headquarters.
"As far away as the highway,
you could hear
"the familiar 'clink'
of the shoes
hitting the steel peg."
NARRATOR:
By the Fourth of July, 1944,
more than a million men
had landed in Normandy
and were struggling to make
progress among the hedgerows.
That week, British planes
would drop 2,500 tons
of bombs on Caen,
beginning a third attempt to
take the city from the Germans.
When it was over,
2,000 French civilians
had been crushed or blown apart
and the Germans had withdrawn
to new defensive positions
just south of what was
left of the city.
Meanwhile, on the Eastern front,
the Red Army
had 28 German divisions
encircled in Belorussia
and killed 40,000 men when they
tried to fight their way out.
The Soviets then took Minsk,
the capital of Belorussia,
and with it more than 2,000
tanks and 150,000 prisoners.
Winston Churchill wrote
to Josef Stalin,
whose country
had suffered the most
at the hands of the Germans,
"The enemy is burning
and bleeding
"on every front at once...
and I agree with you that
this must go on to the end."
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"We said the Fourth
was a quiet day.
"There wasn't excitement--
"no speeches, no parades,
no band music.
"Everybody spent the day
quietly,
but they were all thinking
of you boys"...
"and hoping and praying
that this would be
the last Fourth of July
you'd spend away from home."
"Well, that's about the story
as to how things are
going back home."
Al McIntosh, Rock County
Star-Herald.
(gunfire)
JAMES A. FAHEY (dramatized):
"Today is the Fourth of July,
and a good way to celebrate it
is by killing Japs."
"We fired star shells
all last night and all morning
"until daylight today.
It rained for a while
this morning."
"Yesterday and today
our artillery on the beach
"gave the Japs
an awful pounding.
"The Press News said that
in the first couple of weeks
"of fighting on Saipan
over 6,500 Japs were killed.
"There is a very strong odor
from the beach.
It smells like burnt flesh."
RAY PITTMAN:
Well, your Japanese soldier is
probably the toughest soldier
that fought in World War II
other than the Marines.
And I mean, they were tough.
And you surround one,
he's going to keep fighting.
In Germany, you surround 50,000
Germans and they'd surrender.
Or Italians, they'd surrender.
But you surround one Japanese,
he's going to keep fighting
right on.
He's going to keep firing
till you kill him.
And they had one thing
in mind-- it's killing you.
NARRATOR:
The Japanese troops on Saipan,
now without hope
of rescue or reinforcement
from their shattered fleet,
were resolved to die
rather than surrender.
American forces had cleared
the airfield
and begun a slow, agonizing
march toward the north,
trying to keep from killing
Japanese civilians
while flushing Japanese troops
from their hiding places.
Again and again, Japanese
soldiers threw themselves
at the American guns,
shouting "Banzai!"--
apparently willing, even eager,
to die for the Emperor.
PITTMAN:
We'd hear the Japanese talking
and drinking
and clanking bottles
and everything.
And we knew there
was one coming.
But they'd come at us
and, and, uh...
we had machine guns set up
doing crossfires every way.
They'd have to get through
the crossfire
before we started shooting,
but then some
of them would get through.
I had one that came at me
with a bayonet
and I shot him in the face
and he fell
in the foxhole with me,
and bled all over my pants
and the bayonet went down
between my arm and my chest.
Nearly got me and him dead.
NARRATOR:
Before dawn on July 7,
the Japanese launched
a final banzai charge.
3,000 men, some forced
from their hospital beds
and barely able to walk,
many armed only with clubs
and rocks and shovels,
charged into the American lines.
Bulldozers buried all
but a handful of them
the next morning.
It was the largest banzai
charge of the Pacific war.
SAM HYNES:
We thought of the Japanese
as... mysteriously unlike us.
We knew that they would
fight to the death
where, probably, we would
have surrendered.
We began to learn,
though I don't think we...
gathered a lot of information
about the prison camps,
but we had some and we knew
that they were capable of...
of a cruelty and sadism
in a way that we hoped
our people weren't,
though I've never been quite
sure what Americans would do
in the...
exactly the same situation.
NARRATOR:
On July 10, Saipan was
officially declared "secured."
In almost four weeks
of fighting,
16,525 Americans had been
killed, wounded
or reported missing,
the costliest battle
in the Pacific to date.
Among them
were several black Marines
who had finally
been permitted to fight.
"The Negro Marines are
no longer on trial,"
the Marine commandant said.
"They are Marines, period."
Almost 30,000 Japanese soldiers
were dead, as well.
In the final days of the battle,
some 4,000 terrified
Japanese civilians,
mostly women and children,
had fled
to the island's northern tip, a
high plateau called Marpi Point.
Their government had
convinced many of them
that it was their duty
to kill themselves
rather than fall into the hands
of the cruel Americans,
and the handful of Japanese
soldiers who had survived
were prepared to shoot them
if they hesitated.
Some Marines risked their lives
to halt the madness;
Japanese-American interpreters
with bullhorns
pleaded with civilians
to give up.
But more than a thousand were
either killed by Japanese troops
or chose suicide.
PITTMAN:
When we got down
to the end of the island,
they were jumping off the cliff
at Marpi Point.
They thought we'd eat them.
They thought we'd kill them
and eat them.
Stuff like that.
It's just the Japanese
mentality--
they don't want to get captured.
I never did go down to look
at the bottom of the cliff,
but it must have been
a mess down there.
NARRATOR:
A few Japanese soldiers
decided to swim out to sea,
rather than surrender.
PITTMAN:
So we decided, well,
they're going to die anyway,
we might as well shoot them.
So we set up there
shooting at them.
We'd hear the slugs
hitting around them
and sometimes somebody
would hit one.
But it was a long shot,
trying to hit their head.
FAHEY (dramatized):
"Sunday, July 16:
"It was a warm, sunny day,
"although it rained
during church services.
"It was the first time
I ever went to church
"and saw dead bodies
floating by.
"It is nothing to see men,
women and children floating.
"There must be thousands of Japs
in the waters near Saipan.
The ships just run over them."
NARRATOR:
The Americans went on to take
Tinian and then Guam,
the first U.S. possession
to be recaptured.
The fall of the Marianas
and the damage done
to the Japanese fleet
forced Hideki Tojo to resign
as the Japanese premier.
His successors--
first a general,
then an admiral,
vowed to fight on.
The Japanese had succeeded
at one thing:
The willingness of their
soldiers and civilians
to die rather than surrender
had made Allied planners
painfully conscious
of the bloodshed
that would surely accompany
the invasion
of the Japanese homeland.
DANIEL INOUYE:
The first man I killed.
I was then a sergeant.
I was leading a little patrol,
and I happened to glance up
at the next hill,
and I saw this German.
And so I signaled the men,
and they all quieted down
and I said, "That's mine."
I very deliberately got my rifle
and set the sights,
got the wind,
and just squeezed the trigger,
and bang.
You would think
that at that moment,
after killing a human being,
you would feel
a little remorseful.
I felt... pleasure.
And the men applauded.
"You were terrific, Dan,"
you know?
That was the early times
in the war,
and, uh, we were taught
to kill the enemy.
He was not a good person;
he was an evil person.
So you felt
you had accomplished something.
Before I became a soldier,
I sang in a choir.
I was a Sunday school teacher.
"Thou shalt not kill"
was real to me.
And here I was,
killing someone
and not feeling remorseful.
NARRATOR:
The fall of Rome,
just before D-Day,
had boosted morale,
but it had not ended
the fighting in Italy.
The Allies had failed
to destroy the German army,
and as it fell back,
Hitler sent in reinforcements,
resolved to make the Allies pay
for every inch of territory
they gained.
Among the Americans
in closest pursuit
were the Japanese-American men
of the 442nd Regimental
Combat Team,
fresh from training and eager
to demonstrate their loyalty
to the government that
had forced so many of them
and their families
into internment camps.
It had not been easy
to persuade the military
to give them that chance.
Eisenhower's staff
had initially rejected the idea
of Japanese-American troops,
but General Mark Clark,
commander of the Fifth Army
in Italy,
had said that he would
"take anybody that will fight."
The 442nd would find themselves
fighting alongside
the battle-tested
100th Infantry Battalion,
made up mostly of
Japanese-Americans from Hawaii,
who had been in Italy
for months.
(distant explosion)
They had fought so bravely
and lost so many men,
that they came to be called
the "Purple Heart Battalion."
Together,
the newcomers of the 442nd
and the combat-wise survivors
of the 100th
would be asked to spearhead
the Fifth Army's
drive northward from Rome.
Among them were two men
from Sacramento
whose families
were still behind barbed wire
in the United States.
ROBERT KASHIWAGI:
It was the last
campfire gathering we had
before we went under fire,
and our company commander
stood up
in front of us
Japanese-Americans,
and he says that,
"We're going under fire
"and the very first one
of you guys
that turns your tail
and run the other way,"
he says, "I'm gonna shoot you."
I says, "Oh, that's something.
"You don't ever say that
to a Japanese,
because that's
a very derogatory term."
NARRATOR:
Private First Class
Robert Kashiwagi was guarding
a crossroads the Germans
had only recently abandoned
when he came under fire
for the first time.
(explosions)
KASHIWAGI:
That was a terrible situation
to get into,
because the Germans
would target that crossroad.
SOLDIER:
Ready.
KASHIWAGI:
We were caught in that barrage.
The shell was popping
all around us.
We didn't have time
to dig a hole for a foxhole.
And we were digging the hole
with our nose,
trying to get our head
down below the ground.
NARRATOR:
The white captain
who had insulted
the men of the 442nd
was no longer with them.
KASHIWAGI:
An artillery shell dropped...
killed his first sergeant,
his, uh, runner
and a radio man,
all in front of his eyes.
This captain
became shell-shocked.
He was just shaking
and turned completely white,
and he was not
hardly able to walk.
They almost had to lead him out.
(indistinct chatter)
(artillery fire,
gunfire in distance)
Because of our action,
there were two Germans,
young men...
(voice breaking):
...killed in action,
dead on the side of this...
side of the hill,
and that affected me
pretty... pretty bad.
Because, uh, they were
19 years of age, about,
they were the same age as me,
and I thought to myself,
gee, if this was stateside,
we could've been going
to school together, you know.
That was my first
bad experience of the war,
you know, to see an enemy dead,
still recognizing their youth,
and, uh, that this
shouldn't be happening.
And so that hurted me.
(automatic gunfire)
NARRATOR:
Over the next few weeks,
Japanese-Americans would
distinguish themselves
at Belvedere, Sasetta,
Castellina, Pastina,
Loranzana, Luciana.
The 442nd 100th
fought so well and so hard
that when General Mark Clark
led his men
into the important city
of Livorno,
he insisted that they march
right behind him.
Now everybody wanted them.
Soon, they were back
in action again.
MAN:
Fire!
NARRATOR:
Sergeant Daniel Inouye,
from Honolulu, Hawaii,
was in Company E, 2nd Battalion.
(explosion, gunfire)
INOUYE:
This one experience was so bad
that I had to see the chaplain.
We had just attacked
a farmhouse,
and I ran up there,
and sure enough,
there were three Germans,
two dead and one alive.
He was leaning against the wall.
And he spoke in German,
and I don't speak German,
and he was saying,
"Kamerad, Kamerad,"
and he had his hand up there...
to surrender.
Then all of a sudden,
he stuck his hand
into his jacket,
and the only conclusion
I could reach instantaneously
was that he was going
for a... a gun.
So almost instinctively,
I reacted,
and I hit his face
with the butt of my rifle.
And his hand flew out,
and in his hand
was a bunch of photographs.
He wanted to show me pictures
of his wife and his children.
That's war.
(piano playing
"It's Been a Long, Long Time")
(whistle blowing,
engine chugging)
BARBARA PERKINS:
During the war,
it was hard to keep track
of your loved ones.
Mail was very slow.
And even the news media,
if you knew
what company and troop
and all that was in,
those things weren't published
in any detail at all
as to pinpoint
just where they were.
Well, you just never know.
We lived with that.
That was part of our part
we had to play.
(song ends)
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"Luverne, Minnesota.
"July 20, 1944.
"Somehow,
the gossip grapevine
"had heard that
there was a telegram
"coming through
after 6:00 p.m. last Friday
for Mr. and Mrs. Ray Lester
of Magnolia."
"Ray Lester heard about it,
and his heart was heavy.
"He started walking
down the street.
On the way he met
Scotty Dewar, the depot agent."
"'Which one is it?'
asked Lester,
"because there were four boys
to worry about in that family.
"After being told,
he went sorrowfully home
to break the news to his wife."
"that was made at the dance
in Magnolia that night.
"When the crowd heard the news,
the dance was halted immediately
"out of respect to the memory
of that fighting Marine
who died on Saipan."
Al McIntosh, Rock County
Star-Herald.
FRANK SINATRA:
Gentlemen of the armed forces,
this is the hoodlum
from Hoboken.
I'd like to sing
a tune for you.
My name's Sinatra
and I hope "yiz" like it, hey.
¶ Long ago and far away ¶
¶ I dreamed a dream one day ¶
¶ And now that dream
is here beside me... ¶
AANENSON:
We would be sitting
around our tent area
in the apple orchard
in Normandy
and we would discuss what
they would have to pay us
to really do what we had
just done that day.
We agreed first
that we might do it
for $1,000 a mission, but
less than ten days later--
our losses had
gone up heavily--
we decided that we
wouldn't consider doing it
for less than $10,000 a mission.
And I think that it went
off the radar screen in value
before the end of July,
because there's no way
that you could be
a mercenary enough,
they could pay you enough,
to do what we were doing
on a volunteer basis.
(plane flies over)
NARRATOR:
In the weeks after D-Day,
American pilots, including
Quentin Aanenson,
continued to fly their missions
over the fields and hedgerows
of Normandy every day,
trying to focus on the help
they were giving
to the men on the ground,
and to avoid thinking too hard
about the losses
in their own ranks.
NEWSREEL NARRATOR:
Dashing to a hedgerow
to clear Nazis out
of another line of hedge
across a meadow.
(explosions and gunfire)
The enemy position's blasted
and the Germans occupying
it have enough,
so out comes the white flag
of surrender,
more prisoners taken
in the drive
to the important city
of Saint-Lô.
As the infantry pushes forward,
the way is cleared
by the smashing power
of tanks and heavy artillery.
NARRATOR:
On July 18, Saint-Lô--
or what was left of it after
six weeks of Allied bombing--
fell to the Americans.
General Bradley's forces
had finally reached the line
Allied planners had
expected his men to reach
just a few days after D-Day.
And he was now ready
to send his armor
roaring through the German
lines beyond the city.
But first, Allied warplanes
were called in
to blast an opening.
The operation
was called "Cobra."
The correspondent
Ernie Pyle was down below,
watching from a battered
French farmhouse
with officers from
the 4th Infantry Division.
"of the mass onslaught came over
a little before 10:00 a.m.
They were the fighters
and dive-bombers."
"We stood in the barnyard of
a French farm and watched them
barrel nearly straight down
out of the sky..."
(airplanes flying over)
"And then a new sound gradually
droned into our ears,
"a sound deep,
all-encompassing,
"with no notes in it,
just a gigantic far-away
surge of doom-like sound."
"It was the heavies,
"coming on
with a terrible slowness
"in flights of 12,
three flights to a group
and in groups stretched
out across the sky."
"I thought it would never end."
"And then the bombs came."
"It began up ahead
as the crackle of popcorn
"and almost instantly swelled
into a monstrous fury of noise
that seemed surely to destroy
all the world around us."
NARRATOR:
The bombs continued falling
for an hour and a half.
The bright day grew dark
with smoke, Pyle remembered,
and the steady roar
seemed to fill
"all the space
for noise on earth."
Two days later, on July 27,
the First Army poured
through the newly opened gap
out into the countryside
beyond the hedgerows.
For weeks,
the Americans on the ground
had felt fortunate
to gain 1,000 yards a day.
Soon they would be
covering up to 40 miles
in the same amount of time.
The Germans were reeling.
On August 7, the Americans
stopped a counterattack
cold at Mortain,
and after five days of battle,
forced the Germans to retreat.
Then, on August 15,
in the south of France,
American
and Free French forces landed,
fanned out
in all directions,
and began driving northward.
The following day,
Hitler reluctantly agreed
to pull his battered
Seventh Army
out of Normandy.
It began a desperate
retreat toward Germany.
The Allies caught them
near the town of Falaise.
the Allies poured fire
into the fleeing men...
...from the ground
and from the air.
80,000 Germans ran
the terrible gauntlet.
At least 10,000 died,
so many that the pilots
of the Allied spotter planes
hundreds of feet
above the battlefield
were nauseated by the stench.
So many that after
the shooting had stopped,
General Eisenhower
remembered,
"it was literally possible
"to walk for hundreds
of yards at a time,
stepping on nothing
but dead and decaying flesh."
AANENSON:
I had caught
a bunch of Germans
in... in double tandem trucks,
and they were just
massed in there.
There was so much, uh,
firing into that
and I was the only one
that was firing.
My wingman... his guns
had been jammed and, uh...
the effect on me was that
my right hand quit working
and I was on the way home
and I couldn't
grip with that hand.
So I had to put my left hand
over on top of the stick
to maintain it and go
and land with that.
When I'd have
these nightmares
in years after the war,
many years after the war,
if it was one relating
to that mission
or missions like that,
when I'd get up in the morning,
go out to the kitchen,
Jackie would be there
and she would have had
the coffee made,
and she could tell
when I walked in
that my right hand
wasn't functioning right.
She'd pour a cup
of coffee, not say a word.
She'd hand it
to my left hand.
Never a word said.
We just went on.
(explosions, mortar fire)
PAUL FUSSELL:
A soldier's letter
I was reading recently
is in answer
to his mother's letter.
He was fighting in Europe
somewhere
and his mother
was very frightened
that he was going to be killed.
And she wrote him
and said, "Be careful.
For God's sake, be careful."
And he said,
"You can't be careful.
You can only be lucky."
There's no way, whatever,
to escape it by... by technique
or care or attitude
or fast movement
or by athletic skills and so on.
You're just lucky.
The shell hits somebody
who is not yourself.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
We lived in constant fear
of the telegrams.
Each day we would read the lists
in the newspaper
to see if we could identify any
of the names that were there.
We just never knew when we'd
lose someone that we loved.
BURT WILSON:
During the war,
it was kind of surreal;
we never saw anybody die,
we never saw anybody maimed or
wounded or anything like that.
What amounted to a surrealistic
feeling about the war
came to an end one day
when our neighbors, um,
put a gold star in the window
and pulled all the blinds down.
Their oldest son
had been killed in Italy.
In Sacramento in those days,
the way you dealt
with something like that
was pulling all the shades down
and never coming out
of the house.
And so every time you walked
past that house,
the whole idea of death
was brought home to you
because of the shades drawn
and the gold star in the window.
NARRATOR:
Since D-Day, telegrams
from the War Department
had been arriving on doorsteps
all across America
at a rate inconceivable
just a year earlier.
Mrs. Augusta Niland
of Tonawanda, New York,
received three of them.
One son had died on Omaha Beach,
a second at Sainte Mère-Eglise;
a third was missing
in action in Burma.
A fourth son would be pulled out
of the line,
so that at least one of her boys
was sure to survive the war.
28 men from the tiny town
of Bedford, Virginia,
had landed on Omaha Beach.
19 of them died.
Three more died fighting
in Normandy.
Private First Class
James Donohue
and Staff Sergeant
Frederick Smith,
specially trained Army Rangers,
were lost on June 6,
the first of ten boys
from Waterbury, Connecticut,
who would be buried in Normandy.
McINTOSH: (dramatized):
"Here is one
of life's tragedies.
"Mrs. Henry Smook went
over to Sioux Falls
"with her youngest boy,
Harold, 17.
"It wasn't a shopping expedition
or a long-planned day of fun.
"She had gone
with her youngest son
"to give her consent
to his joining the Navy.
"She didn't know
that while she was there,
a telegram had come
to her home in Luverne"...
"telling her of the death
of her son in France,
Private First Class
Herman Smook."
NARRATOR:
Herman Smook had died
four days after D-Day,
the first Rock County death
on European soil.
("Concerto for Clarinet,
Strings, Harp and Piano"
by Aaron Copland playing)
All across France, the Germans
were in full retreat.
Since D-Day,
they had lost some 240,000 men;
another 200,000 had surrendered.
Allied casualties
were terrible, too.
256,000 soldiers and airmen
had been killed,
wounded, captured,
or reported
as missing in action.
At least 19,000 French civilians
had died, as well.
Countless French villages
had been pounded into dust.
But most of France was free.
("Echoes of France
[La Marseillaise]"
by Django Reinhardt playing)
On August 25, 1944, after
four years of Nazi occupation,
Paris, the City of Light,
was liberated.
OLLIE STEWART (dramatized):
"I, Ollie Stewart, of sound mind
"and fairly sober character,
do solemnly give my word
"that I have never been kissed
so much in all my life.
"Almost every woman I meet
on the street stops
"and kisses me on both cheeks.
It is a beautiful custom."
AANENSON:
We were flying
a mission near Paris,
and as I pulled off
my strafing run
and I turned back over the city
and as I looked down, there were
just thousands of people
jamming the streets
of the Champs Elysées
and around the Eiffel Tower
and the Arc de Triomphe,
and I realized
that I was seeing something
that was basically
the culmination
of why we were there.
We are winning this war.
The good guys are going
to come out ahead.
("American Anthem"
by Gene Scheer playing)
NORAH JONES:
¶ Each generation ¶
¶ From the plains
to distant shore ¶
¶ With the gifts
they were given ¶
¶ Were determined
to leave more ¶
¶ Battles fought together ¶
¶ Acts of conscience
fought alone... ¶
¶ These are the seeds ¶
¶ From which America has grown ¶
¶ Let them say of me ¶
¶ I was one who believed ¶
¶ In sharing the blessings ¶
¶ That I received ¶
¶ Let me know in my heart ¶
¶ When my days are through... ¶
¶ America, America ¶
¶ I gave my best to you... ¶
¶ America... ¶
¶ I gave my best ¶
¶ To you. ¶
("The Wang Wang Blues" by the
Benny Goodman Sextet playing)
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
Ripped by stlc8tr!