(waves lapping)
QUENTIN AANENSON:
We were all granted
about ten days' leave
for our final visit
to our homes.
This was around the middle
of April, 1944.
So I went up to Luverne
to see my parents,
my brothers and sisters.
And it was a very difficult
time, because I knew...
I had the orders
in my possession
that would be sending me
to the European theater
of operations,
and I knew that
we had been assigned
to fly this terribly dangerous
type of combat mission.
So...
when I was leaving
and saying good-bye
to my mother and dad,
we went to the train
station in Luverne
to catch the midnight train.
My sister Mavis was with me,
and I took her aside and
we walked down the platform
for a ways, and I told her
what my assignment had been...
and that the odds
were pretty great
that, uh, I would be killed.
So I had told her...
to be very much aware
of this possibility
and that she should be...
prepared to help my parents.
(dramatic newsreel fanfare)
NEWSREEL ANNOUNCER:
This immense piling up
of war supplies in Britain
is massed for the giant blow
designed to knock out the Nazi--
an astounding panorama
of everything that you
can think of... and more.
Invasion shipping massed
in British harbors
along the English Channel--
barges and boats.
Imagine those stacked-up
amphibious craft
when they stream in swarms
for the landing.
Bombers, which,
in the ground invasion
must keep on hammering,
gliders for airborne troops,
and myriad fighter planes
for the monster air battles
of the offensive designed to be
the final phase
of the European war.
Acres of planes reaching
far into the distance.
("I'm Confessin'" by
The Benny Goodman Sextet plays)
NARRATOR:
By the late spring of 1944,
on both sides of the world,
there were signs that the tide
of war had begun to turn.
The Allies had stopped Japan's
expansion in the Pacific.
They had taken Guadalcanal
in the Solomons
and Tarawa in the Gilberts,
had savaged the enemy
fleet at Midway,
and had begun the long climb
from island to island
toward the Japanese homeland.
In the European theater,
the Allies had
cleared North Africa
of Axis forces and taken Rome.
Allied warplanes were still
bombing Germany night and day.
The Battle of the Atlantic
had been won,
the sea lanes were now open,
and men and weapons and supplies
were flooding into Britain.
And in the east, the Red Army
had driven the Germans
from the Ukraine
and was moving into Poland.
Back home, in places
like Luverne, Minnesota;
Waterbury, Connecticut;
Mobile, Alabama;
and Sacramento, California,
Americans did their best to go
about their normal lives.
(intro to "It's Been
a Long, Long Time" plays)
BING CROSBY:
¶ Kiss me once,
then kiss me twice ¶
¶ Then kiss me once again ¶
¶ It's been a long,
long time ¶
¶ Haven't felt
like this, my dear ¶
¶ Since I can't remember when ¶
¶ It's been a long,
long time... ¶
NARRATOR:
But in the back
of everyone's mind,
hope was combined with dread.
In spite of the progress
that had been made,
everything that had happened
so far in the war
had been a mere preliminary.
The Japanese empire
had begun to shrink,
but its rulers seemed determined
to defend to the death
every island that remained.
Rome may have fallen,
but everyone knew
that Hitler's grip on Europe
could not be broken
until Allied troops
crossed the English Channel,
smashed the German defenses
and drove the Nazis
out of France.
Hundreds of thousands
of sons and fathers and husbands
would be called upon
to gamble their lives
for the sake of victory.
CROSBY:
¶ You'll never know ¶
¶ How many dreams
I dreamed about you ¶
¶ Or just how empty they
all seemed without you ¶
¶ So kiss me once... ¶
NARRATOR:
Naval Ensign Joseph Vaghi
of Bethel, Connecticut--
just up the road
from Waterbury--
went home to say good-bye
to his family that spring.
He had his orders
to go overseas,
and it seemed
to him and to them,
that he would likely
be one of those
who would be asked to run
that terrible risk.
VAGHI:
It was very difficult
because I had two other brothers
already in the service
she knew all of us were going
to go eventually.
And, as it turned out,
we all did go.
All of us were in the service.
And that... that was
kind of rough.
But leaving, she had chin up,
you know, she...
we spoke in Italian.
She spoke English very well,
but she said all of the
sentimental things in Italian.
She said, "Mio caro figlio,
Dio stai con lei.
Non dimenticare
mai tuoi genitori,"
and, uh, it goes on like that.
(newsreel fanfare plays)
NEWSREEL ANNOUNCER:
Hundreds of miles
of invasion coast
are heavily fortified,
bristling with gun emplacements,
as Hitler prepares for
the coming test of supremacy,
battle for the greatest
of beachheads.
Gigantic coastal guns
go into place,
ready to rise up
when the zero hour comes,
when the Allies move
on Hitler's Europe.
(explosions)
No room for complacency.
Hitler is prepared.
(explosions)
NARRATOR:
The Germans had known for months
that the Allies were going
to open the second front
that Soviet leader Josef Stalin
had been demanding since 1941.
Hitler had used that time
to construct his Atlantic Wall,
1,670 miles of fortified
gun emplacements,
radar and observation towers
and bunkers that stretched
from Denmark
all the way south
to the Spanish frontier.
Meanwhile, across
the English Channel,
more than a million
and a half Americans
were now in Britain
waiting for the signal
to start the invasion,
an invasion that would determine
the success or failure
of the Allied effort in Europe.
General Dwight Eisenhower
was in overall command.
The assault was to proceed
in three phases.
First, paratroopers
would be dropped
behind the beaches
in the dead of night
to confuse the enemy and seize
the roads and bridges
that led inland from them.
Then, wave after wave
of airplanes
were to batter German defenses,
destroying enemy emplacements
and creating craters
on the beaches
in which assault troops
could take shelter.
Finally, a massive flotilla
was to ferry thousands
of British, Canadian
and American troops
toward the French coast.
Allied commanders planned
five coordinated landings
along a 45-mile stretch
of the Normandy coastline
between the Cotentin Peninsula
and the Orne River.
Canadian and British troops
under General Bernard Montgomery
would fight their way ashore
at beaches code-named "Gold,"
"Juno," and "Sword,"
where they were also meant
to take the city of Caen,
nine miles inland.
Americans,
under General Omar Bradley,
would assault
"Utah" and "Omaha" beaches.
AL McINTOSH (dramatized):
Luverne, Minnesota.
May 25, 1944.
"Outwardly,
things haven't changed here.
"The lilacs
are out in full bloom.
"The countryside
was never greener.
"At night there are
a million stars
"winking in the sky, with
a couple of million bullfrogs
"parked along the edges
of the bank-full ditches
"croaking a mighty chorus.
"But things are different.
"The staffs of daily newspapers
all over the country
"are on alert in case news of
the invasion of Europe breaks.
"Key executives don't stir
very far from a telephone,
"day or night.
"The belief is
that the long-awaited flash
will come sometime after 11:00
p.m. but before 5:00 a.m."
Al McIntosh,
Rock County Star-Herald.
(drum beating slowly)
PAUL FUSSELL:
We tend to call it the real war.
The rest of it's
just the show-biz war.
The real war involves getting
down there and killing people,
and being killed yourself
or just barely escaping it.
And it gives you attitudes
about life and death
that are unobtainable
anywhere else.
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
Soldiers, sailors and airmen of
the Allied Expeditionary Force,
you are about to embark upon
the great crusade,
toward which we have striven
these many months.
The eyes of the world
are upon you.
The hopes and prayers of
liberty-loving people everywhere
march with you.
NARRATOR:
The greatest invasion in history
began just after midnight
on June 6, 1944--
D-Day--
as the first
of 24,000 paratroopers,
flown over the Channel
in more than 1,000 aircraft,
were dropped behind enemy lines
in Normandy.
The Germans' theory of
the defense of the continent
was they put, they built
pillboxes along the coastline
and they put
their old troops in it.
Then they put
their Panzer divisions
and their SS divisions
and their good divisions
back in central points,
the theory being that
when we hit the beach,
they would come in from
those points and drive us off.
Our job was to get in between
them and the beach
and to have them hit us
instead of the beach.
NARRATOR:
Most of the men of the British
6th Airborne dropped on target,
reassembled, and within an hour
had achieved their objectives,
seizing bridges across
the Orne and Dives Rivers
to keep German tanks
from mounting a counterattack
along the coast.
On the western flank,
the 16,000 Americans
belonging to the 101st
and 82nd Airborne divisions
were less fortunate.
Low-hanging clouds
blocked the moonlight
and obscured the landing zones.
The narrow neck of
the Cotentin Peninsula
was hard to hit from the air.
Many paratroopers fell
helplessly into the sea.
Others landed in fields
and river valleys
flooded by the Germans
and drowned.
Some were blown from the sky
as German tracer bullets
set off the explosives
they carried.
Still others were dropped so low
their parachutes
had no chance to open.
They hit, one man remembered,
with "a sound like ripe pumpkins
being thrown down
against the ground."
The men of the 101st Airborne
were scattered over an area
25 miles long by 15 miles wide.
Most of them got lost.
24 hours later, their commander
had still been unable to find
more than half
his surviving men.
(rapid gunfire)
Elements of the 82nd Airborne
came down in and around
the little town
of Sainte Mère-Eglise,
just behind Utah Beach.
The fighting was already raging
when a glider carrying
Dwain Luce of Mobile, Alabama,
headed toward the landing zone.
A survivor of the invasion
of Sicily
and the landing at Salerno,
he was a captain
in the 320th Glider Field
Artillery Battalion.
LUCE:
We had been in combat before
and we knew kind of what
we were getting into,
but, uh, we knew this
was the big bang
and it was... it was kind of...
worrisome, you might say.
NARRATOR:
Gliders were something new
in warfare:
silent, ideal for clandestine
landings behind enemy lines,
and capable of ferrying
equipment and vehicles
too heavy to be dropped
in any other way.
But they were also fragile,
covered with flammable fabric,
and hard to control.
And in some landing zones,
the Germans had placed forests
of sharpened poles
to tear them apart
and impale the men aboard.
More than half the gliders
missed their drop zones
and scores of pilots
and passengers were crushed
when vehicles and artillery
pieces slammed forward
during crash landings.
LUCE:
I remember, in my glider, I was
sitting up next to the pilot
and I leaned over his shoulder
to look at it
and we dove over those trees,
we were doing 110 miles an hour
and I thought,
this is no speed to land.
But it was too late to change.
I fortunately did not land
in front of any antitank guns,
which were vicious.
I had a friend that landed
in front, in front of one
and he was cut in half.
And, uh, those are things
you don't like to think about
or talk about.
NARRATOR:
Dwain Luce somehow
made it out of his glider
and quickly found himself
part of the continuing battle
to hold Sainte Mère-Eglise.
LUCE:
Oh, we had a fight,
and the Germans
moved people in in a hurry.
(machine gun fire)
You see, we didn't
have heavy weapons...
and we were fighting
heavy weapons.
NARRATOR:
The fighting was confused.
There were no established lines.
LUCE:
There was some guy up on a hill
above me trying
to disrupt my life.
He was, he was shooting at us
and trying to, trying to get us.
And it's kind of like cops and
robbers in a degree because,
I mean, you were in there
mixed up all with them.
they wasn't on one side
and we were on the other;
we were all like scrambled eggs.
NARRATOR:
Surrounded, isolated, out of
communication with one another,
Dwain Luce and his unit
struggled to hold their ground
and block German tanks,
while they waited
for the landing force
to take Utah Beach
and come to their rescue.
LUCE:
Whenever we went in
behind the lines,
they always gave us,
uh, morphine.
The morphine was a little thing
like a toothpaste tube
except it had a sharp, uh, point
when you unscrewed it, you know,
and you could then stick
the needle and break it
and then you pop it in your arm.
We were back there where
if you really got hit bad,
nobody could take care of you.
Sainte Mère-Eglise,
it was a mess.
Terrible.
AANENSON:
Early in the morning
we were awakened
from our bunks--
about 25 or 30 of us--
at the air base that was
just above London,
and we were told to
get in our flight gear
and meet in the briefing room.
And so we assembled in there,
just barely awake,
and we knew
it was something serious.
We could tell
by just the atmosphere.
There were two or three briefing
officers up at the front.
They had a large map
that was covered,
and as we took our seats and
they pulled the curtain back,
they said,
"Gentlemen, this is it.
The invasion of France
has begun."
NARRATOR:
At 4:30 a.m.,
Quentin Aanenson of Luverne
took off for France
as part of the flight
of 11,000 warplanes...
Lightnings and Lancasters
and Liberators;
Mosquitos and Marauders
and Mustangs;
Spitfires and Thunderbolts
and Flying Fortresses,
assigned to bomb and strafe
and batter German defenses
before the first troops
landed on the beaches.
It was Quentin Aanenson's
first combat mission.
As we came in over Normandy,
I looked off to the left,
and it was just a short look,
and I realized later
I was looking at Omaha Beach.
We had to be very careful
of our timing,
and we had to be very careful
that we didn't go inland
too far,
because the paratroopers
had been dropped in there.
And we didn't know exactly
where they were.
And as it turned out they didn't
know where they were either.
NARRATOR:
Aanenson dropped his bombs
and headed back to England.
AANENSON:
It was a mixture of some clouds,
but we could see down
into the Channel
and it was impossible
to understand
really what we were seeing.
There were ships everywhere.
ERNIE PYLE (dramatized):
"The best way I can describe
this vast armada
"and the frantic urgency
of the traffic
"is to suggest that you
visualize New York Harbor
"on its busiest day of the year
"and then just enlarge
that scene
"all the ocean
the human eye can reach,
clear around the horizon."
"And over the horizon.
There are dozens of times
that many."
Ernie Pyle.
NARRATOR:
More than 5,300 ships,
carrying 176,000 men,
were streaming
across the Channel:
battleships and tugboats,
cruisers and barges
and rusty freighters;
gunboats and hospital ships
and converted ocean liners;
ships filled with ammunition
and ships equipped to lay down
screens of smoke
to mystify the enemy--
and a fleet of more
than 2,000 landing craft
to ferry men and supplies
to the beach.
Joseph Vaghi was assigned to be
a beachmaster that morning.
It would be his job to use
flags, blinkers, and a megaphone
to get men, vehicles,
and supplies
safely ashore on Omaha Beach.
It was his first combat, too.
VAGHI:
I had no fear.
We prayed as a platoon,
we prayed together.
And said, "Well,
it's God's will.
"They want us to go over there
"and get this devil
off the thing.
"We're gonna do it.
We know what to do,
and we're ready."
I wasn't scared only because I
had not experienced this before.
WALTER EHLERS:
The more you're in combat,
the more tension
you get as time goes on,
because the odds are
that you may not be
going to make it
because you've seen so many
other people die.
I'd get so sick when
I was going into combat,
I'd... until
that first shot was fired,
why I thought I was...
my stomach was going to turn
inside out or something,
but when the first shots went,
all that goes away.
NARRATOR:
Among the thousands of men
moving toward the beaches
were two veterans
of earlier invasions
in North Africa and Sicily.
They were from
Manhattan, Kansas--
Staff Sergeant Walter Ehlers
and his older brother, Roland.
EHLERS:
He was a little bit
shorter than I.
He had red hair, and he had blue
eyes and a beautiful smile.
And he was a perfect gentleman
all the time.
And he, uh, he was immaculate
in dress and everything.
And he tended to keep
me that way, too.
(chuckles)
NARRATOR:
At 6:30 a.m., the invasion force
began landing in Normandy.
Utah Beach came first.
Drifting smoke that
obscured the target
and strong currents that drove
their landing craft off course
brought the Americans into shore
more than 2,000 yards
from the spot chosen
by the planners.
But General
Theodore Roosevelt, Jr.,
armed only with a cane,
rallied his men
and took the beachhead anyway
in less than an hour.
Of the 23,000 men who went
ashore at Utah Beach,
only 197 were lost.
By late morning, American tanks
were moving off the beach
to rendezvous with the embattled
82nd Airborne
at Sainte Mère-Eglise.
DWAIN LUCE:
We were back there
and we didn't know
what was going on
on the beach, for sure.
We knew that the beach
would hold
if we'd have got our job done.
We also knew that
if the beach didn't hold,
we would probably be left there,
we would be abandoned,
they couldn't get us out.
So naturally, it was
of great interest to us
to get our job done
and see the beach hold.
One of the things
I will always remember,
with a great deal of emotion,
is that first tank
that came through.
Because that first tank
came through,
I knew the beach had held
and I knew help was on the way.
NARRATOR:
British troops would take
the Gold and Sword beaches
almost as fast,
though German tanks
prevented them
from capturing their next
objective, the city of Caen.
Canadian troops took Juno, too,
although 90 of their 306
landing craft were destroyed
by German obstacles,
and one in every 18 men
in their invading force
was killed or wounded.
Still, they managed
to fight their way
seven miles inland
by nightfall.
But for the Americans in the
1st and 29th Infantry Divisions
approaching Omaha Beach,
the most difficult landing site,
almost everything
would go wrong.
Omaha was the broadest
of the five beaches,
and the deepest,
with 100 yards of pebbles,
then sand dunes, barbed wire
and thick undergrowth,
all of it heavily mined.
Behind all that loomed
formidable bluffs
fortified by
2,000 German troops,
many of them battle-seasoned
veterans.
Stützpunkts, or strongholds,
overlooked the four gullies
that led inland-- each manned
by 70 Germans with machine guns,
mortars, and armor-piercing
howitzers,
all zeroed in on the men
about to try to come ashore.
During Phase Two,
American pilots had dropped most
of their bombs miles inland.
There were no bomb craters
in which to take shelter,
and the naval bombardment had
barely dented German defenses.
VAGHI:
As we are approaching it,
we see ships to the right of us,
ships to the left of us.
The skies are loaded
with these flying balloons.
The battleships are shooting and
you could see the projectiles,
the 14-inch projectiles
from the battle wagons,
going through the air.
The smell of powder.
We didn't know what
we were going to hit
when we got in there.
NARRATOR:
Men had been transferred
to their landing craft
12 miles from shore
and while it was still dark,
so that many boats lost
their proper positions going in.
The sea was rough.
The men, most of whom
had had no sleep,
were wet and cold and seasick.
The amphibious tanks that were
supposed to lead the way
and provide cover
for the infantry
were released
too far out at sea;
32 tanks rolled off the vessels
that carried them,
and all but five went
straight to the bottom.
Most of their crews
were trapped inside.
Landing craft were swamped;
scores of men,
burdened with equipment,
slowly drowned,
screaming for help
as other boats wallowed
past them.
Commanders were forbidden
to stop and pick them up.
Along the bluffs,
the Germans held their fire
until the first landing craft
shuddered to a stop
and the ramps went down.
Many men were ripped apart
by German machine guns
before they could step off.
Hundreds more were hit
in the water.
Some badly wounded men made it
to the waterline, collapsed,
then lay helpless
as the tide rose over them.
Those who managed
to push past
the dead and dying
in the shallows
found they had nowhere to go
once they reached the shore.
Some scrabbled at the sand and
shale, trying to dig foxholes.
Others huddled together
behind wrecked landing craft
or German obstacles--
only to find themselves
under concentrated fire.
EHLERS:
We were about a hundred yards
out and we hit a sandbar.
We asked the pilot of the boat,
"Is this as far as it's going?"
And he says,
"As far as it can go."
So he lets the ramp down
and so we rush out the front,
and we go in the water and it's
clear up to my neck like this.
(continuous gunfire)
But we got all the guys
up onto the beach.
And we saw bodies on the beach,
and bodies in the water,
and there's bodies
laying up on the beach.
Most of them
that we saw were dead.
They've wiped out
a whole company.
whole platoons.
They wiped out whole
squads, and so forth.
NARRATOR:
A second wave
of frightened men came ashore
and stalled behind
the remnants of the first.
"Except for one tank that was
blasting away on the beach,"
one of the newcomers remembered,
"the crusade in Europe was,
for all practical purposes,
"disarmed and naked
before its enemies.
A single company of riflemen
could have descended,"
he said, "and swept us up."
(explosion, rapid gunfire)
Joe Vaghi's platoon
came ashore at 7:35.
VAGHI:
Things happened so fast
that you saw men
who were being shot,
you saw them fall.
These things you saw.
The fact that, uh,
this is for real.
NARRATOR:
Somehow, everyone
in Vaghi's platoon
managed to make it
onto the beach,
but it remained
a killing zone,
choked with shattered
and burning equipment
and desperate men
unable to move inland
or retreat from enemy fire.
Joe Vaghi did what he could
to bring order out of the chaos,
directing his men, struggling
to clear a path off the beach,
helping the wounded
and the dying.
VAGHI:
I was bending down.
There was a corpse
on the stretcher,
and as I bent down,
this shell hit.
Well, when I came to,
my clothes were on fire.
NARRATOR:
Vaghi was hit
in the right knee.
struggling to remove cans
of gasoline from a burning jeep
before they could explode
and kill the wounded men
lying all around him.
Far off-shore, General Bradley
considered abandoning Omaha
rather than sending in
more men to die.
Then, the Americans
began to improvise.
Commanders defied orders
and risked
tearing the bottoms
from their ships,
to bring them within
a thousand yards of the beach
and use their guns
to finally knock out
the German pillboxes
and gun emplacements.
And on the beach itself,
officers and enlisted men alike
began taking their survival
into their own hands.
"They're murdering us here!"
one wounded officer
shouted to his men.
"Let's move inland and get
murdered there instead!"
Here and there,
individuals got to their feet
and started forward.
Then small groups
began to follow.
VAGHI:
This officer came up to me
and saw that I was
a beachmaster
and I had the power megaphones
and he said, "Tell these guys
to get the hell off the beach."
So I said, "Got orders here
that you're to get the hell
off the beach now."
The beachmaster said, "Well,
you follow that path there,
"because if you go
to the right or left of it,
you'll be stepping on mines."
VAGHI:
This one soldier, he got up,
and he put a bangalore torpedo
under the barbed wire,
blew a gap in it.
He said, "Come on, follow me,"
and he led the way.
EHLERS:
I rushed my squad through it.
We got off of the beach,
and it was probably
the biggest thing
I ever did in my life was get
those 12 men off of the beach.
NARRATOR:
When the Germans continued
to block the gullies
the Americans hurled themselves
right at the bluffs,
and attacking enemy positions
from the side and rear.
EHLERS:
We went up, right up the hill
into the trenches,
and we were chasing
the Germans then.
We captured four of them
and sent them back down,
and then we got
behind the pillbox
some escaped because they
were running from us--
but we got that particular
pillbox that day.
NARRATOR:
By 1:00, after more than six
hours of desperate fighting,
German resistance
had begun to weaken.
(explosion)
And as the afternoon went on,
combat engineers managed
to clear a safe boat path
through the shallows,
bulldozed five new exits
from the beach...
and built a road that men and
vehicles could follow inland.
35 engineers died doing it.
It had been the bloodiest day
in American history
since the Battle of Antietam
in the Civil War.
Many of the survivors
were in shock,
unable to comprehend what
they'd just been through...
unsure of what
they'd accomplished.
Some 2,500 American soldiers
lay dead on French soil.
Walter Ehlers' brother, Roland,
was among the missing.
EHLERS:
I thought about looking
for my brother, but then,
when we looked at that beach,
there were so many things
down on the beach,
it would be like trying
to find a needle in a haystack.
I figured he was either
wounded or in a hospital
and they just didn't
have a record of it.
NARRATOR:
It would be five weeks
before Walter Ehlers found out
what had happened
to his brother.
EHLERS:
I never saw him die.
He got killed as he was
coming down the ramp on his LCI.
His whole squad got, uh,
wounded... or killed.
I would have rather come back
without my arms and legs
than to come back
without my brother.
That's, uh... that's
what it meant to me.
Well, that stayed with me
for over 50 years.
I had nightmares about that.
He'd come back every night,
and, uh, we'd...
he'd be all neatly dressed
and smiling
like he usually does,
and we'd have a conversation,
and first thing, he'd disappear.
Or I'd go to do something
and he'd disappear.
NARRATOR:
In less than 24 hours,
the Allies had torn a 45-mile
gap in Hitler's Atlantic Wall.
They had lost far fewer men than
their commanders had expected.
More than 150,000 men
were now ashore in France,
and more men and more
equipment and supplies
were coming ashore every hour.
(phone ringing)
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
This is Robert St. John
in the NBC newsroom in New York.
Ladies and gentlemen,
all night long
bulletins have been
pouring in from Berlin
claiming that D-Day is here,
claiming that the invasion
of Western Europe has begun.
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"When we stumbled
sleepily down the hall
"to answer the ringing
telephone,
we made a mental note that it
was shortly before 3:00 a.m."
ST. JOHN:
...heavy fighting is taking
place between the Germans and...
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"We picked up the receiver
"thinking it was
Sheriff Roberts calling
"to say there
had been an accident.
"Instead,
it was Mrs. Lloyd Long,
"playing the feminine
counterpart
"of Paul Revere, saying,
"'Get up, Al,
and listen to the radio.
The invasion has started.'"
ST. JOHN:
...says the British-American
landing operations
from the sea and from the air
are stretching over...
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"We sat by the radio
for over an hour,
listening to
the breathtaking announcements."
ST. JOHN:
Casualties may reach
a dreadful toll.
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"And then we went to bed,
"to lie there for a long time,
"wide-eyed in the darkness,
"thinking,
'What Rock County boys
are landing
on French soil tonight?'"
Al McIntosh,
Rock County Star-Herald.
NARRATOR:
Americans woke up
on June 6, 1944,
to newspaper headlines
and radio bulletins.
It was the news
they'd been waiting for.
But there were
no further details,
no live radio reports
from the beaches.
No one knew where
their sons and brothers
and fathers had landed...
or how those
landings were going.
In Philadelphia, the mayor
gently tapped the Liberty Bell
for the first time
in more than a century.
In New York, traders
on the stock exchange
observed two minutes
of silence
and then went back to work,
sending the Dow Jones average
soaring 142 points
to a new high for the year.
Major League baseball
canceled all games.
Everywhere, church bells rang,
calling people to prayer.
They knelt or bowed their heads
in factories and schoolrooms
and public parks.
In Waterbury,
special masses were said
at the Church
of the Immaculate Conception.
There were prayer services
at Temple Israel
and Beth El Synagogue,
and on the town green, as well.
In Sacramento, workers at the
Pacific Fruit Express Cannery
prayed for the safety
of 100 former employees
now in the service.
In Mobile that day,
no liquor was sold,
and at the railroad station
girls walked up and down
the platforms
holding up
the morning newspapers
so that traveling soldiers
could read the headlines.
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
First of all, here's another
quick news summary
in the eighth hour
of invasion news coverage.
McINTOSH (dramatized):
"And so the invasion news
came to Luverne, quietly.
"There were no whistles,
no sirens...
"no demonstrations.
"Not much was said.
"The coffee shops were filled
almost to standing room
"as the 10:00 morning news
approached.
"There were sober faces
on the men
"as they listened to the news,
"but there was
a smile of exultation
"when they heard
that the Allied forces
had penetrated
ten miles inland."
"One mother dropped
in the coffee shop.
"She shook her head and pushed
the cup of coffee
"placed in front of her aside.
"'I just want to listen
to the radio,' she said.
"Her boy, by all the odds,
was there.
"One didn't have
to be psychic to know
"what was in her mind--
or her heart.
"The prayer that she was
uttering right then,
"as she listened
to the announcer,
"was multiplied a thousand times
and more in Rock County
countless times during the day."
NARRATOR:
That evening, President
Roosevelt spoke to the country.
ROOSEVELT:
Almighty God, our sons,
pride of our nation,
this day have set upon
a mighty endeavor,
a struggle to preserve
our republic, our religion
and our civilization, and to set
free a suffering humanity.
Lead them straight and true;
give strength to their arms,
stoutness to their hearts,
steadfastness in their faith.
They will need Thy blessings.
Their road
will be long and hard...
for the enemy is strong.
He may hurl back our forces.
Success may not come
with rushing speed,
but we shall return
again and again;
and we know that by Thy grace,
and by the righteousness of our
cause, our sons will triumph.
(Benny Goodman Orchestra
playing "The Wang Wang Blues")
JAMES A. FAHEY (dramatized):
"June 6, 1944,
the Philippine Sea.
"At 6:30 p.m. this evening,
"the announcement came
over the loudspeaker,
"that the Allies
landed in France.
"Everyone gave a big cheer
when they heard this.
"I won 40 bucks from the boys
because some time ago,
I bet the invasion would come
off about the middle of June."
James A. Fahey.
NARRATOR:
Seaman First Class
James A. Fahey
of Waltham, Massachusetts,
was the youngest
of four orphaned children.
His brothers, John and Joe, had
been in the Navy at Pearl Harbor
when the Japanese attacked,
and had been spared.
James had signed on
the following year,
assigned to the light
cruiser Montpelier.
Against Navy regulations,
he would record what happened
every day he spent aboard
in a little diary.
FAHEY (dramatized):
"It was a great feeling
as I staggered up the gangway
"to the ship with my sea bag
in one hand
"and the mattress cover loaded
with blankets, mattresses, etc.,
"over my shoulder.
"At last I have a home,
and a warship at that."
NARRATOR:
Fahey went to sea in hopes
of seeing action,
and he saw plenty of it
as a member of a gun crew.
The Montpelier shot down
Japanese planes
and sank Japanese ships
off Guadalcanal,
bombarded Japanese defenses
at Munda,
and survived an enemy bomb
and two torpedo hits
off Bougainville.
A week or so after hearing
the news of D-Day,
Fahey and the men
of the Montpelier
prepared again for battle.
She was now a part
of an 800-ship fleet,
steaming toward the next
American objective
in the Pacific-- the Marianas,
a chain of volcanic islands
from which the U.S.
B-29 Superfortress bombers
could begin to attack
the Japanese homeland.
The fleet's three most important
targets in the Marianas
were Guam, Tinian, and Saipan,
where the Marines
would land first.
FAHEY (dramatized):
"June 13.
"In about 14 hours now, we will
start bombarding Saipan.
"We are only about
1,200 miles from Tokyo.
"I guess I will go down
and buy some candy.
"The candy has been
our old standby
"when we have nothing to eat
at battle stations
for long hours."
NARRATOR:
Saipan was unlike many
of the tiny, flat coral atolls
the Marines had
taken previously.
It was 14 miles long,
featured all kinds of terrain
and was defended by more
than 30,000 Japanese troops.
It was also home
to somewhere between 16,000
and 20,000 Japanese civilians.
(alarm blaring)
(bosun's whistle blaring)
The shelling of Saipan
went on for two days.
Among the Marines
of the Fourth Division
was Corporal Alvy Ray Pittman
of Mobile, Alabama.
He'd been working as a carpenter
alongside his father
when he decided to join
the Marines.
RAY PITTMAN:
I'd made up my mind
I want to get in
the toughest outfit they had.
And I was afraid the war
was going to get over
before I got over there.
So I joined the Marine Corps.
'Course, they sent me
to Parris Island for boot camp.
And I remember going in,
all these guys
standing out on the grass.
They said, "You'll be sorry.
You'll be sorry."
NARRATOR:
Ray Pittman
was in the first wave,
part of a 16-man demolition team
assigned to destroy
enemy strongpoints
wherever they were found,
using explosives, grenades,
and flamethrowers.
PITTMAN:
You never think about
getting hurt yourself.
You think about maybe
some of your buddies
are going to get hurt.
And you wonder
who it's going to be.
I mean, I really didn't ever
think about getting hurt myself.
Of course, when you, when you...
slugs start bouncing off
your amtrack going in,
you know it could happen.
NARRATOR:
The naval bombardment
had failed.
Concentrated Japanese mortar
and artillery fire
rained down among the amtracks
and on the men fighting
for a toehold on the beach.
All four commanders
of the assault battalions
were hit within minutes.
By evening, 20,000 Marines
had made it ashore,
but they could go no further.
The Japanese planned to keep
the Americans pinned down
until their own fleet could
steam in from the Philippines
and destroy them.
Despite the rain of shells,
the Marines began slowly to
fight their way off the beach.
PITTMAN:
I know I was scared a lot...
and losing a lot of friends
really hurts you.
It's really hard
for me to describe,
really, just how
I felt the whole time
'cause there's something
happening every day
and you're so tired and you
can't lift your eyelids hardly.
And something happens,
you get a call to blow
a pillbox here,
to blow a pillbox there.
I mean, you wake up
and go and do your job.
But it's hard for me to tell
just how bad it was--
how I felt.
NARRATOR:
The battle for Saipan
had just begun.
SASCHA WEINZHEIMER (dramatized):
Santo Tomas, Manila.
"The rumor about
the Japanese army
taking over the camp was true."
"If we thought
we had reason to complain
"about how awful our life
was in a concentration camp,
"we soon changed our minds
"and knew we had been
on a picnic till then.
"From now on, we would be the
same as military war prisoners
and not civilian prisoners."
Sascha Weinzheimer.
NARRATOR:
After the Japanese army
assumed control
of Santo Tomas camp in Manila
in the Philippines,
they had taken propaganda
photographs
of some of the prisoners
to show how well they were
being treated.
Sascha Weinzheimer
and her younger brother
were forced to pose
for the photographer.
Things were not
as they appeared.
For 11-year-old Sascha,
her family
and 4,000
other civilian prisoners,
life had gone from bad to worse.
Prisoners-- including children--
were made to bow to the officers
and were beaten if they failed
to go low enough.
Food and supplies from friends
outside the camp were cut off.
There was no more meat,
just rice and dried fish.
WEINZHEIMER (dramatized):
"So almost everything was taken
away from us at once.
We began to know
how bad things could be."
"Even though Mummy and Daddy
kept telling us kids
"to eat everything on our plates
because the day would come
"when we might
have very little to eat,
we didn't really believe them."
Being without food,
I think, is, it...
is one of the worst things ever,
because without that,
nothing is functionable.
We'd lie down in bed, in the
shanty-- we lived in a shanty--
and I had a mattress
on the floor,
my mother and my father
and my sister had one mattress,
and my brother
had a small mattress.
And we'd lie there;
we'd have to go to bed early
because of blackout.
We used to lie down on the floor
and you'd stick your finger
in your stomach
and feel your backbone.
(in singsong):
"Yeah, I feel my backbone."
And we'd, you know,
this would be a game.
These are the games
that we played all the time.
And ironically enough,
it helped.
NARRATOR:
In the late spring of 1944,
John and Glennie Frazier
of Fort Deposit, Alabama,
received a telegram
from the War Department.
Their son Glenn had been missing
in action in the Philippines
for two agonizing years,
and since nothing had been heard
from him since May of 1942,
he was now
officially presumed dead.
Frazier had joined
the army in 1941
in part because he believed
that the young woman he loved
loved someone else.
He was wrong; she had remained
loyal to him all that time.
Now with the latest news,
she began to give up hope
of ever seeing him again.
But Glenn Frazier
was still alive,
a prisoner of the Japanese.
FRAZIER:
When I'd think about home,
I would think about the things
that I missed most
like ice cream and potato salad
and some ambrosia
that my mother used to make
for Christmas and so forth.
And of course
it was always a thought
of if we would get back home.
But it got a time
that we were so weak at...
I had got a time with me
that I was so weak
until I couldn't even remember
whether I had sisters
or brothers.
I couldn't even remember
their names.
And it comes to a time
when you think,
"Did I have a home back...
Did I have a home,
did I have a family?"
NARRATOR:
Frazier had come close
to death several times.
He had endured the Bataan Death
March and nightmarish conditions
at Camp O'Donnell and Bilibid
Prison in the Philippines,
and he had been forced
to perform slave labor
in prison camps in Japan itself,
where he had survived
double pneumonia, torture,
a week of isolation
in a covered pit
and beatings so frequent
they became routine.
Once, when he failed
to lift his feet high enough
while marching, a guard drove
a bayonet into his knee.
FRAZIER:
It started getting infected
and it finally got gangrene,
and Dr. Campbell, which was
our American doctor in there,
had nothing to treat me with
except iodine.
I would hold a cup
to catch all the... the blood,
and he cut it open
with a pocket knife
and would get to the point
to where he would pour
pure iodine in there
to kill the gangrene.
They were thinking
about taking my leg off.
So I told Dr. Campbell
I'd just rather die
than have my leg taken off.
So he fought it and we won.
At one point, there was only
a space in the back of my leg
about a inch-and-a-half across
that the flesh was just
like regular, normal flesh.
The rest of it was decayed.
I could open that wound up
and see my bone.
NARRATOR:
Frazier's leg eventually healed
and he went back to work
on the waterfront at Tanagura,
where he and his friends did
all they could to sabotage
the Japanese war effort.
They risked their lives
to drill holes in the bottoms
of oil barrels,
poured sand into gas tanks,
wrecked machinery,
destroyed a dock
and loosened blocks
so that
a submarine under repairs
slid into the bay upside down.
And through it all,
Frazier thought of home
and of the girl he still hoped
somehow to see again.
FRAZIER:
But the thing
that really kept me going
is seeing if that girl
was still there
and see if, you know, if I still
in my heart was crazy about her
and the fact
that I wanted to live.
I did not want my body
pushing up Japanese daisies.
And I, I just felt that way,
and I thought,
"They gonna have a heck of
a time getting me in a casket."
NARRATOR:
Ten days after D-Day,
bodies were still washing up
onto Omaha Beach,
and because the graves
registration crews
had moved inland
with the advancing troops,
no one was gathering them
for burial.
Finally, men from Quentin
Aanenson's fighter squadron
did the job themselves.
They retrieved the corpses
with long poles,
heaped them with driftwood
soaked with gasoline
and set them ablaze.
A few days later, Aanenson
looked down from the bluff
and saw that the problem
had not been solved.
"More bodies were rolling
in the surf," he remembered,
"as the English Channel
continued to give up its dead."
(vehicles rumbling)
Aanenson's outfit had
recently moved to new quarters,
Advanced Landing Strip A-1,
a freshly built airfield
near Omaha Beach.
Their mission was to provide
close air support
for American infantry
and armor struggling
to fight their way inland.
By June of 1944,
the Allies dominated the air.
(gunfire)
Whenever the Germans
on the ground
broke into the open,
they were subject
to strafing and bombing
from American P-47 Thunderbolts,
the kind of aircraft
Aanenson flew.
(gunfire)
Attacks so relentless,
the Germans came to call them
"steel weather."
(rapid gunfire)
AANENSON:
It was on one
of my very early missions
that I first knew I had...
I had killed men.
We caught a group of Germans
that were on a road
in an area where
there were no trees,
and so there was no place
for them
to... to run and hide.
And we caught them before they
could really get off the roads
and run toward the ditches.
(gunfire)
And I remember
the impact it had on me
when I could see my bullets
just tearing into them,
and... and, uh,
we had so much firepower
that the...
the bodies would fly,
uh, some yards,
and as I... as I was doing this,
I was doing it knowing
I had to do it,
that it was my job.
This is what
I had been trained to do,
and I dealt with it fine.
But when I got back home
to the base in Normandy
and landed...
I got sick.
I had to think
about what I had done.
Now, that didn't change
my resolve for the next day.
I went out and did it again.
(gunfire)
And again and again and again.
(piano playing
"It's Been a Long, Long Time")
ERNIE PYLE (dramatized):
"June 23, 1944.
"This Norman countryside
"looks exactly like
the rich, gentle land
of eastern Pennsylvania."
"It is too wonderfully beautiful
to be the scene of war."
(birds chirping)
"Someday, I would like
to cover a war in a country
that is as ugly as war itself."
Ernie Pyle.
(song ends)
NARRATOR:
Normandy's beauty was deceptive.
Allied planners had failed
to understand the landscape
through which their men
would have to fight
before they could begin to drive
the enemy out of France.
(gunfire, artillery fire,
indistinct shouts)
Normandy was quilted with small,
irregularly shaped fields,
walled from one another
by hedgerows,
earthen ramparts four feet high,
topped with dense hedges
whose tangled roots turned them
into natural fortifications
and made it impossible
to see into
from one field to the next.
(explosion)
In one area that measured
just two miles by four,
there were 4,000 such fields.
Here and there,
ancient sunken wagon tracks
twisted between the hedgerows,
ideal for ambushes
and often concealed
from air attack
by overarching trees.
The Germans took
full advantage of all of it.
American Sherman tanks could not
break through the hedgerows,
and when they tried
to roll over them,
exposed their unprotected
underbellies to deadly fire.
(gunfire)
Each field became what the
newspaperman Ernie Pyle called
"a separate little war,"
fought mostly
by companies of riflemen.
(bullets whizzing by)
LUCE:
The Germans were good troops.
They did not
give up ground easily
there or any other place
I saw them.
You had to respect them
for the fact
they were excellent troops.
(chuckles):
They were too damn good, and...
or they wouldn't have caused us
so much trouble.
(explosion)
NARRATOR:
Progress was measured in yards.
Now the pace was far slower
than the Allied commanders
had anticipated,
and the cost in dead and wounded
was far higher.
Unarmed C-47s,
cargo planes stripped down
so that as many litters as
possible could be lifted aboard,
carried the worst hit
to hospitals in England,
just 20 minutes away,
then turned around
and came back for more.
Emily Lewis was
one of hundreds of nurses
who did all they could
for the wounded.
LEWIS:
All those wounded soldiers,
they were scared to death.
Really frightened
half out of their minds.
I hugged 'em, I was teary-eyed.
It makes me cry to think of it.
Got 'em on my plane,
talked to them.
Some of them were...
so unnerved...
that I-I just had to put my arms
around 'em and hold 'em.
I was 23,
and they were 22, 21,
24, 18, you know.
It was...
it was just... terrible.
But it had to be done, you know?
NARRATOR:
By July 1,
hundreds of thousands of troops
were onshore.
The Cotentin Peninsula
and the port of Cherbourg
had been taken,
and the beachhead stretched
for some 70 miles.
(explosions, artillery fire)
But after three weeks of combat,
it remained, at most,
20 miles deep.
The plan to liberate France
was stalled.
General Bradley feared
that unless something drastic
were done,
the Allies would face the same
sort of ghastly stalemate
they had endured
during the First World War.
To avoid disaster, his men had
to get out of the hedgerows
and find the kind
of wide-open countryside
American armor needed
to make real progress.
The region just beyond
the town of Saint-Lô
was what Bradley had in mind.
It was just 15 miles away...
but to his exhausted men,
it seemed as distant
as their ultimate target--
Germany.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
Ripped by stlc8tr!