(bird singing)
SAM HYNES:
The world contains evil.
And if it didn't contain evil,
we probably wouldn't need to try
to construct religions.
No evil, no God, I think.
No, of course no evil, no war.
But this is not
a human possibility
that we need to entertain.
There will always be
plenty of evil.
And there'll always be wars.
Because human beings
are aggressive animals.
NARRATOR:
When the people
of Luverne, Minnesota,
and Sacramento, California;
Waterbury, Connecticut,
and Mobile, Alabama, went
to the movies in March of 1945,
they saw and heard
a sick and weary
President Franklin Roosevelt--
so sick and so weary
that for the first time
in his career,
he referred directly
to the paralysis
that kept him from standing
without braces.
ROOSEVELT:
I hope that you will pardon me
for an unusual posture
during the presentation
of what I want to say,
but I know that you will realize
that it makes it
a lot easier for me
about ten pounds of steel around
on the bottom of my legs;
and also because of the fact
that I have just completed
a 14,000-mile trip.
NARRATOR:
Roosevelt's strength was waning,
but his message
was undimmed.
The war was still to be won.
It's a long, tough road
to Tokyo.
It is longer to go to Tokyo
than it is to Berlin,
in every sense of the word.
The defeat of Germany will
not mean the end
of the war against Japan.
On the contrary,
we must be prepared
for a long and costly struggle
in the Pacific.
NARRATOR:
Americans had been fighting
for more than three years now,
and the number of dead
and wounded and missing
had more than doubled
just since D-Day.
The Nazis seemed at last to be
on the verge of collapse,
but American men were still
dying in the struggle
to eradicate them,
and Allied planners feared
the final battle with Japan
would stretch on for years.
In the coming weeks,
two men from Mobile
would fight simply to survive:
Eugene Sledge, who had endured
the horrors of the battle
for Peleliu,
would once again
be forced to enter
what he called "the abyss."
Maurice Bell, who had witnessed
much of the Pacific war
aboard the USS Indianapolis,
would find himself hurled
into the center of history.
Daniel Inouye from Honolulu
would lead his men in an attack
so furious that afterwards
even he could no longer quite
comprehend it.
And Glenn Frazier,
from Fort Deposit, Alabama,
who had survived three and a
half years of brutal captivity,
would find that the Japanese
were not his only enemy.
The people of Sacramento and
Luverne, Waterbury and Mobile,
and every other American town
knew that there would be more
bad news from the battlefield
before they could dare hope
to know what it would be like
to live once again in a world
without war.
(tool clacking)
EMMA BELLE PETCHER:
I remember going to New York
on the train.
And at the station
at St. Louis, Missouri,
the platform was
lined with caskets.
With American flags.
It was just as far
as you could see them
on the platform
at the train station.
And I went down reading
the name in brass plaque
that was all the names.
And I cried and cried.
How could you not cry?
HYNES:
The Pacific, as one experienced
it, began at San Diego.
And you got a sense of what a
huge space you were going into.
That this was not going to be
like Europe,
where there was land all around
and it had names.
This was going to be nameless,
empty space.
Almost all of it with little
dots of land in between.
NARRATOR:
In March of 1945, Marine pilot
Sam Hynes was 20 years old,
a former University
of Minnesota student
who, like thousands
of other young men,
had been made to grow up fast
during the war,
passing test after test
on the way to manhood.
He had learned
to live on his own, had married,
mastered the dangerous art
of flying torpedo bombers
and had now received his orders
to proceed 6,000 miles
across the Pacific
to face his final trial: combat.
Hynes landed at Ulithi,
the sprawling coral atoll
the U.S. Navy had turned
into the advance staging area
for the assault
that was about to begin
on the Japanese island
of Okinawa.
HYNES:
It was awesome.
It was huge.
The anchorage was miles across,
and it was covered with ships
of all sizes-- carriers,
battleships,
destroyers, cruisers.
I'd never seen so many ships.
It was like seeing
all the power in your corner.
(laughing):
And there wasn't any power
in the other corner.
NARRATOR:
Okinawa, 60 miles long
and home to almost
half a million civilians,
was the gateway to Japan.
The Allies knew they had to take
it before they could move on
to the home islands,
and were gathering
the largest invasion force since
D-Day-- almost 1,500 ships
and more than
half a million men.
(fierce explosion)
Day after day, in March of 1945,
American and British warships
fired shells and rockets
at Okinawa.
There was little evidence
of the island's defenders.
Allied planners were not sure
just where they were dug in.
But they knew they were
somewhere on the island--
more than 100,000 of them,
well entrenched
and prepared to die
for their Emperor.
The Japanese kamikaze
pilots overhead
were willing to die
for him, too.
There were nearly
100 Japanese airfields
within flying distance
of Okinawa--
and the pilots of some 5,000
warplanes were preparing
to sacrifice their own lives
in order to take those
of as many American sailors
as possible.
MAURICE BELL:
They was trained to fly their
planes one way and no return.
And when they went out
after a ship or something,
they had their funeral before
they actually left.
And they knew they was
never coming back.
They was under the impression
that if they gave their life
that way for their country,
they had a special place in
heaven for them, automatically.
Which wasn't true.
NARRATOR:
Seaman First Class Maurice Bell
of Mobile, Alabama,
was serving as a gunner
aboard the heavy cruiser
USS Indianapolis off Okinawa.
On March 31, kamikazes targeted
her for destruction.
(alarm sounding)
BELL:
I looked up to my right,
and there was one small cloud up
there and just as I looked up,
I saw a plane
come out of this cloud
and it was a Japanese
kamikaze plane.
The very instant
I saw him up there,
he must have spotted our ship,
because he turned into a dive,
instantly, and was coming
straight down.
It looked like he was coming
just as straight
to the very spot
where I was sitting.
A man back there started firing
at it with a 20-millimeters,
and you could see
the tracers hit it.
The plane actually bounced off
the ship,
but the motor and the bomb
went through the deck.
Went through
number three mess hall
and right down there was
three or four or five men
sitting at a table eating.
It killed all of them.
The bomb went all the way
through the ship
into the water and exploded
back up through.
They said that hole
all the way through
was large enough to drive
a 18-wheeler through.
NARRATOR:
Nine sailors died.
29 were wounded.
The Indianapolis was sent to
Ulithi to have its hull mended
and eventually dispatched
all the way across the Pacific
to Mare Island, near San
Francisco, for further repairs.
Meanwhile, the bombardment
of Okinawa continued.
The invasion was to begin
on April 1.
This was the night before Easter
Sunday, the first of April.
And Tokyo Rose, who was the
spokesperson for the Japanese,
TOKYO ROSE:
Japanese special attack planes
launched late Thursday night...
VAGHI:
And having been
through Normandy,
and they didn't know
we were coming,
and here we are going
into Okinawa,
and Tokyo Rose is telling us
"Okay, G.I. Joes,
we know you're coming,
"we're gonna give you a Easter
party, when you land,
and we'll be there
waiting for you."
Well, that really sent shivers
up and down one's spine.
(artillery fire continues)
NARRATOR:
Navy ensign Joseph Vaghi
from Connecticut,
who had been wounded
on Omaha Beach,
was among
the 60,000 soldiers and Marines
moving toward the island
that morning.
He had volunteered
to return to combat.
VAGHI:
When we finally began unloading,
it was quiet.
As the landing crafts went in,
you just walked ashore.
Couldn't believe this.
(Glenn Miller's band
playing "Little Brown Jug")
NARRATOR:
The Japanese
mostly held their fire.
Four divisions-- 75,000 men--
would land that day.
The veterans
couldn't believe their luck.
("Little Brown Jug" continues)
Marine Private Eugene Sledge
of Mobile and his outfit
were at the landing, too,
and so relieved,
they began to sing
the popular hit
"Little Brown Jug"
as they unloaded their gear
and started inland.
They had been warned
that they would be likely
to lose eight out of ten men
before they could make it
off the beach.
They lost none.
("Little Brown Jug" continues)
They were pleasantly surprised
by the terrain as well.
It was "pastoral
and handsomely terraced,"
"like a picture postcard
of an Oriental landscape."
EUGENE SLEDGE (dramatized):
"The weather was cool,
"and there was
the wonderful smell of pines,
"which reminded me of home.
"It was such a beautiful island.
"You really could not believe
that there was going to be
a battle there."
("Little Brown Jug" continues)
NARRATOR:
American infantry and tanks
raced across the island,
cutting it in two.
Then, as Sledge and the Marines
moved north
to clear the central and
northern parts of the island,
the Army turned south, toward
the main Japanese defenses...
...where they began to face
increasingly strong opposition.
(bullets ricocheting)
Go, go, go!
Offshore, the Navy continued
to have its hands full.
NEWSREEL ANNOUNCER:
Sky full of flak
as the Japs attack warships
supporting the invasion
of Okinawa.
Scenes of plunging planes
and enemy bombs land
perilously near.
A low-flying enemy speeds
toward a warship target.
Will the guns bring it down
before it gets to its mark?
(artillery fire)
Yes, it's hit, on fire,
and crashes!
(explosion)
NARRATOR:
On April 6,
Japan loosed a new tactic
against the Allied ships.
Not single kamikazes now--
but flights
of hundreds of them at a time,
dropping out of the sky
to attack the fleet.
(explosion)
The Japanese called
these deadly flights
"Floating Chrysanthemums."
(alarm blaring)
(whistle blowing)
By the end of the day,
they had seriously damaged
17 American vessels
and killed 367 sailors.
VAGHI:
We lost more ships,
we lost more sailors,
we lost more men,
It was one of the worst part...
battles of the Pacific, really.
NARRATOR:
As the land battle
for Okinawa intensified,
the Floating Chrysanthemums
would return again and again,
taking a terrible toll
on the men...
and ships.
GLENN FRAZIER:
If we had an invasion of Japan,
we knew we were dead.
(distant explosions)
They issued orders later
that if, uh,
the minute American or Allied
forces landed on their homeland,
to shoot all prisoners of war.
So we had basically
accepted our fate.
NARRATOR:
Glenn Frazier was one of
168,000 Allied prisoners of war
still in Japanese hands.
He had been a captive
since the surrender on Bataan
in the spring of 1942.
He was now in his fourth
POW camp in Japan, at Tsuruga,
southwest of Tokyo,
on the Sea of Japan.
(gunfire)
One day, their captors
permitted 50 prisoners
to wash their own filthy clothes
in the ocean.
They were sitting around
waiting for their clothes to dry
when carrier-based
American bombers
roared in to attack the port.
FRAZIER:
We run out of the warehouse,
or at the end of the dock, and
were across the railroad tracks
and was waving,
and we knew then
that the aircraft carrier planes
were close.
And we knew that
the end was coming close.
But that did not help
our feelings
as to what was about to happen.
Our lives were
going to be sacrificed.
RADIO ANNOUNCER:
We interrupt this program
to bring you
a special news bulletin
from CBS World News.
A press association
has just announced
that President Roosevelt
is dead.
The president died
of a cerebral hemorrhage.
All we know so far
is that the president died
at Warm Springs in Georgia.
KATHARINE PHILLIPS:
We can all tell you
where we were
when we heard
that Roosevelt had died.
President Roosevelt
was really...
the binding force
for the United States.
When he would come on
and give his fireside chats,
we all gathered
around the radio,
and everyone looked to him
for leadership.
He had led us
out of the Depression,
so we felt that...
certainly he could lead us
through a war.
And when the news came in April
that he had died,
it was a terrible blow
to the entire country.
BURT WILSON:
It was catastrophic,
because he was
the only president we knew
for the first 12, 13 years
of our life.
Now, the thing was,
my parents were Republicans
and hated Roosevelt,
but I loved him.
And most of us kids
loved him, too.
Because he was
the face of America
that was saying,
"Hey, things are gonna be okay."
HYNES:
I was standing
outside a Quonset hut
looking across the little strait
between Saipan and Tinian,
the next island,
and... I felt
a great sense of loss.
More than that, I think, "How
will we go on fighting the war
when our commander in chief
is dead?"
PAUL FUSSELL:
We were all very sad about it.
Less about his leaving...
than about irony of it.
If he'd died
a few months, uh, later,
he could have seen the success
of what he had done.
NARRATOR:
The men of the 100th
442nd Combat Team--
the Japanese-American unit that
had already distinguished itself
in the fighting
for Italy and France--
were back in the mountains
of Northern Italy
when they got word
of Roosevelt's death.
He had signed the order
that sent to internment camps
the families from which
many of them had come,
but he had also provided them
with the opportunity
to prove their loyalty
on the battlefield.
It was that FDR
they chose to remember.
DANIEL INOUYE:
I remember that day,
because when we got the word,
suddenly men in my platoon
took out their bayonets
and put it on.
(gunfire)
And I said,
"What's happening here?"
He says, "Well, I think we got
to do this one for the old man."
They just stood up
and started attacking.
(gunfire continues)
Radio calls coming in
from the company commander,
"What in the hell
are you doing?" you know.
"You're not supposed
to be attacking."
I says, "Captain,
you can't stop 'em."
(laughing)
And so they're all
moving forward for the old man,
a man they had never met.
(bugle playing taps)
NARRATOR:
Many Americans,
overseas as well as at home,
couldn't even remember
the name of the man
who was now
their commander in chief...
...Harry Truman.
MAN:
All aboard!
I guess I had
a million dolls or more...
I guess I've played
the doll game o'er and o'er...
QUENTIN AANENSON:
I had great difficulty
adjusting to the fact
that I was going home.
That's why I'm blue...
Landed at Washington, D.C.,
was processed
through some paperwork there,
caught a train at Union Station
taking me down to Louisiana,
where Jackie was.
To love a doll
that's not your own...
I'm through with all of them
I'll never fall again
Say, boy
Whatcha gonna do?
NARRATOR:
Fighter pilot Quentin Aanenson
of Luverne, Minnesota,
was home on leave that April.
He had been in more-or-less
continuous combat in Europe
since D-Day--
ten ghastly months
during which he'd killed men
and seen friends killed
and come very close
to collapsing from despair.
He expected soon to be ordered
into action again,
in the Pacific this time,
and he desperately wanted
to see Jackie Greer,
the Louisiana girl
with whom he'd fallen in love
before going overseas.
Her letters had been
Aanenson's anchor to sanity.
GREER:
I-I prayed for him to come back,
and I just felt like my prayers
would be answered.
I was walking down the street
and I saw the wedding dress
in a window.
So I went right in and I bought
that dress
and shipped it to my mother and
I said, "Have this ready for me.
NARRATOR:
Now the two were to meet again.
AANENSON:
And I had to adjust to being
away from the war.
The silence was difficult
to get used to.
But it was such a... an exciting
and unbelievable moment.
I was alive,
and this was Jackie.
GREER:
The first night,
we were in the living room
and he formally proposed to me.
And for some reason, I got shy.
And I couldn't quite
make myself say, "Yes."
I don't know why because
I'd been saying yes
for 11 months, you know.
And when I hesitated and,
and couldn't quite say yes,
he said, "Well, now,
just make up your mind."
The funny part was, the door
right near my chair was closed,
and on the other side
of that door was my bed
with that gorgeous wedding dress
spread out all over it.
AANENSON:
I was going to be going back
to the war.
I didn't want to face the idea
that she could end up
being a widow in a couple
of months.
But it... the more we talked
about it,
the more we decided,
"Let's get married now."
So we got married on April 17,
two and a half weeks
after I got home,
in the First Methodist Church
in Baton Rouge.
As I saw her coming down
that aisle,
it was just a thrill
beyond belief.
(dramatic music playing)
NEWSREEL ANNOUNCER:
In their stupendous advances,
the Russian armies
feature massed artillery.
The kind of warfare the Russians
wage on the road to Berlin.
NARRATOR:
By the middle of April 1945,
Soviet troops were just
30 miles from Berlin
and bent on revenge
for the horrors the Nazis had
inflicted on their homeland.
General Dwight Eisenhower
decreed
that the armies
under his command
would not drive directly
toward the German capital.
The deadly task of capturing the
city would go to the Red Army.
Hitler called upon his people
to resist to the end.
"Every village and every town
will be defended and held
by every possible man," he said.
For the Americans in Europe,
the fighting and the killing
sputtered on.
DANIEL INOUYE:
And that's a horrible thing,
knowing that the war is
going to end,
and you have to keep urging
your men to go forward.
NARRATOR:
The 100th 442nd Combat Team
was still in the mountains
of Northern Italy
hammering away at the last
German positions there.
INOUYE:
We had this objective,
a high mountain.
As I was going up,
I suddenly felt someone punching
me on the side.
That's what I thought it was.
I fell down and I got up
and kept on moving.
I had a bullet going right
through my abdomen.
Came out just about a quarter
inch from my spine.
NARRATOR:
Three machine gun nests
were firing down at Inouye
as he continued
to lead his men up the slope.
He hurled a grenade
to knock out the first one,
then killed its crew
with his tommy gun.
He silenced the next gun
with two more grenades.
As he pulled the pin
on yet another
and got ready to throw it
into the third machine gun nest,
German shrapnel nearly severed
Inouye's right arm.
Somehow, with his left hand,
he pried his dead fingers
from the live grenade
and threw it,
then started up the hill again.
INOUYE:
According to the men
and according to my company
commander, he says,
"For a moment,
you went berserk.
You picked up your gun."
I had a Thompson sub-machine gun
and with my left hand
started approaching
the last machine gun nest,
just firing
and with the blood
splattering out.
It was a horrible sight,
I think.
Finally, I got hit again
on my leg,
and I kept rolling down the hill
and that was the end.
NARRATOR:
German prisoners of war
were pressed into service
to carry Inouye
back down the hill.
He was given morphine
at the aid station--
so much morphine that when
surgeons at the field hospital
began to amputate
his shattered arm,
he had to endure it
without anesthetic.
The pain was so intense,
he remembered,
"that dying didn't seem
like such an awful idea."
INOUYE:
I ended up receiving
17 whole blood transfusions.
Before they gave you the blood,
they showed you the bottle,
and on that bottle was a label
that had the name, rank,
serial number and the unit.
And so, here is someone
with some fancy name,
Thomas Jefferson Lee,
a serial number, 92nd Division.
was a unit that we were
attached to in the last battle,
and they're all made up
of African-Americans.
And all the bottles I saw
were from the 92nd Division.
So I must have had 17 bottles
of good African-American blood.
And so here I am.
NARRATOR:
For his heroism under fire,
Daniel Inouye would receive
the Medal of Honor.
It was granted to him
55 years later,
during his sixth term
as a United States senator
from Hawaii.
Meanwhile, events in Europe
were moving so fast
it was hard for the people
back home to keep track.
NEWSREEL ANNOUNCER:
On the final lap
of their drive on Berlin,
Russian troops send
the Germans reeling.
NARRATOR:
On April 25, American
and Soviet forces linked up
at Torgau on the Elbe River.
Germany had been cut in half.
The next day, Soviet troops
began assaulting Berlin itself.
(distant shouting)
On the morning of April 30,
Russian troops fought their way
into the Reichstag,
the symbol of German power.
Less than half a mile away,
beneath the rubble,
Adolf Hitler and his closest
aides huddled in their bunker.
That afternoon,
Hitler named Admiral Karl Donitz
to succeed him,
then shot himself in the mouth.
Only his most fanatical
followers
now continued to fight on.
PAUL FUSSELL:
Eisenhower, on D-Day morning,
distributed to the troops
a general order, which is like a
handbill, and everybody read it
and he said, "We are about to
embark upon the great crusade,"
which we'd been preparing
for for many months, etc.
Now, at first none of us
could believe
it was anything like a crusade,
because we were playing dice
and we were thinking about girls
all the time
and getting as drunk
as possible and so forth.
It wasn't like a crusade.
There was no religious
dimension to it whatever.
When they finally got across
France and into Germany
and saw the German
death camps...
(voice breaking):
they realized that they had...
been engaged
in something like a crusade,
although none of them
called it that.
And it all began to make
a kind of sense to us.
I'm not sure
that made it any better.
It may have made it worse.
To see that it was
actually conducted
in defense of some noble idea.
NARRATOR:
As the Red Army had moved
through Eastern Europe
the previous summer,
it had uncovered at Majdaneck,
in Poland,
the first evidence of the Nazis'
industrialized barbarism.
The ashes of thousands
of human beings
were found in a crematorium.
The American and British press
played it down,
assuming the Soviets
were exaggerating.
Not even the Nazis
could be so murderous.
By the end of April 1945,
more than a hundred camps and
sub-camps would be liberated.
Auschwitz, Treblinka,
Ravensbrck,
Ohrdruf, Buchenwald,
Bergen-Belsen, Nordhausen,
Dachau.
On May 5, advance patrols of the
American 11th Armored Division
came upon Mauthausen in Austria.
There they found
more than 110,000
desperate so-called
"enemies of the Reich,"
men, women and children
confined behind barbed wire.
Many were too weak to stand.
Private Burnett Miller
of Sacramento was there
and saw it all.
And they had put some signs out,
"Welcome Americans,
you've saved us"
and things like this.
And we surrounded the camp
and then, uh,
there was a surge of people
who were in fairly good
condition begging for food,
and we were giving them
what food we had,
and in some cases
it overwhelmed their systems
and actually killed them.
I'm sure we were responsible
for the deaths
of several hundred people
just by feeding them
concentrated food.
We went down in the basement and
there were these big furnaces,
and it looked like cordwood
piled around
and they were bodies in rigor
mortis that they were...
had been preparing to burn
in these big furnaces.
And the fellows that went
into the other barracks
came away just shocked,
some of them very, very sick.
The hospital there,
people dying just thick
and people couldn't get out
of their bunks
and people
in terrible condition.
And then later there was
a big trench,
and it was filled with bodies.
Some were dying,
some were trying to steal food
and, uh, the, the guards
were dispersed all over and we,
we actually saw a guard move
into a house
and we chased him in,
and he was an officer.
And the prisoners who were there
tore him apart,
just killed him right there.
We lived in Mauthausen,
which was an idyllic little
Austrian town on the river,
but you could smell the camp
in town.
And all the villagers of course
said they didn't know anything
about the camp,
and the local priest said
he didn't know anything
about the camp,
and I knew that was a lie,
because you could smell
the camp.
You could just smell,
uh, death.
So it was a horrible,
horrible experience.
And then we came,
at least I came to think,
"Well, you know, this effort
has been worthwhile.
There was a real reason
to do this."
These were inhuman things
that were being done to people.
NARRATOR:
Other Americans were witnessing
similar horrors at other camps.
Ray Leopold, a medic
from Waterbury and a Jew,
was with the 28th
Infantry Division.
We were...
near the Hadamar
concentration camp.
At the same time we noticed
that up on the hill
that the Brgermeister
described as an insane asylum.
We went up there
and found that, true,
they did have
an insane asylum there,
at least initially,
but it was a place
where there was medical
experimentation going on humans.
I really can't tell you
what I saw there.
It affected me profoundly,
and I think all the men
who were with me at that time
were equally affected.
I, um, I felt that
it was too bad
that I was forbidden by the
Geneva Convention to kill.
I... I felt that this was the
most horrible human experience
that had ever been visited
on the face of the earth.
I saw one of those terrible
places where they were...
where they had the people
that were dying and dead
and bodies stacked
like cordwood, cordwood.
That was the little town
of Ludwigslust.
And we made the German people
in that community
go get those bodies
and had a burial in the park
in front of the castle
so that they would never
forget it again.
And we gave them a Christian
and Jewish burial.
But the people did it.
I mean, we... we made
the German people do it.
These people in this country
who say it didn't happen...
It happened.
I saw it; I know.
NARRATOR:
In 1933, there were
nine million Jews in Europe.
By 1945, two out of three
of them were dead.
Thousands of Jewish communities
were wiped
from the face of the earth.
Hitler's regime also slaughtered
nearly two million
non-Jewish Poles.
They murdered more than four
million Soviet prisoners of war,
as well as hundreds of thousands
of handicapped people
and political opponents,
homosexuals and gypsies
and Jehovah's Witnesses
and slave laborers
from all the countries
they'd conquered.
LEOPOLD:
How bad it was,
how wide it was...
We never really knew
how fully extensive
this horror that Hitler had
visited on Europe,
and in particular
on the Jews, how it was.
But here we began to see.
We had no idea
that there was going to be six
million dead Jews as a result.
I... I think the horror
is still with me.
I think there's no apology that
can ever atone for what I saw.
NARRATOR:
On May 8, three days
after Burnett Miller's unit
reached Mauthausen,
Germany finally surrendered.
The war in Europe
had come to an end.
The Reich that Hitler
had promised
would endure
for a thousand years
had lasted less than a dozen.
("Waiting for the Train"
playing)
(children shouting)
HARRY TRUMAN:
General Eisenhower informs me
that the flags of freedom fly
all over Europe.
This is a solemn
but glorious hour.
I wish that
Franklin D. Roosevelt had lived
to see this day.
McINTOSH (dramatized):
Al McIntosh, Rock County
Star-Herald.
"Unlike New Yorkers,
who whooped, hollered,
"and tore up tons of paper
to throw in the streets,
"the news here was greeted
with quiet dignity
"and reverent restraint.
"One by one, the flags blossomed
out on Main Street
"and store by store
the employees quietly filed out
"and the business places were
locked up for the day.
"But there was no shouting, no
hilarious display of any kind.
"Most everybody went home.
"There was quiet exultation
over the fact
"that a great victory
had been achieved,
"but that rejoicing was tempered
by the sobering knowledge
that there was another great war
yet to be won."
(machine gun fire, explosions)
SAM HYNES:
It didn't really make much
difference on Okinawa.
The Japanese were not going
to fight any less hard
because Hitler was out of it.
(machine gun fire)
I suppose there was
a certain satisfaction
that we'd beaten that lot
and could now turn our attention
entirely to this lot,
but aside from that,
I don't think
there was much excitement.
EUGENE SLEDGE (dramatized):
"Nazi Germany might as well
have been on the moon.
On Okinawa,
no one cared much."
"We were resigned
only to the fact
"that the Japanese would fight
to total extinction
"as they had elsewhere, and that
Japan would have to be invaded
with the same gruesome
prospects."
Eugene Sledge.
NARRATOR:
The battle for Okinawa
was not going well.
The Marines had cleared
the northern and central parts
of the island by mid-April.
But in the south,
the Army had been unable
to blast the Japanese from
their main defensive positions,
a succession of limestone ridges
around the walled town of Shuri.
The Navy,
battered daily offshore
by kamikazes
and other Japanese warplanes,
demanded that the Army
undertake a landing behind
the Japanese lines
so that they could be attacked
from two sides simultaneously.
The Army commander refused.
And on the first of May,
the First Marine Division,
Eugene Sledge's outfit,
to shore up the center
of the American line.
SLEDGE (dramatized):
"A column of men approached us
on the other side of the road
"from the 106th Regiment,
27th Infantry Division,
"that we were relieving.
"Their tragic expressions
revealed where they had been.
"They were dead beat,
dirty and grisly,
"hollow-eyed and tight-faced.
"As they filed past us, one
tall, lanky fellow caught my eye
"and said in a weary voice,
'It's hell up there, Marine.'
"I said with some impatience,
"'Yeah, I know.
I was at Peleliu.'
He looked at me blankly
and moved on."
NARRATOR:
Japanese shells shrieked down
as the Marines struggled
to find cover.
Friends died, old friends
who had fought alongside
Sledge on Peleliu.
"Replacement lieutenants
were killed or wounded
with such regularity,"
he remembered,
"that we rarely saw them
on their feet
"more than once or twice,
and never got to know
their names."
Get down, get down.
The Marines inched
their way toward Shuri,
blasting and burning the enemy
out of their hiding places
one ridge, one village,
one gulley at a time.
SLEDGE (dramatized):
"I found it more difficult
to go back
"each time we squared away
our gear to move forward.
"The increasing dread of going
back into action obsessed me.
"It became the subject of the
most tortuous and persistent
"of all the ghastly war
nightmares
that have haunted me
for many, many years."
"The dream is always the same,
going back up to the lines
during the bloody month
of May on Okinawa."
HYNES:
Terrible things happened
at Okinawa.
But a man in an airplane
above the battle
doesn't see the terrible things.
What I saw was drifting smoke,
explosions.
You see destruction.
You can imagine the devastation,
but you don't exactly see it.
You don't see the dead civilians
who died in their thousands.
You don't see the dead Japanese.
You don't even see
your own dead.
I dropped some bombs on
buildings that blew up.
If there was anybody in them,
I suppose I killed somebody.
I don't know.
I'd like to think I didn't...
but that's what I was being paid
for, was to kill people.
(indistinct shouting)
NARRATOR:
Eugene Sledge and his fellow
Marines were now pinned down,
just 20 yards from enemy lines
and under fire from three sides,
on the slope of Sugar Loaf Hill,
the key to the defense of Shuri.
Artillery shells uncovered
half-buried Japanese corpses
and tore dead Marines
into pieces.
Rain pounded down, more than
a foot of it in a week,
washing maggots and feces
into the Marines' foxholes.
The stench was overpowering.
There was no relief from
any of it, day after day.
SLEDGE (dramatized):
"If a Marine slipped and slid
"down the back slope
of the muddy ridge,
he was apt to reach
the bottom vomiting."
"I saw more than one man
stand up horror-stricken
"as fat maggots tumbled out
of his muddy dungaree pockets,
"cartridge belt, legging lacings
and the like.
"We didn't talk
about such things.
"They were too horrible
and obscene
"even for hardened veterans.
I believed we had been flung
into hell's own cesspool."
NARRATOR:
Nearly 3,000 Americans died
taking Sugar Loaf Hill--
more per square foot than
anywhere else in the war.
In late May, the Japanese began
a carefully staged withdrawal
slipping back ten miles or so
to their last redoubt,
another series of ridges
at the island's southern end.
It would be three more weeks
before its last defenders
were killed and their commanders
committed suicide.
By then, 92,000
Japanese soldiers
and as many as 100,000 Okinawan
civilians were dead.
Of the 235 members
of Eugene Sledge's Company K
who landed on Okinawa,
just 26 emerged unhurt.
Of the 254 men brought in to
replace those who had fallen,
only 24 remained.
In the end,
more than 12,000 Americans died,
60,000 were wounded--
the worst losses
of the Pacific war.
Among the dead were Private
First Class J.J. McCarthy
of Waterbury; Sergeant
Jeff Fleming of Sacramento;
Private First Class Lowell Reu
of Luverne,
and Private Ernest Roy
of Mobile.
As the Allies prepared to move
on to Japan itself,
still more terrible losses
seemed inevitable.
HYNES:
We were told
that in the invasion of Japan,
we would be the first land-based
single engine bombing squadron.
To go in, be in on the invasion
of the Japanese home island.
That would be heroic stuff.
But at the same time, by then,
our sense of the strangeness
of the Japanese opposition
had become stronger.
And I could imagine
every farmer with his...
with his pitchfork
coming at my guts;
every pretty girl
with a hand grenade
strapped to her bottom
or something...
That everyone would be an enemy.
NARRATOR:
The Allies planned to begin
with the island of Kyushu
on November 1, 1945.
More than 500,000
Japanese troops
were already in position
to repel them--
and another six million
were either under arms
or ready to be called up.
Women and schoolchildren
were drilling
with sharpened bamboo spears.
The Americans did not expect
to be able to move against
the larger island of Honshu
until April of 1946.
Former president Herbert Hoover
headed a commission
that suggested half a million
Americans might die
before the islands
could be taken--
along with perhaps
seven million more Japanese.
Military planners came up
with different estimates,
was that the cost in casualties
was likely to be astronomical.
The end of the war
in the Pacific
still seemed very far away.
G.I.'s who had once talked of
getting "Home Alive in '45"
began to coin new slogans:
"Back in the Sticks in '46,"
"Back to Heaven in '47 "...
even "Golden Gate in '48."
NEWSREEL ANNOUNCER:
The soviet premier,
the remaining member
of the original Roosevelt-
Churchill-Stalin Big Three.
Now President Truman greets
Prime Minister Attlee.
And the conference
of the Big Three at Potsdam
sets the policy
of the Allied powers.
NARRATOR:
In mid-July, the Allies met
in Germany, at Potsdam,
and set forth the terms
under which they would agree
to end the war.
Japan's leaders would have
to abandon
every inch of their empire,
face trial for war crimes,
submit to being disarmed, and
agree to American occupation
until a new, democratically
elected government
could be established.
Unless they agreed to all of it,
the declaration warned,
they could expect
"the utter devastation
of the Japanese homeland."
Japan chose not to respond
to the Allied ultimatum,
and tried instead
to persuade Russia,
which had never declared
war on Japan,
to broker more favorable
surrender terms.
For most of Japan's leaders--
despite the agony the Japanese
people were enduring,
despite the even greater agony
that seemed sure to come--
unconditional surrender
still remained unthinkable.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
Ripped by stlc8tr!