THAT I WANTED TO FIGHT MY WAR
IN THE AIR.
THERE SEEMED TO BE
SOME SORT OF AN APPEAL ABOUT IT
OR A SENSE OF EXCITEMENT,
SO THAT WAS MY OBJECTIVE.
SO WITHIN THREE WEEKS
OF PEARL HARBOR,
I WENT OUT TO FORT LEWIS,
WASHINGTON,
TO APPLY TO THE ARMY AIR CORPS.
I WANTED TO BECOME
A FIGHTER PILOT.
AND MUCH TO MY SURPRISE,
I FAILED
THE COLOR VISION TEST.
AND I CONTINUED TO TAKE THE TEST
AT OTHER LOCATIONS
OVER A PERIOD OF TIME
UNTIL, GRADUALLY,
I MEMORIZED WHAT I SHOULD SEE --
WHAT NUMBERS AND SYMBOLS
I SHOULD SEE ON THE TEST.
AND THEN I PASSED IT,
BUT IT WAS NOT UNTIL I GOT
TO ANCHORAGE, ALASKA,
AND I WAS WORKING
FOR THE CORPS OF ENGINEERS
WHILE I WAS STILL TRYING
TO GET IN THE SERVICE.
AND I PASSED IT UP THERE
IN EARLY AUGUST OF 1942.
THE DAY THEY WERE KILLED,
WE TALKED
ABOUT THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
AND WE PACKED UP THEIR THINGS.
AND MAYBE AT
THE OFFICERS CLUB THAT NIGHT,
ABOUT WHAT
THE ANGLE OF THE FLAK HAD BEEN
SO WE COULD TRY TO AVOID
CERTAIN APPROACHES ON TARGETS.
BUT THEN WE NEVER TALKED
ABOUT THEM AGAIN.
WE NEVER TALKED
IT'S JUST AS IF
THEY DID NOT EXIST.
YHAUNTED US ALL THE TIME..
WE THOUGHT ABOUT -- OR I DID.
I CAN'T SPEAK FOR THE OTHERS.
BUT IT WAS THE KILLING,
THE NUMBERS OF...
TO SEND ME
ORTO A FIGHTER SQUADRON,ED
FIGHTER GROUP,
FIGHTING OFF OKINAWA
TO PARTICIPATE
IN THE INVASION OF JAPAN.
AND WHEN THE ATOMIC BOMB
WAS DROPPED ON HIROSHIMA
ON AUGUST 6, 1945,
AND WE STARTED TO COMPREHEND
WHAT THIS MEANT,
AND THEN THE SECOND ONE
WAS DROPPED ON NAGASAKI
FOUR DAYS LATER,
WE REALIZED
THAT OUR WAR WAS OVER
AND THAT WE WERE GONNA LIVE
THROUGH THIS THING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
IT ENDED LIKE THAT, SO FAST.
AND THOSE OF US
THAT WERE PRIMED AGAIN --
FORTIFIED PSYCHOLOGICALLY
AND EMOTIONALLY
TO GO BACK TO WAR --
WERE NOW REPRIEVED,
AND WE WOULD BE ABLE
TO GO ON WITH OUR LIFE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO UNDERSTAND THE OBJECTION
TO THE FACT THAT THE ATOMIC BOMB
WAS DROPPED.
WE JUST BURNED
ALL THE ADRENALINE
THAT OUR BODY COULD PRODUCE.
AND SOMETIMES
WHEN WE WOULD COME HOME
AND LAND OUR AIRPLANE
AND TAXI UP
TO OUR HARDSTAND
AND TURN OFF THE ENGINES,
WE WOULD JUST COLLAPSE,
JUST SITTING THERE
IN THE COCKPIT.
THERE WAS NOTHING ELSE LEFT.
WE HAD BURNED
ALL THE ADRENALINE.
WE HAD USED
ALL THE ENERGY THAT WE HAD.
SOMETIMES I HAD TO BE
HELPED OUT OF THE COCKPIT.
THE FELLOW
WHO OWNED THE BUILDING
SAID THAT WE HAD TO LEAVE
BECAUSE HIS SON WAS COMING HOME
FROM THE PACIFIC.
HIS SON HAD BEEN INJURED,
AND HE "DIDN'T WANT ANY JAPS
IN HIS APARTMENT BUILDING."
AND I SAID, "BUT MY
SISTER-IN-LAW IS PREGNANT.
SHE'S EXPECTING IN AUGUST --
END OF AUGUST."
THE BABY WAS BORN
ABOUT THE 21st.
BUT HE WAS ADAMANT,
AND ST. PAUL WAS JUST --
THERE WAS NO PLACE TO BE RENTED.
WE WENT AD AFTER AD,
LOOKING AT PLACES.
THEY WERE JUST LITTLE,
YOU KNOW,
PLACES NOT REALLY LIVABLE,
TO ME.
MY SISTER-IN-LAW AND I BOTH
WENT TO CHECK THEM OUT.
SHE WAS PREGNANT,
AND IT WAS SUCH A CHORE.
FINALLY, I SAID,
"YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GONNA GO OVER
AND TALK TO THIS FELLOW."
FIRST OF ALL,
I WENT IN THE FRONT.
AND IT WAS A SUNDAY.
AND HIS WIFE AND HER FRIENDS
WERE SITTING IN THE FRONT.
I SAID,
"I'D LIKE TO TALK TO MR. LAUER."
"MR. LAUER IS IN THE BACK.
HE'S WATERING."
SO I WALKED TO THE BACK
OF THE GARDEN.
HE WOULDN'T TURN OFF THE HOSE
AT FIRST.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
HE WAS VERY HARD OF HEARING.
SO I SAID, "MR. LAUER,
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU!"
AND I TOLD HIM,
"MY HUSBAND IS IN THE PACIFIC.
"HE IS WITH
MILITARY INTELLIGENCE.
"HE'S FIGHTING SIDE-BY-SIDE
WITH YOUR SON
AND I SAID,
"I'M SORRY THAT HE WAS INJURED,
BUT YOU JUST HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
THAT WE'RE ON THE SAME SIDE."
I MADE THIS PLEA AND, "EH?"
AND A COUPLE OF TIMES,
HE COULDN'T HEAR.
AND THEN FINALLY
TURNED OFF HIS HOSE,
AND DIDN'T SAY "YES,"
"NO," OR ANYTHING.
AND SO I WENT AWAY THINKING,
"WELL, TRIED MY BEST."
AND I LEFT
AND DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING AFTER.
WE WERE ABLE TO STAY.
SO I THOUGHT,
"WELL, IT MUST HAVE WORKED."
AND I TOLD HIM,
S"BE SURE TO ASK YOUR SON.
"BECAUSE HE'LL TELL YOU
THAT THESE NISEI BOYS
ARE FIGHTING WITH THEM
RIGHT THERE."
BUT IT SEEMED
LIKE HE NEEDED MY HELP
MORE THAN I NEEDED HIS.
HE WAS A SWEET KID,
SO AGREEABLE,
A LITTLE BIT GULLIBLE,
AND VERY GOOD-LOOKING.
AND I JUST FELT
THAT HE NEEDED ME.
AND HIM LEAVING LIKE THAT
REALLY BROKE MY HEART,
I TELL YOU.
AND, OF COURSE, MY MOTHER --
THAT MEANT TWO BOYS NOW
WERE IN THE SERVICE.
AND, UM...
IT WAS REALLY HARD
TO GIVE THEM UP.
FROM HIS LETTERS,
YOU COULDN'T TELL.
HE WAS A RESERVED PERSON.
AND I DON'T THINK
HE WANTED US TO KNOW
BECAUSE HE WAS PROBABLY
PROTECTIVE OF MOTHER AND I
AND MY OTHER BROTHER.
HE'S A WONDERFUL GUY, ANYWAY.
NO, HE NEVER COMPLAINED.
WE LIVED WITH THAT.
THAT WAS PART OF OUR PART
WE HAD TO PLAY.
HE NEVER GOT A CHANCE
TO GO TO A CAMP TO REGROUP
OR REST AND RELAXATION
OR BE ANALYZED.
A FRESNO BOY THAT WAS
A FRIEND OF BOTH OF US,
AND HE HAD SEEN HIM IN GERMANY.
AND HE SAID,
"HE LOOKED TERRIBLE.
AND I THINK
THEY SHOULD SEND HIM HOME."
WELL, IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
AND WHEN HE DID GET DISCHARGED
AND CAME HOME,
HE CAME TO SACRAMENTO
AND STAYED WITH US
FOR ABOUT TWO DAYS
OR THREE DAYS.
HE SEEMED FINE.
HE WAS KIND OF
A QUIET KID ANYWAY,
SO THERE WAS NO WAY
FOR ME TO KNOW.
I DIDN'T DETECT ANYTHING.
BUT HE WAS REALLY SUFFERING
FROM TRAUMA.
SO, HE WENT HOME TO MY MOTHER
IN FRESNO.
AND INSIDE OF A WEEK,
SHE WAS CALLING ME
AND TELLING ME
THAT SHE THOUGHT MY BROTHER
WAS HAVING SOME PROBLEMS
EMOTIONALLY.
I GUESS HIS --
IT WAS OVERPOWERING --
I GUESS THE DEPRESSION
AND THE TRAUMA
UNTIL HE JUST HUNG HIMSELF
FROM THE KITCHEN LIGHT.
AND MY MOTHER CAME IN
AND FOUND HIM.
MM-HMM.
YEAH, SO...
HE WAS 22.
WAR CAN BE ROUGH.
MY POOR MOTHER --
SHE WAS NEVER QUITE THE SAME.
MY GRANDFATHER...
TRAINED ME
TO BE A WARRIOR.
THE ANCIENT TRIBAL-WAR DAYS
WERE OVER.
BUT BEING...
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
A WARRIOR...
IN HIS TIME --
BEFORE THE RESERVATION
WAS SETTLED --
HE KEPT TRAINING ME
TO BECOME A WARRIOR.
THEN, OF COURSE,
I WOULD RIDE HORSES ALL MY LIFE,
EVER SINCE
I WAS A LITTLE BOY.
BUT IN THE WINTERTIME,
HE WOULD WAKE ME UP
EARLY IN THE MORNING.
HE SAID, "ALL RIGHT,
DON'T PUT YOUR SHOES ON.
"DON'T PUT YOUR CLOTHES ON.
RUN AROUND THE HOUSE
BAREFOOTED."
IT'S MAYBE 15, 20 BELOW ZERO.
EVERY MORNING,
IT WAS TRADITION
WITH THOSE OLD INDIAN MEN
TO TAKE A DIP IN THE RIVER.
SO IN WINTERTIME,
WE'D GO TO THE RIVER THERE,
MAYBE 15, 20 BELOW ZERO.
WE'D GO TO THE RIVER,
AND HE'D CUT A HOLE
IN THE ICE.
IT WAS ALREADY CUT,
BUT HE HAD TO CUT IT AGAIN
FOR HIS HORSES.
SO HE'D REMOVE
THE THIN LAYER OF ICE.
THEN WE'D GO IN THERE.
I'LL TELL YOU,
THAT'S PRETTY COLD.
HE TRAINED ME TO BE
PHYSICALLY STRONG.
BY HIS TRAINING
AND MY OBSERVING
THE ACTIVITIES AROUND ME --
MY ENVIRONMENT...
THE MOVEMENT OF THE ANIMALS,
THE BLOWING OF THE WIND
DIRECTION, AND SO FORTH,
SO I WAS GENERALLY
WELL AWARE
OF WHAT I'M DOING
OR WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
SO DURING WORLD WAR II,
I WAS NOT AFRAID,
I KNEW WHAT I WAS DOING,
AND I KNEW
I WAS GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
SO, HE TRAINED ME THAT WAY,
MENTALLY.
I WAS READY TO GO OVERSEAS.
AND A COUSIN OF MINE
HAD JUST COME BACK FROM EUROPE.
HE WAS A TAIL GUNNER.
AND BEFORE HE LEFT,
A MEDICINE MAN,
A SUN DANCE MEDICINE MAN --
POWERFUL, SACRED POWERS.
SO HE GAVE MY COUSIN...
AN EAGLE FEATHER,
A FLUFFY FEATHER
PAINTED YELLOW.
"ALL RIGHT," HE SAID,
"PUT THAT
INSIDE OF YOUR HELMET.
THAT'S YOUR PROTECTION."
THAT HELPED A LOT,
TOO, YOU KNOW?
SO AS LONG AS THAT
SACRED PROTECTIVE FEATHER
WAS IN MY HELMET,
WHY, I WAS NEVER AFRAID
OF ANYTHING.
I NEVER PANICKED.
AND I THINK I SURVIVED...
QUITE ADEQUATELY.
SOME SOLDIERS GET EXCITED
AND GET SCARED,
PANIC AND RUN,
AND THEY GET SHOT DOWN.
BUT I'M ALWAYS
IN CHARGE OF MYSELF.
I KNEW
WHAT THE ENEMY WAS GONNA DO.
SO I WAS ALL RIGHT.
AND THAT LITTLE MEDICINE
IN THERE,
I THINK THAT KIND OF GAVE ME
THAT...FEELING
OF HAVING POWER
OVER MYSELF
AND THE ENEMY.
I'VE SEEN A LOT
OF SAD SITUATIONS --
PEOPLE GETTING KILLED,
LYING THERE,
CIVILIANS, SOLDIERS,
BOTH SOLDIERS --
AMERICAN SOLDIER,
GERMAN SOLDIERS.
AND ONE OF THE WORST
I'VE WITNESSED
WAS WE WERE...
ADVANCING
INTO THIS LITTLE TOWN.
AND OUR COMPANY COMMANDER
STEPPED ON A MINE.
BOY, BOTH LEGS WERE GONE --
JUST THESE STUBS.
AND HE WAS SITTING THERE.
AND I WAS STANDING THERE
AND COULDN'T HELP HIM.
I WAS SCARED, YOU KNOW,
SHOOK UP.
AND HE LOOKED AT HIS LEGS,
THEN HE FELL OVER DEAD.
HE DIED.
THAT WAS TERRIBLE.
YEAH, THAT WAS TERRIBLE.
I SANG A SONG THAT BELONGED TO
A CHIEF WHO USED TO LIVE HERE,
A CHIEF
BY THE NAME OF GREYBULL.
AND HE WOULD SING THAT
WHENEVER THEY MEET
THE CHEYENNE, YOU KNOW?
AND WHEN THEY DO THAT,
READY TO CLASH,
WHY,
A CHEYENNE MEDICINE MAN
WOULD SING A SONG --
I MEAN, A CROW MEDICINE MAN
BY THE NAME OF GREYBULL
WOULD SING THIS SONG.
AND THE WORDS WOULD SAY,
"THE CHEYENNE ARE COMING NOW
TO DO BATTLE.
"TODAY I SHALL RUN OVER
ONE OF THEM.
"YES, IALL OF THEM." THEM.
SO I SANG THAT SONG.
FIRST IT WAS
THE DEAD GERMAN BOYS
LYING ALL OVER
THE FIELD OF BATTLE
AND BEGINNING TO TURN YELLOW
AND SO FORTH,
THEIR EYES OPEN.
I'D NEVER SEEN A CADAVER
WITH EYES OPEN BEFORE.
I'D SEEN DEAD PEOPLE,
LIKE MY RELATIVES,
IN COFFINS AND SO ON.
THEIR EYES WERE ALWAYS
DECENTLY CLOSED.
AND WHEN YOU SEE
VIOLENTLY KILLED PEOPLE
WITH HOLES IN THEM
AND MISSING LIMBS AND SO ON
STARING AT YOU WITH OPEN EYES
AS IF THEY WERE ALIVE,
YOU FEEL TERRIBLY DISCONNECTED
FROM THINGS.
ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO SAY
SOMETHING TO THEM?
ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO SAY,
"I'M SORRY.
DID IT HURT MUCH?"
AND SO FORTH?
AND I WAS STILL IN COMMAND
OF MY PLATOON.
AND WE ATTACKED A GERMAN
POSITION THROUGH A SMOKE SCREEN,
WHICH WAS SO THICK THAT
YOU DIDN'T KNOW WHERE YOU WERE.
IT WAS A BIZARRE THING.
IT WAS A TECHNIQUE
FOR GROUND WARFARE
FROM THE FIRST WORLD WAR.
AND THERE WERE DEAD GERMANS
ALL THE WAY ALONG.
AND PEOPLE WERE STEPPING
ON MINES
AND BLOWING THEIR FEET OFF
AND THINGS.
AND MY PEOPLE
WERE RELATIVELY UNTOUCHED.
AND WE HAD TO CLEAR
A SMALL WOODS
THAT WAS SEPARATED FROM
EVERYTHING ELSE,
MAYBE A HALF-MILE WIDE
AND A MILE LONG.
AND THE GERMANS HAD BEEN
PREPARING THAT DEFENSIVELY,
THAT POSITION, FOR MONTHS,
PROBABLY SINCE NORMANDY.
AND WE ATTACKED IT
AS CHEERFULLY AS WE COULD,
RUNNING IN WITH OUR RIFLES
AT PORT ARMS AND SO ON
THROUGH MACHINE-GUN FIRE.
AND A NUMBER OF PEOPLE
WERE HIT AND KILLED BY THAT.
AND ON MY LEFT, I REMEMBER,
I WAS LYING ON MY STOMACH,
TRYING TO KEEP
AS LOW AS POSSIBLE
TO AVOID THIS MACHINE-GUN STUFF
THAT WAS GOING ON
ABOUT AN INCH ABOVE MY HEAD --
SO CLOSE I COULD FEEL THE HEAT
OF BULLETS AS THEY PASSED BY.
WHO'D NEVER IMPRESSED ME
ONE OF THVERY MUCHCEMENTS,
BECAUSE HE WAS RATHER FAT
AND CLUMSY --
AND HE WAS AIMING AT A MACHINE
GUN SOME DISTANCE FROM US.
AND BEFORE HE COULD GET
A SHOT OFF,
THEY HIT HIM WITH,
I THINK, ABOUT THREE BULLETS.
AND I SAW ONLY HIS BACK.
I DIDN'T SEE HIS FACE
OR ANYTHING ELSE.
THERE FLEW LITTLE CLOUDS
OF WHAT LOOKED LIKE DUST,
BUT THEY WERE
POWDERED BLOOD,
THEY WERE BITS OF FLESH TISSUE,
AND THERE WERE PIECES
OF CLOTH UNIFORM.
AND ABOUT THREE OF THESE
CAME AT ME,
AND THEN HE COLLAPSED,
AND THAT WAS THE END OF HIM.
WHEN I CAME OUT OF THE WAR,
I COULD NOT BE RECOGNIZED.
AND I HAD A TERRIBLE TIME
WITH MY FAMILY
BECAUSE THEY'D BEEN READING
THE SATURDAY EVENING POST
AND LIFE MAGAZINE
ALL DURING THE WAR.
AND THEY THOUGHT IT WAS
A SORT OF CHEERFUL GAME WE WON.
THEY KNEW
I WAS IN THE INFANTRY,
BUT THEY THOUGHT
THAT WAS A BRANCH OF THE SERVICE
WHERE YOU DID
A LOT OF RUNNING --
ATHLETIC STUFF AND SO FORTH.
AND THEY HAD NO IDEA THAT
IT WAS ABOUT CLOSE-UP KILLING.
THE MISSION OF THE INFANTRY,
AS I LEARNED IN TRAINING
MANY TIMES --
WAS THAT THE INFANTRY
IS CHARGED WITH THE MISSION
OF GETTING AS CLOSE
AS POSSIBLE TO THE ENEMY
AND DESTROYING HIM.
AND THAT MEANS TEAR HIM TO BITS
IF POSSIBLE.
SO THAT WAS IMPOSSIBLE FOR
MY PARENTS EVEN TO UNDERSTAND.
AND HAD SOME NOTES,
FAIRLY BLOODTHIRSTY,
THAT I'D WRITTEN
ABOUT THE WAR.
AND I GAVE THEM
TO MY DAD AFTERWARDS.
AND HE COULDN'T FINISH THEM.
ABOUT ALL THE GOOD WAR STUFF,
TO SAY THAT I'M OFFENDED WOULD
BE A GRAVE UNDERSTATEMENT.
I'M APPALLED BY IT --
BY THE LACK OF IMAGINATION
OF AMERICANS,
BY THE OBLIGATORY OPTIMISM
BY THEIR DIFFICULTY
IN UNDERSTANDING
THE TROUBLES OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE LESS WELL-PLACED
THAN THEY ARE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE POOR.
AND THE INFANTRY ARE THE POOR
IN TIME OF WAR.
I'VE HAD A VERY DIFFICULT TIME
SOMETIMES
TRYING TO EXPLAIN
WHAT HAPPENED TO ME.
PEOPLE WILL SAY,
"WHY ARE YOU SO IRRITABLE?"
"I'M IRRITABLE BECAUSE I THOUGHT
OF A COLLEGE FRIEND OF MINE
"WHO SPENT THE WAR AS
AN ADMIRAL'S AIDE IN THE PACIFIC
"AND NEVER FIRED A GUN
OR WAS FIRED AT.
"AND THE CONTRAST BETWEEN WHAT
HE WAS DOING AND I WAS DOING
"IS JUST TOO APPALLING TO BEAR
WITHOUT SOME KIND OF EMOTION
OF RESISTANCE AND ANGER."
I WAS ANGERED THAT
EVERYBODY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE -- THE, UH...
SITUATION OF SOLDIERS
WHO FOUGHT THE WAR
ON THE GROUND.
WELL, BASICALLY,
WHEN YOU'RE AN O.C.S.,
AND YOU LIVED, ATE, SLEPT,
AND EVERYTHING ELSE TOGETHER.
YOU STUDIED TOGETHER.
AND I STILL REMEMBER IT.
IT WAS GALLAGHER,
GALLOWAY, GAMBLE,
GARDENER, GALT, AND GINSBURG.
FORWARD OBSERVER IS UP FORWARD
TO FIND TARGETS
FOR THE ARTILLERY.
AND YOU WORKED
WITH THE INFANTRY.
IN OUR UNIT,
THE FORWARD OBSERVER,
IF THE INFANTRY WAS MOVING,
YOU HAD TO STAY
WITH THE LEAD PLATOON
OF THE ATTACKING COMPANY.
CHANCES ARE YOU WOULDN'T BRING
ARTILLERY DOWN ON YOURSELF,
YOU'D KEEP IT OUT IN FRONT.
AND THAT WAS THERE.
BUT WE ALSO WENT FOR TARGETS,
IF WE COULD GO OUT
AND FIND SOME TARGETS.
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
IT WAS BORING.
WE DIDN'T HAVE
BUT FOUR OFFICERS.
AND MOST OF THE TIME,
THERE WASN'T BUT ONE AVAILABLE.
IF I WAS NOT FORWARD,
THEN I HAD TO READ THE MAIL.
AND IT WAS JUST ABOUT AS BORING
AS YOU COULD GET.
I DO RECALL ONE FELLOW
THAT I JUST DIDN'T READ
HIS LETTER TO HIS GIRLFRIEND.
AND THERE JUST WASN'T
IT WAANY SENSE TO IT. DAY.
HE WAS ONLY WRITING HIS WIFE
ABOUT A PAGE.
[ LAUGHS ]
BUT THE GIRLFRIEND
WAS IN ENGLAND.
WHICH BASICALLY HAD 50 PEOPLE,
JUMPED OFF ONE MORNING,
AND I HAPPENED TO HEAR THEM
ON THE RADIO THAT AFTERNOON.
THE BATTALION COMMANDER
WAS ASKING HOW MANY MEN HE HAD.
HE WANTED TO WAIT FOR DARK,
AND HE WAS SENDING UP
CHOCOLATE BARS.
HE SAID,
"WE GOT ONE FOR EACH MAN.
HOW MANY DO YOU WANT?"
AND HE SAID, "SEND ME FIVE."
HE ONLY HAD FIVE MEN LEFT
OUT OF HIS PLATOON --
HIMSELF AND FOUR,
APPARENTLY.
BUT YOU JUST LOST FOLKS
LIKE MAD IN THERE.
I'M SITTING,
AFTER I WAS CAPTURED,
SEVERAL DAYS LATER --
MAYBE A WEEK, I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS IN THIS LITTLE VILLAGE
WHERE I HAD FIRED.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
ONE ROUND GOT AWAY FROM ME,
I HAD KNOCKED THE STEEPLE
OFF THE CHURCH.
BUT I'M SITTING
ON THE CHURCH STEPS,
AND THIS GERMAN OFFICER GAME UP,
AND HE WAS ARTILLERY.
AND HE COULD TELL
I WAS ARTILLERY.
YOU HAD YOUR BRASS
ON YOUR COLLAR.
"WERE YOU THE FORWARD OBSERVER
OVER THERE?"
I SAID, "YEAH.
AND YOU UP THERE?" "YES, SIR."
AND HE SPOKE BETTER ENGLISH
THAN I DID.
HE'D BEEN TO SCHOOL
IN ENGLAND.
AND HE CAME OVER THERE
AND GOT CAUGHT UP IN THE WAR --
CAME HOME,
GOT CAUGHT UP IN THE WAR.
AND HE WAS JUST LIKE I WAS --
HE WAS JUST IN THE WAR.
SO HE AND I
HAD OLD-HOME WEEK
SITTING THERE
ON THE CHURCH STEPS.
BUT THAT WAS
AN UNUSUAL EXPERIENCE.
BUT I WAS GLAD TO SEE HIM.
WELL, ON ONE,
WE WERE ON A RAILROAD CAR,
AND THE AMERICANS CAME IN
STRAFING IT.
YOU JUST TRIED TO GET AWAY
FROM THE TRAIN.
AND I WENT OUT A WINDOW
AND DOWN THE INCLINE
AND ACROSS TO WHERE
THERE WAS A BRIDGE --
A LITTLE BRIDGE OVER A ROAD,
NOT A BIG ONE.
AND THERE WERE TWO OR THREE
GERMAN SOLDIERS UNDER THERE
THEY THOUGHT THE AMERICANS
HAD LANDED OR SOMETHING.
THEY WANTED
TO SURRENDER TO ME.
AND I DIDN'T WANT THEM.
THAT I WASN'T IN ANY POSITION
TO TAKE THEM CAPTIVE.
BUT, YEAH,
THEY TRIED TO GIVE UP TO ME.
WHEN I WENT INTO THE MARINES,
THE FIRST THING WAS --
WE HAD A LITTLE SCRIP
TO EAT WITH.
AND WHEN YOU WOULD STOP
IN A TOWN LIKE MACON, GEORGIA,
THE REGULAR MARINES,
THERE HAD BEEN
NO BLACK MARINES.
SO THE REGULAR MARINES
WOULD EAT IN THE DINING ROOM,
IN THE REGULAR AREA.
BUT IN ORDER
TO HONOR MY SCRIP,
THEY TOOK ME UPSTAIRS
IN THE PRIVATE DINING ROOM,
AND THEY BROUGHT ME
ANYTHING I WANTED TO EAT
AS LONG AS I DIDN'T EAT
DOWNSTAIRS.
AND I IMMEDIATELY ORDERED
THE FILET MIGNON
WITH ALL THE TRIMMINGS.
IT WOULD REMIND YOU OF HOME.
AND IT BROKE YOUR HEART.
FOR INSTANCE, THEY HAD BANDS
WHO WOULD COME OUT
AND ENTERTAIN THE TROOPS.
AND ONE BAND
BROUGHT OUT LENA HORNE.
AND WE HAD
THE WHITE TROOPS AROUND US,
AND THEY WOULD MAKE SEATS
OUT OF MAKING TREES EVEN
AND PUTTING AIRSTRIPS.
WHEN SHE CAME OUT AND SAID,
"SHOO, SHOO, SHOO, BABY,"
A WHOLE STRIP FULL OF WHITE BOYS
FELL OFF THEIR SEATS.
WE WERE PROUD AS PUNCH
TO SEE LENA HORNE
AND OTHER PEOPLE --
COUNT BASIE, DUKE ELLINGTON.
"THIS IS WORTH FIGHTING FOR,"
IS WHAT WE THOUGHT,
"IF WE CAN JUST GET BACK HOME
AND GET A CHANCE
TO ENJOY SOME OF THIS."
OUR ATTITUDE WAS,
IF THE GERMANS
OR THE JAPANESE
WON THE WAR,
THE WHITE FOLK WOULD GET
ON THEIR SIDE,
BOTH THE GERMAN OR JAPANESE
AND THE WHITE FOLK.
SO WHAT WE DID WAS GO OVER THERE
AND WIN THE WAR
AND THEN COME BACK UP
AND PICK UP THE GAUNTLET
WHERE WE TRIED TO GET
OUR CIVIL RIGHTS.
THAT WAS THE FEELING.
I WAS ON A LIST SOMEWHERE
IN THE NAVY
TO BE CALLED UP
AT THE APPROPRIATE TIME.
AND I WAS IN COLLEGE AT
THE UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA.
AND I'D SPENT MY MONEY.
ONE OF THEM WAS ALREADY
ANA MARINE FIGHTER PILOT..
THAT WAS UNENDURABLE
FOR ME TO BE A COLLEGE BOY
AND HIM TO BE
A MARINE FIGHTER PILOT.
SO I FELT THAT I HAD
TO ACCELERATE THIS SOMEHOW.
I WENT
INTO THE RECRUITING OFFICE.
AND THERE WAS,
TO MY ASTONISHMENT,
AN OLD FRIEND OF MINE
AT THE DESK.
AND I SAID, "I'VE GOT TO GO."
AND AS I TALKED TO HIM,
IT GOT MORE AND MORE INTENSE.
"I'VE GOT TO GO!
I'M OUT OF MONEY!
EVERYONE ELSE IS GOING."
AND HE WENT
TO THE CORNER OF THE ROOM
WHERE THERE'S A GREAT PILE
OF FILES
AND FINGERED
DOWN TO THE BOTTOM,
PULLED ONE OUT,
PUT IT ON TOP,
AND SAID, "YOU'LL GET
YOUR ORDERS NEXT WEEK.
DON'T TELL ANYBODY."
AND I WENT OUT,
AND IT WAS LIKE THAT MOMENT
AT THE BEACH
WHEN YOU CLIMB THE LADDER
OF THE DIVING BOARD
UP TO WHERE YOU USUALLY DIVE OFF
AND THEN KEEP GOING TO THE ONE
WHERE YOU MIGHT JUMP OFF...
AND KEEP GOING STILL
UNTIL YOU GET THE VERY TOP,
WHERE YOU'VE NEVER
JUMPED OFF BEFORE.
AND THEN YOU STEP UP TO THE EDGE
AND JUMP.
I FELT THAT I WAS IN
EMPTY SPACE.
SOMETHING HAD HAPPENED TO ME
THAT HAD NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE,
AND THAT I HAD DONE IT.
YOU DON'T HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO
DETERMINE YOUR LIFE VERY OFTEN.
YOUR PARENTS DO THAT FOR YOU.
YOUR TEACHERS DO THAT FOR YOU.
THAT WAS GONNA CHANGE MY LIFE
BUT I JUSFOREVER. DECISION
AND IT DID.
EVERYBODY JOINED.
I WANTED TO BE A PILOT.
AND EVERYBODY
WAS IN THE AIR FORCE.
AND THEY WORE PINK PANTS
AND HATS WITH THE GROMMET
TAKEN OUT.
THERE WAS SOMETHING SPURIOUS
TO ME ABOUT THOSE GUYS.
THEY FLEW TOO HIGH.
I WANTED TO BE IN --
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
I WAS 17 YEARS OLD.
THESE WERE IMPRESSIONS
THAT DIDN'T HAVE ANY BASIS
IN REALITY.
I ALSO THOUGHT
THAT THE MARINE CORPS,
WHICH WAS AN ELITE OF THE NAVY,
AS I SAW IT,
AND THEREFORE
WAS THE BEST OF THE BEST,
WOULD BE THE ORGANIZATION
TO FLY WITH, IF I COULD.
I BEGAN FLYING IN --
FROM A LITTLE GRASS FIELD
NORTH OF DALLAS.
AND IT WAS WONDERFUL.
THE FIRST EXPERIENCE
OF BEING UP IN THE AIR
AND SEEING THE WORLD
DOWN BELOW YOU --
IT'S INDESCRIBABLE.
BUT IT ADDS A DIMENSION TO
THE WORLD YOU'VE BEEN LIVING IN.
GROWING UP IS A SERIES OF TESTS,
INEVITABLY,
MOTIVATED
PARTLY BY CURIOSITY,
ABOUT WHAT IT'S LIKE TO DO
THINGS THAT GROWN-UPS DO
THAT YOU'VE NEVER DONE BEFORE,
AND PARTLY
A SERIES OF TESTS
OF YOUR READINESS
TO BE AN ADULT, I THINK.
BY PASSING THE TESTS,
YOU EARN ADMISSION
TO THIS CLASS OF PEOPLE
THAT YOU THINK
ALL KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
AVIATION IS CERTAINLY LEARNING
TO FLY AS A SERIES OF TESTS.
BUT YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
THAT AS AN 18- OR 19-
OR 20-YEAR-OLD KID,
YOU'RE, AT THE SAME TIME,
STILL GOING THROUGH
THE OTHER SET OF TESTS.
YOU'RE FINDING OUT
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE DRUNK.
YOU'RE TRYING TO PASS THE TEST
WITH GIRLS...
WHEN YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WHEN YOU GET THERE.
YOU'RE, UH...
YOU'RE TRYING TO LIVE
INDEPENDENTLY.
YOU'RE TRYING TO ACT
YOU'D BE DOING THOSE,
YOU SEE,
WHETHER YOU'D WERE
IN MILITARY TRAINING OR NOT.
ON TOP OF THOSE, THEN,
ARE THE TESTS ABOUT SOLOING
AN AIRPLANE
AND DOING YOUR FIRST LOOP
AND DROPPING YOUR FIRST BOMB.
THERE WAS A SONG,
WHICH WAS SOMETIMES --
THE REFRAIN OF WHICH SOMETIMES
WAS "BLESS THEM ALL"
AND SOMETIMES "FUCK 'EM ALL,"
DEPENDING ON THE AUDIENCE
AND WHO WAS SINGING.
AND THE VERSES WENT...
THEY S--
THEY SENT FOR THE --
THEY SENT FOR THE ARMY
TO COME TO TULAGI
BUT GENERAL MacARTHUR
SAID NO
HE GAVE AS HIS REASON
THIS ISN'T THE SEASON
BESIDES, THERE IS NO USO
FUCK 'EM ALL
THE LONG AND THE SHORT
AND THE TALL
FUCK ALL THE ADMIRALS
IN ComAirSoPac
THEY DON'T GIVE A DAMN
IF WE NEVER GET BACK
SO WE'RE SAYING
GOODBYE TO THEM ALL
AS BACK IN OUR FOXHOLES
WE CRAWL
THERE'LL BE NO PROMOTION
THIS SIDE OF THE OCEAN
BUT CHEER UP, MY LADS
BLESS 'EM ALL
THAT'S THE LEAST OBSCENE
OF MY REPERTOIRE.
IF YOU WANT THE REST OF THEM,
I COULD OBLIGE.
THE ATOMIC BOMB WAS,
OF COURSE,
AN ENORMOUS --
MORE THAN A BIG HELP.
IT WAAND WE FELT THAT,WAR.
AND WITH RELIEF,
BUT ALSO WITH A KIND OF SADNESS.
WE HAD BEEN TURNED
INTO ARTIFICIAL ADULTS
FOR A FEW YEARS.
AND WE'D LIVED LIVES
THAT WERE FULL OF EXCITEMENT,
LIVES THAT WE COULD NEVER HAVE
KIND OF ANTICIPATED LIVES,
BACK IN MINNEAPOLIS
AND BONESTEEL.
NOW IT WAS ALL OVER.
AND I'M SURE I WASN'T
THE ONLY PERSON WHO FELT,
"NOW I WILL HAVE TO GO BACK
TO BEING WHO I REALLY AM,
"WHO IS
A COLLEGE UNDERGRADUATE
"AT THE UNIVERSITY
OF MINNESOTA.
"HOW BORING THAT WILL BE.
"HOW NARROW AND LIMITED
THAT WILL BE.
"WHAT KIND OF FUTURE
WILL I HAVE
"THAT WILL BE AS MUCH FUN
AS BEING A PILOT
IN THE MARINE CORPS?"
WHEN THE JAPANESE SURRENDER
WAS ANNOUNCED TO US...
WE...FELT --
THE SQUADRON DECIDED
THAT IT OUGHT TO...
MAKE SOME GESTURE
OF CELEBRATION.
AND WE...
TOOK OFF AS A SQUADRON,
IN FORMATION,
AND FLEW OUT
OVER THE FLEET IN BUCKNER BAY.
AND I EXPECTED THAT
WAS WHAT IT WAS GONNA BE --
WE'D FLY OVER THE FLEET,
AND THEN WE'D GO HOME AND LAND.
THE MAN LEADING THE FLIGHT
SIGNALED TO GO INTO A COLUMN.
SO WE ALL PULLED BACK,
ONE BEHIND THE OTHER,
AND DOVE ON THE FLEET.
HE PULLED UP
ANAND DID A BARREL ROLL.T,
NOW,
A BARREL ROLL IN A TBM
IS LIKE
A FAT LADY DANCING.
SHE SHOULDN'T DO IT.
AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN SURE
SHE CAN DO IT.
AND THEN THE NEXT PLANE
DID IT.
AND THEN IT WAS MY TURN.
AND I PULLED UP
AND PULLED IT OVER,
AND ALL THE RUBBISH AND DEBRIS
IN THE BOTTOM OF THE AIRPLANE
CAME FLOATING UP
INTO MY EYES,
AND THE CREWMAN IN THE BACK
RATTLED AROUND A BIT, I GUESS.
AND THEN WE CAME OUT
AND IT WAS STILL FLYING
AND THE WINGS
HADN'T FALLEN OFF.
AND THEN WE WENT BACK
AND LANDED.
AND I RECKONED
WHAT WE WERE DOING
WAS GIVING DEATH
ONE MORE CHANCE.
IT WAS LIKE THE STORM.
OF COURSE
IT COULD HAVE BEEN ME.
BUT IT WASN'T.
I GRIEVE FOR THEM EVERY DAY,
THE TWO OR THREE
WITH WHOM I WAS MOST --
WHO I WAS CLOSEST TO.
BUT, THEN,
PEOPLE DIE IN LIFE.
NOT THAT YOUNG,
BUT EVERY LIFE
HAS SOME GRIEF IN IT.
AND YOU GO ON LIVING.
I TALKED RECENTLY
WITH A FRIEND OF MINE.
HER NAME
IS GEORGINE DuVIVIER-HALL.
SHE'S ABOUT MY AGE,
A LITTLE YOUNGER,
WAS IN COLLEGE IN PENNSYLVANIA
DURING THE WAR --
A LITTLE WOMEN'S COLLEGE
CALLED WILSON COLLEGE
WHERE SHE SAID THEY WORE
WHITE GLOVES TO DINNER,
OR AT LEAST WHITE GLOVES
WERE PART OF IT.
SHE SAID SHE REALLY
WASN'T AWARE OF THE WAR.
THERE WAS KIND OF INNOCENCE
IN THIS PLACE,
AS THOUGH THE WAR
DIDN'T EXIST.
BUT WHEN SHE WENT HOME
AFTER THE TERM ENDED,
SHE HAD TO SIT IN A BOXCAR
SITTING ON A COFFIN
WHICH WAS THE COFFIN
OF AN AMERICAN SERVICEMAN.
IT SEEMED
AN ODD JUXTAPOSITION.
THEY WERE CASUALTIES FROM
SOMEWHERE BEING BROUGHT HOME.
GRAVE RESPONSIBILITY --
I WAS NOW IN CHARGE
OF THREE SQUADS,
A TOTAL OF 41 MEN.
AND THEN I BEGAN TO REALIZE
WHY THIS WAS DONE.
IN YOU'RE AN ENGINEER,
YOU'RE SELECTED
TO BE AN OFFICER
BECAUSE YOU KNOW MATHEMATICS
AND LOGARITHMS AND ALL OF THAT.
IF YOU'RE
AN ARTILLERY OFFICER,
BECAUSE YOU KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT TRAJECTORY AND PHYSICS.
WHY WOULD THEY SELECT SOMEONE
FOR AN INFANTRY OFFICER?
WELL, HE HAS TO KNOW HOW TO READ
THE MAPS AND THE COMPASS,
BUT HE HAS TO KNOW
HOW TO KILL.
I WON'T TELL YOU
THHOW MANY MEN I KILLED.T.
THERE ARE SOME WHO COUNT SHEEP,
SO THEY TELL ME,
BUT THERE ARE TIMES IN MY LIFE
WHEN I COUNT MEN.
AND THAT'S A TERRIBLE THOUGHT
BECAUSE I'M CERTAIN
THE AVERAGE PERSON,
IF HE OR SHE
RAN OVER A CAT,
YOU'D NEVER FORGET THAT.
SO HOW IN THE WORLD CAN YOU
FORGET KILLING A MAN, YOU KNOW?
WELL, I WAS IN OAKLAND
GETTING READY
TO GET ON A SHIP
FOR A BOAT RIDE
BACK TO HAWAII.
I WAS IN MY UNIFORM
WITH THREE ROWS OF RIBBONS
AND THE CAPTAIN'S BARS
ON MY SHOULDER.
I MUST HAVE LOOKED
PRETTY GOOD,
WITH A HOOK ON MY RIGHT HAND,
WHERE IT USED TO BE.
AND SO I THOUGHT
I'D JUST GET A NICE HAIRCUT
SO I'D LOOK NEAT.
I LOOKED AROUND OAKLAND.
HERE WAS A BARBERSHOP.
THREE CHAIRS, I REMEMBER THAT --
ALL THREE EMPTY.
THE BARBERS ARE JUST STANDING
AROUND, SO I WALKED IN.
THIS ONE BARBER
APPROACHED ME.
AND HE LOOKED AT ME,
AND HE SAID, "ARE YOU A JAP?"
YOU KNOW,
THAT WAS A STRANGE WELCOME.
AND I SAID,
"I'M AN AMERICAN."
"WELL, I'M ASKING YOU,
ARE YOU A JAP?"
I SAID,
"MY FATHER WAS BORN IN JAPAN.
"MY MOTHER IS JAPANESE.
I SUPPOSE THAT MAKES ME ONE."
"WE DON'T CUT JAP HAIR."
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
"HERE I AM IN UNIFORM.
IT SHOULD BE OBVIOUS TO HIM
THAT I'M AN AMERICAN SOLIDER,
AND THAT FELLOW, VERY LIKELY,
HAD NEVER WENT TO WAR."
AND HE'S TELLING ME,
"WE DON'T CUT JAP HAIR."
I WAS SO TEMPTED
TO STRIKE HIM,
BUT THEN, I THOUGHT,
IF I'D DONE THAT,
ALL THE WORK
THAT WE HAD DONE
WOULD BE FOR NIL.
SO I JUST LOOKED AT HIM,
AND I SAID,
"WELL, I'M SORRY
YOU FEEL THAT WAY."
AND I WALKED OUT.
BUT IT BECAME CLEAR TO ME
THAT WHAT CAPTAIN ESPINGER
SAID WAS VERY CORRECT.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A LONG STRUGGLE,
A TOUGH ONE.
THAT IF IT HADN'T BEEN
FOR THAT CHILDHOOD THAT WE HAD,
STRESSED AND KNOWLEDGEABLE
IN MATTERS
THAT WERE SO OUT OF PROPORTION
FROM REGULAR CHILDHOOD,
WE PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE
THE PEOPLE WE WERE TODAY.
AND IT'S JUST LIKE ME LIVING
IN THE WINE COUNTRY HERE
WHERE I JUST FOUND OUT
THAT THE MORE STRESSED THE VINE,
THE BETTER THE WINE
AND THE GRAPE IS.
SO DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
SO IT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
I THINK LUVERNE PROBABLY
WAS CLEANER DURING THE WAR
THAN AT ANY TIME
IN ITS HISTORY,
PRIMARILY BECAUSE
WE KIDS WOULD GO OUT
AND WE'D GO TO THE ALLEYS,
BACK ROADS, DITCHES --
ANYTHING TO FIND SOMETHING
OUT OF METAL
BECAUSE YOU COULD GET,
LIKE, A PENNY A POUND
FOR SOMETHING OF THIS NATURE.
AND THEN IF YOU TOOK THEM
DOWN TO THE THEATER,
IF YOU HAD TWO, THREE,
FOUR POUNDS OF SCRAP METAL,
YOU WOULD GET A FREE TICKET.
MY TWO BROTHERS AND I
WENT OUT ONE TIME
AND MADE A HORRENDOUS HAUL.
WE JUST -- I DON'T KNOW.
THE ONE MAJOR THING
THAT I REMEMBER IN THERE,
WE HAD A BRASS BEDSTEAD,
AND WE HAD OLD WHEELS
WE FOUND.
WE HAD MORE THAN ENOUGH
TO GET INTO THE THEATER.
SO THE KIDS
WHO DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH --
WE WERE DOWN ON MAIN STREET
RIGHT BY THE THEATER,
AND WE'RE HANDING OUT --
"WHAT DO YOU NEED?
"YOU NEED A TIRE?
HERE'S AN OLD RIM.
HERE'S AN OLD PIECE OF METAL,"
OR WHATEVER IT WAS.
THEN DOC BOMENE, WHO WAS
THE MANAGER OF THE THEATER,
CAME DOWN AND TOLD US, "I DON'T
WANT YOU DOING THIS ANYMORE.
THESE KIDS HAVE TO GET
THEIR OWN STUFF."
TWO POUNDS OF MILKWEED
WOULD MAKE ONE LIFE VEST.
SO THEY GAVE EVERYBODY
THESE SACKS, OR BAGS,
AND THEN WE WOULD GO OUT
LOOKING FOR MILKWEED.
AND WE GOT TWO CENTS A POUND
FOR THESE.
OKAY, NOW,
NTHAT'S A LOT OF MILKWEED.
STUCK IN ONE OF THESE BAGS.
BUT WE WOULD HAVE OUR PATCHES.
WAS FROM OLSEN'S DAIRY OUT
TOWARD THE BLUE MOUNTAINS,
ALONG THE OLD ROCK ISLAND
RAILROAD.
AND WE'D GO OUT THERE
AT NIGHT OR AFTER DINNER,
AND WE WOULD CRAWL DOWN
IN THESE --
IT'S NOTHING
BUT WEEDS AND BRAMBLES
AND WE'RE COLLECTING THESE
GOD-AWFUL MILKWEED PODS.
BUT WE WOULDN'T TELL ANYBODY
WHERE WE WERE GOING
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T WANT ANYBODY
"FINDING THE MILKWEED
IN OUR PATCH" KIND OF THING.
IN ONE YEAR, I THINK
THERE WERE LIKE 1,300 BAGS
THAT WERE TURNED IN
OF THIS MILKWEED.
I COULD NEVER UNDERSTAND
HOW THEY WERE GONNA TAKE
THIS LITTLE BIT OF STUFF
AND SAVE SOME NAVY PILOT
WHO ENDED UP
IN THE PACIFIC OCEAN.
BUT THAT WAS THE STORY WE GOT.
AND THERE WERE WARDENS
ALL AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THESE GUYS WOULD GO OUT THERE.
AND WE'D HAVE
THESE BLACKOUTS.
THE SIREN WOULD RING DOWNTOWN.
THEN YOU HAD TO TURN OFF
ALL YOUR LIGHTS
UNLESS YOU HAD
A BLACKOUT CURTAIN
THAT YOU COULD PUT OVER YOUR
WINDOW SO THAT NO LIGHT GOT OUT.
THE DADS --
MY DAD, THESE OTHER GUYS --
WOULD GO OUT, AND THEY WOULD
WALK AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
NOW, I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
HOW THE GERMANS WERE GONNA FLY
ALL THE WAY ACROSS
THE ATLANTIC OCEAN
AND THE JAPANESE WERE GONNA FLY
ACROSS THE PACIFIC OCEAN
I MEAN, I HAD NO CONCEPT
OF WHAT WAS GOING ON.
THEY WANTED THESE GUYS
TO HAVE GUNS,
BUT THEY DIDN'T HAVE
ANY GUNS FOR THEM.
SO MY DAD, THE FIRST COUPLE
TIMES HE WENT OUT,
I GUESS YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO HAVE THIS NOTION
THAT YOU'RE CARRYING A WEAPON.
HE THOUGHT
THAT WAS KIND OF DUMB,
SO HE'D GO OUT
WITH HIS 12-GAUGE SHOTGUN.
HE HAD NO SHELLS OR ANYTHING.
AND THEN IT GOT TO BE
WHERE THESE GUYS
WOULD STAY OUT FOR A WHILE.
AND MY MOTHER
FINALLY FIGURED OUT
THAT THEY MAY DOWN
AT DOC BLAKE'S
OR ED COLLINS' OR SOMEPLACE
HAVING A HIGHBALL.
SO IT WAS MORE
OF A SOCIAL THING, I THINK,
FOR THESE MEN TO PROTECT US
FROM I DON'T KNOW WHAT.
THEY HAD TO GO OUT
ON THESE NIGHTLY PATROLS.
COLLECTING ANYTHING
AT THAT TIME
WAS OUR BASIC SOURCE OF INCOME
FOR KIDS.
AND WE COULD GO --
NOW THIS SEEMS
KIND OF RIDICULOUS.
BUT WE COULD GO TO
ROVER'S POOL HALL, FOR EXAMPLE,
AND HAVE A HOT DOG
AND A MILKSHAKE AND A CANDY BAR
THE HOT DOG WAS A DIME,
AND THE MILKSHAKE WAS A DIME,
AND THE CANDY BAR
WAS A NICKLE.
AND IF YOU HAD 11 CENTS,
YOU COULD GO TO THE MOVIE
BESIDES.
SO WE DIDN'T REALLY NEED
A LOT OF MONEY.
BUT WHAT MONEY WE GOT,
WE GOT FROM A LOT
OF THE SCRAP THINGS.
WE HAD AN ARMY AIR BASE
THAT WAS 30 MILES AWAY.
AND A LOT OF THOSE SOLDIERS
CAME OVER TO LUVERNE
ON THEIR R&R,
SO WE HAD SOLDIERS AROUND US.
THEY WERE FLYING LIBERATORS
AND P-47s OUT OF SIOUX FALLS,
SO WE HAD A LOT OF AIRPLANES
OVER US.
IF SOME GUY WAS DATING
ONE OF THE LUVERNE GIRLS,
LET'S SAY,
AND THEY WENT UP ON AN EXERCISE
AND HE WAS FLYING ONE OF THESE
P-47 THUNDERBOLTS,
HE WOULD COME ZOOMING DOWN
MAIN STREET
LIKE 200, 300 FEET
OVER THE CITY.
AND THE WINGS ARE GOING
LIKE THIS TO LET --
IF SHE'S WORKING
WITH THE PHONE COMPANY,
SHE'D KNOW WHO IT WAS.
I MEAN, THIS IS KIND OF A WAY
THEY WERE SIGNALING.
AND WINDOWS WOULD RATTLE,
AND PEOPLE WOULD GET ALL UPSET.
"YOU KNOW, THESE GUYS
SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS."
BUT I DON'T THINK
IT EVER STOPPED THEM.
I REMEMBER
ANOTHER FUNNY THING.
AND WE WERE ALL EXCITED
THE BOMTO SEE THEM, A LOT.
THESE BIG LIBERATORS
AND B-29s,
SOME OF THESE THAT THEY
WERE FLYING OUT OF SIOUX FALLS.
AND SO IF WE COULD HEAR THEM
COMING,
WE'D SAY, "BOMBER! BOMBER!"
AND EVERYBODY WOULD RUN OUT
THE BACK DOOR,
AND WE'D LOOK UP
AND WATCH THESE.
WELL, WE HAD A COCKER SPANIEL,
RINKY.
RINKY WOULD HEAD FOR THE BACK
DOOR JUST AS FAST AS HE COULD.
ALL YOU HAD TO SAY IS, "BOMBER!
BOMBER!" AND RINKY IS GONE.
AND ONE TIME MY MOTHER HAD JUST
WAXED THE KITCHEN FLOOR.
AND WE SAID,
"BOMBER! BOMBER!"
AND RINKY GOES TEARING OUT
TO THE BACK DOOR.
HIS FEET ARE JUST CHURNING AWAY
LIKE CRAZY,
FALLING DOWN, TRYING TO GET OUT
THE BACK DOOR TO SEE THAT.
BUT WE ALL RAN OUT TO WATCH
THESE PLANES GO OVER.
AND THEY WENT OVER A LOT.
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS TERRIBLE
CONFUSION DURING COMBAT,
JUST UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, NO ONE KNEW
WHAT WAS GOING ON,
AND I DON'T THINK
THE GERMANS DID, EITHER.
BUT ONE OF THE MOST CONFUSING
THINGS WAS THE RADIO.
WE ALWAYS HAD A RADIO
IN SOMEPLACE AROUND US
SO THAT WE COULD CONTACT
HEADQUARTERS,
AND THEY WERE ASKING
WHERE WE WERE.
CALL FOR ARTILLERY FIRE,
YOU COULD TALK
TO THE ARTILLERY OBSERVER.
BUT THE RADIO
WAS JUST MADNESS
BECAUSE THERE
WAS ALWAYS SOME GUY
PINNED DOWN IN A TERRIBLE
SITUATION, SCREAMING FOR HELP,
AND THEN A VERY COOL, CALM GUY
IN THE BACKGROUND
SAYING, "THIS IS RABBIT 3.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?"
AND THIS GUY WOULD SAY,
"CUT THAT CRAP OUT!
WE'RE GETTING FIRED ON!"
BUT THIS COMING
FROM ALL DIRECTIONS.
WELL, WHEN THE WAR ENDED,
I BELIEVE I WAS IN PARIS
AND LIVING A VERY,
VERY SPLENDID LIFE.
IT WAS VERY, VERY GOOD.
I WAS WORKING FOR A BRANCH
OF STARS AND STRIPES
CALLED ARMY TALKS,
WHICH WAS A MAGAZINE
THAT WAS PUT OUT,
AND TRAVELING RATHER FREELY
AND HAD SOME NICE GIRLFRIENDS
AND A VERY, VERY INTERESTING,
MATURE GROUP OF GUYS
WHO EDUCATED ME MORE THAN
THE COLLEGE HAD EDUCATED ME.
THEY WERE --
AND WHEN THE WAR ENDED
IN JAPAN,
IT WASN'T THE GREAT CELEBRATION
TO PARISIANERS.
BUT TO WE IN THE ARMY
WHO THOUGHT MAYBE WE'D GET SENT
TO JAPAN OR SOMETHING,
IT WAS A GREAT CELEBRATION.
AND PARIS IS A GREAT PLACE
TO CELEBRATE.
SO WE DID LOTS
OF CELEBRATING THERE,
QUITE UNLIKE V-E DAY.
YOU KNOW, I DID SHOOT
AT A FELLOW ONE TIME.
AND IT WAS IN BAYREUTH...
THE HOME OF WAGNER.
AND THERE WAS A RIVER
THAT SPLIT THE TOWN IN HALF.
AND WE'D MOVED DOWN
TO THE RIVER.
AND WE WERE IN A LITTLE BAR.
AND IN OUR RADIO,
IT CAME THROUGH
FROM WAY UP IN BACK OF US
THAT THERE WAS A SQUAD
OF GERMANS
COMING DOWN THE ROAD
THAT WE WERE AT.
AND WE WATCHED THEM,
AND THEY CAME DOWN.
AND THEY WENT IN A BUILDING
ACROSS THE STREET.
AND WE REALLY DIDN'T WANT
TO PUT UP A BIG FIGHT.
BUT PRETTY SOON ONE CAME OUT
AND CAME DOWN
AND LOOKED AT THE BRIDGE THAT
HAD BEEN BLOWN THAT WE WERE IN,
THEN TROTTED UP THE ROAD
A COUPLE BLOCKS.
AND WE THOUGHT, "WELL, THE SQUAD
UP THERE WILL PICK HIM UP."
PRETTY SOON,
HE CAME TROTTING BACK.
SO WE REALIZED
THERE'S NO SQUAD THERE.
SO EVERYBODY SAID,
"WHY DON'T YOU SHOOT HIM?"
"NO, YOU SHOOT HIM."
I ENDED UP
HAVING TO SHOOT HIM.
AND THE NEXT THING I KNEW,
I WAS OUT THERE.
HE FLEW UP IN THE AIR,
AND TWO OF US,
THE NEXT THING WE KNEW,
WE WERE OUT THERE NURSING HIM.
AND THEN THE SQUAD CAME OUT
FROM ACROSS THE STREET
THAT'S THE ONLY ONE
I'M EVER SURE I SHOT.
I SHOT AT LOTS AND LOTS
OF THINGS.
BUT YOU'RE SHOOTING AT SMOKE.
AT WHERE YOU COULD SEE
MACHINE-GUN FIRE COMING FROM.
YOU WERE SHOOTING AT TANKS,
WHICH WAS USELESS.
YOU NEVER KNEW
WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
THIS WAS THE ONLY CASE WHERE
YOU COULD REALLY SEE SOMEBODY.
AND NOBODY REALLY WANTED
TO DO IT.
HERE HE WAS,
AND HE WAS DOING NO HARM.
AND HE WAS REALLY
JUST TRYING TO RETREAT.
BUT WE COULDN'T THINK
OF ANY OTHER WAY TO DO IT.
OUR MOVIE STARS IN THOSE DAYS
WERE GUYS LIKE JAMES CAGNEY
AND HUMPHREY BOGART
AND EDWARD G. ROBINSON
AND THOSE GUYS.
AND WE GREW UP
ON ADVENTURE STORIES.
WHAT IS THE REASON
FOR A STORY TO EXIST?
IT'S TO TAKE YOU OUT OF
A DRAB EXISTENCE, ISN'T IT,
INTO A DIFFERENT WORLD?
THAT WAS HOW WE GREW UP.
AND THOSE WERE OUR AIMS.
AND WHEN THE REAL WAR BROKE OUT,
IT DID GIVE MANY OF US --
MANY LATINOS ENLISTED,
THOUSANDS.
AND I SUSPECT THAT
IN THE BACK OF THEIR MINDS,
THERE WAS JAMES CAGNEY
DOING HIS THING IN A WAR MOVIE
OR SOMETHING.
BUT THEY DID OKAY IN REALITY.
ESPECIALLY IN IWO JIMA,
WE DID FIND MANY, MANY JAPANESE
WHO HAD KILLED THEMSELVES.
THEY BLEW THEMSELVES UP
WITH HAND GRENADES.
THEY DISEMBOWELED THEMSELVES
WITH THEIR KNIVES.
AND SOMETIMES,
WHEN WE THREATEN TO BLOW THEIR
CAVES UP AND BURY THEM ALIVE,
THEY, IN AFFECT, SAID,
"SCREW YOU. GO AHEAD AND DO IT."
AND WE DID.
WE BURIED A LOT OF THEM ALIVE.
OUR ATTITUDE
WAS "BETTER THEM THAN US."
AND WE HAD A SAYING
IN THE MARINE CORPS --
THE JAPANESE WANT TO DIE
FOR THE EMPEROR,
AND WE WANT TO HELP THEM.
AND TIT'S THAT SIMPLE. IT.
YOU'RE IN A WAR.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE FEELING --
YOU FEEL SORRY FOR A GUY
WHEN YOU SEE
THAT HE HELD A HAND GRENADE TO
HIS BELLY AND BLEW HIMSELF UP,
BUT VERY BRIEFLY.
WHO, POTENTIALLY, MIGHT HAVE
KILLED OR ONE OF YOUR BUDDIES.
THEY WERE TOUGH PEOPLE.
SO, YOU KNOW, IF THEY WANTED
TO BLOW THEMSELVES UP,
THAT WAS ONE LESS GUY
TO NAIL YOU.
AND THE SHELLING
WAS SO INTENSE
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA LOSE
MY MIND.
AND I THOUGHT, "GEE, I'VE BEEN
IN THIS TOO DAMN LONG ALREADY.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE."
BUT I DIDN'T REALIZE UNTIL
LATER,
WHEN WE WERE TOLD
ABOUT THAT DEFENSE,
HOW EFFECTIVE THAT DEFENSE WAS
AND HOW MUCH ARTILLERY
WE WERE TAKING.
I THOUGHT IT WAS ME.
THAT WAS MY WORST MOMENT.
THAT NIGHT,
WE WERE GATHERED.
AND THE LIEUTENANT CAME OVER,
AND HE SAID,
"IF WE'RE DRIVEN OFF
THE BEACH,
TRY TO SWIM TOWARDS
THE TRANSPORTS."
AND WE THOUGHT, "JESUS,
WHAT IS HE SAYING TO US?"
I KNOW THAT SOUNDS RIDICULOUS,
BUT THEY ACTUALLY TOLD US THAT.
"IF WE'RE DRIVEN OFF
THE BEACH,
START SWIMMING
FOR THE TRANSPORTS."
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO SWIM RIGHT.
I SINK LIKE A ROCK.
FOR US,
IT WAS LIKE THE JAPANESE --
IT WAS DO IT OR TOO BAD.
WE MET THE CADETS WHEN THEY WERE
TRAINING OVER IN PENSACOLA.
AND I HAD ONE CUTE BOYFRIEND
WHO WAS FROM THE MIDWEST.
AND WHEN HE KNEW HE WOULD HAVE
SATURDAY NIGHT FREE,
HE WOULD FLY HIS TRAINING FLIGHT
OVER MOBILE
AND DIVE DOWN
AND BUZZ MY HOUSE TWICE.
AND THAT WAY, I KNEW HE'D BE
OVER THAT SATURDAY NIGHT.
AND I WAS NOT TO DATE
ANYONE ELSE.
I WAS TO SAVE
THAT SATURDAY NIGHT FOR NORMAN.
SO I HAD AN OLD-MAID NEIGHBOR
ACROSS THE STREET.
SHE'D SIT ON HER FRONT PORCH AND
WAIT TO SEE IF WE'D BE BUZZED.
SHE'D COMING RUNNING ACROSS
THE PARKWAY OUT HERE,
YELLING,
"KATHARINE, HE'S COMING!
"KATHERINE,
HE'S COMING TONIGHT!
WAS ALERTED TO WHETHER
SO,HE WOULD COME OR NOT.OD
WELL, THE LAST PERSON
WE THOUGHT WOULD EVER BE KILLED
WAS MY UNCLE CHARLIE TUCKER.
HE WAS SUCH A MACHO PERSON.
HE JUST DID EVERYTHING WELL.
AND WE JUST NEVER THOUGHT
ANYTHING WOULD HAPPEN
TO CHARLIE.
IF ANYONE WOULD COME THROUGH
THE WAR,
IT WOULD BE CHARLIE.
SO, WHEN THE NEWS CAME
THAT CHARLIE WAS MISSING
IN ACTION AT GUADALCANAL,
WE WERE DEVASTATED.
WE KEPT THINKING
THEY WOULD FIND HIS --
FIND HIM ON AN ISLAND ALIVE.
WE KEPT THINKING THAT MAYBE HIS
PLANE HAD GONE DOWN SOMEPLACE
WHERE HE COULD GET ASHORE
AND BE SAVED.
IN FACT,
BEFORE WE FINALLY GAVE UP
THAT THEY WOULD NEVER FIND
CHARLIE
BECAUSE WE JUST DID NOT THINK
THE LORD WOULD TAKE HIM.
BUT YOU KNOW
THE WONDERFUL THING?
HE STAYS 22 YEARS OLD.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
I MADE UP MY MIND THAT I WOULD
NEVER MARRY A MAN IN UNIFORM
BECAUSE I LOVED THE UNIFORMS.
SO I THOUGHT,
WELL, MAYBE I WOULD MARRY HIM
AND REALIZE I DIDN'T
LIKE HIM AT ALL --
THAT IT WAS ALL THE UNIFORM.
SO I DID NOT MARRY
TILL AFTER THE WAR
BECAUSE OF THAT
AS MUCH AS ANYTHING.
AND THE MAN I DID MARRY
HAD ON A UNIFORM,
BUT IT WAS A PILOT'S UNIFORM.
AND I NEVER SAW HIM
IN HIS DRESS NAVY UNIFORM
TILL THE DAY I MARRIED HIM.
AND HE WORE IT IN OUR WEDDING.
SO --
OH, AND I DID LIKE HIM IN IT.
I REALLY DID.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
Ripped by stlc8tr!