Your attention, please.
There has been an accident
at Maison Blanche.
It involved Porsche number 64,
driven by Michael Delaney
and Ferrari number 18,
driven by Fioro Belgetti.
Senora Belgetti,
Attention, attention...
Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen.
On this circuit, the world's
most famous motor race is run.
Conceived by Charles Faroux
and Georges Durand
shortly after
the first World War,
the course was named after
the nearest town
and the number of hours
that men and machines
are put to the supreme test
of speed and stamina.
The circuit is 13.469
kilometers, or 8.418 miles.
Composed of country roads linked
with the main highway
nearly all of it open to traffic
363 days a year.
Along the 3.2-mile
Mulsanne straight
the cars reach a maximum speed
in excess of 230 miles per hour.
The first race was run in 1923.
The lap record was nine minutes,
39 seconds.
The average speed,
66.69 miles per hour.
Last year, the lap record
was three minutes, 22 seconds.
The average speed,
145.508 miles per hour.
The race is open
to six classes of cars--
from the smallest
production models
to the largest sports
and turbo-type engines--
all competing at the same time
on the same circuit.
There are 55 cars
and 1 10 drivers
representing countries
from all over the world.
They will drive day and night,
through sun and rain.
Beneath his racing suit,
each driver must wear
fireproof underwear
capable of withstanding
2,400 degrees Fahrenheit--
the temperature of burning
gasoline-- for 15 seconds.
His blood type must be indicated
on either suit or crash helmet.
Each car has two alternating
drivers.
No driver may total more
than 14 out of the 24 hours.
Each driver must have
at least one hour rest
between turns at the wheel.
No one may drive more
than four consecutive hours.
For the first time
in the history of this race,
the running start,
with the drivers lined up on
the opposite side of the track
then running to their cars
at the fall
of the tri-colored flag,
tests speed of action
for reasons of safety.
This year, the drivers will be
securely strapped
into their driving seats
prior to the start of the race.
Yellow flags and yellow lights
along the circuit
indicate the presence
of an accident
or as it is called
in the racing world, a "shunt".
Yellow means danger.
No overtaking.
The race will start
4:00 p.m. Saturday,
and finish 4:00 p.m Sunday.
The car covering the greatest
distance in 24 hours
shall be the winner.
In the case
of the last two cars,
this will be the supreme test
of 3,000 miles.
And so, ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the most famous
motorcar race in the world--
the 38th running
of the grand prix
of endurance
and efficiency--
the 24 hours of Le Mans.
We're pleased to welcome
Michael Delaney back to Le Mans
after his unfortunate accident
here last year
and to see that he is
in such good form
following his exciting race,
a fortnight ago
at the Nurburgring
where Ferrari's top driver,
Erich Stahler,
narrowly beat him.
The Delaney-Stahler rivalry
will be interesting to follow
on this very different circuit
where the endurance of the car
is as important as is the skill
of the driver.
It is now five minutes to four.
Five minutes to start.
Will all drivers be
in their cars
in one minute's time, please.
Drivers... to your cars, please.
Four minutes to start.
Three minutes to start.
Two-and-a-half minutes to start.
Two minutes to start.
And once again, here are the
first ten qualifying positions:
Number 25,
driven by Kurt Ahrens;
number 15,
driven by Michael Parkes;
number 21,
driven by Johann Ritter...
...number 22,
driven by Paul-Jacques Dion;
number eight,
driven by Erich Stahler...
...number five,
driven by Lugo Abratte;
number six,
driven by Vito Scaliso;
number seven,
driven by Claude Aurac;
number 20,
driven by Michael Delaney...
...number 14,
driven by Gilles Marnier.
Over three minutes have passed.
We may expect the cars through
the check gate any moment now.
Will it be Porsche or Ferrari
in the lead?
Here's the leading car,
Porsche number 25,
in for its first pit stop
for fuel
and possible driver change.
And here comes Erich Stahler,
Ferrari number eight,
closely followed by the first
of the Gulf-Porsche cars,
number 20,
driven by Michael Delaney.
Watch out
for the red Lola.
Okay.
Pretty quick pit stop
for the Ferrari...
...and here comes 20,
back on the track.
Still in first place.
Gulf-Porsche number 21,
driven by Johann Ritter,
entering the pit.
And... Porsche
number 20 Delaney.
20 by four.
Okay, thank you.
My colleague has just handed me
a weather report,
and it looks as if
the possibility of rain--
which was previously forecast--
will shortly be upon us.
Just one more, Mr. Delaney.
Hello.
You had a very good start.
It's a long race.
Are you well?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
What will you tell
Peter and Erica
when they get old enough
to ask what their father
does for a living?
I'll tell them
that their father
is the greatest
chauffeur in the world.
If you had a choice,
would you like to tell them
something else?
For example,
"Well, this week, daddy's
flying to Switzerland."
Yes. The new motor factory
is almost completed
and I have to interview
various applicants for...
What are you trying
to tell me?
Would you like that better?
Only if you'd like it better.
If they ask me what their mother
does for a living,
I'll say "she lies."
"She can look straight
into your eyes
"and tell the biggest lies
you've ever heard
in your life."
Really?
Yes.
It's the right time to stop.
I can finish quite well
in this race.
Perhaps even...
Well, in any case,
it's the right time to stop.
As was forecast,
we have our first touch of rain.
It's going to be
very interesting
to see what tactics
the team manages in the rain.
If it's only a shower,
they won't change
from dry to rain tires.
But if it does continue,
they must.
Your attention to the pit area.
The longtail Porsche,
number 25, is coming in,
after having been
out on the circuit
for only 14 minutes,
since its last stop
for fuel and driver change.
The team of Kurt Ahrens
and Vic Elford
has built up
a formidable early lead
on the factory Ferraris
and the Gulf-Porsche team.
However, it appears now
that something definitely
out of the ordinary
has befallen the Austrian entry.
You will recall that
this is the car which,
for the first time
in the history of Le Mans,
averaged a speed in excess
of 150 miles per hour.
Mr. Delaney.
You know the white longtail
is out of the race
with a blown engine.
Yeah, well, that's bad luck.
Do you think
it will be
another
Ferrari-Porsche race?
A little early to say,
but I think so.
What kind of race
will you drive?
Try to save the machine,
go as fast as I can, try to win.
Do you think it will be
like Nurburgring--
a race between
you and Stahler?
I hope not, ma'am.
And what do you
think of Stahler?
Stahler?
I think he's probably
one of the best drivers
in the world.
Excuse me.
What do you think
is the most difficult thing
about Le Mans?
To go as fast as possible,
and keep the car on the road
for 24 hours.
That's difficult.
Would this be
the same kind of race
you had with Delaney
at the Nurburgring?
Well, this is Le Mans.
It's a different thing,
you know?
Do you think
that you and Delaney
will end up having
a close race here?
Maybe. He's fast, I'm fast,
so we're always together.
Good luck.
Michael...
How's that German
car running?
Fast. Ferrari?
Fast.
It's getting wetter.
Slipping and sliding.
Michael, uh...
the press is making
a big thing about us.
Yeah. But it's money.
That's American.
Michael...
be careful.
Now don't be a pain
in the ass, Erich.
And here are
the official positions,
two hours into the race.
In first place,
Ferrari number eight
finished 35 laps
at an average speed
of 144.981 miles per hour.
In second position
is Gulf-Porsche number 20
at 35 laps...
All cars have come into the pits
to change to rain tires,
with the notable exception
of the three
Gulf-Porsche entries
and the four Ferrari team cars.
It is apparent that neither
Porsche manager David Townsend
or Ferrari manager
Loretto Fuselli
wants to call his cars in
for an unscheduled pit stop
during this closely
contested race.
Looks kind of hairy
out there.
At practice
it didn't rain,
so this is really
your first time
out in the weather
at Le Mans.
Ja, it is.
Why doesn't Townsend
bring them in for rain tires?
Why don't you ask him?
It's raining worse
at Mulsanne.
They're due in,
in 1 1 --
In 1 1 minutes. I know.
Your attention, please.
There has been an accident...
It involves Lola number 1 1,
and Porsche
number 47.
Fortunately,
the drivers are not hurt.
Bring them in
for rain tires.
Here we are.
Ferrari's decided
to change at last.
And Porsche number 20
has come into the pits, also.
Now we should see a race develop
between the mechanics,
and they will determine
who's going
to be the first to go out.
20 is away first.
Delaney now leads Le Mans.
And there goes Stahler,
now in second place.
-No problem.
-No problem, yes, yes.
It's nothing!
It's going well, Claude,
isn't it?
Oui. I can feel it.
The machine is good.
This might be the year.
Well, let's hope so.
It's a long race.
I know.
Don't think
too far ahead.
Lisa?
Yes?
Would you like
some coffee?
No, thank you.
Ciao.
What problems
have you got out there?
Only thing is,
that off the Mulsanne,
in the middle of the road...
...if you stay
a little bit to the right
and watch it when you come up
over the hump,
has a little bit of tendency
to go this way.
Be a little careful
before you go into the cape,
and you can out-brake
the Ferrari.
Hey, guys, move it!
All right, Mike...
How long?
Merci.
Monsieur.
Bon soir,
Monsieur Delaney.
Bon soir.
Hello, Mike.
How you doing?
Cheese, please.
Seems to be
the only seat left.
May I sit down?
Where are you living now?
In Paris.
I have to watch myself
in Paris.
I always get fat there.
I heard you and Erich
had quite a race
at the Nurburgring.
Well, he keeps me honest.
Can l, can l
get you something?
No, thank you.
Were you hurt badly
in the accident?
No.
Was it difficult
to get back to racing?
Not really.
But it must have been
very difficult for you.
It was, in the beginning.
I'm better now.
I was just wondering...
why you came back here.
For myself.
Delaney's on his way.
Dixie.
Check the rear uprights
on 20, 21 and 22.
All right.
It is 5:00 a.m.,
the 13th hour of the race,
and the Ferrari-Porsche battle
continues unabated
with only 12 seconds
separating the two lead cars:
Gulf-Porsche number 20,
Ferrari number eight.
As of this moment,
there are 25 cars
left in the race.
I shall give you
a precise listing of
the most recent abandonments
in a few moments' time.
Watch the handling,
Michael.
Just a slight return
about the rear uprights.
Here's the second
Ferrari team car coming in.
Number seven,
piloted by Chris Barnett.
Another driver change
should be in order.
Yes, Claude Aurac
will take over.
Your attention, please.
Your attention,
please.
There has been an accident.
It involves
Ferrari number seven,
Porsche number 20.
Both cars are out of the race.
I shall tell you about
the drivers' condition
as soon as I get word
from hospital.
This way.
Please sit down
there, please.
Yes.
Can you tell us about Aurac?
Do you know if Michael
caused the accident?
We just want to ask you...
I don't know.
I don't know
and I don't want
to talk about it!
Do you compare this
to last year's shunt,
the one in which this lady's
husband was killed?
I have just received word from
the pit box that Marta Simca...
...that Marta Simca number 30,
out of the race
due to gear box problems.
Just got word from
the hospital about Claude.
It's bad, but they say
he will pull through.
And Delaney?
Nothing serious,
but he's out of the race.
Are you all right, Michael?
I'm fine.
You sure?
Yeah. I'm all right.
Where are we running?
Third and fourth.
Michael, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
It was a bad shunt.
Yeah.
Where are you running?
Third.
If you try to nail Scaliso
do it down through
Maison Blanche.
He doesn't like it there.
Thank you.
Michael, are you all right?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
No. I'm fine.
Then what happened to the car?
It was my fault.
I made a mistake.
I wrote the car off, David.
David.
This isn't just
a thousand-to-one shot.
This is a professional
blood sport.
And it can happen to you.
And then it can happen
to you again.
When people risk their lives...
shouldn't it be for something
very important?
Well, it better be.
But what is so important
about driving faster
than anyone else?
A lot of people go through life
doing things badly.
Racing's important to men
who do it well.
When you're racing it's...
it's life.
Anything that happens
before or after...
it's just waiting.
What happened
on the Delaney shunt?
There was a problem
with the maul,
slower traffic
got in the way.
The car is finished?
Yes, the car
is finished.
Hey, David,
21 's coming in!
Get the jack!
It's a wishbone.
Your attention in the pit area
with the leading car:
Gulf-Porsche number 21
is experiencing something
other than a routine stop.
From the action of the
mechanics, it would appear
that there is a problem
with the rear suspension.
Here is the second place car,
Ferrari number eight,
coming in for what should be
its last stop for fuel
and driver change.
Erich Stahler will
take over for the final
driving session, and no doubt
will resume the lead
from Gulf-Porsche number 21
still in the pit.
Too slow.
Stahler's in trouble.
The bonnet's up
on Ferrari number eight.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the first and second place cars
are in the pits
experiencing
mechanical difficulties.
Yeah?
Hello, David.
Are you fit, Michael?
Well, I'm a little stiff...
I say, are you fit?
My knees are sore.
Stahler's Ferrari's
in the pits
with ignition problems.
We got 21 in
with a broken
rear wishbone.
Dixie's fixing it now.
I want you to replace Ritter.
He's not quick enough.
Excuse me.
Michael, I want you
to drive flat-out.
I want Porsche
to win Le Mans.
Your attention, please.
Announcing a change of drivers.
Gulf-Porsche number 21
will be driven
by Michael Delaney,
replacing Johann Ritter.
Repeat:
Gulf-Porsche number 21
will be driven
by Michael Delaney,
replacing Johann Ritter.
The car is running good.
Brakes are okay.
Darling,
does it really matter?
Yes, it does.
But you were
going to quit anyway.
Yeah...
but not this way.
Ladies and gentlemen,
through the Chicane and
along the grandstand straight,
here is the new leader,
Ferrari number five,
driven by Lugo Abratte,
with only eight minutes
remaining
in the 24 hours of Le Mans.
And now, in second place
is Larry Wilson,
in Gulf-Porsche number 22.
And now, through the Chicane,
and going into the final lap,
is the Veida Ferrari
number five,
driven by Lugo Abratte.
And in second place
is Larry Wilson,
in Gulf-Porsche number 22.
And, on the same lap,
having made up nine seconds
on the two leaders,
are Ferrari number eight
and Porsche number 21,
running third and fourth--
Erich Stahler
and Michael Delaney,
pushing their cars to the limit
in this,
the most closely
contested finish
in the history of Le Mans.
Your attention, please.
I have just received word
that the first place car,
Ferrari number five,
driven by Lugo Abratte,
is out of the race
with tire trouble.
With only two minutes
remaining in the race,
the lead has been taken over
by Gulf-Porsche number 22,
driven by Larry Wilson.
Larry Wilson in 22.
Porsche wins Le Mans!
And second, Michael Delaney
in Gulf-Porsche number 21.
And third, Ferrari number eight,
driven by Erich Stahler.
Thank you, Michael.