So young!
We're over here! Wait for us!
We're gonna get photos!
- Come, Cabiria. They're calling us.
- I'm coming.
Where's Wanda?
Wanda, come on!
Marisa!
Get lost!
With that nose
you want a photo?
Who's takin' the picture?
How much?
Now what do we do?
You need to confess. Down there,
where it says confressione.
I already confessed yesterday.
Watch out! He's a cripple!
I'm gonna ask for mercy
from the Madonna too. Like you.
What am I asking for?
You don't remember?
I could ask for a villa
in Peripli.
That's not what you said!
Don't you remember?
I'll ask for whatever I feel like.
But you said you'd ask...
I changed my mind.
Why are you talking like that?
See? You made
my candle go out.
Thirty masses at 1,000 each.
That's 30,000.
I gave them 35.
Yeah, you did okay.
You never know.
How's the act of contrition go?
I forgot.
"My Lord, I repent
with all my heart."
- Yeah. What's after that?
- It's written in the confessional.
Wait here.
We can't go in together!
That's enough for now!
Use the other entrance!
Take it easy. Don't push!
I'm sick. I can't help it.
He's sick too. Can't you see that?
Careful, Uncle.
- There's the altar, Uncle.
- I can't.
I can't go on. I can't move.
I'll hold you till we're at the altar.
I gotta rest.
Rosie, come here.
I think he's gonna pass out.
Try again, Uncle.
We're almost there.
Everyone has a secret agony.
Everyone has a wish
for You to fulfill.
Open your heart to the suffering,
O Holy Virgin!
Mercy, Madonna!
Call out with all your hearts,
"Viva Maria!"
- Heal me, Madonna!
- Make me well, Madonna!
Wanda, over here!
Stay close.
What happens next?
I don't know!
You oughta hear my heart beating.
I'm shaking.
I feel so strange, Wanda.
Now all kneel and pray.
Amleto, will the Madonna
bestow Her grace on me?
I think so.
Now approach the altar
of the Virgin.
Look into Her sweet eyes,
and in Her glance, each one of you...
will feel the light of hope
turned on in your heart.
Madonna, help me...
to change my life.
Bestow your grace on me too.
Make me change my life.
- Uncle, now!
- I'm afraid.
Drop the crutches.
She'll have mercy on you.
I'm afraid!
I'm holding you!
Madonna, I'm a sinner.
A worm of the earth.
Have mercy on me, Madonna.
Don't leave me!
Lost your tongue?
Have a drink.
Careful, Wanda.
One glass and she's smashed.
What are you doing?
- I'm thinking.
- About what?
- What did she say?
- She says she's thinking.
Too much thinking
will make your head explode.
Look at those delinquents!
Stop with the damn ball!
They're doing it on purpose!
I'll fix 'em!
Next time I'll kick it
the other way!
You wanna stay here by yourselves?
Uncle and I will leave.Just say so.
- Why should we want to?
- What's wrong with you?
- What if we wanted to?
- What's the matter, Cabiria?
Hey! Come over here
and get your ball!
Come over here
if you want it!
Go get her.
She can't even walk.
I'm not gonna tangle with her.
She'll manage.
This music's boring!
Let's rock!
What are you doing, you nut?
We haven't changed.
Nobody's changed!
We're all the same as before,
just like the cripple.
What do you want to change,
Cabiria?
You think this is the end?
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna sell the house.
Everything. I'm leaving.
Good-bye, you guys.
I'm through with all this!
Where'll you go?
Where? Think I'm like you?
I know where I can go. I know.
Just look at those little nuns!
Where you going
with that banner?
Looking for snails?
Why'd you make her drink?
I made her drink?
Did the Madonna give you mercy?
Did she?
Cabiria! You wanna get us arrested?
Amleto, look at her!
What?
Bring her back!
Leave me alone!
I wanna listen. Go on playing!
Come here, kids!
Come enjoy yourselves!
Come dance with us!
Forget about your banner!
Why do you always butt in?
Get lost!
Cabiria!
You're in no condition for this!
- Leave me alone!
- You're blind drunk!
Who's drunk?
What do you know?
Is the show any good?
Hey! I asked you a question!
You want me to say it stinks?
As you can see, ladies and
gentlemen, my assistant's head...
has been completely
impaled by the daggers.
There's no doubt
that his head must be...
soaked in blood.
You'll be amazed to see, instead,
that his head has disappeared!
In the second part
of our show, we'll feature...
experiments with magnetism,
hypnotism and auto-suggestion.
Would anyone in the audience
care to volunteer? Prego, Signori!
I will!
Come right up.
Don't be afraid.
There's absolutely no danger.
We now need a representative
of the fair sex.
- How about you, Signorina?
- Who, me?
Yes, you! Good! Come up.
Be brave!
No, I don't want to.
Would you leave those young men
up there all alone?
You go, then!
Come on, chickie!
We need a laugh.
Wanna laugh?
Just look in the mirror!
Come on, Signorina,
don't make us beg.
Should I come and get you?
I'll come and get you.
Don't be afraid.
We're all good friends.
They're all tricks.
- Will you come?
- Sure! I'm coming.
Think I'm scared?
It's all fixed anyway.
There's no reason to be afraid.
You've showed how brave you are.
Come, you'll be fine.
Now, let's enjoy ourselves.
Oh, I'm so forgetful!
It's really unforgivable!
I completely forgot that
Signorina Elvira is still inside.
Oh, this heat!
You're hot too, aren't you?
How about a nice boat ride?
Does anybody here get seasick?
I was on the Isle of Elba
as a kid.
You barely got to Ostia.
Nobody here gets seasick?
That's very good.
Ah, here's our boat.
We named her Intrepid because
she always defies the waves.
Come on, boys.
Don't make me beg you.
Signorina, you stay here.
The boat is waiting. The sea is calm,
and the weather is fine.
I'm getting out of here!
Where are you going?
Damn, he's good!
He zapped him!
Look into my eyes!
Take the oars
and start rowing.
The sea is calm, transparent.
Feel the breeze.
Enjoy filling your lungs with air
saturated with salt and iodine.
Dolphins!
Boy, look at 'em jump!
One of you doesn't feel so good.
Things are looking bad, boys.
It's the open sea now.
The waves are swelling.
Hear the wind whistling.
It's a hurricane!
Help! Hold the rudder!
It's every man for himself!
Mamma mia bella!
I'm drowning!
- Scared, weren't you?
- You'd have been too!
You were plenty scared!
Where are you going?
- You mean me?
- Yes.
- Isn't it over?
- No.
It's not over.
You'd leave me here all alone?
What's he want now?
Signora or signorina?
- Did you have fun watching?
- Not really.
I'd like to talk with you
a moment. Come here.
- Are you from Rome?
- Yeah, I live in Rome.
In what part of town?
Colonna? Parioli? Prati?
In Prati.
Come on, be honest with me.
Where do you live?
In Borgata San Francesco.
What's so funny?
Don't pay any attention to them.
They're just joking.
So, you're not married,
but you'd like to be.
Why should I get married?
- I'm no dope.
- Who'd marry her!
All girls want to get married.
I know a nice young man
who'd be happy to marry you.
Me?
He's rich, handsome,
rides a horse and drives a Ferrari.
Let's see if we can arrange it.
What type of work
do you do?
She's a countess!
Listen, I'm fine the way I am.
I got everything.
And now I'm leaving.
I don't need anything!
That's a fact!
Even better.
So you're rich?
With a bank account, houses.
I own the house I live in. Okay?
And now I'll get going.
One moment.
Don't make me look foolish.
At least let me introduce you
to the young man, Oscar.
Who the heck is Oscar?
Please step forward.
How elegant you look.
Come here. I'd like to introduce
you to the Signorina.
She wanted to meet you too.
A pleasure.
The pleasure is all his,
believe me.
Now that you've met,
I'll leave you two alone.
This is a beautiful garden,
filled with flowers.
You can talk, confide in
each other. No one is listening.
Look, Signorina,
Oscar is offering his arm.
Come, Signorina, take his arm.
There's no harm in that.
But we just met.
You're strolling now.
The paths are full of flowers.
The birds are chirping.
Oscar dares not speak.
He's shy... sensitive.
Now he says, "Signorina..."
"I've been hoping to meet you
for such a long time."
"May I ask you a question?"
"You're not spoken for, are you?"
"There was never
a man in your life?"
"Ah, I thought so."
"I often see you standing by
your window, and at Sunday mass."
"Your eyes are always lowered.
You're always with your mother."
"That's good. Picking flowers
indicates a gentle soul."
"Signorina, may I hope
to see you again?"
"Ah, thank you.
What did you say your name was?"
"Thank you. I'll save this flower
like a precious object."
"Would you dance with me?"
Play, Maestro.
Oscar and Maria wish to dance.
The orchestra will play
a beautiful waltz.
"I'm wealthy, but I'm alone
and unhappy."
"What good are fancy cars,
long journeys and luxury hotels?"
"Smoke! Illusion!"
"What I really want is a home,
children, and a wife like you."
When I was eighteen, that's when
you should have known me!
I had long black hair.
This long.
"For me, you'll always be eighteen."
Then it's true?
You really love me?
Is it really true?
You're not trying to fool me?
Do you really love me?
There, there. It's all right.
What happened?
What did you make me do?
Still here?
I have to close up.
I'm going! I'm going!
Listen, are those creeps
still out there?
Everybody's gone.
There's nobody left.
Now get going.
I gotta close up.
I'll show them a thing or two!
Pardon me, Signorina.
I'm Donofrio, accountant.
Forgive my boldness.
I don't normally
stop young ladies in the street.
I was inside
among the audience.
Oh! You were there, watching!
Great show!
I bet you like that stuff!
If I ever see that slimeball again...
Signorina! Please,
don't misunderstand me.
I agree with you!
In fact, I sympathize with you.
I came to tell you
how moved I was.
We can all pretend to be
cynical and scheming.
But when we're faced with
purity and innocence...
the cynical mask
drops off...
and all that is best in us
awakens.
I wanted to thank you.
You did me good.
It's gotten chilly, hasn't it?
Excuse me.
It's the nighttime humidity.
May I buy you something?
I really don't know you.
Those damn creeps
are still there!
Excuse my persistence, but
these experiments with magnetism...
are extremely dangerous.
They can cause imbalances
and other disturbances.
That's why I felt so strange!
Cold, hot, sweaty.
Like I had a fever.
How about that!
I would suggest a Fernet.
It'll do you good.
Come, we'll sit down.
Just a moment.
Please sit down.
Two Fernet, please.
I swear, I've rarely suffered
as I did tonight.
When that charlatan spoke words
of love to you in Oscar's name...
and you answered with such
modesty and trepidation...
it made me sick.
Something hurt me in here.
I was ill. Really ill.
Hurry up. I'm closing.
Don't be upset.
Some things cannot be touched
by human vulgarity.
Even amidst a crowd
that laughs idiotically...
there's always someone
who understands, who knows.
Someone who appreciates.
But what did I do?
You acted out a very tender
and delicate love scene.
I'm still deeply touched.
I can't even express it.
Yes. What struck me most...
is that deep inside,
you're as pure as you were at 18.
When you went to Mass
with your mother...
and had long black hair,
falling down to here.
I really said that?
Closing time.
How much?
150 lire.
- Thank you.
- Hey, you, go sleep at home!
Listen, Signorina.
What happened tonight is
extremely important to me.
Just imagine, if you will...
I'm not from around here.
I just came here by chance.
I enjoy strolling in the city
in sections that I don't know.
I went into that music hall
without knowing why.
There's no explanation for what
happened. As if guided by fate.
Yes, that's the word: fate!
But who are you?
You sound like you're from Parioli.
What do you mean?
You talk like they do in Parioli.
A refined type.
I told you my name is Donofrio.
I'm a government employee.
What do you want from me?
You might understand me better
after I tell you my first name.
It's Oscar. My name is Oscar.
- Your name's Oscar?
- Yes.
So what? Your being Oscar
could be a coincidence, no?
Sure. But isn't it strange that
the hypnotist chose the name Oscar?
Signorina, I really must see you
again. You're waiting for the bus?
Yeah. I'm dead tired.
I gotta get to bed.
Do we say good-bye now,
never to meet again?
Impossible.
I've got to see you again!
The city is vast and we still have
so much to say to each other.
When and where
can we meet again? Please!
I don't know. I'm busy. I work.
I'm a salesgirl. Anyway,
what'll we say to each other?
- What?
- What would we say?
There's the bus. So long.
Arrivederci.
Please, don't say no.
I work too.
Maybe we can meet after work.
Like tomorrow evening. Signorina,
wait, how about tomorrow evening?
- In the evening I can't.
- Sunday afternoon, then?
Sunday?
Sunday, the Stazione Termini,
at 7:00.
I don't know. I feel so strange.
What're you doing?
Hurry. Let's go!
Here I am!
I was over there. Sorry I kept you
waiting. I was in the wrong spot.
Thank you for coming here.
You might have thought me
annoying, out of line.
It was all so strange...
as if I were dreaming.
I took the liberty,
if you'll accept.
Thanks. You didn't have to.
My pleasure.
Let's go that way.
He says he likes to talk to me.
And he talks and talks.
Boy, does he talk!
The type who reads a lot.
Well educated.
Last night we saw a first-run
movie at the Metropolitan.
- Hey! That's your third!
- They're so good!
I know they're good.
So we saw this first-run movie.
A costume picture.
Gladiators, with Christian martyrs.
He explained to me that
it wasn't a true story.
It's make-believe,
just for the movies, understand?
And then, he told me that...
he gets a kick out of
talking to me because...
because I understand him.
He's even good-looking.
Black eyes, brown skin.
A northern type.
Then we had pizza
at a trattoria.
He always pays.
Even for the flowers.
- Nothing? He wants nothing?
- Of course not.
Do me a favor, Cabi!
I'll be meeting him again
tomorrow.
What's he after?
How do I know?
And who cares?
As long as he pays!
Oh, sure!
The cops!
What you all need is jail!
Arrest them all!
I'm not running away.
If you want me, I'm here!
How are you?
How elegant you look today!
How are you feeling?
- Fine, and you?
- Thank you. Here. For you.
- Thank you. You shouldn't have.
- Don't mention it.
- It's too much.
- Take it.
Where shall we go?
Wherever you want.
It's a sunny day.
Let's go to the Aventino.
Your family's not from Rome?
No. I have no family left.
My mother and father died
when I was a child.
Loneliness is a heavy burden,
but I'd rather be alone...
than make compromises.
We lived in Puglia,
in a small village.
The name is unimportant.
You wouldn't know it.
I grew up in an old house.
I remember the oil lamps.
My father owned a small plot
of land. His name was Giovanni.
My mother's name was Elsa,
the poor soul.
I like the name Elsa.
It's pretty.
I had no brothers or sisters.
When my father died...
some ruthless relatives
robbed my mother...
of what little property
she had, leaving us very poor.
I went looking for work.
What are you doing, my child?
Good day, Father.
Some alms for Sant'Antonio?
Sorry, I've no money on me.
Never mind. Some other time.
What's important is
to always be in God's grace.
You are in God's grace,
aren't you, my child?
You're not in God's grace?
Why not?
Everyone should be
in God's grace.
Whoever lives in God's grace
is happy.
I'm in God's grace
and I'm happy.
I even went to the Madonna
to ask for Her grace.
Maybe you didn't know how to
ask, or maybe you didn't need it.
Are you married?
That's bad. Girls should get
married and make children.
Matrimony is a sacred thing.
In the grace of God, my child.
Ask Sant'Antonio for help.
If you need me,
I'm Brother Giovanni.
I'm at the San Francesco
Monastery, but I'm hard to find.
I'm always running around.
Hey, Blondie!
So long!
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow I'm busy.
Then the day after tomorrow.
Same time.
I'm busy then too.
How come?
I was gonna tell you...
I don't know if I'll keep seeing you.
But, why?
It's not that I'm uncomfortable
with you.
But what's the point?
What am I doing with you?
We're both wasting our time.
And doing what?
Anyway, what do you
want from me?
If you want...
I'll marry you.
I wanted to ask you before.
But I didn't have the courage.
I've wanted to...
ask you since
the first time I saw you.
What are you saying?
Marry me?
Marry someone you've seen ten times?
Someone you don't know?
That's not how it's done!
Thank God I'm more honest
than some others.
Excuse me,
but that's not how it's done!
What do you know about me?
About who I am?
Is this how it's done?
You shouldn't fool somebody
this way!
Why pick on me
of all people!
Really!
I've asked you no questions, and
I don't want to know anything.
Who cares?
Prejudices don't touch me.
Because what matters is...
is that I know your inner self.
We are... we are
two lonely creatures.
We have to stick together.
I need you.
Don't tell me that.
Don't say that, if it isn't true.
But it is!
What did you do?
What is it, you nut?
I'm getting married,
that's what!
He asked me to marry him! We're
buying a store in Grotta Ferrata!
He's almost signed the contract.
Without me knowing, he arranged
it all: a store, a house!
I'm selling everything!
I'll sell the house... the house...
We're getting married
in two weeks!
Wanda, I'm leaving!
Does he know that you...
Of course he knows!
I told him everything.
I didn't hide anything
from him.
But he's a saint. An angel!
He didn't want to know
anything. He didn't care.
He loves me! He loves me!
Wanda! He loves me!
Who's there?
May I see Brother Giovanni?
He's not back yet.
Why do you want to see him?
- To confess to him.
- Go to church for confession.
I want Father Giovanni
to hear my confession.
He can't hear your confession.
He's not an ordained priest.
I know, but...
I'll wait for Father Giovanni.
Fine. Then wait.
Why'd you pack this?
I'm not taking that!
Should I take the owl?
Nah, it brings bad luck.
But I'll take the seashell.
See if it fits.
If it fits, I'll take it.
I sold that.
Put it over there.
What a waste!
Leaving all this good stuff.
- Here are the dishes.
- I sold them. Leave 'em!
Them too?
Why not?
I got paid for them.
It would've cost more
to move everything.
He sold everything back home.
So I'm selling everything too.
We're starting over!
Everything new.
Me, I'd have taken all the stuff.
Are you forgetting anything?
What could I forget?
- Did you take the money?
- Of course! I'm no idiot!
See? You forgot your fur.
Fur? What fur?
- No! I don't want that.
- How about giving it to my aunt?
Sure, but hurry!
They're waiting to move in!
Damn it! Those lowlifes.
Close the suitcase, will you?
Tight.
Oh, la mamma!
Take one more look,
and then I'm getting married.
What?
I'm getting married too.
What did I say? Nothing.
How do I look?
Looks good on you.
It cost me 1,200 lire.
You got robbed.
You paid too much.
Ah, my pocketbook.
Good-bye, D'Artagnan.
Let's get going.
Time to leave.
See them? I can't stand
those starving bastards.
Let's go.
Here are the house keys.
I'm leaving. Arrivederci.
If you need anything, just tell
my friend, Signorina Wanda.
She'll write to me.
Arrivederci.
Have a good trip. Good luck!
Thank you. Likewise.
Never mind. I don't wanna
say good-bye to anybody.
It's better that way.
I'm so happy now,
and then all these people...
they'll ask questions.
Ah! Luciana!
I'm leaving.
I'm getting married!
- Send us some wedding candy!
- I will!
Say good-bye to Nando and
his uncle, and to everyone.
Nice, eh?
They're pretty.
You're getting married...
and I never met
this fiance of yours.
I couldn't bring him
where everybody knows me.
Here's the bus.
It's here.
Ciao, Wa'.
Why are you crying?
Who's crying?
Aren't you crying?
I'll write the minute I get there
with my address.
And you'll get married too.
Let's go.
Hurry, the suitcase.
I'll send my address right away.
Stay out of trouble. You'll...
You'll get a miracle, like me.
- Yeah, sure.
- It'll happen.
- What are you doing?
- I want to pay.
- But there's no reason.
- Please! You've always paid.
Anyway, what's mine is yours now.
It's all the same, isn't it?
Waiter!
It's getting late.
You'll see how beautiful
the sunsets are up here.
You want to get me drunk?
It's such a light wine.
The money.
Put it away.
It's my dowry.
350,000 for the house.
That's all those crooks would pay.
They knew I was in a hurry,
so they took advantage.
Then I got all my money
from the bank.
400,000.
See? I made them give me
all new bills.
Because you never asked
if I had money.
You, you're an angel,
a saint!
If you knew what I went through
to end up with this money.
I told you, I don't want to know.
Please!
Let's get away from here.
The beatings I took.
You see, some guys are
just after a girl's money.
You wouldn't believe it.
Everything for love.
But not that way.
But what about my old age?
Who worries about my old age?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Waiter, keep the change.
Let's go.
I didn't want to go on
like that forever.
I'd have quit if I could,
even tomorrow.
I'd have gone away.
To live that way forever?
I already owned the house.
Know what me
and Wanda planned?
We were gonna rent a newsstand.
Understand?
Where are we going?
It's so nice here.
Let's take a little walk. Okay?
I don't even remember
how I started.
I was a child,
that's all I remember.
And the suitcases?
We'll take them later.
You shoulda seen me at 15...
with my long black hair...
down to here.
Who understood anything?
My mother just wanted the money.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
We're just strolling.
What's the name of that song?
Won't you kiss me?
Come.
I know a shortcut.
Oscar! Where are you?
What a bad boy you are!
Look at these flowers.
Like 'em?
They stink, but still.
I never saw flowers
like these before.
Let's go.
I'm coming.
Smell them.
What kind of flowers are they?
What's wrong? Are you sad?
Me? No. Why?
You stopped singing.
Wait a minute.
Why don't we carve
our initials on the trees?
Let's go. The sunset
is beautiful in the woods.
The sunset, eh?
Where do you wanna go?
What a strange light.
Beautiful, isn't it?
I guess there is some justice
in the world.
You suffer,
you go through hell...
but then happiness
comes along for everyone.
You've been my angel.
Your hand is freezing.
Are you cold?
Having regrets?
Beautiful, eh?
Look how deep it is!
I'd love a boat ride
right now.
Are there any boats
down there now?
- Can you swim?
- Not me!
I almost drowned once.
But they saved me.
Just imagine!
I was pushed in!
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
You don't want to kill me,
do you?
Answer me!
You want to kill me?
You want to kill me!
Don't just stand there.
Say something!
Speak! Don't be like that!
Speak!
Tell me.
For... the money?
For the money.
Kill me! Kill me!
Throw me off the cliff!
I don't wanna live anymore!
Kill me! Throw me off the cliff!
Go ahead!
Shut up, stupid!
I don't want to hurt you.
Can't you see that?
I don't wanna live anymore!
Kill me! Kill me!
Maurizio, hurry up!
We're leaving!
We're gonna lose our way
going home!