Go over there.
It's beautiful!
Come on!
Giorgio!
Help! Help!
Help! Somebody's drowning!
Where's Romolo?
He went to City Hall.
To hell with City Hall!
It's a woman.
There she is!
Tino's not here either?
Is she trying to drown herself?
There she is.
Go in after her.
Jump! If she gets to the sewer
she won't come up again.
A woman's drowning!
You guys head her off.
I'll go in after her.
Pascello, run!
Come over here!
What are you doing? Not like that!
Turn her upside down!
Stefano, hurry up!
Where'd you fish her out?
Careful.
Hold her under the stomach.
She was drowning!
She probably slipped.
Mario saw her.
She musta slipped
and fell in.
- Did she jump off the bridge?
- No.
- Did she go under?
- Three times.
- At least seven times!
- Ten times!
She must have swallowed a lot.
We'll need some help. Stefano!
What happened?
- Faster with the arms!
- She lost a shoe.
I think she's dead.
Get the water out,
before it's too late.
Look how it's rushing out.
Move it, kids!
We saved her!
Beat it!
Let's get Pompeo.
He never seen anyone drown before.
Look.
I don't wanna look.
I'm afraid.
Looks dead to me.
Dead bodies don't
throw up water.
She opened her eyes!
Put her down.
We'll give her
artificial respiration.
She's bleeding.
It's just a scratch.
What she needs is brandy.
Brandy nothing!
What she needs is milk.
Quiet! She's coming to. You, with
the motorbike, go get some milk.
I'm outta gas.
Take it easy now.
You're all right.
You can thank the Holy Father.
You're fine.
Where's Giorgio?
What Giorgio?
Where are you going?
Who's she looking for?
- Wasn't she alone?
- Yes.
Who does he think he is?
Take it easy. Come here.
I'm going home.
Where are my shoes?
Here. There's only one.
She's got seven souls, like a cat.
See? She can hardly stand up.
Poor thing. She's in bad shape.
You were almost dead.
Leave me alone!
Let go of me!
Hey! We're the ones who saved you!
You saved me.
Now I wanna go home, okay?
Okay, suit yourself.
Go home. Good-bye.
Hi, Cabiria.
You know her?
Sure. She's Cabiria.
Where's she live?
On Via Cecilia.
She lives the life.
Giorgio! Open up! It's me!
It's me! Cabiria!
Wanda!
Wanda! Have you seen Giorgio?
What happened to you?
Mind your own business.
Did you see Giorgio?
- Which Giorgio?
- My Giorgio.
What happened to you?
What do you want from me?
What do you want?
I don't want nothing.
Mind your own fat ass!
Go inside and dry yourself off.
I don't have the keys.
Where'd you put them?
In my purse.
Where's your purse?
Giorgio's got it.
We took a walk by the river and...
I fell in.
He got scared and ran away.
Cabiria! Open up!
Come on, open up.
I gotta sleep!
Tell me something.
How much did you have
in your purse? Answer me.
If you see Giorgio, I'm right here.
What are you doing?
You're right to stay home.
Go to bed and
get some sleep.
I'll see you later
when I get back.
Why didn't you take your aspirin?
Take it, it'll do you good.
You still here?
Aren't you tired of yakkin'?
Can't you see I had enough?
Get lost!
Who told you
we were friends?
Get lost, will you?
And don't come borrowing
my thermometer anymore!
Who's asking you for anything?
What a nut!
You're a sweetheart!
Someone would throw you in the
river for 40,000 lire?
Drown you for 40,000 lire?
Nowadays they'll do it for 5,000.
Someone who loves you?
What love?
You met him a month ago.
You don't know his name
or where he lives.
Can't you understand?
He pushed you in!
He pushed you in the river!
And you were lucky,
because if it had been me...
I'd have held your head under
myself! You nut!
Tell the cops!
I'm no stool pigeon!
Take my advice!
Report him!
But why? Why'd he do it?
I gave him everything.
I gave him everything he wanted.
He didn't have to do it.
I'm such a moron.
What if I died?
That's it! The party's over!
We're through! Finished!
Silk shirts! I'll give you silk shirts!
Find another jerk like me!
Look what I bought him!
A checked suit!
Camel-hair coat!
Never again! Never!
And who's gonna feed you now?
St. Peter?
Eternal love!
You dirty vitellone!
Go back to selling balloons!
I'll burn it all!
Chicken soup, veal chops.
You should drop dead!
This is the last time!
You'll never see me here again.
This is my last evening.
I shouldn't even be seen with you!
Look how classy I am.
You look like Moby Dick to me.
How dare you!
Know where you belong?
In the nuthouse!
Use your eyes!
Take a good look at me!
Look at me. A grande dame.
She gets worse all the time.
They oughta put her away.
That's how you'll end up!
And that's the heater.
- This car's got everything.
- Even Coca-Cola.
- Gimme a ride?
- This ain't no tank!
- Get out!
- I'm not getting out.
Come on, move!
- Why should I?
- I'm taking Wanda for a ride.
You don't know how to drive.
It's my car. I can do what I want
with it. Get out.
I'll visit you in the hospital.
This I gotta see.
Why not the bigger model?
Another one! What do you know about
cars? You're always in the bushes!
You're always on two wheels!
Here comes the psycho again.
- Bye, handsome.
- Bye, sweetie.
Remember to come see
your princess.
Cute! Real fancy!
Me, I'd have picked a grey one.
It's a fancier color.
But this one's cute.
You're gonna kill the battery!
Wanda, get out.
I don't wanna fight tonight.
Neither do I, you fanatic.
Still, a Fiat is a Fiat.
With a car, life's a lot different.
You sit up there, high up...
and you signal right, left,
vroom-vroom.
People think you're well off,
a secretary, a daddy's girl.
The men all chase you.
It feels great!
- Listen to her!
- What?
I know how she got that car!
That cokehead!
Wait!
Stay right here!
- Let me get out!
- Stay!
You're dancing, Cabiria?
You're in luck!
I'm the best dancer in Rome.
Come on!
Now she found another
deadbeat to say "I love you."
One who'll send her off begging.
Get off the street, dear,
or I'll have you arrested.
Here I am, gentlemen!
Here I am!
Just as well.
Who needs you!
Where you going with
the car? To the old-age home?
Maybe if you were 20 years younger!
Filthy flea bag!
You're just jealous!
Hear that, Cabiria?
She can't get away with that!
Look how you'll end up,
you lousy whore!
"Please, be kind.
Have a heart!"
"Please, for my Giorgio's sake!"
Do it! Poke her eyes out!
Wanda, here we go again.
Forza, Cabiria!
Never mind her!
Hit her low, in the belly!
Don't stop them!
It's too much fun!
Stop it before the cops come!
I'll kill her!
Let go of me!
Get her in the car.
Get her away!
- Leave me alone!
- Get inside!
I'll punch you a new face!
It's not over yet!
She ruined my face!
Forget about her.
You're scared of me, right?
You lousy loser!
Have a smoke.
Where you wanna go?
To Via Veneto.
Via Veneto?
Think you're the Empress Poppea?
Listen, Cabiria, you and me oughta
have a talk one of these days.
You're not doing it right.
Who's watching over you?
Look at Marisa and me.
She's safe wherever she goes.
Nobody in Rome would harm
a hair on her head.
You know why?
Let me out.
What do you expect
to do here?
Girls fight for spots on
Via Veneto and Villa Borghese.
Cabiria, why not find yourself
a serious man? Respectable, like me.
I don't need one.
- I say you do.
- I say I don't!
Why should /slave
for filthy pigs like you?
Let's drop it.
Yeah, drop it.
Better let me out.
Yeah, it's better.
So long!
Moron! Degenerate! Go take a walk
on the Passeggiata Archeologica!
Can't I look?
Know how gorgeous you are?
Get going.
Oh, yeah? We'll I'm staying
right here! See?
Sorry.
Are you blind?
Jessie!
Jessie! How can this happen?
Alberto Lazzari!
Jessie, I don't want to get upset.
Jessie, cut it out!
Let go!
Don't make me lose my temper.
Come back inside.
Give me the keys.
- Go inside. Don't be stupid.
- Don't you touch me, you pig!
Move over. Let me in.
Where are you going? Where?
- Do I get the keys or not?
- No!
- You're not getting out!
- You're hurting me. Let go!
Jessie, dear, listen.
Listen one last time.
- There's no more to say.
- I'm tired. You're exhausting!
- Let go! You're ruining my fur.
- I bought it!
You louse!
- Wait a second.
- What for?
You can go.
Lousy second-rate ham!
Listen, Jessie. If you don't
come back, it's over!
Fine! It's over!
Finished!
At last! So much the better.
Thanks, thanks, Jessie.
What do you want?
Go away!
Hey, you!
I'm talking to you!
Get in.
Who, me?
Yes, you. Hurry up. Get in.
Fast!
Close it.
Get out.
But why?
Come on, get out.
What's it gonna be, Mr. Mustache?
What's going on here?
Get out, get in, get in, get out!
Make up your mind!
Come on. Let's have some fun.
- He said to go in.
- So go in.
How are you, sir? How about a table?
Tonight's show is exceptional.
Your umbrella, Signora?
Right this way, Signora.
Who's that?
May I help you?
Sit over here. Come on.
Please.
Sit over there.
Alberto!
Monica.
What are you up to, Alberto?
Are you shooting?
- Yes.
- No need to introduce him!
Pleased to meet you.
Yesterday the Americans
gave me a screen test.
It turned out fantastic.
I have a 16-millimeter print at home
if you want to see it.
Ladies and gentlemen, that was part
one of our show. Before you dance...
I'd like to salute and applaud
an illustrious guest who is...
honoring us with his presence.
Must I applaud too, Alberto?
Okay, boys! Mambo number 26!
Do me a favor,
come to our table.
A bunch of my friends
would love to meet you.
- Come on, Alberto.
- I can't.
I'm with the lady.
Let's dance.
Mambo. The world turns
around the mambo.
What a mambo.
Oh, boy! What a mambo!
If you wanna be with your friends,
don't mind me.
What?
Don't let me keep you
from your friends.
That's enough. Let's go.
Good night, Commendatore.
Get in. Hurry up!
- Did you eat?
- No. Well, a little bit around 8:00.
- Let's get some supper.
- What?
Let's have supper.
Good. Where are we going?
My house.
Wait! Wait a second!
Hey, Fancy Pants!
I'm talking to you!
Look at me!
Look who I'm with!
Up yours!
Know who this is?
- Did anyone call?
- Nobody, Commendatore.
- What do you mean nobody?
- Nobody called.
- Were you awake or sleeping?
- Nobody called. I was here.
All right.
Supper for two in my room.
If Miss Jessie calls, I'm asleep.
If she insists, I'm asleep.
If she still insists, I'm still asleep!
We'll eat upstairs.
What's your name?
What?
Come on, move.
What? Another dog?
Look at these!
You got fish too?
Yes.
Now, where did I put it?
- Leave it for the maid.
- But it'll get wrinkled.
Idiot! What made me do it?
Did you ever see an idiot?
Well, you're looking at one.
Just leave it!
Come.
What was your name again?
Where are you from?
What?
- Where do you come from?
- From Rome. Piazza Risorgimento.
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
You like it?
Kind of.
It's not really my thing.
It's not my taste, but, yes.
Beethoven's Fifth.
I love it.
Come in.
Leave it there.
I'll take care of it. Go.
And close the door.
Let's see what he brought us.
Caviar, lobster.
Help yourself. Eat.
I'm not in the mood.
Help yourself.
I don't know if you like it.
1949...
Take that off.
It's hot in here.
Guess I tore it.
Where do you live?
Past the gas station.
- Where?
- On the road to Ostia.
- You come to Via Veneto?
- Via Veneto? Me?
I work the Passeggiata Archeologica.
Much more convenient.
Why?
I'm on the Cilia.
Subway takes me right there.
There's another girl,
my friend Wanda.
She lives there too.
But I don't bother with the others.
The others sleep under the arches
in Caracalla.
Mind you, I have my own house...
with water, electricity, bottled gas,
every convenience. I got everything.
Even a thermometer.
See this one here?
She never, ever
slept under an arch.
Well, maybe once.
Or twice.
Of course, my house is...
nothing like this.
But it's enough for me.
I like it.
Eat. Eat something.
What's wrong?
Damn it! I know who you are!
I know!
Can I say it?
Can I?
Alberto Lazzari! I knew you
right away! I saw all your movies.
Very nice!
Which is your favorite?
Well, the last one.
You had a costume with all that
stuff, then Vittorio Scraman came...
pushed the door open,
"Fermi tutti!"
Then it was his daughter.
That wasn't me.
What do you mean?
You're as good-looking
as your house.
Bring the glasses here.
- Champagne.
- Sit down.
What's wrong now?
Who's gonna believe this
when I tell 'em?
They already think I'm full of it.
I might not believe it myself
tomorrow.
You have to do me a favor.
Give me a picture...
and write, "Cabiria was here
at my house-- Alberto Lazzari."
"Cabiria Ceccarelli was at my
house."
Write it just like that.
Now let's eat.
And you eat too.
An olive.
Should I open it?
Chicken! Some chicken breast
to chase away the blues.
Here's your plate.
If you want to play more
of that music, I'd like it too.
And what's this?
I saw it in a movie once.
- Commendatore.
- Yes, Davide.
- It's Signorina Jessie.
- I said, tell her I'm sleeping.
- She's here.
- What?
- She's downstairs.
- Just don't let her in.
She's already in.
She's coming up.
Idiot!
Alberto, open up.
- Who is it?
- Don't be stupid! Open up!
So? Open up.
It's very important.
One moment.
- The picture!
- Oh, yes. Hurry up!
Alberto, will you open up?
Go in the bathroom a minute.
Yes. I'll get rid of her. Hurry!
I'm not leaving.
I'll stay here all night!
- Quiet, don't move.
- Open up.
Alberto, please open the door.
Open up, you bastard!
What do you want?
What's on your mind?
I'm tired.
I have to be up early tomorrow.
I'm working. You know that, right?
I'm thirsty. Give me a drink.
- What?
- I'm thirsty!
Now what?
I can't go on this way!
Well, neither can I!
Your jealousy
is morbid, unbearable.
I'm tired of it.
I can't take it any more.
Let's call it quits while we're
still friends, okay?
No. That's too easy!
I'm not going anywhere!
Jessie, don't do this.
Get some sleep.
You're tired and
I'm falling apart.
We'll call each other tomorrow.
- I know you've stopped loving me.
- Who told you that?
You've stopped loving me.
- Admit it.
- I'd never say such a thing.
Admit it, and I'll never
bother you again.
But I'd be lying.
Even if we saw each other
occasionally...
every two or three days,
I'd be happy.
Why so seldom?
We could be together much more.
- Every day?
- Yes, every day.
But stop being so jealous. Is it my
fault that women always look at me?
But you're ugly!
How do I get outta here?
Hey, Cabiria. Alberto Lazzari's
been lookin' for you!
I'm not even talking to you!
- Don't listen to her.
- Who's listening?
Hey, Cabiria, there's Limpy.
There's a winner.
Hey, you old lecher!
Homesick for jail?
Come on, Cabiria,
let's have a good laugh.
Why'd you bring him along?
Guess a weed never dies.
The Madonna might
have mercy on my uncle.
What mercy?
The pilgrims of the Madonna del
Divino Amore just went by.
I don't believe that stuff.
- Don't you believe in miracles?
- Not me.
Should we go there on Sunday?
We'll all have
something to ask for.
You goin', Cabiria?
Me? I don't know. I'll think about it.
Besides...
what would I ask for?
I've got everything.
I'll even be done
with the mortgage soon.
But I might go anyway.
I haven't said no.
We'll see.
Think the Madonna would
waste a miracle on him?
Funny, huh? The Madonna knows
how you made your dough.
Selling coke
and pimping women.
I'm going to see the Madonna...
and I know exactly
what I'll ask for.
Don't make fun of stuff like that.
You really want to go?
What'll you ask for?
I'm talking to you.
Hey, you! Shorty!
Wanna lift?
A shortcut.
He calls this a shortcut.
I've been walking an hour.
Who knows where I am?
You live in the caves too?
I've never seen you before.
I've got my own house.
Gorgiano! Gorgiano!
It's me. Come up.
How are you doing?
Not so bad, thank you, sir.
And where's Pietro?
Sleeping?
They took him to the hospital
two days ago.
Said he was in bad shape.
- And, you, what do you need?
- Whatever you want, thanks, sir.
Here's a blanket. Is that all right?
What hospital did they take Pietro to?
To the Fratebene fratelli.
All right, I'll visit him
if I have time.
Hey, Dark Hair.
Who is that guy?
But who is he?
With some charity?
Hey, I'm talkin' to you.
Can I help you?
Going back to Rome later?
Can you give me a lift?
Yes, later.
Elsa!
Ah, caro!
I was expecting you Saturday,
but you came today!
I was just thinking yesterday,
"He comes every nine or ten days.
"He came Wednesday,
so he'll show up Saturday!"
Bomba! But I know this one!
Bomba, you live here?
I wish I had everything I used to.
A place in Rome, a place in Ostia.
Showered with gifts!
Money in the bank! Jewels! Gold!
I had five kilos of gold!
She's not lying, you know.
Now who'd believe it?
But this one in her day--
Here they don't even
make me comb my hair.
But if I wear a low-cut blouse...
and the white earrings, then... ha!
Come, come, Elsa. Take this.
Oh! Look at the sweets you brought!
And only for me!
None for the others!
Give it to me to hide.
The one with the chocolate!
Pignoli! Look at the pignoli!
Like rainfall!
Thank you, caro, thank you!
And when will you be back?
When?
God protect you from evil, my son.
Of course...
there's lots of starving people
in Rome, eh?
You drive around at night a lot?
Not as much as needed.
How about during the day?
No, in the daytime,
the poor wander about.
How would I find them?
Go figure.
Me, I'm out at night too,
and I've never met you.
But how'd you get the idea...
the idea of doing this job?
I don't even know myself.
Like that. Little by little.
We're here. There's your tram.
Do you live far from here?
About 19 kilometers,
on the way to Ostia.
What's your name?
Maria Ceccarelli.
Are you alone?
My father and mother
died when I was little.
I came to Rome later.
Now go and get some sleep.
So I--
Arrivederci.
Go ahead, tell me.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Don Vincenzo,
the group from Rieti is here.
Get your prickly pears!
Fresh prickly pears!
Gimme a hand, Maurizio.
Wanda, get a load of this crowd!
There's the candle guy.
Come on, Uncle.
How much for the candles?
Take your pick.
I got some for 50, 100, 150.
The biggest you got.
We'll take two each.
Wanda, the candles! Over here!
Are these all right?
I just want one. I'll pay for it myself.
Maybe I'll pay you later.
No, I'll pay for them all.
- What'll I do with it now?
- Stupid!
How much altogether?