CAPTAIN PANTOJA AND
THE SPECIAL SERVICE...
You're sure this is our man?
Intelligence investigated his life...
private and professional.
Entered the Academy...
first place.
Chose administration.
He was...
class valedictorian.
He hoisted the flag...
in every yearly closing ceremony.
And even to date...
no cadet has matched his average.
He prefers sports and studying...
but also socializes.
Here he is with Alfonsina Reaño...
they married three years later.
She's a decent girl...
down to earth, good housewife.
This looks nice!
I wonder where they'll send us.
Don't you?
Anywhere they say is good for me.
Right.
You married the army before me.
Where would you like them
to send us?
Chiclayo, again. Maybe Tacna.
What about the mountains
or the jungle?
I hate the mountains.
The jungle... Maybe Iquitos.
As long as it's a city...
and not some camp.
Think of our little cadet.
Now we can send for him, right?
Now?
Maybe.
Or tonight.
Who cares if it's not Saturday?
I'm late, Pochita.
It's half an hour to the ministry...
disregarding traffic.
All right. Let's eat breakfast,
Captain, sir.
I have an appointment
with the General.
Yes, Captain. He's waiting for you.
Congratulations,
on your brilliant promotion.
Thanks, sir.
I heard of your promotion.
First place by unanimous decision!
Congratulations.
Thank you, General, sir.
Sit down.
Cigarette?
No, thanks.
You see?
He doesn't smoke or drink.
No bad habits.
He can represent our army
in paradise...
next to Saint Martin and Saint Rose.
I must have some habits
you don't know about.
We know everything about you.
You wouldn't believe how much.
Well...
let's cut to the chase.
The mission
we are about to give you...
is of the utmost secrecy.
Here's the thing, Pantoja:
Recently,
our troops in the jungle have been...
riled up.
At first, we thought...
there were only isolated occurrences...
maybe caused by the climate
or their diet.
But things...
have gotten worse.
General Scavino
and especially Father Beltran...
whose daily memos
I'm up to here with...
have taken some action.
But no type of punishment...
has solved the problem.
So, more drastic measures
are in order.
That's where you come in.
I don't understand, General, sir...
This is a very important mission.
General Scavino will brief you
upon your arrival.
You will leave on Monday.
I hope you like the jungle.
From now on,
you have all my support...
on this difficult task.
I wish you luck.
The army's prestige...
is in your hands.
And as paladin of the Amazon...
I feel compelled to raise my voice...
to defend the women of our land!
I am not unpatriotic.
But my love for the army...
can't make me hide the truth.
The raping wave that is
sweeping our region...
tarnishing the honor
of our beautiful women...
has a guilty party!
The rapists are the soldiers
of our army!
Yes, ladies and gentlemen...
our very own soldiers.
It's hard to admit it...
but I have irrefutable evidence!
What is happening to our army?
What do...
the authorities have to say about it?
Captain Pantaleon Pantoja
is entrusted with...
the mission of implementing...
a "Visitors' Service for Garrisons,
Border Posts...
and Related Quarters"
to fulfill the needs of...
Excuse me, sir.
What do you mean by "visitors"?
Do you mean?
Whores!
Yes, whores!
General Collazos
and his strategists from Lima...
have concocted the idea
of taking women...
from camp to camp,
so the troops may fornicate.
And you, a Peruvian army Captain...
will be acting as pimp...
or whatever sex merchants
are called.
Excuse me, sir.
I don't consider myself fit
for this mission.
Please reconsider...
It's too late.
It's an order to be obeyed.
I will do my best.
I don't want you in these headquarters
or in any other.
You are excused from attending
official ceremonies, parades, etc.
And I forbid you to dress in uniform.
Even at my workplace?
Your work will be done far away
from headquarters.
What kind of support will I have
for my mission?
An officer has been appointed.
Lieutenant Bacacorzo...
will serve as liaison between you
and your superiors.
Any other questions, Captain?
We won't live in the villa
with the other officers.
- Why?
- I'm sorry.
We will be civilians.
I will pose as a merchant
on business.
I don't understand your job.
Why do we have to hide?
I'm talking to you.
I'm listening Pantaleon Pantoja,
tell me what this is about.
There would never be lies between us,
remember?
Why won't you tell me?
I'll be working in the...
Intelligence Service.
Intelligence Service?
Now I understand the mystery!
What must you find out?
I can't tell you.
Orders.
Come on.
Who do you have to spy?
Is it war with Ecuador?
Does it have to do
with the Rio Protocol?
You can't imagine what keeping
my mission from my wife is like.
I've never lied to her, Lieutenant.
Ever.
Many would want to be in your shoes,
Captain.
Not me.
I'm in a jam.
How can I organize this service?
I've had no contact with prostitutes!
Where do I start?
At the beginning.
Go to a brothel and look.
I recommend Madam Leonor's...
better known as Chuchupe.
She's closing, and her girls
will be out of a job.
They're the best around.
I would come with you...
but you know
Scavino's orders.
- Hello, cutie.
- Hello.
- Do you dance?
- Sorry.
I don't dance.
You like cutting to the chase, huh?
Me too.
But you have to buy a ticket first.
You don't understand.
I'm not here to... satisfy my needs.
I'm here to talk with Mrs. Leonor.
Could you tell her, please?
I'd be glad to.
We can still do it.
Listen.
Look for me when you are through.
I just love
clean-cut boys like you.
Good evening.
My name is Pantaleon Pantoja.
Welcome to Chuchupe's.
Here, we're nice to everyone...
except soldiers
who want to fuck for free.
What can I do for you?
I would like to talk business.
In private.
Are you telling me to go?
A drink?
A beer and two glasses.
On the house.
Or do you prefer
something stronger?
No. I don't drink.
I am a businessman,
and I have come to Iquitos to...
to invest.
I heard you are closing down...
and I thought I could...
Open a brothel?
Here's some advice.
You seem like a nice man,
and I like you.
This is a rotten business.
If you want money,
open a restaurant.
That's strange.
I was told that because of the heat...
demand was high.
And it is.
But, with the soldiers
that won't pay...
the bribes, and the rent...
I'm losing money.
So I'm closing and keeping
my meager savings...
for my golden years.
I feel sorry for my girls...
I am fond of them.
They're good, hardworking girls.
Maybe we can reach an agreement...
that will benefit us both.
Your knowledge is very valuable
for my plans.
If you do close down...
I'd be interested in hiring you...
and some of your girls.
I'm listening.
Taking hookers to the military posts!
It would be great business!
But they would never let us in,
Mister Pantoja.
I already have permission.
And don't call them hookers
or whores.
The correct term is "visitors."
You have permission?
Don't tell me you are a soldier.
Of course not.
I want you to think it over.
I'll be back in a few days
with a work plan...
I accept now! This is heaven sent.
"Colombiana" wants to speak to you.
Colombiana?
- What does she want?
- Should she wait?
No. I'll see her now.
If she wants a job, there's none.
I'll be right back.
Go ahead.
- Is she really Colombian?
- Nobody knows.
She says she is.
She's been working abroad...
and probably got into trouble.
Very attractive.
The best this land has to offer.
But I don't recommend her.
She's rotten goods.
Two men have already
killed themselves over her.
It's about time!
It's past eleven.
I have a splitting headache.
It figures. You know what?
I'm glad you feel sick.
You came tumbling in at sunrise.
Don't you remember?
Lower your voice, please.
I've never felt so bad.
Come pet me.
You're going to tell me
what this is about.
Where were you?
It's this damn job.
You know I hate these things.
You've been with women,
haven't you?
I'm sure you have been with women.
Never, Pochita.
Don't cry. You make me feel
like a criminal.
You know I don't have eyes
for another.
Then tell me where you were.
The undersigned,
Captain Pantaleon Pantoja...
a Visitors' Service for Garrisons...
Border Posts
and Related Quarters...
respectfully informs:
That he has taken possession
of the site located on the Itaya River...
as Command Quarters...
and Logistical Center.
That he has under his command
the two soldiers...
named Sinforoso Caiguas
and Palomino Rioalto...
whom the superiority
has adequately chosen...
due to their fine conduct records
and their indifference...
toward the opposite sex.
That, during the first week,
the undersigned...
employed most of his time
in cleaning.
That a week might seem
an excessive time...
to carry out this task...
but the facility's condition...
can only be described...
as disgusting.
Since the army had abandoned
this facility...
it had been used illegally.
The undersigned provided
Caiguas and Rioalto...
the necessary equipment...
to burn the debris, clean...
and disinfect the facility.
The walls have been repaired...
the grounds have been cleaned...
and the small dock
has been repaired.
The undersigned
is proud to inform that...
using ten...
and twelve-hour shifts...
and disregarding his wife,
who has conditioned a house alone...
has turned the dump he received...
into an inhabitable, orderly...
and clean place...
as is expected of every army facility...
even if it is clandestine...
What do you think of my new outfit?
Horrible.
I prefer you in uniform.
You're going out again?
I'd rather stay here with you...
and make our little cadet...
We could do it right now.
Don't you want to?
I can't. I'm going to
the movies with Alicia.
I'm starting to get jealous of her.
What do you expect me to do?
It's your job's fault.
It's hard for me too.
We have to be patient.
Leave it. Don't get dressed.
I like you more every day.
I don't know you anymore.
And, with those clothes...
it's as if I was cheating on you.
The voice of Sinchi!
Good afternoon, dear listeners.
Continuing
with our moralizing campaign...
in defense of our women's
physical and moral integrity...
your servant, The Sinchi...
invites you to join our cause...
in demanding
a clear and forceful answer...
from the authorities...
to the abuse carried out...
by depraved members of our army.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen.
We demand
punishment for the rapists...
Good afternoon.
You are seven minutes late.
If you were in the service,
you'd be fined.
I'd pay happily to work...
with you in the service.
You'd work fourteen-hour days,
and on holidays.
And that's not enough.
The results of the quarter polls...
are alarming.
Look at that!
Now that's a babe!
You know the Colombiana?
You sure move quickly!
I saw her at Chuchupe's.
If she were in the service...
we'd be famous.
Maybe later on.
For now, Chuchupe
and Chupito are recruiting.
Well, here are the poll results.
They're alarming.
Potential number of users
of the Visitors' Service: 8,726.
Number of renderings...
"Renderings"?
Monthly service renderings,
desired: 12.
So, if the service
is to satisfy the demand...
it should administer
a monthly average...
of 104,712 renderings.
104,000?
That's a lot of hookers...
I mean... visitors.
Averaging 20 renderings a day...
for each high quality visitor...
working full-time, we would need...
2,271 prostitutes?
That man has gone mad!
He'll turn our whole army
into a brothel!
Calm down. Let me continue.
...2,271 visitors, which is surely
impossible at this time.
I suggest beginning with five...
who would administer
4,800 monthly renderings...
in six-day weeks, working full-time.
He requests permission to recruit
"Chuchupe"...
a woman with experience
in the matter...
who would act as chief of staff...
and would supervise
the feminine element.
This is an insult to the uniform!
That man should
be put in jail!
The undersigned requests authorization
to carry out a trial experiment...
and awaits the go ahead
to enlist...
the first five visitors,
who would be earning...
A salary extracted
from our institution's funds!
General Collazos
will never allow this!
ACCEPTED
You will arrive first...
in order to talk with the users...
and install sites for the renderings.
Sites? Renderings?
You have to get used to the terms.
Users are clients, sites are the beds...
renderings are screwings...
and visitors are the girls. Right?
- The candidates?
- Tomorrow morning.
I've called ten top-notch girls...
so you can choose five.
Chuchupe!
Chupito!
I heard you closed down.
A great loss for the city's nightlife.
What will you do now?
- A new business?
- Something like that.
German Laudano Rosales...
at your service.
I see you aren't a local.
The Capital?
Pantaleon Pantoja.
Welcome to this land of
friendship and beauty.
Have you been here long?
He has a popular radio show,
"The Voice of Sinchi."
My wife listens to it.
I hope she likes it.
What brings you here?
Are you "hunting"?
I'm happily married.
No, on business.
Well...
good luck in your...
"business."
It's been a pleasure.
See you around.
He asks too many questions.
He's a professional busybody.
Don't mind him.
In order to gather information...
the undersigned
investigated products...
with alleged aphrodisiac properties...
to personally verify...
over a four-day period,
in what way...
these products
could enhance the problem...
of the troops.
Some of these products...
brought on an increase...
of sexual behavior,
to the point where...
only self-fondling
and the virile act occupied him...
affecting concentration...
his nervous system...
and his working efficiency.
He requested intercourse with his wife...
an average of three times a day...
which logically made her uneasy...
as she was not accustomed to this.
Because of this, I recommend...
to my superiors that the intake
of these products...
be prohibited
at jungle posts and quarters.
I inform I have enlisted
the first visitors.
A difficult task since...
I was still under the influence...
of long acting aphrodisiacs.
Thank you. Call the next one.
What do you think?
It's harder than I thought.
You must like one over the rest.
- May I?
- Come in, girl.
Here I am, Mister Panta.
Good morning.
Name, please.
Pechuga.
Luisa Canepa,
not taken or involved.
Ok, miss.
Show me.
Accepted!
They're coming, Captain!
The undersigned,
Captain Pantaleon Pantoja...
respectfully informs:
That the expected vessel...
arrived at our logistic center
of the Itaya River.
It was piloted by petty officer
Carlos Rodriguez...
who was quickly told
of the mission's secrecy.
There are only six days until
we carry out the trial mission...
at the post of Horcones.
Mrs. Chuchupe, please.
Rules are rules.
I need not tell you...
that here lies
the future of the service.
The girls are ready, sir.
Bring them in, please.
Caiguas and Rioalto
have designed uniforms.
What do you think, sir?
With a zipper for quick removal.
What do you think?
Lalita's clothes could be tighter...
to show her titties.
It's as tight as can be.
Lalita is slim.
Not an ounce of fat.
You must fatten up.
The troops like meaty girls.
Double rations, starting today.
The uniforms. Do you like them?
Why is everything red and green?
The screwing, sorry...
the rendering cards too.
They're the service's colors:
Green...
for the beauty of the region.
Red for the ardent army men...
we help soothe.
I suggest we paint our nails green.
It's lovely!
Is the lingerie red and green too?
Want to see?
There's no need.
Well done.
Dismissed.
Mr. Rodriguez!
I won't tolerate that.
Control your urges...
or I will remove you
from the service.
- Is that clear?
- Crystal clear, sir.
Don't worry. I know Chuchupe.
I assure you everything is ready
for our arrival.
It'll be fine.
This is the hour of truth.
All right, ladies.
We're almost there.
We're ready
for "body to body combat."
- How do I look?
- You are all fine.
In Horcones...
some twenty brave soldiers
await you.
They endure many sacrifices
for our country.
Some of them
haven't seen a woman for months.
This is only a trial mission...
but if it's carried out
with patriotism and resolve...
the service will cover
the whole Amazon region...
bringing happiness to our soldiers.
Let's hear it...
for the Visitors' Service...
and for our glorious armed forces.
There it is! Get ready!
Show those men what you can do!
Let's do it!
Until they beg for mercy!
Silence!
Come, Sandra, hurry up.
Iris... Iris, hurry.
Five minutes before 1600...
the visitors occupied their sites.
Lalita and Pechuga at the depot...
others at the infirmary
and the mess hall.
Stay back!
I need not remind you...
that these ladies must know...
that our country's soldiers
know how to behave as men.
They're all yours, sir.
The instructions are:
First...
each user can stay up to
twenty minutes in a site.
This is the maximum time allowed.
Second...
the user is entitled to
one normal rendering...
so you will leave the site
as soon as it's over.
It is forbidden, and punishable
by definitive exclusion...
to request of the visitor such
aberrations as:
Manual or oral masturbation,
sodomy...
the "black kiss"...
and other extravagances.
Finally,
those awaiting their turn...
will do so in complete silence
and order...
and not disturb the fellow in action.
- Understood?
- Sir, yes, sir!
Give the order.
First line, forward!
4 minutes, 46.
Next.
6 minutes, 11.
Nobody has reached
the maximum time yet.
These variations
are only a symptom.
This post is isolated, so the users...
have contained virility.
Some for months.
That's why they're so quick.
A record! 2 minutes, 22.
How about that?
We'll have to include abstinence...
in our future estimates. Yes.
A resounding success!
And everything went along
with order and on time.
Pantoja was able to save
18% of the budget...
allotted for the trial.
Post commander, Lieutenant Santana...
congratulates the Visitors' Service...
and requests its regular functioning.
Enough, Lopez. It's very clear.
Write:
To General Roger Scavino.
We inform you...
that the Visitors' Service
for Garrisons, Border Posts...
and Related Quarters,
is now functioning.
Ten thousand a week?
But this is a delirious
exaggeration, Pantoja!
No, sir. It's a proven statistic.
Look at these charts.
It's a careful...
if not conservative, estimate.
10,000 renderings...
cover primary
psychobiological needs.
To fulfill virile plenitude...
53,200 renderings are needed.
Who the hell has told you...
that virile plenitude can only
be reached by fornicating?
The specialists...
Father.
Call me Commander!
Excuse me, Commander.
I brought some documents.
They're excerpts from the works of
Sigmund Freud, Austrian.
Of William Steckel...
whose nationality was not stated...
of the Reader's Digest...
and of Carlos Seguin, our compatriot.
If you...
prefer books, I have them
at the Logistic Center.
I have been informed...
you give out pornography
at the camps.
At Borja garrison,
your midget assistant...
gave out this filth:
"Two Nights of Pleasure"...
"Maria the Tarantula,"
"Julia and the Horse"...
"I'm Going in There,"
"Super Ass."
True.
My assistant suggested it.
The result was a faster erection.
Now it's regular practice.
So it wasn't just once!
The service is giving out
pornography!
We lend it,
we can't afford to give it.
The result is positive.
A soldier that reads in line...
finishes three minutes earlier.
This allows us to reach...
500 weekly renderings
with five visitors.
Now I've heard everything!
I wish to leave, General.
I understand, Father.
Well-assorted for
you to pick, sir.
I only wanted ten!
I can't examine all day.
The word spread, and women...
sprang out of every
neighborhood.
It's not my fault.
Let's pick the five we need.
Send them in, one by one,
with their cards.
The Colombiana first.
Ok, hurry up!
Let's make a line.
Have you filled in your cards?
Good morning.
The famous "Pantyland"!
I couldn't picture it.
- The famous what?
- Pantyland.
That's what they call this place.
You will please refer to it...
as Logistic Center, not Pantyland.
Do you know why you are here?
Chupito told me a little.
He said...
you would tell me about salary...
and obligations.
Right. There'll be three
convoys a week...
and ten renderings per convoy.
Convoys are the trips?
Correct.
So renderings must be...
The salary is 50% of what is
discounted from soldiers...
the other 50% is for upkeep.
It's explained here.
Now...
if you don't mind,
though it may not be necessary...
I must follow the rules.
This way.
Here?
Yes.
Please undress.
I've got my period.
But, if you don't mind...
What's wrong?
It's only an exam of presence.
That's a steamy imagination, miss.
It did seem strange,
there isn't even a rug.
So...
do you think I'm ok?
I'm skinny,
but I promise to fatten up.
You're fine.
So you like me?
You passed. Get dressed.
Thank you.
When do I start?
Tomorrow.
Report to the dress department
for a uniform.
Dress department?
On the lower level.
Could you help me with
the zipper?
It's stuck.
There you go.
What? Let go!
What's wrong?
I must warn you about two things.
First:
You will call me "sir"...
as the other visitors do.
Second:
Don't ever do that again.
Well, you had a bulgy fly.
I didn't mean to offend you.
So forgive me.
Do you?
Don't let it happen again.
Now, please leave. I'm busy.
Whatever you say, sir.
See you tomorrow.
Look over there.
We're men too!
You keep everything!
They're locals.
They probably found out we'd pass by.
I don't like this.
If the service goes public,
it would be our end.
Nobody will know.
Sinchi's voice.
Program produced and directed
by yours truly...
German Laudano Rosales,
The Sinchi.
Good afternoon, dear listeners.
I beg you to take your young children
away from your radio...
since my known frankness...
leaves me no choice
but to refer to the crudest facts...
and terms:
Prostitution, my dear listeners!
A new system of flesh commerce...
through our sacred jungle rivers.
A mobile, motorized brothel...
called Pantyland is known to be...
clandestinely sending...
its sinful services
to our army's quarters.
So it has been informed...
to the office of Amazon Radio...
through letters and phone calls.
I'm listening, Father.
We'll talk later.
These shameless odalisques
have been seen...
navigating down
the region's main rivers...
towards the military quarters
and posts of the jungle.
So, I ask:
Who is behind...
this industry of sin,
flourishing before the very eyes...
of the authorities?
Nothing will stop our crusade
for progress...
morality, culture...
and patriotism
of the Peruvian jungle.
The time has come...
to unmask the monster and...
as the apostle did
unto the dragon...
behead it with a single stroke!
How was I?
Telluric, Maestro. Telluric!
Good morning.
Here so early?
The summon was for 9:00 a.m.
Excuse me, Mister Panta...
I needed to talk to you...
alone.
What about?
Please, don't smoke in this office.
Tell me.
Is there a problem?
It's you, Mister Panta.
Me?
I feel you have something
against me.
What?
You don't talk to me or look at me.
As if I offended you.
You're mistaken, miss.
I treat you as the other visitors.
I'll be blunt.
I think you want me
to fall for you.
What?
I am married, miss.
Like most of the men
I go to bed with.
It's no reason for...
It's a reason for me.
It should be for you.
You see?
I speak and you get skittish.
But, you know what?
I like that.
I'm like a crab.
I go against the flow.
So keep at it...
and I'll fall for you.
I don't advise it.
"Mixing work with pleasure is a sign
of ill proceedings."
That's kind of hard
in our line of business.
You know what I mean.
Don't you feel anything
when you see us naked?
That would be horrible.
Being clean-cut does not
mean being a fool.
I love it when you get angry...
you're so cute.
Here, dry off.
Thank you.
I don't think you are a fool.
But you like me
and won't accept it.
You are a very attractive woman.
I'm not indifferent to your charms...
but it's impossible.
Not even once?
Out of curiosity?
- You could order me...
- No I can't.
It would be an abuse of authority.
It's perfectly ok.
You should try your goods.
It would be like...
a quality test.
Please...
leave.
We won't discuss this again.
They've told you bad things
about me...
and you're scared.
But I'm not like you think.
I'd love to spend more time with you!
To send for our little cadet!
All day, every day!
Don't you like it?
Panta, please!
Forgive me.
I love your neck!
I know what's in store for me.
What is it?
Don't tell me you're
a Peeping Tom now. Pervert!
Keep walking.
How can they do that in public?
Come in.
You sent for me?
Take a seat, miss.
I sent for you to refresh
your memory about regulations.
Here is a copy.
Clarify your doubts...
and feel free to ask.
Are you angry?
You dare to ask me that,
after the show...
you put on in public?
Now I get it.
This is about yesterday.
Are you jealous?
A visitor is not a whore...
but yesterday,
you behaved like a whore.
Regulations don't prohibit friends.
That's quite an obscene friend.
You are to stop seeing that man.
Thank you.
He's not just a man.
His name is Nicolas.
And he wants to marry me.
If that is what you wish...
But please, think it over.
I remind you that, if you marry...
you'll have to leave the service.
We don't admit married women.
He wants to get married.
I just want a little
care and protection.
Don't I have that right?
I guess so...
Forgive me.
I have been unjust.
Don't worry...
I'm used to it.
Olga...
You are a strange person.
I don't understand you.
You should do something else.
You too.
This job doesn't become you.
You don't even try your own visitors.
Excuse me.
Miss... Wait.
Yes?
Are you...
still willing to volunteer...
to carry out a quality test?
Yes. Of course.
I must inform you that this test...
will only be done once...
will be secret,
and is strictly work-related.
Make no mistake, Olga...
the only motive that moves me
to perform this test...
is to verify
and perfect the service...
- One, Pechuga.
- Two, Sandra.
- Three, Iris.
- Four, Lalita.
- Five, Vanessa.
- Six, Colombiana.
- Seven, Coca.
- Eight, Salome.
- Nine, Pichuza.
- Ten, Peludita.
In flesh and blood.