Work plan?
Three convoys: Two of 48 hours,
and one returns tonight.
I already drew lots.
Lalita...
Vanessa...
and Colombiana.
We go to Bolognesi garrison.
It returns on Thursday at noon.
Start boarding.
I want you to work well...
and remember:
Work...
...ennobles and dignifies!
- Let's get to work.
- Excuse me.
Is there a problem?
No, nothing.
I just have something in my shoe.
Thank you.
You are not coming?
No. I have work here.
Too bad.
I thought we could repeat the test.
Don't you want to sleep with me?
The test allowed me...
to gather important information.
I thank you, but I don't consider it
necessary to repeat it.
Any trouble?
We're five minutes late.
No, Chuchupe.
This must not happen.
This situation may affect...
the personnel's performance
and concentration.
Then we could go to a hotel...
so we aren't seen.
Pocha, I've told you not to call
me at work, unless...
What?
I'll be right there!
Here are the last results.
You're sure, doctor?
Yes.
Your wife is pregnant.
I wanted to be sure
before I told you.
At last, Pantita. At last!
I'll be a father!
A penny for your thoughts.
What are you doing here?
They left without me.
And your machine?
I thought you never stopped working.
The Dalila returns at seven.
So you are working.
A cigarette?
No thank you.
Since the test,
we've never been alone.
Are you nervous?
What is it you want, Olga?
Nothing in particular.
- I thought you and I...
- "You and l"?
There is no "you and I."
That was very clear.
For work...
- Can't you think of anything else?
- No!
Even less when I speak to you.
Excuse me, I have to go.
Stay.
I'll leave.
You know?
You may be an excellent boss
and lover...
but as a person,
you're insufferable.
I'm not your lover...
miss.
But you want to be.
Today, we have stopped
along the way...
to celebrate
the 20,000th rendering...
carried out by Pechuga.
20,000 renderings given
to the soldiers and petty officers...
of our border units...
that signify a success.
They prove that the service...
has employed its capacity
to the fullest...
as can be deduced from
the 20,000 renderings...
and its components.
Our objective, for the year...
is to reach 200,000 renderings.
It's an ambitious
but possible figure...
if personnel maintain
their high performance...
as they have to date...
and with the coming reinforcements.
Here's to the 20,000!
Look! It's beautiful!
Cut the cake, Mister Panta!
Do you care to dance?
Are you ok, Mister Panta?
I'm not used to these celebrations.
I've had too much to drink.
I'm woozy.
Take it easy. Close your eyes.
There you go.
Partner switch!
Why didn't you dance with me, Olga?
Why didn't you ask me to?
You've treated me
as if I was invisible.
It's complicated, Olga.
I don't understand.
A man either likes a woman
or he doesn't.
And you don't seem to like me.
I like you.
I like you a lot.
I haven't stopped thinking
about you since...
You know...
Since we slept together?
Olga...
If only I could...
You can!
You just have to want it!
I like you.
I like you so much.
The famous Colombiana!
Excuse me?
Look how many are in her line.
Don't you like this saddle anymore?
I like you, but...
I'll ride another filly, this time.
Get back in line, soldier!
My record allows me to choose...
so I'm trying the Colombiana.
Return to your line.
Miss Colombiana already
has too many users.
Each visitor can give...
up to twenty renderings.
And, with me, there are...
Nineteen.
Nineteen users, sir.
Soldier?
User number twenty, sir.
Gentlemen.
Can't you see
the lady is overloaded?
By your turn, she'll be too exhausted
to perform well.
I suggest you return to your lines.
No.
I don't tire easily.
On the contrary...
I get more aroused
with each soldier.
The last ones will be
just as well tended as the first.
Try it. Fall in at the end.
Regulations demand ten renderings.
That's it.
Just ten.
Forgive me, Olga.
I don't know
what is happening to me.
It's your flirting...
I can't stand it.
The soldiers look at you...
as if you were a...
A visitor.
That's what I am, right?
It's abusive that the visitors
are only for soldiers.
We ask that civilians
in the army reserves...
be able to use this service,
just as the soldiers.
This service exists only in your minds.
How can you request such nonsense?
We've seen the boats, sir.
Boats filled with women.
We have needs too.
Not just the soldiers.
I have no information about this.
You've been drinking
too much chuchuhuasi.
But, General...
Do I look like a pimp?
No, General.
If the press finds out about this...
you wouldn't last long in office,
mayor.
Now, get the hell out
of my sight!
Out!
What's wrong?
Remorse, again?
I hate doing this to my wife.
I know...
You never cheated. You made love
every other Saturday, at 10:00 p.m.
I know it by heart, Panta.
Come here.
Relax. Nobody's watching.
You can't be too careful.
Are you ashamed of me?
That would be crazy.
There's a party on Friday.
I'm on leave that day
and I want to go.
You can go with Sandra.
I want to go with you.
With me?
You know that's impossible.
We can't be seen together.
These little girls are something.
You said it: Little girls.
Dumb babies...
not one of them worth anything.
Show me a woman
that'll take your breath away...
one that'll give you goose bumps.
There!
There is a woman.
Got you, Pantaleon Pantoja!
You jerk!
Come on, you've got work.
What are you doing?
Just working, Mister Pantoja.
We have enough.
Right, Mario?
Mr. Sinchi is here.
He has a present for you.
What is it you want?
I can make sure they disappear.
Surely, you don't want your wife
to see them.
That's what friends are for.
You know we are not friends,
Mr. Laudano.
Wrong! If I wasn't your friend,
you would be out of business.
And I am not talking
about the pictures I have.
I'm talking of something bigger.
Pantyland!
Don't get angry, Mr. Pantoja...
I speak of the thriving business
you run before everyone's eyes.
Rubbish.
After careful investigations...
I now have enough evidence
to sink you...
into disgrace and ruin.
If I were to speak on my show...
- Why don't you?
- Because I am for progress.
I am ahead of my time.
But the whole city pressures me...
and I think my silence
deserves a reward.
Blackmail then?
I'll help you, man!
For a few dollars...
I'll defend the Visitors' Service
and its mastermind.
Don't answer right away.
Sleep on it...
consult with your wife, your lover...
Don't get nervous!
Caiguas, Rioalto!
What? Stop them!
Let go, damn it!
Throw him in the river!
Nobody blackmails me!
Don't commit suicide!
I'm superman in Iquitos!
I can't swim!
You'll be sorry about this!
There is nothing in Iquitos...
that The Sinchi's voice
can't knock down.
You asked for it!
This is war! War!
As the clock that adorns
our studio wall strikes 1600 hours...
Amazon Radio is pleased
to bring its listeners...
the most listened to
program on the dial.
The voice of Sinchi!
I promised to unmask that lawless...
unscrupulous individual...
who, unpunished,
runs that depraved den...
known as Visitors’ Service...
better known as "Pantyland."
The Sinchi fulfills his promises,
my dear listeners.
Pantaleon Pantoja...
is the name of this dark character!
Pantaleon Pantoja, who has come...
from the depths of hell, supported...
by powerful and invisible interests...
to fill his name with shame,
ladies and gentlemen!
Yes, General.
I've heard nothing.
What?
Pocha!
...because, as a matter of fact,
Pantaleon Pantoja has a wife...
and has been leading a double life.
On one hand,
neck deep in the swamp...
of his affair with Olga Arellano...
the Colombiana...
remembered as the beautiful
whore from the north...
while appearing to lead...
a respectable life.
Hiding under the ignorance...
in which he kept his own wife...
to whom we extend...
all our moral support,
and we remind her...
that life is better under
the light of truth...
than under...
ignorance.
What does the army
have to do with Pantyland?
Does Pantoja have
the authorities' consent...
to enter quarters with prostitutes?
General Scavino, Father Beltran...
the mayor, the prefect.
Are they aware of these dealings...
and are looking away?
We will continue to investigate,
no matter who may fall!
With the courage
that has been our trademark.
You have heard: The Voice...
of Sinchi!
Devastating, Maestro!
Devastating!
Let me explain!
There's nothing to explain.
Get out of the way.
- You can't go!
- Let go!
Think of our little cadet!
You can forget about him and me.
You liar!
You hypocrite!
It's this job's fault!
You know me!
When I had to feed a regiment...
I gained weight!
I learned how to cook!
When I was in charge of uniforms...
I designed combat fatigues myself!
Remember?
They thought I was a fag!
Work absorbs me.
It transforms me. I can't control it.
Then stay with your whores,
your Colombiana...
and all that filth!
Don't touch me!
You're disgusting!
Let go of me!
I have offended an officer.
I know this is grave, but...
Three Our Fathers.
- Shame on you!
- Excellence!
What do you know?
Nothing, but...
Don't lie!
No, your Excellence.
You are a soldier of God!
Yes, Excellence.
You must fight Satan!
Please listen to me.
What can you say?
I've presented my resignation.
I've asked to be relieved of duty.
What did he say?
Nothing, yet.
I hope they relieve...
Secret mission!
Intelligence!
You are a liar!
Don't call, until you are
out of that filthy world!
Idiot!
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you.
How are you?
Not well.
What will happen now?
Good morning.
It's General Collazos.
General, sir.
I read your request.
Yes, General.
I'm surprised at you.
You were selected for your managing
and military qualifications.
Remember our glorious predecessors...
Bolognesi, Ugarte, Caceres.
Did they surrender
when they faced adversity?
No, sir. The true army man,
musters up his strength...
in the face of adversity.
You are a soldier.
You must not surrender.
You are to keep the service running.
Do I make myself clear?
Good morning.
As you command, General.
He even approved the ten
new visitors I had requested.
You see?
You should be happy.
There'll be no stopping you.
Forty visitors.
Not bad at all, Captain.
I have many enemies.
My wife won't talk to me.
She'll come around, Captain.
And don't worry about Father Beltran.
They've screwed him.
From head chaplain, he has gone
to parishioner at Iquitos cemetery.
With your tenacity,
you'll be rid of your enemies...
I'm only worried
about that damned Sinchi...
If I were you, Captain...
I've been ordered
to silence him.
Great! My assistants
will silence him.
They know where to hit.
Not like that. It's worse.
How's it going, dear Pantaleon?
One moment.
Wonderful view.
Congratulations.
What?
You wanted to speak to me,
Mister Pantoja?
A wise decision.
People like us should not harm
each other.
It's a waste of time.
I have not called you to talk...
but to give you this.
You will open it...
and tell me if it's enough.
Are you trying to bribe me?
You threw me in the river.
And now you pay me
to speak well of your brothel?
To not speak at all.
To never again mention the service.
I don't know, Mister Pantoja.
Pantyland is a very important
occurrence...
of the end of the millennium.
CNN will want a chronicle.
That would get a great audience...
Every month
you will receive an equal sum.
Now, you're talking, my friend!
I won't waste your time.
See you next month and...
If you wish,
and for no extra cost...
I could make a special broadcast...
to disprove some facts...
I made public against you
and could surely...
See you next month.
You're not eating?
I'm not that hungry.
You've lost a lot of weight,
since your wife left.
So I've been told.
Did they answer my report?
Due to the alarming presence
of civilians on the riverbanks...
I propose the
"Ordinary Rotation System."
This will impede civilians
of estimating our arrival.
To function adequately...
the plan requires
100 visitors and 5 ships...
that would permanently
navigate the rivers.
100 visitors? 5 ships?
That's nothing, tiger.
Listen to this.
I propose a bonus for
the visitors on convoy...
considering they are
risking their lives.
I attach to the project,
a social security plan...
compensation for time served,
and other benefits...
a worker is entitled to by law.
This isn't funny, Lopez.
This is starting to worry me.
Are we supposed to pay whores'
benefits and stop buying weapons?
Your new plan is not authorized...
nor may you hire more visitors.
I don't understand.
You made the service too efficient.
- They're scared.
- But, our goals!
Demand is way ahead of supply.
Let things be.
Relax and take a break.
I will prepare
a more convincing report.
I have the results
of the polls.
Now officers are asking
for the service.
95% of Captains and below
request visitors...
and 55% of the higher ranks.
This service requires,
and that's still under the minimum...
four vessels and 272 visitors.
Yes, but...
It would be a special group
of visitors, from Lima or overseas.
The OS! That's Officers' Section.
It sounds nice.
Exclusive Officers' service...
You're working too much.
You're going to be sick.
No task is worth your health.
First, you wanted to quit.
Now you're working to death.
I resigned and was ordered
to continue.
And I shall do so
against all odds because...
it's all I know.
If only everybody was like you!
What do you say we go
to Nauta and relax?
Thanks, but I have a lot
of work backed up.
I'll turn in my project on Monday.
Don't get up.
She left most of her clothes.
Maybe she'll return.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I would never buy this.
Is this how decent ladies sleep?
I look like a nun.
Do you like me better this way?
What's the matter?
Don't you know?
Can't you tell?
Is this about tomorrow?
Not just tomorrow.
I don't want to work.
I want to be with you.
We are facing a crisis.
I have to convince my boss.
And you are fussing about work!
I'm just saying the boss's woman
always gets treated better.
But not me.
You treat me like a whore.
Are you with me,
because I'm the boss?
What do you think?
I'd rather not know.
Fire me, Panta.
End this.
You want that?
Good morning,
to all my Amazon friends...
listening to this program...
throughout the farthest corners
of our jungle.
Today I wish to speak about
Mister Pantaleon Pantoja.
- Turn it off!
- No, I want to hear.
Gentlemen admit their mistakes...
so I say this from
the bottom of my heart:
I misjudged you, Mister Panta.
Letters signed by
the very soldiers and Sergeants...
that patrol our borders
keep pouring in...
and in them they tell me:
Mister Sinchi...
why do you insult Mister Pantaleon?
Get ready, girls.
Nobody has ever done for us
what he is doing.
We have needs. And thanks...
to Mister Panta
we serve our country better.
These sincere comments
made me think.
When I denounced Pantoja,
I forgot about the soldiers...
and about the commendable mission...
that Mister Pantaleon
has been carrying out to satisfy...
the needs of Peru's sentinels.
Attention Horcones post.
We're approaching.
Arrival in ten minutes.
I repeat...
Horcones!
We are being hijacked!
Horcones, do you copy, damn it?
This is the Eva!
May day!
Mister Panta, as he has fondly
come to be known in our jungle...
does not look for fame
or recognition...
Spread your legs!
Dear friends, I have in my hands
a report from the police.
Do you know how many rapes
have been reported...
since Mister Panta...
started the Visitors' Service?
Zero!
You heard right, zero!
Shit! Soldiers!
Damned soldiers!
Our jungle is calm.
Our mothers, sisters and girlfriends...
can now walk the streets
without fear.
The people of Loreto
can take pride in living...
in the only place in the world...
where sexual crimes
are no more.
Emotion overwhelms me
and I speak for myself...
as for the whole Amazon region
when I say:
Thank you, Mister Panta.
Thanks to you
and to your valiant ladies.
Could you please leave me alone?
Mourned through the night...
the mauled body of Olga Arellano,
also known as Colombiana...
reaches its final resting place.
This is The Sinchi...
we are at the Cemetery...
and many people have attended.
The coffin is approaching
its final place...
accompanied by a military escort.
Yes indeed,
a military escort and an officer.
At ease!
I am resurrection and life.
Those that live in me
shall not die eternally.
Lord, receive this sinner
and grant her...
eternal rest.
Lord, hear our prayer.
Olga Arellano...
we wear our glorious Peruvian uniform...
to mourn you.
It is our duty
to make known to the world...
with a full sense of responsibility...
that you have fallen
in the line of duty.
You are a martyr...
consecrated to serving
the soldiers of Peru.
Beloved Olga Arellano.
Your soldiers...
spread through the Amazon region...
whose lives you enlightened...
weep for you.
Your coworkers weep for you too.
In their name I tell you...
your sacrifice was not in vain.
It will motivate us
in our army-given mission.
Personally...
allow me to thank you deeply...
for so many tokens of affection...
for so many intimate lessons...
that I shall never forget.
Olga Arellano...
rest in peace.
Attention!
Present arms!
Get out of the army...
and stay with us.
We have a small sum
we wish to invest.
We could even apply for a loan.
With your brains, we'd be...
rich in no time.
I was ordered
to organize the service.
It's not a business interest.
Start your own business.
We don't want another brothel.
We want a company of visitors.
A modern, efficient company.
You'd be the boss.
I need to have bosses.
If I don't have them...
I don't know what to do.
I'm made to obey orders.
My calling is the army...
and I wish to die a soldier.
You must understand that.
What is it, Chuchupe?
I said no crying.
Forgive me, but I can't help myself.
It's the best job I've had.
Why do they shut it down?
The soldiers were so happy.
The goals were being reached
perfectly...
but that's the army.
The bosses know best.
Lighten up, Chuchupe.
Excuse me, miss.
Maybe there's a mix-up.
My appointment was at six.
Must I still wait?
Yes.
They're interviewing the General.
Look, it's starting!
Miss, the army has never sponsored...
or financed such an enterprise.
You deny the existence
of the service?
Of course I do, miss.
Categorically.
We've seen Captain Pantoja...
giving military honors...
to a prostitute.
He stated that the murderers...
should be court-martialed.
Miss, those ideas...
don't hold water.
High Command
has ordered an investigation...
to the last consequences.
And I assure you...
that those responsible
will be punished.
Thank you.
Studios.
You're famous.
Could I have your autograph?
You know who just left?
Yes, General, sir.
I saw the interview.
I want no explanations.
I saw you giving
your pathetic address.
Whatever!
You went mad and...
honestly, there is
no punishment severe enough...
for your acts.
Not even a firing squad.
I alone am responsible.
I accept any punishment.
You will go before
a disciplinary council, Pantoja.
That means you will be expelled.
Because of your record...
we offer you a more dignified exit:
Ask to be discharged tomorrow.
I will not, sir.
Your career is over.
You committed professional suicide.
Work as a civilian.
Your managing talent
can't be denied.
You'll make more money.
Are you crying, Pantoja?
Be a man, damn it!
I beg you excuse
my weakness, General, sir.
But I can only be a soldier...
it's my life.
If you make me leave...
Do you wish to remain
a Captain forever?
This will stain your record for life.
I will try to redeem myself.
You don't wish to be discharged?
We'll make it tough on you.
You know how that is.
I know.
I'll withstand anything.
My responsibilities impeded me
from answering earlier.
My wife, my daughter, Marina,
who is a beauty...
and my mission are my main
distractions and companions.
Regardless of distance...
I remember you with affection.
Give my regards to Mrs. Leonor
and Chupito...
to Pechuga and the rest
of my ex-visitors...
whom I never will forget.
Receive a warm hug from
your friend, Pantaleon Pantoja...
Peruvian Army Captain.
Read it again, please.
It's so beautiful.
Lieutenant.
I write this letter...
at four degrees below zero.
Collazos sent me...
to an isolated post.
My mission is to carry out...
social labor
in the area of literacy.
The 1973 census
recorded 1'784,281...
illiterate individuals...
and this region had the lowest
literacy rate in the country:
36.9%.
Which means 658,399 illiterate.
I... love...
my... Peru.
According to estimates,
an adult with an IQ...
not under 80 learns to read
in 6 to 9 months.
See you tomorrow.
Very good.
I've formed eight groups of fifteen...
which comes to 120 students.
Being optimistic...
illiteracy will be eradicated
in 6 years.
I continue to serve
our glorious institution...
with dedication.
Are you finished?
There's a group at six.
Absenteeism is high...
that could invalidate my estimates.
I'll make house calls.
You can't stop working!
Let's go home.
I'll be right with you.
I hate your smoking habit.
It's because of the cold, Pocha.
I'll be in the house.
Don't be long...
Translated by Gaston Vizcarra...
Laser subtitles by
Titra California, Inc.