Pantaleon and the special service
Are you sure this is the
man we are looking for?
Intelligence investigated his
professional and private life.
He got into the Chorrillos military
school with the best grade.
He chose the service corps.
Best grades in math, economy
and administration.
That's why during his whole carrier he got to
raise the flag every final day of the year.
Since he graduated, 8 years ago,
nobody has equalled his grades.
He prefers sports and study to
parties, but he has a social life.
After three years of going out,
he married Alfonsina Rea.
She is a decent girl, serious and
a good wife that takes care of her house
We have confirmed that
Cpt. Pantoja is no womanizer.
Not one escapade in 5 years of marriage.
He doesn't drink nor party
Sounds as if you were talking
about a saint, not a soldier.
Listen to what cpt. Montes wrote about him.
"Born organizer, mathematical sense
of order, executive capacity..."
"He leaves fond memories in Chiclayo and I request
for him to be comissioned for one more year..."
" to this station, as he conducted the
regiment with inspired efficiency."
This captain is our man, Lez.
- Panta, breakfast is ready.
- Coming!
- Pocha, Did you sew my galon?
- Yes, my lieutenant!
- Did I hear wrong or you said lieutenant?
- Excuse me, my captain.
Util I get used to it, you'll be
my little lieutenant, darling.
How beautiful this is!
Where do you think they'll send us this time?
I hope they leave us in Lima. And you?
I don't care. As long as there is
a quarter is good enough for me.
You and your vocation. You are married
first to the army and then to me.
Where would you like to be?
Other than Lima, of course.
Chiclayo again. Or Tacna or Piura
And the mountains? Or the jungle?
It's a possibility.
I hate the mountains. The jungle...
Iquitos could be.
It has to be a city, not a camping
ground or some garrison because...
you have to start thinking
about the little cadet.
- I can start dreaming about ordering him, or?
- Now?
May be... Or at night
It doesn't matter that it's not saturday.
I'm 5 minutes late. And it takes
me about 30 to get to the ministry
that is, if there is no traffic.
- Ok.
Let's have breakfast my captain.
Good morning ma'am, I am Cpt. Pantoja.
I have an appointment with Gral. Collazos.
He is waiting for you,
together with colonel Lez.
- Congratulations on the new spaghetti.
- Thank you my colonel.
- And by the brilliant way you got it.
- Thank you colonel.
I was informed about your promotion. You got the
first place by unanimous decision of the jury.
- Congratulation Cpt.
- Thank you my general.
Sit down.
- A cigarrette?
- No thanks.
You see my general neither a smoker
nor a drunk nor a man of the ladies.
An officer without vices. We already
have somebody to represent
our army in paradise, together
with San Mart匤 and St. Rose of Lima.
Let's not exagerate. I must have
some vices you don't know about.
We know everything about you.
You would flip if you knew
how much we have investigated you.
Well, let's take the
bull by the horns, then.
This matter requires absolute discretion!
I am talking about the
mission we will entrust you.
And it's the following, Pantoja:
From some time now the
troop in the jungle has been
- ... rioutous, excited.
- When we were informed about the problem...
we thought they were
isolated cases, manageable.
Caused by the climate or
the food in the area.
But it wasn't so.
Things have gone from bad to worse.
Gral. Scavino and father Beltr疣,
who has been busting my balls...
asking us to do something,
have taken some measures.
But up to now, neither punishments
nor lessons have solved the problem
That's why we have decided to take more...
radical measures
and it's here where you come to work!
I am a bit confused. The truth is that...
You'll be in charge of
something very important.
Gral. scavino will give you all the details
as soon as you reach your destination.
You are leaving next monday, Pantoja.
I hope you like the jungle.
You have all my confidence and support
for this dificult and delicate mission.
I wish you the best of lucks, Pantoja.
And remember, the reputation
of this institution is in your hands.
Well, the thing started to work.
But this is useless!
You'll identify these bandits, ladies.
- Stop crying.
- Do we have to go out in front of these soldiers?
They'll form outside, you peek through the
window and tell when you recognize the one.
Take a good look, ladies, take a good look.
Chose.
Which one do you prefer as
father of your children?
Gral. Collazos, my general.
Hello? Tiger, How is it going?
OK, OK. I'm going to receive this cpt.
But I warn you, I wash my hands
from this whole business!
- These strategists at Lima!
- Do they still have this special service in mind?
May god have mercy!
Something doesn't smell right.
What does the reputation of the army...
have to do with climate,
food and health of the troop.
- I don't get it.
- Darling, stop thinking about it.
- As soon as you talk to Scavino you'll know.
- Maybe something happened in the jungle.
- I'll check the internet.
- Just a little bit, my captain.
Now you mission is to
take your wife to the movies...
and to buy her sommer clothes
so that she doesn't fry in the jungle.
- It's an order.
- Whatever you say my general.
Afterwards I'll let you get under
my sheets as a price...
and I'll allow you to
caress me at discretion!
Pochita, you are wrinkling
my uniform, honey.
As the guide of the Amazon region, ,,
I feel obliged to speak in defence
of all the women of the region.
I am not an antipatriotic, no!
But my love for the army doesn't
prevent me from saying the truth:
This wave of rapes that
plagues our region,...
terrorizing and dishonoring
our beautiful women,...
has a culprit.
The rapists are soldiers of our army.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,
our own soldiers.
It's painful to admit...
but I have undeniable proof.
What is happening with our army?
I ask myself: What do the
authorities have to say about this?
What does Gral. Scavino have to say...
and what does father Betr疣,
the army chaplain, have to say?
They should be lock in a prison for life...
for abusive and perverts but
the mercy of our lord is infinite...
and he opens them a door for
their repent and salvation.
Soldiers, Do you swear
by God and fatherland...
to take these womes as wives,
to honor them...
and be faithful until death do you part?
Yes, I swear!
Don't worry ma'am, after a couple of
days the mosquitoes don't bite anymore.
- They won't even look at you.
- Thanks.
Don't stop eating "cecina"
with "tacacho", it's very soft.
Uf! It's so hot!
I can't stand these clothes anymore.
You have to get used to this, baby.
This is the coolest season of the year.
I hope that in the army compounds they
have air contioned. If not, I die!
It's the first thing I am gonna
ask Scavino. And if not...
I'll get one installed for you.
Uf! You are all wet. Really wet.
Us human beings sweat when we're hot.
- I'm going to get dry.
- No! It doesn't bother me at all. On the contrary.
- Ok, now we have to unpack.
- Wait, wait, there's no hurry.
- Panta! What are you doing!?
- Take it all off.
- I don't know you anymore!
You! Always so serious.
Wait, I take it off.
Remember you have a meeting with Scavino
You'll fall asleep. You
always fall asleep after...
- I want you to know that I disagree
with the service you've come to organize.
I don't know what my mission is going to be. Gral.
Collazos told me you would inform me.
In a few words: The troop
is fucking the "cholas".
Officers don't know what to do anymore
with all the lawsuits for violations.
He have asked doctors,
sociologists, sexologists.
And after much bla bla bla,
we came to the simple truth.
Any soldier that comes to the
jungle becomes a... dick head
- I still don't get it. I am not an expert
, but I can't see how...
- Just a second.
Cpt. Pantale Pantoja
(Peruvian Army) is entrusted with...
the mission of organizing,
implementing and managing
a special services of hostesses
for garrisons, border posts...
and similars", with the duty of
fulfilling the natural needs of
Etc, etc, etc...
- Excuse me Gral.
What do you mean with these...
- ... hostesses? Do you mean...?
- Whores.
Yes, whores.
Gral. Collazos and his Lima strategists...
had the great idea of giving
women to the troops.
Moving the from one camp to the next
and letting the soldiers fornicate
And you, a Captain of the Peruvian Army,...
will serve as the macquereau, a pimp...
or however those individuals
that commerce with sex are called.
Excuse me, my general.
But I don't think I'm capable
of carring out this mission.
- I beg you to reconsider...
- It's already too late for that. It's an order.
- And orders are to be fulfilled.
- I'll try to do the best I can.
- I don't want you to come close to the
headquarters, nor any other dependency in Iquitos.
You are excused of attending
any official act,...
parades, tedeums, etc.
- And I forbid you to use the uniform.
You'll dress as a civilian.
Do I even have to come
to work as a civilian?
Your work will be very, very far
away from the headquarters.
What logist and material
support can I count on?
Lieutenant Bacacorzo has
been designated for that.
He'll be the link between
you and your superiors.
Any other question, Captain?
We won't live in the military compounds nor
will you mingle with the wives of the officers.
- Why?
- I'm sorry, chola.
We'll pretend we are civilians, I'll be
a trader that's starting a new business
What kind of job did they give you?
Why do we have to hide like this?
- I'm talking to you.
- I'm listening, Pantale Pantoja.
Can you explain what all this is about?
You promissed we would never
lie to eachother. You promissed.
Why don't you want to tell me?
The thing is that I'm going to work...
in intelligence.
The intelligence service?
Well, then I get all the mistery.
What do you have to find out?
- I can't say anything, those are my orders.
- Pantita, tell me.
What do you have to spy? Is there going
to be a war with Brazil or Ecuador?
Does it have to do with the Rio protocol?
You have no idea, lieutenant, what it means
to have to hide from my wife...
this thing of the mission.
I had never before lied or hidden
anything from her. Never.
Many officer would give
anything to be in your shoes.
Not me. They up screwed me with this job.
How am I supposed to organize this service
if I had never had contact with prostitutes?
- I don't even know where to begin.
- From the beginning captain.
Go to a cathouse, to see how are things.
I recommend you Do Leonor.
A.K.A "La Chuchupe"
She wants to give up her business and
her girls will be out of job.
I would love to go with you,
but my instructions are very specific.
- Hi honey.
- Good evening.
- Do you want to dance?
- No.
I'm sorrry... I don't dance.
You like to go to the point, don't you?
Me too.
- First get a token by the cashier.
- No, you don't understand.
I'm not here to satisfy my instincts.
I come to talk business
with the owner, Mrs. Leonor.
Could you tell her that
I want to speak to her?
Delighted
But one thing doesn't prevent the other.
Listen. When you're finished talking...
look for me.
I love serious guys like you.
Good evening ma'am.
My name is Pantale Pantoja.
Welcome to "Casa Chuchupe".
Here we treat good everybody...
except those dickheads,
the soldiers, that want to fuck for free.
Tell me, what can I do for you sir?
I would like to talk about
business with you, but in private
Does it mean you are kicking me out?
- Would you like something to drink?
- A bier and two glasses.
The first round is on the house
Or would you prefer something stronger?
No thank you.
I don't drink.
Look, I am an entrepreneur...
and I have come to
live here, in Iquitos,...
with the idea of
investing in some business.
I heard that you want to close yours...
and I was thinking...
- To set up a whorehouse?
I'll give you some advice.
You look like a decent guy and I like you.
Don't get into this, it's a bad thing.
If you want money set up a dinner.
Strange. I had been told that here...
there is a lot of demand,
because of the heat and everything.
Yes, but between soldiers and politicians
that get the service and don't pay...
the bribes you have to give and
the rent that is higher every month,...
I'm loosing money. The best
is to cut from the root...
and keep the few savings I still
have left for my retirement.
The only thing I regret are my girls.
I like some of them a lot.
They are good girls, healthy, hard working.
Perhaps we can reach a good
agreement for both of us.
If you are interested.
Your knowledge, your experience,
that's all very valuable for my plans.
If you close your place
I would like to hire you.
- You and some of your girls.
- I'm interested.
Take hookers to the military
posts in the jungle.
I would have never thought about something
like that, it's a wonderful idea.
But don't dream Mr. Pantoja. They'll
never let us into the bases.
I already have the permission to go in.
And don't call them hookers,
nor whores, please.
The appropriate name is "hostesses"
You have permission to
go into the barracks?
Don't tell me you are a military man!
Of course not.
I want you to think very
well about what we talked.
In a couple of days I'll
come with a work proposal.
- First...
- I can tell you now. I'll do it! You were sent by heaven.
- Sorry, the colombian
wants to speak to you.
The colombian? I thought she was out of Iquitos...
What does she want?
- Should I tell her to wait?
- No, let me talk to her now.
If she is looking for a job,
she came to the wrong place
- Would you wait a minute, Don Panta?
- Sure, go ahead.
- Is she really colombian?
- Nobody knows. She says so.
She was working outside. Probably came
back because she got into trouble.
- She's very atractive.
- Yes, one of the best things you can see around here.
But I wouldn't recommend her to you.
She is marked, cursed.
Two men already died for her.
A bad thing sir.
Well, it was about time.
- It's more the 11.
- Pochita, my head is killing me.
How would it NOT hurt you?
And do you know what?
I'm glad you feel so bad.
You came here in broad day light falling stupid!
Don't you remember?
Can you lower your voice a bit?
I had never felt so bad. Come to cuddle me.
You are going to explain me what
all this is about Pantale. Right Now.
- Where were you last night?
- It's a thing of this damned job
- It's part of the mission,
you know I hate these things
- You were with women, weren't you!?
- No!
Men only get drunk until
dawn if they are with women.
- I am sure you have been!
- That never, Pochita, no!
Don't cry, you make me feel
like a criminal and I am not!
I never had nor will have eyes
for another woman, you know it.
Then tell me where you were last night.
" The undersigning, Cpt. Peruvian
Army, Services, Pantale Pantoja,...
responsibe of organizing
a special service...
for garrisons and frontier
posts of the Amazon region
respectfully writes,
greets and informs:...
That he took posesion of the location
on the shores of the Itaya river,...
designated by the V region as
headquartes and logistic center.
That the two soldiers sent to the service
are already under his command,...
Soldiers Sinforoso Caiguas
and Palomino Rioalto,
which were chosen correctly
by the authorities...
by their good behaviour, docility,...
and aparent indiference
to the opposite sex,...
because, otherwise, the kind or work
and the idiosincrasy of this place...
could give way to temptations
and problems for the service.
That the first week, the undersigning
concentrated his time and effort...
in the cleaning and
ordering of the location.
That a week to clean could
be considered excesive...
but the ground was in
unsuitable conditions for use...
and, if you allow the
expresion, disgusting:...
As the army had it
abandonned, this deposit...
was used for heterogeneous
and ilegal practices.
The undersigning had to equip
Sinforoso Caiguas and Palomino Rioalto
with the necessary equipment
(attached are receipts Nr. 1, 2 & 3),...
so that they, working diligently,
would burn the trash,...
mop the floors and walls,
and desinfect everything with creoline.
We have proceeded to
whitewash and paint the walls....
and to clean the external terrain...
and the small dock, that had
severe damage, was repaired.
After all that, I have the
honor to inform, that in 7 days
imposing, in any case, with
work sessions of 10 and 12 hours,...
and neglecting his wife, that
without his help had to deal with...
looking for and setting up a house,...
the undersigning managed to turn the pigpen
he received into an inhabitable place,...
simple but ordered, clean
and even pleasant,..
as corresponds to any dependency
of our army, even if clandestine,
as is the one at hand."
- Hi, What a miracle, you so early!
- Let me introduce you to Alicia...
the neighbour that helped me
to clean this pigpen. Alicita...
mi husband, so you see I am not a widow.
Nice to meet you, and thanks for everything.
Excuse me, I'm in a hurry.
Well, Pochita, I go.
Let's leave the movies for tomorrow.
No, he'll go out again in a while.
- I'll come for you, for the 8'movie, ok?
- Yes.
What do you think? This
will be my new attire.
Horrible. I prefer you
with your uniform, Panta.
- Are you going out?
- I'd prefer a thousand times to stay here with you...
and order the little cadet. Although,
if you want, we can do it now...
- A quicky, don't you want?
- I don't want and I can't
I am also going out, I'm going
to the movies with Alicia.
I'm getting jelous of your friend.
You are all the time together.
You disapear every night.
It's you secret job's fault
It's as difficult for you as it is for me.
We have to be pacient darling.
Stop that.
Don't change, stay like this.
I like you more everyday.
Panta, I don't know you anymore.
And with those clothes... I feel as if I
was cheating on you with another man.
The voice of "Sinchi".
Good afternoon dear listeners.
Continuing with our moralizing campaign...
and defending the physical
and moral integrity of our women...
your server, Sinchi,...
invites you to join our crusade...
and finally demand to the
authorities an answer,...
clear and strong...
about the abuses commited...
by unsocial elements of the army.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,...
we demand exemplary
punishments for the rapists...
Good afternoon.
You are 7 minutes late.
If you were a member of the service...
I'd fine you with 20 soles.
- I'd pay delighted cpt.
I'd give half of my salary away to
be able to work with the service.
I don't recommend it, you'd
have to work 14 hours per day,...
including holydays. And even so
we wouldn't be able to satisfy the demand.
The results of the polls in
the barracks are alarming.
Uyuyuyuyuy...
Look at that captain.
The best body in the Amazon
Don't tell me you don't
know "the colombian".
Evidently you are getting to
know you ground very fast.
I saw her one night at Chuchupe's.
Wouldn't you like to have
her under your command?
That monument would make us famous.
Later, maybe. Chuchupe and
Chupito are the one recruting....
I don't mess with that.
Well, here are the results of the survey.
It's alarming.
Potential number of users
of the service: 8726?
Number of dispensations...
Dispensations?
Monthly dispensation
(average wished per user): 12
Which means that to cope with demand,..
We would have to ensure a
monthy average of 104 thousand...
712 dispensations.
- 104 000?
You're going to need a
battalion of hookers.
- I mean, hostesses.
- With a mean of 20 daily dispensations...
for a hostess of great
quality and output,...
working full time and
without delays, we would need
2271 prostitutes!?
This guy is crazy, nuts.
He wants to turn our army into
the biggest brothel of the world.
Please, calm down, father.
Let me continue.
221 hostesses. Naturally
imposible at the moment.
That's why I propose to start
with a convoy of 5 hostesses...
.. that could carry out 4800
simple dispensations per month,...
in weeks of 6 days, working
full time and no delays.
I ask for permission to recruit
Leonor Curilincha, a.k.a Chuchupe,...
european woman with huge
experience in the matter,...
and who would act as chief of
staff and responsible for enrolling...
and guarding the female element.
This is too much! An insult to our uniform!
We should put this guy in jail!
The undesigning requests
authorization to carry out a pilot test
and asks for the permission
from the command to enroll..
the first 5 hostesses, that
would earn a salary of...
A salary taken from our institution!
Gral. Collazos willl never allow it!
Caiguas, Rioalto and you will go
to the post to talk to the users...
and prepare the locations
for the dispensations.
- Locations, dispensations?
- You have to get used to the new language.
Users, are the clients,
locations are the beds,...
dispensations are the fucks
and hostesses are the girls.
Isn't it true, Don Panta?
- And the candidates?
- Tomorrow, I called 10 girls, you can choose those 5.
They are all first quality and trustworthy.
Chuchupe, chupito.
I heard you closed your
place. What a pitty.
A great loss for the bohemian
night life of our city.
What are you going to do now?
Are you thinking about a new business?
- Yes, something like that.
- Allow me to introduce myself.
Germ疣 L疼dano Rosales, at your service.
I see you are a foreigner.
From the capital?
- Pantale Pantoja, good afternoon.
- Welcome to this beautiful land...
where we worship friendship and beauty.
Have you been long around here?
The friend is a journalist.
He has a radio show: The voice of Sinchi.
Yes, my wife listen to it all the time.
I hope she likes it.
What brings you here my friend?
Big hunt?
I am a happily married man.
I came to set up a business.
Well, good luck.
I wish you lots of
luck in your "businesses".
It has been a pleasure.
Until the next occasion.
I don't like this guy.
He makes too many questions.
He a professional busybody.
Don't worry, he's like that with everybody.
- Problems?
- No, excuse my distraction, the thing is...
Do you know that guy?
He's from Lima, Pantale Pantoja.
- Not at all. Why?
- Don't know, forget about it.
Weird character.
What is he doing with Chuchupe?
With the objective of collecting
information for the special service,...
the undersigning carried out and
investigation with some products...
that have, following the local
lore, aphrodisiac properties.
The undersigning decided to
investigate personally during 4 days,...
how can these products affect...
the problem that caused and has
maintained the special service.
That the consumption of some of
these products had the effect...
of an increaseof the sexual appetite and
seminal impulses of the undersigning,...
to the point where the bad
touchings and the virile act...
took hold of his mind,...
with detriment of his power of
concentration, general nervous system,...
and efectivity at the job.
In consequence...
he was forced to request
and obtain from his wife...
an average of 3 intimate
encounters per day,...
with her consequent
annoyance and surprise,...
as she is not used to this rythm of requirements.
For all the expressed above,...
the undersigning requests
that instructions be given out...
prohibit the use of such products...
in the frontier posts,
garrisons and similar.
The undersigning also
informs that he enrolled...
the first group of hostesses,...
a very difficult job as he is still
under the effects...
of long term aphrodisiacs.
Thanks cutie. Tell the next one.
And? What did you think?
It's more difficul than what I thought.
You have to like one more than the rest.
- May I?
- Come in darling.
Hi.
- Here I am, Don Panta.
- Good morning.
- Your name please.
- "Pechuga" (Breast).
Luisa C疣epa, single and
with no serious relation.
Very well lady.
Show me what you've got.
Accepted... Accepted!
Cpt. they are coming.
The undersigning, Cpt. Pantale Pantoja,...
salutes and informs as follows:...
That the ship lent by the fluvial forces...
arrived to our center in Itaya river.
The ship was brought by
subofficer Rodr刕uez Saravia,
who understood the
secret character of the mission.
The pilot test in Horcones...
will be carried out in
only 6 days form now.
Do Chuchupe, if you please.
The rules are the rules.
Gentlemen, the future of the service
depends on the succes of this operation.
The girls are ready.
Do you want to see them?
Yes, let them in.
Caiguas and Rioalto designed
the clothes of the hostesses.
This one is with straps, sir.
What do you think?
- And with a zipper, for a quick skining.
- What do you think?
Lalita could have the
clothes a bit tighter,...
to mark her thingies.
- It fits like a glove.
The thing is that Lalita has a
streamed body, just fiber, no grease.
Start getting fat, then. You know how
the troops like them, big as a house!
Chupito, from today on, doble food rations.
Coming back to the uniforms,
do you like them or not?
They are very pretty.
But is everything going to be green and red?
Even the cards for the fucks...
I mean, dispensations,
are made in those colors.
Those are the colors of
the special service.
Green for the exuberant
beauty of the region.
And red for the manly fire
our service will help to placate.
I propose that we paint our
finger and toe nails in green.
- Look how pretty!
- And the underwear, also red and green?
- Do you want to see?
- It's not necessary, Pechuga.
Congratulations, you've done
a great job, you can go now
Mr. Rodriguez.
We won't tolerate any kind of disrespect.
If you are not able of controlling your
lower instincts and carry the mission...
according to the norms, I'll have
you removed from the service.
- Is that clear?
- Yes sir, clear.
Don't worry, Don Panta.
I know Chuchupe..
She has the locations and
everything else ready for our arrival.
- Everything is going to be fine.
- This is our hour of truth, Chupito.
Very well ladies.
We're about to get there.
Whenever you want, Don Panta.
We are ready for the... hand-to-hand.
- How do I look?
- You all look fine.
There in Horcones,...
20 brave soldiers wait for you.
They sacrifice...
day after day for their fatherland,
giving away all the conforts...
and basic needs one is used to.
Some of them have months
without looking at a woman.
This is only a pilot test
but we'll carry it out with patriotism
and lots of commitment
and sacrifice. I assure you...
that the special service will grow
through the whole region of the Amazon
bringing joy and consolation
to our hardworking soldiers.
Let's do three hurrays.
For the special service...
and for our glorious armed forces.
Hip, hip, ra!
We are there, Don Panta.
Get ready for the landing.
Go ahead, ladies, show these
soldiers what you are capable of!
- Let's go, damn, squeeze them
until they beg for mercy!
Silence!
Come on, Sandra, hurry up, hurry up.
Iris, Iris.
At 16:05 our hostesses occupied their...
posts. Lalita and Pechuga
stayed at the groceries deposit.
Iris at the nursery, Sandra
in the radio station...
and Vanesa in the dinning room.
Back! Back, back, back!
I don't need to remind you that
is you job to show these ladies...
that the soldiers that serve our fatherland,
also know how to behave like men!
They are all yours, sir.
The instructions are the following!
1. Each user can stay a
maximum of 20 minutes...
That's the longest time
according to the rules.
2. The users have the right to one
dispensation, normal and simple,
which means that soldiers
must leave the location as soon...
as the dispensation is over.
It is strictly forbiden...
under punishment of expulsion,
to request sexual perversions like...
manual or oral masturbation, sodomy...
the so called black kiss...
and other extravagances
not worth mentioning.
Finally, the users that wait,...
must keep absolute silence and order...
so as to not disturb the fellows in action.
- Understood!?
- Understood!
- Give the order to start.
- First row, go ahead!
- 4 minutes, 46 seconds.
- Next!
Hey! Hey!
6 minutes 11 seconds.
So far no one has reached the maximum.
These marks are only a general indicator.
Due to the isolation of the posts,
the users have virile impatience...
kept during a long time.
- Some have been here for months.
You see? That's why they
are so abnormaly fast.
This one has the record.
2 minutes 22 seconds.
- What do you think?
- Whe are going to have to consider the prolonged
abstinence variable in our
future calculations. Yes.
A success. A complete success.
Everything worked...
with the greatest order and
in the times assigned.
Besides, Pantoja managed to save 18%...
of the amount we gave for the test.
The commander, Santana, sent
a very complimentary report...
congratulating the special service.
He wants it to start working
as soon as posible.
Enough, Lez. Everything is clear.
Well, write then,
Let it be know to the chief commander
of the V region, Gral. Roque de Scavino,
that the special service
is authorized to carry out the
mission for which it was created.
10 000? 10 000 weekly?
You are mad!
No my Gral. it's a scientific statistic.
Look at these graphs.
It's a very careful calculation...
and actually conservative.
Look, the 10000 weekly dispensations...
correspond to the primary
psycobiological needs.
If we were to completely
satisfy the needs of the soldiers...
the amount would be 53200
weekly dispensations.
Who put this aberration into your head?
Who told you you can only
be satisfied as a man fornicating!
The best sexologists, biologists
and psycologists, father.
I've told you to call me major, damn!
- Excuse me major.
You'll allow me to show
you some material...
with excerpts from
the austrian Freud,...
Virgil Stekem, whose nationality was not...
in the consulted enciclopedia,
the popular magazine
"Selections", and Dr. C.A.
Segu・ our countryman.
Nevertheless, if you prefer to see
the book directly, I have some...
of them in the small library of the center.
- There I wanted to get!
I have been informed that you
distribute pornography to the soldiers.
I know it well. In Borja,
you helper, this dwarf...
gave away that filth.
" Two nights of pleasure", "Life, passion
and death of Maria the Tarantula",...
" Julia and the horse", "Sit
here, I'll go in there",...
"Superass".
- Yes, sir.
It was an idea from my
helper that I decided to try.
And as a result we accelerated
the erection of the soldiers.
And thus we where able to save time.
Now we do it regularly.
So it wasn't once, nor the
idea of this satanic dwarf!
The special service gives
pornography to the soldiers.
We just lend the magazines.
We have no budget to give them away.
But I assure you, Gral. that
the result has been positive.
The soldiers that reads while waiting...
finishes betwen 2 and 3
minutes before one that doesn't read.
These saving have allowed us
to reach the 500 weekly dispensations
with only 5 hostesses.
- I'll have to listen to everything before I die! God!
Allow me to leave Gral.
I understand you father.
- Finish you report at once!
- The situation of the service is dramatic.
We a lot of effort we have
reached the 500 dispensations
But we are over-requested.
They call us by phone, radio...
Pantoja, I am going to complain
to the command of the V region!
You are discriminating us!
The garrison of Santiago river...
receives a convoy each week
and us only once per month.
Do you think 2 hostesses can
serve 130 soldiers and 18 officers?
What the fuck is going on!
My people has been since 3 weeks...
waiting for the convoy! The days go by!
We need to grow.
I am waiting for the
authorization of Gral. Collazos...
to increase the unit to 10 hostesses.
Collazos has informed me about
your request and he ordered me...
to make you come to
listen personally to your report.
- But you know very well that...
- I know what you think about me, Gral.
but... Do you have an answer?
The army wants us to
continue with our service.
- Do you mean we can count on more girls?
- Only 5 for now.
Tomorrow I want you to bring
10 girls to choose 5.
Actually 4, because I already
have thought of one.
The colombian.
I respect whatever you say,
but I don't think it 's a good idea.
- That woman is very difficult.
- And dangerous.
I have thought very well about it.
I am ready to run the risk.
The gains she could bring to
the service justify the decision.
In any case, if she fits into the
system, fine, if not, we take her off.
We don't lose anything.
You are shameless!- They are low lifes, I know.
But what can I do?
- You even accept it as something normal!
- How can I deny it if you saw me?
- This has to do with my job. My mission...
- I am sick and tired of that mission!
Just let me know that
you have gone with that wh...
Calm down, darling. I swear
nothing is going to happen.
- That woman...
- I could have thought anything,...
but that you, always so decent,
serious, hard working...
would go with that parrot
and that horrible dwarf...
That you would become a...!
The only thing I can promise is to
be seen as little as I can around them
I am very sorry but that is part of my job.
The letters are too little for my taste.
Why don't you paint the
background yellow, like the Eva
Don Panta likes it that way,
like the uniforms of the girls.
Did you see? He loved it!
And what do you think about the name?
I don't know I would
have preferd Geraldine.
- it's more poetic.
- Geraldine?
Hey, look. There they are.
The new girls.
Assorted, Don P., a show of bone and meat.
You can eat at your pleasure!
I asked you for 10, you brought 20.
I can't be the whole day examining.
The voice spread out
and women came like flies!
From all neighbourhoods.
They even came from San Juan de Munich!
- It's not my fault, Don Panta.
- Well, let's get those 5.
Didn't the colombian come?
She must be in the toilet, sir.
There she is Don Juan.
Make them form in a line and
send them in with their cards.
Let's start with the colombian.
- Aha.
Hurry up! We don't have all day.
Fast! Everybody forms a line!
There you go!
Did you finish filling out your cards?
- Good morning.
So this is the famous "Pantiland".
I couldn't imagine how it would be like.
- The famous what?
- "Pantiland" That's how everybody calls this place.
- Funny name, isn't it?
- If you don't mind, I'd like to ask you to...
refer to this place as the
logistic center. No Pantiland.
- Did Chupito explained you
why I made you come? - Yes.
She told me you would inform me...
about the pay and the obligations.
Yes, it would be 3 weekly convoys and a
minimum of 10 dispensations per convoy.
A convoy is a trip to the barracks?
- Genau.
So... the dispensations must be...
You'll get 50%...
of what the soldiers pay.
The rest is invested in maintenance.
It's all explained here.
Now If you don't mind, and
maybe it's not necesary in your case,...
I have to follow the rules.
Here.
- Here? -Yes.
- Could you take your dress of, please.
What a pitty, I have my "visit",
but if you don't mind...
What is wrong?
Would you prefer to do it somewhere else?
It's just a physical exam.
You have a hot imagination, lady.
Ah. I was thinking where
everything was going to be...
if there isn't even a carpet. Or?
And? Do you like me?
I'm a bit skinny, but in one
week I gain back my weight
- You are very fine.
- So, You like me?
You are approved, you can get dressed.
Thanks
- When do you want me to start working?
- Tomorrow, report...
a t 8:00 in the Clothing
Department to get your uniform.
- Clothing department?
- Ground floor, Chupito will show you.
Could you help me with the zipper, please?
It's stuck.
Fine.
What are you doing? Leave me!
- What is going on?
- I have to tell you two things.
You can't use first names.
You have to refer to me as Mr. Pantoja...
as the rest of the hostesses. Second,...
never again have this
type of behavior with me.
Ok, but your pants were
swollen up, Don Panta.
I didn't want to offend you,
I just wanted to do you a favor.
Forgive me.
Do you forgive me?
Ok, never do it again.
And now, please leave, I
have other things to do.
Yes, sir.
See you tomorrow.
- Do you still have a lot to do?
- No, this is the last one.
Pechuga, 1 528 dispensations,
first trimester.
Panta, Does you work have anything
to do with food provisions?
- Pochita, please...
This are secret documents.
You know I can't tell you.
But you are working so
much lately, darling.
You are out the whole day and
you bring your work to bed.
Things are moving faster than we espected.
I'll be ready in a minute.
I have to send this report to
Lima before I leave on mission.
This months you have been more
than 10 times away from Iquitos. - 12 times
Hey! Look there.
We want women!!
We are also machos, damn!
You want them all for you!
We also want them!
They are just the natives.
But they found out we were coming.
I don't like this Chuchupe.
If it becomes public...
the kind of service we give,
it would be the end.
Don't worry, Don Panta.
Nobody is going to find out.
"The voice of Sinchi"
Program produced and
directed by your friend,...
Don German Laucha Dorsales, "El Sinchi".
Good evening, dear listeners.
I beg you to send your
children away from the radio...
because,
I will have to talk crude facts...
and call things by their name.
PROSTITUTION! My dear listeners.
An ingenious system of carnal traffic...
through the sacred rivers of our Amazon.
A movile and motorized
whorehouse, called "Pantiland",...
is hiddenly sending...
its sinful and inmoral services
to the quarters of our fatherland.
We have been informed by
many letters and telephone calls.
- Hello?
- Yes, father, I am listening.
We talk later.
they have seen many times
this group of shameless mermaids...
navigating through the
main rivers in the area...
in direction to the garrisons
and posts of the Amazon.
And I ask: Who is behind
this industry of sin...
that flourishes under the
very eye and pacience of the authorities?
Nothing will stop our
cruzade for the progress...
moral, culture and
peruvian patriotism of the Amazon.
The moment has arrived
when whe have to unmask the world
And just like the apostle
with the dragon,...
cut its head by one stroke!
We still don't know who presides...
this industrial complex of
hustlers of "Pantiland".
But your faithful servant
sets himself to investigate...
and reveal the identities
of the responsible...
Fall who may!
- How did I do, Paquito?
- And earthquake, master, an earthquake!
Gral. Scavino is really pissed off
because of those declarations...
of Sinchi in the radio.
You can imagine how is Father Beltr疣.
He has all the reason to be worried.
People are starting to
talk about the service.
As long as we grow it will be more
and more difficult to keep the secret...
of this mission. And now this...
journalist that...
meanaces with investigating.
This guy wants a bite of the cake, Cpt.
If he bothers too much, just give
him a bit of money and matter solved.
Pay him? No, I don't
deal with blackmailers.
I've never done it and never will.
Good morning.
What are you doing here so early.
The appointment was at 9.
Excuse me, Don Panta, but...
I needed to talk a minute with you.
- Please.
- What is it about?
I ask you not to smoke here.
Well, tell me. Any problem?
- It's about you, Don Panta.
- About me?
I think you have something
against me and I don't know why.
- What do you mean?
- That you won't see me nor talk to me.
I would even say that my
presence bothers you.
You are mistaken.
I treat you in the same way
I treat the rest of the hostesses.
Can I be honest with you, Don Panta?
- I think you treat me that way to make
me fall in love with you. - What!?
I remind you I am a married man.
Just as most of the guys
I sleep with, Don Panta.
- Being married is no reason for a man to...
- Well, for me is a reason...
more than enough and it should be for you too.
- You see?
You see how I was right?
I just talk to you and you start to boil.
But you know what? I like that.
The thing is that I am like the crabs.
I like to go against the current, so...
if you trash me around I am going to fall in love with you.
- I don't recomend it.
" To mix work with pleasure,
is the worst measure"
That is something very difficult
to do in our profession, Don Panta.
You know very well what I'm talking about.
Do you feel anything when
you see us in the sun?
That would be horrible.
I warn you, I am a decent man, not a moron.
Don't make a mistake.
I love it when you take
out your agresive side.
You look cute.
Here, get dry.
Thanks
I don't think you are a moron.
But I do think you are just
holding back you desire.
I can't deny that you are a very...
attractive woman.
And don't think I am indiferent
to your charm, but...
it is not possible.
Not even once?
Not even a little bit curious?
If you order me...
- I can't give you that type of orders. I would be...
abusing my authority.
There wouldn't be anything wrong with that.
You have the right to
check the goods you offer.
It would be something like...
certifying quality.
Please, go away.
And I don't want you to
mention this matter again.
The thing is that they've
told you bad things about me...
and you are afraid of me.
But I am not the way you think.
No, don't be unfair.
You know very well I would
love to spend more time with you.
Yes, to order the little cadet.
Can't you think about something else?
- Don't you like to do things?
- Let go, please!
Sorry, darling, but your neck!
I know what is waiting for me at home.
What is going on?
Hey!
Oh God gratious.
Don't look, you like to look.
- You are such a pervert!
- Come on, walk.
Doing these things in
public is too much, Panta.
Go ahead.
- Good morning. Did you call me?
- Sit down.
I have called you to
remind you the rules...
and your obligation to
respect it. Here is a copy.
Study it again and if you
have questions, ask.
Are you angry with me?
- You even dare to ask!?
After the vulgar show you
offered in the street?
Now I get it. Yes.
It's about yesterday at the pier.
- Don't tell me you're jelous.
- The rules clearly state that...
a hostess is no whore.
And last night you were...
behaving like a comon prostitute.
- The rules...
don't ban going out with a friend, Don Panta.
- One doesn't behave...
like that with a friend. So,
for the good name of the service,...
i would prefer that you don't see
this subject any more. Thank you.
He's not a subject.
His name is Nicol疽 Lobat.
And he wants to marry me.
If that is what you want...
But...
Think very well about it, please.
I have to remind you, that if you mary...
you'll have to go. We can't
take married women here.
He's the one that wants to get married.
I just want a bit of affection...
and protection.
I have that right, don't I?
I suppose so.
Excuse me. I think I've been unfair to you.
Don't worry, I am used to that.
Olga.
You are a very strange person...
I don't understand you.
- You should do something else.
- You too.
This work is not for you, Don Panta.
You don't even dare to taste your
hostesses like any other would do.
Excuse me.
Miss,...
wait.
- Yes?
Do you still want to volunteer...
to do a quality control?
Yes, of course.
I have to inform you that
this test will only be done once.
It's strictly secret and laboral.
I don't want you to get
confused, Miss Olga.
The only motivation for these controls...
- One, Pechuga. -Two, Sandra.
- Three, Iris.
- Four, Lalita.
- Five, Vanesa. -Six, Colombiana.
- Seven, Coca
- Eight, Salom・
- Nine, Pichuza.
- Ten, Peludita.
- Entire and complete, Mr. Pantoja.
- Working day plan?
Three convoys. Two 48-hours-long and
another one coming back tonight.
I did the draw with the sticks,
don Panta.
The first convoy of 3 girls to Puerto
America camp by Morona river.
Rioalto is feeding Dalila so
we can depart immediately
Don't let Chupito
drive.
- She's always screwing up, don Panta.
- 20 soles fine...
to Peludita for talking
without permision.
- What else do we have?
- Convoys 2 and 3 leave at "El Eva".
In number two: Lalita, Vanesa
and La colombiana.
I lead the harness Bolognetti
at Masane river.
The way back journey planned for
thrusday noon, Mr. Pantoja.
Good. Start boarding.
And be good...
like it should be,
and remember...
- Work...
- Ennobles and dignifies.
- And now to work.
- Excuse me, don Panta.
Is there a problem?
No.
No. None at all.
It's just that I got
a little stone in my shoe.
Thanks.
Aren't you coming this time,
don Panta?
- No, I've got things to do here.
- What a shame.
I had thought we could repeat
the quality control test.
Wouldn't you like
to spend the night with me?
We got top results from this test
and they allowed us to collect valuable...
information and first hand. I
thank you for carrying out the test
but it think it's neither necessary
nor convenient to repeat it.
Is there a problem, don Panta?
We're five minutes late.
No, none at all, Chuchupe.
This should never happen again. Your lack
of discretion sets me in a difficult and
akward situation with the rest of the
personnell, which capacity, besides, can...
disminish because they'll
spend the time doing
comments that will take their
mind off their business.
If that's what worries you,
we can go to a hotel...
or to another place
where nobody can see us.
Hello.
Yes.
Pocha, I've told you not to call me
when I'm at work unless...
What? I'm coming right away.
Here are the results
of the analysis.
- Are you sure, Dr.? -Yes, Mr. Pantoja.
Your wife is pregnant.
I didn't want to tell you anything
until being complety possitive.
Finally a Pantita! Finally!
I'm going to be a father!
You're very pensive today, don Panta.
What are you still doing here?
I was the last one taking a shower.
They left without me.
It's weird to see you
without your machine.
- I thought you never stopped
working. - "El Dalila" comes back at 7.
- That means you really are working.
- Mhm.
A cigarette?
No, thanks.
Since the day of the test
we haven't been completely alone, have we?
Are you nervous?
What do you want, Olga?
Nothing special, don Panta.
- I thought you and me...
- You and me... nothing!
I thought it was clear
enough since the beginning.
- Because of work...
- Can't you think of anything else...
- ... besides work?
- No. And even less when I talk to you.
- And now excuse me, I'm
going to work. -No, you stay.
I'm the one who's leaving.
But you know what? It can be
that you as a boss and as a lover...
are just excellent, but as a person
you are unbearable.
I'm not your lover, Miss.
But don't you wish to be, don Panta.
Today we've allowed ourselves
to stop on the way...
to celebrate the perk
number 20 thousand...
and it's lucky Pechuga's turn.
Woo! Woo!
20 thousand perks
for two classes and soldiers...
in our border units...
that all constitutes a humble success
to our service.
Prove that the escort
service has fully made use...
of its operative potential,
as it comes off...
from the descomposition of the total
20 thousand in its constituend humans.
Our goal
for what's left of this year...
is to reach 200
thousand perks,...
an ambitious figure,
but not impossible,...
if the personnel keeps it up
as it has up to now...
mantaining its high
output average and...
with the backups we've
planned to hire soon.
Long live our service!
The boat! Look!
Let don Panta cut the tart!
Oh, beautiful!
Want to dance, don Panta?
Come on!
Are you ok, don Pantita?
I'm not very used to
this kind of reunions.
I think I've drunk too much.
I'm a bit tipsy.
Easy. Just close your eyes. Like this.
Lean.
Everybody changes dancing partners!
- You didn't want to dance with me, Olga.
- Why didn't you ask me to?
All this time you've treated me
as if I was invisible.
Everything's so complicated, Olga.
I don't understand
what's so complicated.
A man likes or not a woman.
And you've demonstrated
you don't like me.
I like you.
I like you very much.
And the truth is I haven't been able to
stop thinking about you ever since...
Well...
Eversince we slept together.
Olga,...
if I could...
Of course you can.
It's just a matter of wanting to.
But not here.
I mean it for you.
I think we are making a scene.
I like you. I like you very much.
- So this is the famous colombian?
- What?
They all got the hots for her.
Look how many stand in her row.
Hey, hey, hey! Where do you think
you're going, you fatso?
- Don't you like this saddle anymore?
- Yes, I like it, Pechuga, but...
I think this one time I'm
riding another mare.
Private, go immediately
back to your row.
My record of service allows me
to fuck the escort I want,...
and I've decided to try
the colombian to see
if she's as good as
they say she is, Sr.
You go in this moment back
to Pechuga's row!
- Miss Colombiana already has
enough users. -Each escort can...
have a maximum of 20 perks.
That's stated in the regulations, Sr.
And with me it'd be...
19.
19 users, Sr.
- Where do you think you're going private?!
- I'm number 20, Sr.
My record of service
allows me this choice. -Sres.
Don't you realize that the
escort has an overload of work?
When your turn comes, she'll
be so tired that her performance...
won't even be 25% as good
as her regular performance.
- I recommend you to go
back to your row. -No.
I don't get tired that easily, don Panta.
Quite the opposite. Every soldier
leaves me more... ardent.
I assure you, the last ones in my row will
be looked after just as the first ones.
If you don't believe me,
stand on my line.
10 perks is what the
regulations order. You don't have...
any obligation to look
after more soldiers. Only 10.
I'm sorry, Olga.
I'm just going crazy.
No... I don't know what's wrong with me.
Your flirting with the troop, I just
can't stand it. It makes my blood boil!
It makes me want to imprison all those
soldiers that look at you as if...
- I don't know, as if you were an escort...
- An escort?
That's what I am.
But it's not your duty to flirt with them.
It's not stated in the regulations.
I just do it to attrack them,
Don Panta.
It's not only a matter of having
good looks. You have to...
You have to know how to sell yourself
and show it to the client with...
smiles and those things
so that he comes to my row.
I don't want to you to do that!
There's no need on doing that.
The system is organized in such a way
that you all have 10 perks guaranteed...
- ... for the basic payment.
- Well, but our profit
is in the special perks.
If I just set for serving you well,
my profit reduces by the half.
What I can accept
is to be relieved from my job.
I don't ask you to retire
because there is a work contract
that you've signed and you have to keep.
Besides, the service estimates
don't suppose that your
performance can be so high.
Is it so hard to understand?
Look, I can explain it to you in
another way. My
it's not supposed that any esc...
We consider it an abusive privilege
that the escort service...
is for your exclusive use.
We demand that citizens...
of age and with a record of service
have the right to use this service.
And the same low fares
soldiers have.
But this service only exists
in your perverted minds, Sres.
How does it occur to you to
go to court for such nonsense?
We've seen it with our
own eyes, Sr.
Your boats come full of women.
We also want women, Sr.
Not only soldiers have necessities.
I haven't got any information
of what you're telling me.
I think you're drinking way too
much "chuchuaye" my friends, uh?
- But General! -Do you think
I'm stupid, mayor Paiva?
- No, General. -If the press knew
about this stupid petition...
your mayoralty wouldn't last long,
Mr. Paiva Rumbu・
And now, out of my face, damn it.
What are you waiting for?!
Damn it, out of here!
What's going on?
Mhm? Do you regret it now?
I feel like a piece of crap
doing this to my wife.
I know.
I had never cheated on her.
They only did it once every two weeks,...
saturdays at 10 pm.
I already know it by heart, Panta.
You've told me a thousand times.
And?
Come on, don't exaggerate
nobody is watching.
Its never unecessary to be
extra careful. You never know.
- Anyone could say you're ashamed
to be seen with me. -You would have to
be nuts to feel ashamed
to be seen with a woman like you.
There is a party on
friday at "La Colcha Verde".
On that very same day I have
a day off. I want to go.
- You could go with Sandra.
She's algo got the day off. -No.
I want to go with you.
I refuse.
You know it's impossible.
I've told you a thousand times
they can't see us together.
You can't deny that some of the
girls are as good as it gets.
You've said it, girls,
only snotted little brats.
No real female that's
worth the shame.
Show me a real woman.
One that leaves you breathless.
- ... that gives you the goose bumps just
by looking at her and that... -That one!
That woman is a big female.
Gotcha, Pantale Pantoja!
You're an idiot!
Come here. You've got to work.
What are you doing?
I'm covering up the "social events" part
from the local newspaper, Mr. Pantoja.
I think we've got enough,
haven't we, Mario?
Mr. Sinche is here to see you, don Panta.
He says he's got a present for you.
Very good, Mr. L疼dano,
what do you want?
I can take care of them, because
I suppose you wouldn't want...
your wife to see it.
It's natural, I understand,
and that's what friends are for.
You know we are no
friends, Mr. L疼dano.
You're wrong, Mr. Pantoja.
If I wasn't your friend your
business would be ruined.
I'm not talking about those pictures
and the negatives I have.
I'm talking about
something bigger, Sr.
I'm talking about Pantiland.
Don't take me wrong, Mr. Pantoja.
You know I'm talking about the
prosperous clandestine business...
you've patiently put together.
I don't know what you're
talking about.
After meticulous research,...
I've got proves that
can make you go under...
and even ruin you.
If I said all I know...
- And why don't you do it? -Because
I'm progressive, Mr. Pantoja.
I'm a 21st century man,
too advanced for my times.
But the whole city makes
pressure on me.
And I think my silence
deserves a little reward.
You are here to blackmail me.
To help you, man. For
some dollars,...
I'm willing to defend
the escort service...
and the brains of the team.
They'll make such a
fuzz about you, Mr. Pantoja.
What do you say?
You don't have to answer right away.
You first sleep on it,...
ask your wife, your lover. Don't
get nervous, man. Calm down.
Caiguas, Rioalto.
What's going on? Arrest them, Pantoja.
Let go of me, damn it!
Throw him into the river.
Nobody blackmails me. ,...
-And if you ever come back...Don't
suicide, don't be stupid!
I'm a superman in Iquitos!
I don't know how to swim!
You'll regreat for this, Pantoja!
There is nothing strong
enough in Iquitos...
that Sinchi's
voice can't tear down!
You've asked for it! This
is war! War!
At 16.00 sharp...
on the clock hanging from the wall
in our studio,...
Radio Amazonas brings
to you proudly...
our dear listeners,...
the most famous program
from our station:...
"Sinchi's voice".
I promised to unmask
this individual with no principles...
who runs this
den of inquity and...
perdition, the so called
"escort service",...
more commonly known
as "Pantiland".
"El Sinchi"...
keeps his promises,
my dear listeners.
We've been doing research,...
auscultated, verified
everything.
And now we're in the position
to reveal the identity...
of this sort of...
sub-human being.
In a short time, he's made possible
to raise right at the doors of our city,...
that source of moral devatio that
has to be kicked out of Iquitos and...
out of the Amazonia together
with his caravan of sluts in auction.
Pantale Pantoja...
that's the name
of this dark character.
Pantale Pantoja, come...
from hell and supported
by powerful and invisible interests...
to fill with embarrasment
your names, ladies and gentlemen.
Hello?
Yes... Yes, my General.
No. No, I haven't heard anything.
What?
Hello? Hello?
Damn it!
Because, indeed, it's
true that Pantale Pantoja...
has a wife and has been
leading a double life...
sank, in one side,
in a foul swamp...
of his affair with Olga Arellano,...
the colombian, as remembered as
beautiful and popular eastern prostitute.
In the other hand, pretending to have
a decent and respectful life...
and that deep ignorance hole
his wife was sank in,...
to whom through this station
we offer...
all our moral support.
And we remind her...
that's it's better to live
enlighted by truth...
than in the darkness
of ignorance.
What does the army have
to do with Pantiland?
Does Pantaleon have the
consent of authorities...
to introduce prostitutes
in the barracks?
Are General Scavino, father Beltr疣,
the mayor, the prefect,...
aware of this lust traffic
and just turn a blind eye?
We, Loreto's people, will
keep investigating...
with the bravery, love
and truth characteristic of us.
You've heard "Sinchi's...
voice".
Devastating, master.
Devastating!
Pocha?
- Pocha, let me explain you.
- There's nothing to explain.
- It's all clear. Out of my way!
- Pochita,...
- ...you can't leave like that.
- Let me go! -Think of the little cadet.
- You are my wife and...
- Forget about me and the little cadet.
- You are a liar, hypocrit! -It's all fault
of that damned work of yours.
Pocha. Pocha, you know
how I am.
Remember when I got in charge
of this regiment's ranch...
that I got very hungry, that
I put on 11 kilos, I learnt how to cook.
Or when I was responsible for
the garrison's uniforms. Remember?
Remember that I got into,
fashion? That I even designed...
new battle pants myself? That the
General thought I was gay?
That's me. Work takes up on me,
it transforms me, I can't help it.
Then keep your whores,
your colombian...
- ...and all that crap!
- Pochita... -Don't touch me!
You disgust me!
Leave me alone!
And I've also been unfaithful...
by word and by thought to
my superior for punishing me.
- I know it's a big mistake...
- 3 Holy Fathers y 10 Ave Mar僘.
Hello?
His Excellency...
No, not me, but...
No, His Excellency.
Yes, His Excellency.
Yes.
Pocha? Please, listen to me.
Let me speak.
I've quitted, Pochita.
I've asked the General.
To relieve me from my charge.
- And what did he say? -Nothing. But
I'm confident he'll let me go.
Secret mission, Intelligence service.
You're a liar, Pantale Pantoja!
Don't you ever call me until
you're completely out of this...
disgusting world you've
got yourself into! Idiot!
Pocha... Pochita...?
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
How are you?
Bad.
What's going to happen now?
Hello, Yes?
Good morning, Pantoja.
General Collazos speaking.
Good morning, my General.
- I read your application
for relocation carefully. -Yes, my General.
I'm surprised by your
less competitive attitude.
You were selected
because of your good qualities...
not only in the administrative
but in the patriotic field.
Remember our glorious
ancestors. Mollesi, Darte, C當eres.
Do you thinik they thought
of giving up right away?
No, sir. The militar who's got the
service feeling in the blood...
turns stronger
at difficult times.
You're a soldier, you can't
give up, Pantoja.
And the way you're serving your country
in these moments is making...
- ...the service work. Do you understand?
- Good morning.
As you wish, my general.
He even authorized to enroll
the 10 escorts that I had requested...
- ...as backups. -See how everyone
is against you?
You should be glad, captain.
And whit this recognition
nobody will be able to stop you.
40 escorts.
Not bad, captain.
I have plenty of enemies, Bacacorzo.
And my wife doesn't want to know about me.
Your wife will understand,
give her some time.
And don't worry about Beltr疣.
You're fucked. From commandant
chaplain you came to be...
the humble parish priest
of Iquitos' cementery.
With your persistence and patience
you'll get rid of all of your enemies.
I'm only worried about
the queer of Sinchi.
- If I were you...
- General Collazos ordered me...
- ...to do him.
- Excellent.
I have a pair of assitants
that will leave him mute forerver.
They really know how to beat up, Capt'n.
Without leaving any traces.
No, Bacacorzo, it's not
about that. It's something worse.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four...
five, six, seven, eight!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight!
Dear Pantale, how are you?
Just a moment, Mr. L疼dano.
Nice sight. Congratulations.
- Beg your pardon? -They told me you
wanted to talk to me, Mr. Pantoja.
Wise choise. People of our rank
can't hurt or confront each other.
- It's a waste of time. -I didn't
bring you here to chat, Mr. L疼dano.
I wanted to give you this.
Please open it and tell
me if it's enough.
Mr. Pantoja, are you trying to
bribe me?
You threw me into the river
because I was trying to blackmail you...
and now you want to pay me
to advertise your brothel?
Not to advertise it.
I don't want you to ever mention...
- ...the escort service. -To tell you
the truth, I don't know, Mr. Pantoja.
"Pantiland" is one of the
most important events...
of the end of the millenium in Iquitos
and in the rest of the world.
I wouldn't be surprised if CNN or
the Time ask for a cronique.
- That'd give me a rating... -Every
first day of the month...
you'll receive the same
amount of money.
We're understanding each other now,
dear friend Pantoja.
But I'm not taking any more
of your time, illustrious friend.
Next month if...
If you want, for free,...
you could do
a special report...
to refute some data...
that I once said about you...
- ...and that surely...
- See you next month.
Don't you want to eat, capt'n?
I'm not hungry.
You have to eat. You've been putting off a
lot of weight eversince your wife left.
Yeah, I've been told so before.
Is there a response
to my last report?
Seen what's been happening
to civilians in rivers, waiting...
for the service's convoys,
I propose we create a system...
of extraordinary regular
rotation.
This system will keep the civilians
from forseeing out arrival,...
which will eliminate their presence
and the difficulties they represent.
In order for it to work out,
100 escorts are necessary...
and 5 ships, to be permanently
navigating...
- ...in amazonian rivers.
- 100 escorts?
- 5 ships?
- That's nothing, Tiger.
Listen to this.
I beg you study the possibility
of giving a risk bonus...
to all those escorts
who depart with the convoy, given that...
by accomplishing their mission,
they risk their lives. Likewise,...
attached to the project,
find pages 25 and 26,...
a social benefits plan
including health insurance,...
compensation for long term
services, and simmilar...
all workers have rights
according to the law.
This is not funny. This Pantoja
affair is starting to worry me.
And now the army has to stop buying
weapons in order to hire whores...
and pay for their social
security.
You're authorized
to carry out your new plan,...
as well as you're not authorized
to hire new escorts.
I don't understand, everything
was perfectly explained.
Do you know what your sin is? Having
made the service the mos efficient...
organ in the army.
That can scare anyone.
It's a long wat to go. Deman
overlaps the offer.
Maybe it's convenient
not to do more request by now.
Let some time pass by.
Take a break.
This is an emergency, tenent.
I'll prepare a more convincing report.
I got the polls, and 172 requests
signed by the subofficials...
asking to be allowed to
use the escort service.
95% of the officers,
claims to have escorts.
And 55% of the higher
rank officers.
In order to be able to give this service,
the regular prestations plan,...
under the minimum limit
of sexual vitality, demands...
4 boats and 271 escorts.
- Sounds reasonable, but... -Would
we have to create a special sector?
Exclusive escorts for officials,
brought from Lima or even from abroad.
Do you like what OS stands for?
Officer Sector.
Sounds good, doesn't it?
- Captain... -Or Officially
Exclusive Service.
Captain.
You're working too much. If you
keep it going like that you'll get sick,...
smoking like a chinese and not eating.
No job deserves...
the sacrifice you're doing.
A couple of days ago all
you thought was quiting,
and now you're almost
dying for the service.
It's my sense of responsibility.
I quited and they made me keep working.
And now I'll do, no matter what, because
of my odd habit of doing everything right.
Because...
Because it's the only way I know.
If everyone thought the way you do, this
country would be the American Switzerland.
I got a 4x4. Let's go for a ride,
you'll calm down.
Thanks for the invitation...
but I have a lot of work to do.
I'm handing my new
project in on monday.
You left almos all
of your clothes, huh?
Or you left too soon,
or you think of going back.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I would have never thought
about buying anything like that.
Is that how decent women sleep?
Looks like a nun's nightie.
Or you like them more like that?
- What's up with you now?
- Don't you know?
- Don't you realize? -Just because I'm
allowing you not to work tomorrow?
It's not only because tomorrow.
I don't want to work.
I want to be with you.
They just rejected my project.
The service is in such an emergency.
I have to finish this report
to convince my bosses,...
and all you do is problems
because you don't want to work.
All I'm saying is the boss's wife
receives special treatment. Always.
But for me,
it's all disadvantages.
You treat me as if I were
one of your whores.
Is that why you are with me?
Because I'm the boss?
What do you think?
I rather don't know.
Fire me, Panta.
Let's this all end
for once and all.
Yes?
Is that what you want?
Good morning,
ladies and gentelmen...
listening this program
sent out of Iquitos...
reaching the most hidden
places...
in our jungle.
Today I want to talk about
don Pantale Pantoja.
- Shut him up.
- No, leave it, I want to hear.
It's normal to correct one's mistakes,
and I'm telling you,...
with my hand on my heart,...
that I misjudged you,
don Panta.
Heck!
Letters never stop coming...
from soldiers and sargents
in our borders...
en cuarteles y
guarniciones inhpitas.
And they say:
"Mister Sinchi,...
why do you insult don Pantale?
We're coming.
Be aware.
Nobody's ever done that.
We're all human, Mr. Sinchi.
We all have necessities.
And thanks to don Panta
we serve our country better".
All that sincerity
made me reflect.
And by exposing Pantale Pantoja,
I didn't take the soldiers into account.
I didn't take into account
don Pantale's mission...
to satisfy...
the most intimate necessities
our Peru's heroes.
Attention, Horcones post.
Escort service approaching.
It'll be 10 minutes by boat.
I repeat. Escort service...
Horcones, we've been robbed!
Pirates, I believe!
Waiting for confirmation! Horcones post,
waiting for confirmation, heck!
Eva is trying to establish communication!
S.O.S.! S.O.S!
Don Panta, that lovely nickname
that's made him famous...
in our wild jungle,...
is an enemy of fame
and recognition.
Open your legs, damn it!
Dear friends,
I have in my hands...
a report from
the National Police.
Do you know how many rapes
take place monthly?
It's worth mentioning, that eversince
don Panta introduced this program...
the escort service.
Zero.
Just as you've heard.
Pucha! The militants!
They're all gay!
Don't leave me!
Fuckers!
Shit!
Don't!
Our Amazona is in peace.
Our mothers, sisters
and girlfriends...
can now go on the street...
fearless.
We Loreto people can be proud
of living in a place,...
..the only place in the
whole world,...
where sexual crimes have
been abolished.
Excitement carries me away.
And all it's left to say,...
in the name of the whole Amazona
and my self,...
thank you, don Panta.
Thank you,...
and your sacrified escort.
Where?
Could you leave for a moment
please?
After being kept vigil over night...
the precious body of Olga
Arellano, a.k.a. Colombiana,...
has arrived to its final
destiny, my friends.
This is your friend Sinchi.
We're now in the cementery...
where a lot of people
have gathered.
Approaches her coffin...
accompanied by a troop...
Rest!
Weapons!
I am resurection and life.
Whoever believes in me,
even when he's dead, will live.
And whoever believes in me
won't die eternally.
Receive, Lord, this sinful woman,
forgive her offenses...
and allow her, Lord,
to rest in peace.
- Let's pray to the Lord.
- We beg you, Lord.
Amen.
Olga Arellano!
We've put on our glorious
uniform from the Peruvian army...
to bring you to your
last resting place.
It's our duty to claim
besides everyone's eyes,...
with a plane sense of responsibility,...
that you fell as every soldier does
when serving his country.
You're a martyr.
A victim of all those who didn't
know you were consagrated to our soldiers.
Loved Olga Arellano,...
the soldiers,...
your soldiers from
the whole Amazona,...
whom you served,...
cry for you.
Your coworkers are also crying.
In their name...
I let you know that
your sacrifice was not in vain,...
and that your blood will
be the engine to keep working...
in the mission the
army entrusted us.
And in my name...
allow me to thank you...
for your affection and understanding,...
for those intimate lessons...
I'll never forget.
Olga Arellano,...
rest in peace.
Attention battalion!
Weapons!
March.
Good morning, my general.
I beg you read this letter.
And after reading it, do the
honours.
In this letter I declare myself responsible
for what happened at the cementery.
And how do you justify yourself, Pantoja?
Thanks to you everybody
is speaking about the escort service.
They were before, Sr. Long
time before Horcones,...
it was of the public domain.
In order to appear
dressed as an official...
to honour a whore
as if it was...
a soldier. Olga
Arellano died serving her country.
Don't be cinical, Pantoja.
I know that whore
was your lover.
You would have done the same
if it had been another escort.
I did so because the army
has to honour their labour.
Which labourr, Pantoja?
Do the soldiers?
Do you really think the army
has to thank those sluts?
It's a hard job.
A rather risky one.
After Olga Arellano's death,
all the others wanted to leave the service.
And I understood we had
to rise their spirits.
Inject them some energy.
And that's why I did the memorial.
So that they'd feel supported...
by this institution and
kept working.
You should have let her go.
Because, happily, the escort
service was cancelled, Pantoja.
Cancelled?
I know I deserve a punishment...
for proceeding without
your permission, but...
cancelling the service?
I don't understand, it's never
been this good.
The soldiers' health reports...
0% of rape crimes prove it.
Forget about the service.
Gone, dead.
That's the good part of
the murdering of that whore.
Well, you have to close the
service today,...
fire the personnel and leave
Iquitos first thing tomorrow morning.
Leave the army, Mr. Pantoja.
Leave the army and stay with us.
We have some capital to invest.
We could even ask the bank for
a loan, if you wish.
And with you being good at this,
we'd turn millionaire right away.
I organized the service following
orders. As a business,...
I'm not interested. You
create a company.
We don't want to set
a leathal bachelor pad.
We want a escort service company.
Big, modern and efficient.
And you'd be our boss.
I need to have a boss.
If I didn't have one,...
I wouldn't know what to do. I'm
made to obey orders.
The militia is my life. And
I want to dye serving the army.
That's something you have
to understand.
What's wrong, Chuchupe?
I've told you not to cry.
Sorry, don Panta, but
I can't help it.
It's the best job
I've ever had.
Why did they close the service?
Soldiers used to get so
happy just by seeing us.
This year's objectives are
being accomplished.
But that's the army.
Bosses know better...
and they consider it wise
to shut down the service.
Change that face, Chuchupe.
Don Pantita, we want you to
keep a good memory of us all.
To the best boss in the world.
Ladies.
Thank you.
I will never forget you.
Sorry to bother you again, but...
Isn't there a confusion?
- I was booked for 6. Are you sure
I have to wait? -Very sure.
The general is being interviewed
but he'll be right with you.
Look, look, it started.
The general is speaking.
Miss, the army has never
organized nor sponsored...
such a company.
- How about the service?
- Of course, Miss.
- Explicitly.
- But we've all seen...
captain Pantoja honouring
a whore.
Moreover, Pantoja himself
has pointed out...
that assasins should
be processed in a military court.
Miss, that's nonsense.
The State ordered meticupous
research...
which will be taken to extreme
consequences if necessary.
So I assure whoever is responsible
for this will get what he deserves.
Well, thanks, general.
Carry on!
You've turned famous.
Could you give me your autograph?
- Do you know who just left?
- The reporter, my general.
I listened to your declarations
in the lobby's TV.
I won't ask you to explain.
I read your letter, I saw you saying
that pathetic speech...
Anyways, you went nuts.
Do you want me to tell you the truth?
There is not punishment severe
enough for what you did.
- Not even executing you would
pay for what you did.
- I'll take all charges.
- Given that this is a serious thing,...
we've thought about
sending you to the discipline council.
Which means you'll be expelled.
But considering your record,
we propose a way out...
a honourable way out.
Quit today. Full period.
I refuse to quit, Sir.
Your carreer is over.
You commited suicide.
Quit. Get yourself
a job.
Your talent is admirable.
Work on the street,
you'll earn more anyways.
Are you crying, Pantoja?
What's wrong?
Behave like a man, heck!
Sorry. I beg you
forgive me, my general.
But I can only be a militar.
It's my life.
And if you make me go...
Do you want to be
captain forever?
The event in Iquitos
will stay in your record.
I'll try to make it up
to you, Sr.
Are you sure you don't
want to quit?
We'll make your life impossible.
You know how this is.
I know, but I'm willing
to take any risk.
My responsibilities kept me
from answering before.
My woman, my 3 month
old daughter, she's so pretty...
and the responsibilities of
my mission,...
are what distract me.
- Besides from being far away...
- ...far away...
I always remember you with
love and respect.
Say hi to do
Leonor and Chupito,...
to Pechuga and the rest
of the escorts,...
I will never forget you.
Hugs...
Pantale Pantoja, captain of
the Peruvian army.
Start again, will you?
She's so pretty.
My dear tenent:...
I'm writing at 4.200 m above
the see level and minus 4 degrees.
General Collazos kept his promise
of sending me to...
loneliest and furthest post.
My mission is to keep
the territorial integrity...
and teaching people to
write and read.
The 1973 census registred
1.784.281 illiterate people,...
and this region has the highest
illeteracy level in the country:...
36,9%. That means,
658.399 illiterate people.
I... love...
I love my... Peru.
According to empiric research, the
individual's lerning process...
of 15 or older, and with an
IQ no lower than 80,...
would take between 6 to
9 months with two hours daily.
See you tomorrow.
Very good, every day better.
To respond to this demand,
I made 8 groups of 15 people,...
which means teaching
120 people.
It's an optimistic scennario, in 6 years
I could teach the entire region.
I keep on serving with
determination and honesty...
our glorious institution.
Panta.
Are you done with
the last group?
No, I'm still wating
for the 6 ・clock one.
But the absences level
is quite high.
And this variable can spoil
my expectations.
I will have to implement a home
visits program.
If there's no work,
you make it up.
- Don't you want to eat? Let's go home.
- I'm coming right away.
- You turned into a human chimeney
after being in the jungle.
- It's because of the
cold weather, Pocha.
- Because of the cold weather. -Well, I'll
wait for you at home. Don't be too late.
Is to try the improve the service.