♪Subtitles: Aage Brock
resync & additions by♪  XQ2☻
All systems good.
Estimated touchdown...
We just lost contact.
... (Russian)
Excuse me please.
♪ Helan goes
tyulahop falalalala
My beer! Hell, fucking shit!?
Dear Denmark. Dear Danes.
In less than 24 hours,
the greatest event in our
history will take place:
Kurt Maj's Saturn Expedition!
The purpose is to find
eco-friendly energy resources
that will benefit people on Earth
and the Danish welfare state.
We transmit live from Cape Kurt.
But let's have a closer look at
the project's creator: Kurt Maj!
Tycoon and media kingpin, Kurt Maj,
is a man of many talents.
Deeply affected by the rapidly
escalating global warming,
Kurt Mej has made it  his personal
cause to fight for the environment.
And now, always the pioneer,
he's on his way to the stars!
You're on in ten minutes, Per.
How's the suit?
Well, it's not as cool as the one
I wore for NASA's Mars Mission.
But then again,
I'm not exactly going
on a 48 hour space walk, am I?
You're so cool, Per.
You and me, Per. Forever!
DANISH UFO ASSOCIATION
ANNUAL CONVENTION
Per! Per! Per! Per!
And now, the man we've
all been waiting for,
Lecturer and real-life astronaut:
Per Jensen!
- When the stars beckon...
- Here we come!
Per! Per! Per! Per!
...that you cannot refuse.
Drop by Earth and let's chat.
I look forward to meeting you.
END PROTOCOL
NAME FILE:
- Mr. Maj, over here!
- Showtime!
Dear Denmark. Dear Danes.
In just a fow hours, Kurt Maj's
Saturn Expedition
will be a reallty.
What has inspired this heroic deed?
Ever since Cape Kurt discovered
limitless resources on Saturn,
I knew that Denmark
would have to
claim exclusive rights to them.
It is therefore of
vital importance
to claim that planet
for Denmark!
Isn't this project
of greater benefit to you,
than Denmark, as such?
Rubbish!
Kurt Maj Enterpsises
has financed
the project as a national gift.
- But...
- Imagine all those riches!
It will be the end of taxes, and
the beginning of greater welfare.
Mr. Maj, we have a problem.
Our navigator has fallen ill.
It seems to be food poisoning.
Caused by this Kurt Maj TV Dinner.
But he's being treated by
the Danish Medical Services,
so all is well.
How will we find a new navigator?
Go over the list once more.
Try to squeeze its tummy.
How many do you want?
The crew could have perished
from lack of oxygen or small pox.
Voila! There you go.
I'll never bathe again.
No, why start now?
CONTRACT
What the hell is this?
Kurt Maj and Denmark need you!
- Say what?
- We need a new navigator.
And you're the man
for the job.
Do you want me to go to Saturn?
- Please follow us.
- It's urgent.
Yes, but... I haven't got
the time just here and now.
I have lots of plans.
Laundry and TV...
Time is running.
I'll have to leave. Goodbye.
What's your problem Jensen?
You're a trained astronaut,
right?
When the stars beckon,
I will be there!
I guess I could serve my country.
Perfect!
We knew we could count on you.
No problem. I'll just call a cab.
I'll meet you out front in ten...
We have some transportation.
But I need to go home first.
Go for it, Per!
I need to cut my toenails.
I need to get that board sanded
before I leave, or...
- Wait...
- Bye, bye.
Welcome aboard, Per.
Let's have a nice chat, now.
This is our command center.
The best brains in the nation
are gathered here.
That computer has been
programmed
to bring you all the way
to Saturn.
So you are just a safety measure.
What are the chances
of a mishap?
Zero percent!
Besides, your commander,
Skrydsbøl,
is a distinguished soldier.
You will not find a more steady man.
You've disgraced the Army.
You've failed us.
You are a failure, Skrydsbøl.
Basra!
THE MISSION COMES FIRST
Arne? Where are you?
- Help me, Arne... Arne
- Gerd! Gerd!
Get away from him, you bastards!
I'm coming, Gerd!
The reading materlals
you asked fer.
Die, you filthy
Al Qaeda combatant!
Skrydsbøl is known to run
a tight ship
on all of his missions.
Arne Skrydsbøl at your service.
If I may be so bold as to say...
You'll make a great team.
I promise you, I will not fail
It needs to be cleared.
Hold on...
Hello?...In the 3rd matrix
of the launch coordinates.
No, in the third...
Well, look at the binary code!
Susanne speaking.
Yes, I heard. They're
looking for a new navigator.
You want me to ..?
I'll be there right away. Yes!
Susanne, welcome aboard.
As always, a sight for sore eyes.
I'm glad you thought of me.
I've always wanted to go on
a space mission.
I'll do my best.
No! Susanne, my sweet...
You know, we can't send you
out there.
- Why you are...
- I'm what?
I'm your technical director.
No, it just won't work.
You brighten up the
premises down here.
We've chosen this guy.
- Per?
- Susanne?
You know him?
- We used to be lovers.
-We went to the Astronaut Academy.
Then you're the perfect team.
Per is, to put it mildly,
not suited
for an expedition
of this magnitude.
Fiddlesticks.
Per is a true man of the people.
Per is a fucking fraud!
The closest he ever got to space
was when we watched Star Wars!
Why do you insist on hiring
the most incompetent idiots
for the expedition?
I hope you know
what the flipping hell
you're doing!
I guess someone's
on the rag today.
Susanne Mortensen, here
Technical Director of Project Saturn.
I need the exam papers from
Space Academy for a Per Jensen.
Yes, right now.
Well, you'll just have to wake
the security guard!
TIME FOR LIFT OFF!!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Our beloved Oueen of Denmark
and the Prince Consort.
Accompanied by our dear
Prime Minister.
Oh la la.
Exquisite taste, Monsieur.
I'd like to stress a point here.
I demand strict discipline.
As representatives of Denmark
we'll be part of history forever.
Please welcome, Arne Skrydsbøl
and two of Denmarks's finest pilots.
And finally,
the experienced astronaut,
Per Jensen.
Here you are, Madam.
Ow, merde!
Hello, beautiful!
Don't just stand there
dawdling, men.
All aboard now!
Hup, hup, hup, hup!
Wait! Do I have time
to take a crap?
Just a teeny-weeny crap?
A proper hello to you! I'm Jamil,
your cook on this trip.
Hi, there. My name is Per
and I'm the new navigator.
Don't worry,
I'll get you to Saturn.
Come here.
A cheese sandwich
with jelly and cress
or a Company Sandwich?
Isn't that a Club Sandwich?
Hey, it's alright.
No, it's important
that I learn.
I flunked the
Danish Citizen Test
but if I work hard
on this trip
and learn to be a real Dane,
they promised me
a second chance.
Then I'll bring my
family up here and
we'll open a classy restaurant.
Look!
HOT DOGS
Howdy ho, space homos!
Yo ho, you two Princesses.
It's hot-ass-mothafuckin party time!
Ole is in charge of supplies.
Here's some high culture
for your Danish Test, Jamil.
SQUIRT IN MY ASS
WITH: WERNER FUCKHAPPY
& HELGA HORNYBITCH
It's German, but,
we do it the same in Denmark.
I'm not sure my
wife would approve.
Come on, man!
Saucy young chicks!
Are those
girls you've been porking?
You son of a dog!
I'll butcher you halal style
and feed you to the rats!
I just want to be
your pork partner!
These are my family photos!
Time out, boys.
Gorm the Old, Harald Bluetooth,
Sweyn Forkbeard, Harald II,
Canute the Great... I'm sorry.
I was way too sensitive.
A real Dane can handle
insults and taunts.
You're absolutely right there,
my little monkey boy.
You fat...
You big, fat bastard.
Right on!
Stand by for lift off.
Man your stations.
Sergeant Skrydsbøl.
Wait a second.
We've got T minus 4 minutes
and 12 to lift off!
It is a clear violation.
You must read it
before lift off.
Is it cleared
according to protocol?
No, but it contains...
It can be contaminated
with anthrax!
But it's about Per. He's...
Brief me when we're airborne.
Now, let's have a bitchin'
awesome heck of a party! Here.
Beer. The favourite soft drink
of the Danes.
Beer is a pacifier, not a satisfier.
Balthazar!
No, Balthazar! Come back here!
10, 9, 8, 7...
Main booster start.
4, 3, 2, 1...
Lift off!
Mon cherie!
Man, this sure is enough
to make your
asshole rock and shake,
ain't it?
Mr. Maj, look over here.
Owr, but really...
ACCESS DENlED
Kurt Maj, look over here. Mr.
Prime Minister,
look at the duck.
Mr. Maj, I seem to have a problem
with protocol 314.
It's a video,
but I can't access it.
And I've never heard of it befere.
Don't trouble your pretty head
with that technical stuff.
But I'm Techical Director, Mr. Maj.
What's the protocol on knocking
before approaching your superior?
- That... yo shod knock flsth?
- Exactly.
If this had been Kabul,
your mother would've had you
back in a body bag.
Look me in the eyes... I knew it!
You've got it.
The look of death.
We've stared death straight
in the eyes.
You never forget your
first time, huh?
The first kill!
Mine was in Belrut '82.
Them were the days.
How many kills have you had?
That is... two... eh,
fifty... ninety!
It's an honour to
have you aboard.
Let's have a real
astronaut chat.
Yes, definitely. I just have to
check some... navigation stuff.
That's right, Per.
The mission comes first!
What a beautiful cow.
Please sit down. (GERMAN)
- Bratwurst?
- So big!
I just love that movie, dude!
Ole has to watch it at least
once a day.
Then little Ole will
come out to play.
And for a dollar,
I'll let you watch.
Aah, pussy, wonderful pussy.
Let's have some pussy...
See what I've made, dude.
A pee bubble!
Made of pee!
Yikes! Get that thing away from me.
It's just like urine squash!
No! My photos!
Ole's invented a
new sport with pee!
I'll be damned...
Be quiet!
Yuck, shame on you!
That's what comes from
having such a...
WOG aboard this craft. Yuck!
I expect discipline on this mission!
In the Gulf, we didn't have any
of this stinking
monkey business!
HOT DOGS
They're almost there.
All hands on deck!
ETA on Saturn
in T minus 15 minutes.
Ready for landing?
Say, what are you doing?
I'm ready to put on my helmet
in case of...
acute decompression symptoms?
Of course! Why didn't
I think of that?
Good point, Per.
Touchdown. Welcome to Saturn.
Good! Form formation:
"The Capture of Saturn".
All hands!
I hereby raise this flag
as a symbol
of the Danish
colonization of Saturn.
For King, Country...
No, for God,
King, and Country.
Yes, I'm ready.
♪ God save our gracious King...
No, dammit!
♪ And hero is Denmark, and hero
♪ is Denmark, olé, olé, olé.
This is a clear breach
of the chain of command!
Turn that thing off!
From the top!
♪ Hey ho, here we go,
♪ d'ya want Ole's cock you filthy ho?
And Ole... Ole...
Don't worry. It's under control.
Give me your wristwatches.
We, the White Gods,
bring you gifts
as a token of our
good intentions.
Obey us,
or we'll use our fire sticks!
They don't like you
shouting at them.
Fiddlesticks!
Primitive civilizations
need to know who's in charge.
- Hear, hear!
- They don't seem primitive.
We come from a highly developed
country called Denmark.
We want to use your
natural resources
for our high
technologlcal machinery.
We'll teach you about
democracy and
freedom of speech.
As a little bonus!
See how he turned hostile when
I mentioned freedom of speech?
It's the way you say it.
Draw your weapons!
Let's see how they like
good old-fashioned brute force!
- Bad idea!
- Basra!
Dang it! Ouch!
I don't believe it.
My trigger finger!
Shit!
The closest planet
we could find
is in the Solaris cloud,
just 12 years...
Get to the point!
What is the size of
its water supply?
- Two percent.
- Two percent?
But we have sucked dry,
all the other planets
in the galaxy.
You idiot!
2% will not even keep
the army going for a week!
Bon appetit.
Beloved Dictator,
we have captured
this gang of aliens.
We demand to be treated
in accordance with
the Geneva Convention...
...our military rights.
Insert the translators now!
Let me go, you terrosist bastard.
This is utterly...
They don't have an orifice
in their back
for the translators.
They must have an incredibly
primitive DNA structure.
Hey, wait! There's an
orifice further down.
Roll in the machinery.
Oh, yes! A little more
to the left, please.
Tell me where you come from.
Just state your name,
rank and home port.
Arne Skrydsbøl, Navy sergeant,
Planet Earth.
What business
have you on Saturn?
Arne Skrydsbøl,
Navy sergeant, Earth.
Are the translators
fitted right?
Fuck, that hurt!
It should work perfectly.
Take them away.
Bring them back when
it's time for dinner.
You two, come with me.
Hopelessly outdated.
What's he saying?
I've kept an eye on you since my
first test probes
reached Saturn.
I know that water is
of vital importance to you
yet you have
problems procuring it.
Allow me to present,
Planet Earth.
Earth, known as the Blue Planet.
78% of it is covered in water...
just waiting to be sucked up.
This is an offer
you cannot refuse.
Drop by Earth, and
we'll discuss this.
I look forward to meeting you.
Strip this sorry
craft of everything,
and then prepare my spaceship.
Where the hell are they?
They went out
to stretch their legs.
They should have
been back by now.
Hey, that might be them!
What?
Oopsy daisy!
There goes all of our communication!
I won't stand for
that tone of voice.
Accidents do happen, you know.
It'll take days to
re-establish connections.
That was our only server.
Annoying, isn't it?
Well, I'm sure
you'll figure it out.
Come here.
We have a pretty gift for you.
Gu ga gu ga gu ga.
Well, horrible testicle torture
is an unavoidable aspect
of our business.
Look at it
as an occupational hazard.
That makes it all easier.
Cheers, Ole.
My last one!
It should join the rest
of the Brewsky family
in my belly.
I'm like a beautiful flower.
I need a beer or I'll wither away.
I'm withering away!
What are you doing?
I think our prison cell
is made of
frozen metallic gas.
It has crystallized
and appears hard
but vaporizes if
exposed to alcohol.
How the hell did you know?
I have a doctorate
in nuclear physics.
Any monkey can claim that.
Let's rock'n'roll, boys!
Halt! Prison break!
Basra!
Great teamwork.
Let's go! Hup, hup, hup.
They're getting ready
for something.
Yeah, but what?
Look! Our spaceship.
And there's the boss dude.
Saturn Force One, departure!
Destination: Planet Earth.
Earth?
Operation Suck Earth Dry.
Proceed to hut 3 and
await the Dictator's signal.
- Suck Earth Dry?
- Sounds kinky!
The Dictator is on his way
to Earth
to launch an invasion.
I knew it was a rogue state!
Look at that giant
vacuum cleaner.
If he reaches Earth
and transmits the signal,
it would mean...
The End of the World!
We'll put an end to that.
Move over, boys!
Time for some boobs and beer.
I found this in the Earthlings' craft.
Some outmoded audio-visual media
based on electromagnetic current.
You're so good, Hans!
I'm so horny! (GER.)
Seems to be an instruction
manual on Earth customs.
Interesting.
Ow! Fucking shit!
Then there's a slight increase.
You hold it in for ten minutes.
Saturn mission to Cape Kurt,
come in.
Per, let's get'er in the air
so we can eliminate that UFO.
I haven't had much
practice with this model,
I'm used to the Apollo type.
You and I have the look of death.
Remember that.
Always nice to have
a clear view.
Right?
Per, hurry up!
HANDBRAKE
Tilt, Per! Tilt!
What's the matter with you, kid?
Don't worry.
I'll take it from here.
I flew the Hercules planes
when we carpet-bombed Belgrade.
Post-traumatic stress disorder
is quite common
after dangerous missions.
Ow! Old fucking plece of shit!
Yes! Come on. Expedition...
Expedition, Cape Kurt calling.
Can you hear me?
- Hello.
- Per, is that you?
This is George from
the Short wave Radio Club.
Any kinky girls on line?
Hello? Hello...
Ole has totally freaked out.
Enemy in sight!
The Earthlings' spacecraft!
It's gaining on us.
Let them come.
Fire! And not just a
warning shot either.
Just throw it right at them.
They're gone.
- Contact! Per, eliminate them.
- What?
Let me have a shot at it.
You know dog fights too,
Mr. 9/11?
No, three years in the
Accommodation Centre.
PlayStation, see?
Way to go, Jamil. Bull's eye!
The UFO seems to be unharmed.
They don't stand a chance
against our deflector shield.
Give me an estimate
of the steering system
of their pathetic vessel.
A black hole.
It's sucking us in!
Arne, turn the wheel!
Way to go, Arne!
Red alert!
Take over.
I'll check the air lock.
Red alert! Red alert!
CONFIDENTIAL
Per, would you please come with me?
Just activate the jet pack,
scoot over to the UFO and
attach the explosives.
Have you gone mad, man?
Don't worry, Per.
This should be a piece of cake
for a seasoned astronaut like you.
Wait! I'm not an astronaut.
I've never been to space before.
I don't know how to ride
a jet pack!
I've known that
from the moment I saw you.
Arne Skrydsbøl has a keen eye.
You smell like a con man.
Arne, I can explain it all...
No, you cannot!
Know... who sailed Olfert Fischer?
An ole fart?
Hello?
Shot them...
call it friendly fire.
Can you hear me?
Arne, this is dangerous!
You've endangered the mission.
What with your lies
and fake exam papers.
Wait! I lied for a reason.
It had better be a good reason.
I lied because I was in love.
I see.
That's the worst excuse ever!
Have you never been in love,
Arne?
I was close to my pup,
Dick Cheney.
But I shot it
when it ate my medals!
I'm talking about
real love, Arne.
Have you never been so
madly in love
that it hurts, just to see her?
That's how I felt about Susanne.
She'd just been accepted
into the Academy.
I thought,
I'll be an astronaut, too,
just to be close to her.
But I flunked all the tests.
Get to the point, or
I'll shoot you in the head,
like little Dick Cheney.
So I started cheating
to impress her.
Yes, I tampered with
my exam papers.
No Dane with any kind of
space-slash-military training
is fooled by a con.
Yes. She was mad about me,
and everything was just great.
Then she found out I'd cheated
and went totally ballistlc.
She said I was a disgrace
to the space program.
She never understood.
I didn't give a fuck
about the space program.
I just wanted to be with her.
You activate the bomb
on the red button.
No!
Oh, no!
- Where's Per?
- There.
It's always nice to have
a clear view,
right, Per?
Activate the jet pack, you idiot!
Hell, bloody!
- Oh. no.
- No more games.
What kind of abomination is this?
Some sort of advanced
remote control.
They've taken over
our control system.
What the fuck are you up to?
Goodbye.
Get us outta here!
Typical!
Per!
You are a trained astronaut,
right?
We'll be a part of history forever.
You're so cool, Per!
You smell like a con man.
Per is a genuine
man of the people.
Per is a fucking fraud!
Susanne!
Susanne... no!
Per! Oh, no, it's all my fault.
Bloody hell!
The autopilot is down
with a fatal error.
This is a crisis situation.
We'll never make it back to Earth.
What happened to Per?
He was sucked into
the black hole.
We have to go in after him.
A suiclde mission?
You'd like that!
We have to try.
Arne, where are you?
Arne, for fuck's sake!
The mission always comes first!
Per failed us. I can do nothing!
What the hell is wrong now?
We've run out of gas.
Well, you'll have it your way then.
Beloved Dictator, we're
entering the Earth's atmosphere.
He was right.
They've got enough water to keep
the fleet running for 20 years.
Send the co-ordinates
to the invasion force.
I don't know what to say,
but I think
something has gone
terribly wrong.
What's going on?
Someone is entering
the atmosphere.
Oh, no!
Six. One, two, three, four... Oh, no.
Oops, Mr. Prime Minister,
this is going to be expensive.
We'll just cut back on
senior citizen care, again this year.
- Mr. Maj.
- Susanne. What an entrance!
Our spaceship is lost,
and an unidentified vessel
is approaching.
I think it's hostile.
The Danish People's Party protest.
There comes a time when you as a
citizen of this peaceful nation,
are forced to perform that
noble defence mechanism,
which we, over the generations
have proudly resorted to,
again and again,
and proven that we master it
to perfection:
Total subjection!
What?
We're talking about cool cash here.
Imagine the export rights and
exchange of sustainable
technology.
Your re-election is
ensured because you
can lower taxes AND
preserve Welfare.
You can't just do that!
Leave this to the men, now.
OK, you sweet little thing?
I think we've
passed through it.
Never underestimate
Danish design.
The atmosphere is compatible.
We're really out
in the sticks, huh?
We have to survey the area
and find fuel,
if Denmark is to be saved.
Look! A light.
DENMARK HAS VISITORS FROM SPACE
Cheers!
D.U.F.O. BIDS YOU WELCOME
I'm so horny. (GERMAN)
We want to take all your girls
and squirt in their assholes.
Give me your big cock.
Ach, ja! Ach, ja!
Dear Danes!
Let's welcome our new allies.
These fascinating beings
have come to
negotiate the future
export of goods.
Of all nations on
Earth they chose us.
Because Danish goods
are the best!
If we enter into this agreement,
then early retirement
is guaranteed
for all coming generations.
That's not true!
The aliens are hostile.
They've murdered our astronauts!
Well, as soon as someone takes
a splendid initiative
to create prosperity,
the leftwinged,
paranoid eco-freaks
crawl out of their
filthy wood works.
Some people will
always be naysayers,
when it comes to progress,
but real Danes will agree that
those who try to slow progress
are traitors!
- You fucking communist!
- Filthy bitch!
But where is
the Saturn Expedition then?
Traitor!
Welcome to Earth.
Prepare a translator.
Attention! This looks like
a cultural leftist
art installation.
Hey, there's doorbell.
OUR FATHER & SONS
I'm Saint Peter,
and I can smell your earthly
vessels from in here.
No time to chat, Santa Claus.
We're on a mission and
have run out of gas.
Gas? I don't know
anything about that.
But... come on in and ask.
HEAVEN
Just make your inquiry
at the counter over yonder.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
So, take off your boots,
don't drag your dust in here.
We need gas. I demand to
talk to your superior.
It's him.
Hey, what's up, guys?
Want a guided tour of the garden?
I'm willing to help you
suck up all the water from Earth.
The oceans, the ground water,
the whole shebang.
And what do you expect
in return?
I want the island
of Greenland.
The Kurt Maj Drink is top notch.
It's made from pure
Greenland ice.
The Kurt Maj Drink,
the only water.
$ 399 a bottle.
When you've sucked up
all the water,
it'll be more valuable
than gold.
People have to drink
Kurt Maj Drink.
I already extracted
large quantities
and stored it at
different spots
all over the world.
Have a Kurt Maj Drink!
You can't do that!
Kill her.
CATALOGUE OF SINS
Excuse me, are you Jesus?
No, man. I'm Stand-in-Jesus.
My older brother is on Earth
trying to make a comeback.
The old man is
making an effort to
get the business booming again.
We haven't had much following
these days.
Disgusting!
Sexually deviant mutants
with wings.
LIES
ADULTERY
TAX FRAUD
Yes! Alright!
BEER, PUSSY & HORN MISIC
Hell changed its
marketing strategy
from eternal
punishment and misery.
Now their slogan is:
"beer, pussy & horn music"
How can you compete with that?
Let me go, you
disgusting cockatoo!
- Look!
- Let go of me, for fuck's sake!
I haven't got the
time to be dead.
Hey, Per.
I never thought
I'd see you again.
Where have you been, Per?
Little Per, my friend.
It's worse than
the IRS up here.
I told them I had to return, but
they asked for a load of papers
- Oh, no. You're not dead are you?
- No.
What about the UFO?
Well, it got away, didn't it?
Let's just find some gas and
blow this hippie commune.
We don't have stuff
like that up here.
The whole place is wind-powered.
God Almighty!
You must help us save Earth.
Earth?
But that's our entire clientele.
Say, the Holy Ghost might
be able to help you.
What do we need that for?
Ouch, you filthy little creep!
They're flying vermin.
Easy now. Trust me.
ANGEL PUSSY
Unfortunately,
these guys have to return.
- Good luck with it all, then.
- Likewise.
Where do you think
you're going?
What do you mean?
Our policy is strict:
Once you've died and gone
to Heaven, that's it!
I'm not even a
member of the Church.
What the hell?
Fuck off, you fucking parasite!
Where's it going? Come back.
Filthy shit bird.
It's a gas station! Right on!
- Look. They sell Danish beer.
- Beer?
Brewsky!
Yes!
Well, Arne. It's fllled up.
And so what?
We have no autopilot,
and our navigator is an impostor!
Right on!
This beer's heavy.
Per's never here
for manual labour!
Aviation deck, check.
Flaps, check.
Engine burst, check.
We're ready for lift-off.
I found the manual.
Just push start,
and we're headed
right for Earth.
Well, let's go then, Per.
Alright, when the stars beckon,
here we fucking come.
We're flying at 20 times
normal speed.
Do we need these
translators anymore?
I'm so sore in my butt.
It might contain info about the enemy.
Keep it up there, and you'll pass
the Dane test, next time.
Well, boys. we're almost home.
Hello. - Susanne?
- Per, is that you?
I thought you were dead.
How did you find your way back?
Per handled that.
He turned out to be
an outstanding navigator.
Susanne, has the UFO arrived?
Yes, but I've...
The invasion fleet
is on its way.
The invasion fleet?
Did the dictator
bring a remote control?
Of course!
The dictator uses the remote control
to log into the operative system
of other spacecrafts
and control them.
If you could get hold of it,
we may be able to stop
the entire UFO fleet.
Okay. I'll do my best.
We'll come as fast as we can.
So this is where you're hiding,
On an intergalactic date.
- How sweet.
- Leave her alone!
When the stars beckon, then
big, bad Per is on his way!
Why do you think I picked
a bunch of losers and a
burned-out soldier?
You're good for nothing,
and that made you
perfect for my little mission.
Wish I had time to chat, but
I've got a planet to suck dry.
Say goodbye to Susanne now.
I thought you'd
done away with them.
They don't know
what they're in for.
Put the pedal to the metal.
Let's go!
Where did that come from?
We're dead meat, boys.
We'll hit the moon. Shit!
This is gonna be one tough
crash landing!
Oh, no. The invasion fleet.
Why did I join this
shitty mission?
I'll never see my
dear family again.
I've lost everything
for fucking Denemarci!
Sandwiches, beer
and crappy soccer!
You can't even beat the Swedes!
And silly proverbs!
Who the hell lives in
a house of glass?
And who wants one bird
in the hand?
It's a shitty nation!
I have to speak to my God.
Where the heck is Mecca?
Just face Earth.
That should do it.
Git yer goddam hands in the air
you Taliban motherfucker! (ENG)
This is the perfect place to erect
your water exploitation machine.
You can't just take
the water on Earth.
It belongs to all of us.
You get the Kurt Maj Drink,
instead.
But ordinary people
can't afford it.
Then they'd better start saving up.
A strong signal on our radars
seems to indicate more
incoming UFOs.
It's almost an army.
So many to build that machine?
My soldiers won't build anything.
We'll have slaves do the work!
Let's just do the fat one first. (ENG)
Never point a thing like that
at other people.
It's fucking dangerous.
European peace lovin' pussy!
You don't move bitch,
or I'll bust a cap in your white ass!
Tyrone, maybe we should
contact those boys in the UN!
Who the fuck cares!
They's trespassin' on my Moon
They brought a desert-nigger too,
let's just waste'em
Hold it right there!
We're on our way to Earth
to stop an alien invasion.
We don't have time for
your foolishness.
That ain't no European peace lover,
he's one of us, a red blooded Republican
Now, what's that about alien
bitches taking over the earth?
Work is progressing
at a steady pace.
We expect to be ready
in 24 hours.
You have 12.
Danes can't work any faster.
Their work ethic has
deteriorated
from decades of being
public employees.
Wrong answer.
You're in charge now.
You've got 12 hours, understood?
Start the countdown!
Hey, kabob.
This is our secret space program
called 'Nucular' Emergency Manoeuver
Or Nukem for short. Check it out.
Now, where's that Denmark place?
There we go!
Hey, let the grown-ups have a look.
Hornbæk Beach. High society tits!
We can nuke anything from up here.
See those two white-ass bitches?
What's that?
It's the countdown for
the end of the world.
Susanne!
Someone ran off
with your girl.
Treachery on the home-front.
She's been taken hostage!
At least the problem is solved.
We'll nuke the platform and be heroes.
We can't!
Susanne is down there.
Let me tell you
something, Per!
I've only had one true friend,
Gerd, my second in command.
During a mission in Basra
he was caught in enemy crossfire.
I could either
complete the mission
or save Gerd. I chose Gerd.
If Gerd died, I wouldn't have
anyone left in my life. Nobody!
It didn't work.
The mission went totally awry.
Arne!
Gerd was killed. 60 bullets.
I was demoted from colonel
to sergeant.
I'd forgotten the
most important rule
in the army:
The mission comes first.
But this is my chance
to make it right!
That's not right, Arne.
You went through the black
hole to save me.
It wasn't quite like that.
I get your point
about not nuking anybody,
but how can we stop them?
Kurt Maj had a point.
We are just a bunch of losers.
We didn't get this far
just to end up nuking
hundreds of innocent people.
Did we at any time have
the odds in our favour?
Would a bunch of losers
have survived
everything we've been through?
We aren't losers. We're astronauts.
We represent Denmark
in the entire universe
and Denmark doesn't nuke
innocent people
just to serve a greater cause.
I suggest we put it to a vote.
Danish democracy is the thing!
All in favour of saving Denmark
in a humane way.
- Hear, hear!
- Utter foolishness!
Per, do we have a plan?
No. But I know
someone who might.
RACE OF TERRORISTS FROM SATURN?
ALIENS DO ExIST
Mom! I was supposed to go
with the others to see the aliens.
I think you have some visitors, Ib.
Coffee's served.
Why did we let ourselves
be fooled?
What are we going to do?
Let me see.
All aliens are prone to
be eliminated by
some Earth stuff.
They may get the flu and die.
Or mosquito spray,
shampoo, or cooties.
DUFO has taped everything on
the aliens since they arrived.
We've only got
an hour and a half left.
Wait! Rewind a bit.
There. Pause!
- Slow forward.
- How about a beer?
- Why, it's beer!
- Of course!
Yo, have a beer!
They're back!
Per!
We've got her,
they won't touch us.
Keep them out of
the control room.
Lead them onto the upper deck.
- But how?
- Just do it. Now!
The suction machine!
We have to stop it.
Come on, Arne!
Where is the control room?
Over here, boys.
You! Get all these people
as far away as possible.
- Stop your griping, Susanne.
- Susanne!
Let's split up.
Arne, Ole, stop the engine.
Jamil, come with me.
You stay here and fix that door.
Come and get me
you oversized lizard!
Susanne!
Take that!
- Only ten minutes left!
- Yo!
Per! I'm coming!
Jamil...
Jamil, no!
- Jamil...
- I can't feel my legs. Cold...
Don't die! You have to
become a real Dane.
We'll visit the landmarks.
I'll introduce you
to 'Ida Davidsen' and
let you taste her
open-faced sandwiches.
Per, you need to be a father
to my kids.
Jamil Junior and Jamilla.
Promise to talk to
my wifo, Nadja,
cousin Ali, uncle Nadim
and Dina.
My cousin and her children,
Hakim and Yassir
and their wives
and Mohammad, my other cousin...
Right, right, all of them.
Wait, I have more
pictures here.
"There is a lovely land..."
It didn't penetrate you.
Your photos stopped the bullet!
You made it!
Hey, greenhorn. Skol!
Right on, Susanne!
Let's get out of here.
We have to stop that suction machine.
What the hell does it say?
You have to mount
a translator.
You can borrow mine.
Fine, just hurry up.
Ha!
Billy Bob, keep an eye on
our Danish friends.
Holy monkeys, there's the sign!
Let's nuke'em!
Yeeeha!
That's a helluva titty twister!
What are you up to?
A nuclear missile
is on its way.
We just need to
get out of here.
Susanne and Ole
are still up there!
The mission comes first.
That's the way it is.
That sounds just about right.
You could've told me
where it went.
ON/OFF
Why couldn't you have read it?
- Susanne!
- Per!
You were so good up there!
Why didn't you just
come right out and say it?
- Susanne.
- I thought you were a lame smartass.
Susanne, not now!
There's a nuclear missile
on its way.
Basra!
Arne?
I told you I only had one
true friend.
I see now that's not true.
I've gained two new friends.
Sometimes, friends come
before the mission.
Alright, three friends then.
Run, dammit, run!
- Arne!
- You shall not pass, you bastard!
Arne!
We can't get away. He's too heavy.
Jamil, the gun!
Bottoms up!
- Right on, man!
- Yeehaw!
Hurry up! The missile is coming.
Yeehaw!
Fools! I have thousands of
UFOs left in the universe.
Did you really think
it would be that easy
to beat me?
Scheisse! (GER. Shit)
Would a desert princess like you
wanna see the palm rise
at Ole's oasis?
Bloody hell, Ole!
Remember, respect for traditions.
That doesn't count when we're
talking about my cousin.
Do you really understand Danish
if you use one of these?
Where will we spend
our honeymoon?
We could begin
with the Milky Way.
After that,
we'll just follow the stars.
SUSANNE HAS GOT A TIGHT PUSSY
I sensed that something
was not right
with the strangers.
So I decided to isolate them
at my oil field
and exterminate them.
It was a tough battle,
but my plan worked.
I had them exterminated.
And now, Kurt Maj Enterpsises
has always been very keen on
getting cheap,
alternative energy resources
for the Danes.
So let me introduce
my latest project:
The Journey to the Sun!
What the hell?
They haven't been true to
the comic at all!
♪Subtitles: Aage Brock
resync & additions by♪  XQ2☻