The best superhero
crime fighter on the planet
is Mr. Spandex Avenger.
Ooh, cute tights. Oh, my gosh.
I totally have the same pair.
Mr. Spandex Avenger isn't
as tough as my robot.
Your robot has
an ice cream tub head.
Aren't those the lights
from Dad's bike?
Yeah, yeah. You watch.
My robot's gonna win the gold
medal at the Robot Olympics.
Sorry, I'm late.
The group project presentation
is due today:
Wall walking.
Let's see it.
- You didn't work on your group project?
- I wanted to.
But Alex wouldn't
take time from Dean.
I like that Dean.
Very nice boy.
Thank you, Dad.
Besides, I made time.
- You were building a friend.
- I have friends.
And they're all
building robots, too.
Hey, we just doubled
our clique. Sweet.
- Max?
- Dad, can't talk now.
Look, working together as a team
is extremely important.
We'll practice wall walking now.
Alex, Justin, grab your wands,
and stand on
either side of Max.
All right. Now,
say "havity no gravity."
Havity no gravity.
OK, Max.
Walk up the wall.
Oh! Hey!
There's my emergency hamburger
on the top shelf.
- Alex, Justin, concentrate.
- Dean texted me back!
Your phone's interfering
with my robot.
- Come on, don't...
- Whoa!
...lose your concentration.
Max, are you OK?
Nope! This is an emergency!
And I can fix it
with my emergency burger.
Sync by fant0m
www.addic7ed.com
Yo, Russo.
How about a root beer?
No thanks, I'm working.
No, I mean how about
some more root beer?
I'm not thirsty.
I was trying to
get you to come over there
so I could ask you if you'd like
to go roller skating Friday night.
You mean like on a date?
Our first date?
You want it
to be our first date?
No, first dates are sappy.
But we have to go
on a first date sometime.
Not if we call this fun little
exchange our first date.
It was fun.
I had a great time.
Thanks for walking me home.
So I hear you and Dean are going
out on a date Friday night.
How did you possibly hear that?
He just asked me a minute ago.
My robot's got hyper-hearing.
I'm tapped into his signal.
Harper and I have
been testing it out.
Well, your robot heard right.
Dean and I are going skating.
Well, you'd better be careful with
that one because Dean has a reputation.
He is dangerous! He has a key
chain with a bottle opener on it!
He even uses it
on twist-offs!
No, a reputation with girls. There's a corner
of the roller rink known as Dean's Corner.
Where he takes
girls to kiss them.
That's true, Alex!
He's a kisser!
Change channel!
I don't know, Alex! With Dean's
reputation, I'd be nervous!
Oh, would you!
My goodness, Harper!
People make that stuff up.
The point is I like him a lot
- and I'm gonna go skating with him.
- Hey, Alex, good news.
Two couples are gonna
come roller skating with us:
Joey and Kate and that
Zeke guy really wants to come.
So I'm thinking
we should find him a date.
- Maybe you could talk to your
friend Harper. - I'm right here.
- I'm her friend Harper.
- Oh! Nice to meet you.
You're not as weird
as everyone says.
Thank you. You are as scary
Thank you!
Great, so we're all going
to the roller rink.
A group date? I thought this
was gonna be an alone thing.
- What am I, 15?
- Yeah, Alex. You are 15.
Would you just
let me be mad?
Alex, I just got off the phone
with your math teacher.
- You haven't turned in the last three assignments?
- Really?
That's the first
I've heard of this.
First you've heard
of the assignments?
No, the first I've heard
I'm in math.
Do your homework.
Fine. I need your help
with something.
I'm not doing
your math homework.
No, no. It's about
my first alone date with Dean.
It's gone from awosome to a
six-some. It's totally wrecked.
Oh, yeah! That happened
to me when I was your age.
- But I eliminated the other couples.
- Really? How? What did you do?
Well, I challenged the girls
to a breakdance competition.
You should be good, beat them
and humiliate them into not going.
Always start with
the popping and the locking...
...before you go
into the ground work.
- Like this.
- OK. Wow!
That's good, Mom.
I'll definitely do that.
Oh! I think something popped
and something locked.
Yeah, Kate. I know you had your
heart set on going skating,
but I hear Tears of Blood
arplayinan impromptu concert
in the park
this Friday night.
T.O.B. playing?
Their drummer recovered?
No! I'm trying to
get rid of people
so I can go on my
alone date with Dean.
Yep, they're
totally playing.
I know they're your favorite
band. That's why I'm telling you.
- They're my favorite band, too. Ask if I can go.
- Stop it!
Um, so, um, we'll miss you
at the roller rink.
OK, bye!
OK. One couple down,
one to go.
- And try to keep up.
- I'm keeping up.
I'm gonna go call
the ticket broker right now.
There is no... He why
don't you give me the money.
I'll get you some tickets.
I can't believe it!
Somebody's been robbing delis
in alphabetical order.
They're calling him
"The Alphabetical Order
Deli Robber."
- What?
- Yeah.
He started with the Aardvark
Café, then he hit the Banana Hut,
and he's worked his way up
to the Umbrella Stand.
- Umbrella Stand Deli?
- It's food you can eat in the rain.
- Oh.
- According to this article,
the robber's been stealing
money out of tip jars.
So what? You don't
give us the tips anyway, Dad.
And you know half that money's
'cause of these dimples right here.
Oh, well, he's also
taking all the cupcakes.
Cupcakes?
What a messed up world!
- What are the cops doing about it?
- Nothing.
I ess they're too busy with criminals
who steal big things like cars and jewels.
Are you kidding me?
I haven't used a car
or a jewel in years,
but I eat a cupcake
every morning.
Yeah, that's why your dentist sends
me a Christmas gift every year.
Wait a minute.
If the Deli Robber just robbed
the Umbrella Stand Deli,
then that would mean...
♪ A B C D E F G
H I J K L M N O P ♪
♪ Q R S T U... ♪ V!
The Viking Deli
is probably next.
- That's just down the block!
- Yes, it is, Maxy.
And after the Viking Deli,
then...
♪ A B C D E F G
H I J K L M N O P ♪
♪ Q R S T U V... ♪
W! Waverly Sub Station!
That's us!
Oh, boy, if only The Spandex Avenger
were real, he could stop the Deli Robber.
Introducing...
...Maximan!
Uh... Max,
what's with the costume?
I'm not Max. I'm...
Maximan!
Defender of the
New York delis.
Dad told me the Deli Robber
just robbed the Viking Deli.
And if I'm not mistaken,
W's next.
I'm not mistaken, am I?
About the alphabet? No.
About everything else going on?
Absolutely.
Hey, Max, I heard you're working
on the alphabet. Good for you.
Dad, never mind about the alphabet.
What I need to learn is a spell.
Something that would
tie someone up. Like shoes.
Like a person-sized shoe
that robs delis.
I got just the thing.
Here. Toss that rope
in my direction,
and say "soap on a rope,
soap fell off a rope,
rope shot out of my hand,
rope tie up that man."
Great. Simple.
Soap on a rope,
soap fell off the rope,
rope shot out of my hand,
rope tie up that man.
- It didn't work.
- That's because you need two other wizards to help you.
- Do you know what you need to do now, Max?
- Yeah.
I need to learn a spell
that makes two other wizards.
Alex, I know I'm your best friend and all,
but there's no way I'm going to Skate Barn.
I hate that big skating
chicken they have.
It's OK, Harper.
I'm not making you go.
Oh, my gosh, thank you, Alex.
You're such a good friend.
Yeah, you're totally not getting
why I'm not making you go.
Oh, I know why.
You want to be alone with Dean.
But I don't think
that's a good idea.
Don't forget about the corner
where he makes his move.
And I'm not talking
about the spinning fly-bys.
Harper, that's just a rumor.
It's not true.
Hey, Russo.
Hey, what's-her-face.
I've got a nickname.
I'm thinking tonight I'll meet you at the
roller rink in that corner by the lockers.
Oh, the corner.
All right.
Alex, hold this.
That's "Dean's Corner."
Harper, there's no
such thing as Dean's Corner.
It's purely coincidence that he
asked me to meet him in a corner.
He asked me to meet him
in the corner.
Mum, I took your advice and I managed
to get rid off of all the other couples,
so now it's
just me and Dean.
Ooh! Which pop
and lock moves did you use?
The thing is now Dean wants to
meet me in his kissing corner.
Oh, Alex,
I'm very disappointed in you.
But I don't want to kiss him.
I mean, I really like him.
It's just I don't want to be like all
those other girls. What should I do?
Well, honey, this is
what you need to remember:
If a boy really likes you,
he'll like you for who you are.
And I think who you are
is a very beautiful girl
who, you know, can sometimes
be a little scary, you know.
And a little devious
and sometimes very sneaky.
And would it kill you to clean
a dish from time to time?
Mom! Mom, please
stay on the subject!
This is about me going
on a date, but not kissing.
Kissing? What's this
I hear about kissing?
- Who are you kissing?
- Dad, I'm not kissing anyone.
- I'm gonna go on my date with Dean.
- I never cared for that boy.
What? Just yesterday you said,
"I like that Dean. Nice boy."
Well, of course he was nice. He was just
using me to get to you and I fell for it.
Darn Dean's winning smile
and twinkling eyes.
Hi, Dean. Here you are.
Second date. Alone.
In the corner.
Just like you said you'd be.
You're kind of just saying everything
you're seeing. Is everything OK?
Yeah. I was just thinking
that we go skating right away.
Because we're here.
At the Skate Barn.
Second date.
In the corner.
Alone when we
should be skating.
You're still doing it.
Yeah, you're right.
Can we just skate?
- Absolutely. That's what I came for.
- Great. Thank you.
Hey, everybody,
reverse skate.
- You really just want to skate?
- Yeah. I love this song.
Me, too. Way more than
standing in that corner.
Sorry about the pile-up.
Let's everybody reverse back!
Really? Are you kidding me?
Um, 'cause I kinda thought
you'd want to do something else.
- Oh, I know what you mean.
- You do?
- Bet I can lap you.
- You don't.
What are you
looking at, chicken?
OK, we've trained
long and hard for this.
I've reprogrammed you with the
latest in digital technology.
We're ready for the big
synchronized robot event.
So you'll dance with a robot, but you
won't help your own brother fight crime?
Yeah. Pretty much.
I got to get to the Robot
Olympics. You're on your own.
No, Justin, I can't be.
Dad taught me a spell to tie
someone up, but I need partners.
- You're going after the Deli Robber!
- I'm gonna stop him, too.
- Spells or no spells.
- No, Max, you can't go out there alone.
- You'll get hurt.
- No. I'm gonna use
- my limited knowledge of tae kwon do.
- You don't know tae kwon do.
That's what "limited" means.
Oh, look.
We're near the locker corner.
Maybe we should
stop there for awhile.
I mean, I know I said
I didn't want to before.
But now that you don't want to,
I kind of wondered why not.
- I don't need to stop.
- Um, why not?
Why don't you want
to stop in the corner?
You usually stop
in the corner, right?
You stop there so often, I
believe they call it Dean's Corner.
Oh, I get it.
You're tired since I lapped
you. All right. Go rest up.
What? No! I...
The spinning fly-by?
Chicken costume? Harper!
What are you doing here?
Feather.
I couldn't go on the skating
date because I work here
and I was embarrassed
to tell you.
You're embarrassed to tell me about a
job where you wear a ridiculous costume?
You went to school yesterday
dressed as a pilgrim.
And what are you doing
in Dean's Corner?
Now that he doesn't want me in
the corner, I want to be in it.
But suddenly I'm not good
enough to kiss? Here he comes.
- Go! Go!
- Stay out of that corner!
Um, Dean, can I talk to you?
There's a lot of rumors going
around about you in this corner.
Oh, man. I was afraid
this was gonna happen.
- I know I got this reputation.
- And if it's true,
it kind of makes me feel like
you don't want to kiss me.
Look, kissing is all some
girls seem to care about.
- I was just hoping you weren't one of those girls.
- I'm not.
That's not all I care about.
I mean, that's all I cared about
the past hour,
but what is up with you?
It's like you're...
OK.
Look, what happened
with those girls
is after I'd kiss 'em, they'd
run off and tell their friends.
They wouldn't even
finish the date.
You think I'd kiss you
and then take off?
- I don't know.
- Well, I wouldn't.
I'd also play that claw machine
where you win stuffed animals.
That's my favorite game.
I won a caterpillar last week.
So, do you want to kiss me, or...
Where did we land with all this?
- You're not gonna take off, right?
- Absolutely not.
Skateboard chicken
dance time, everyone!
And I do mean everyone! Even
you two, over in this corner!
You made me come over here!
- That was nice.
- Alex!
Quick! We have to get Max. He's
gonna try and stop the Deli Robber!
- That's insane!
- I know, but he won't listen to reason.
He could get hurt.
We have to help him.
- What am I gonna do?
- Come on, Alex. Is this the skateboard chicken dance?
Will you come on? Go!
- Max, wait!
- Max!
- You can't stop the Deli Robber!
- I got this figured out.
I'm gonna go over to Murrieta
Clown Supply to buy 40,000 marbles
for 50 cents each.
That's...
A million dollars?
Max, think about
what Maximan would do.
He'd walk up that wall and lasso
the culprit when he least expects it.
Here comes somebody!
OK, we'll do the wall walking
spell to get you up there.
Havity no gravity.
Waverly Sub Station.
I'm going in.
Soap on a rope,
soap fell off the rope,
rope shot out of my hand,
rope tie up that man!
- Nice work, Max!
- You got him!
The jig's up, evil-doer.
You've stolen your last
tip jar and cupcake.
Wait a minute.
How many people
do we know go...
Dad!
- Dad.
- I knew it.
Crime runs through these veins.
That explains my struggle
to stay good.
Actually, Max, I think Dad
made the whole thing up.
- There is no Deli Robber.
- Curses! I took the bait.
I wanted you guys
to work as a team.
Wait a minute. So I went
through all this for nothing?
Not for nothing. You worked
hard! You did a good job!
And I spent a whole month on that robot
and then gave up the Robot Olympics?
Yes! For the team!
Excellent!
And I left Dean after
I promised I wouldn't.
What an admirable sacrifice.
I'm proud of all three of you.
As long as you didn't
kiss the boy, Alex.
Aw, Dad is so
proud of you guys!
- Hi.
- I'm leaving.
- You're like everyone else.
- Will you give me another chance?
- Why should I? - Because I had
to help my little brother, Max...
Sync by fant0m
www.addic7ed.com