Hey, Mom. Okay, so you and Dad
crossed over into New Jersey, right?
Then it's official. I'm in charge.
Because what if there was a tidal wave
or something?
I know, I know, I know. But if there was,
then would I be in charge?
Yes.
All right. I'm in charge.
Oh, look, a tidal wave.
Now you're in charge.
Not funny, Alex.
This is my new sweater.
Justin, when you wear it every day
for a week, it's not new,
it just needs a wash.
Okay, I washed it. You're welcome.
Oh, well, have a good day, guys.
I'm out of here.
Alex. Where do you think you're going?
- I'm meeting Riley at the street fair.
- You're not going to the street fair.
And you have to listen to me
because Mom and Dad left me in charge.
Justin, most 16-year-old boys have fun
when their parents leave town.
Being the authority figure is fun.
Now, I've prepared
a wizard-training review sheet
on some spells that I feel
Dad hasn't covered enough in class.
"Murrieta-animata"? I know this one.
It's the one that makes you think
you're the boss of me.
No. Murrieta-animata is a spell for
making an inanimate object come to life.
Thanks, that's the answer. Well,
I'm done with my review. See you later.
And then Jessica Miller
told Marianna O'Shaunnesy
I shouldn't be able to get out of gym
if no one else could,
so then Marianna said that...
- Riley.
- What?
You were staring
at Marianna O'Shaunnesy.
I wasn't staring.
Is it because she's got bigger hips
than I do? Because I think they're fake.
I was just looking, that's all.
Alex, why do you always get so jealous?
Just looking, huh? As in, just browsing?
As in, doing a little shopping around?
What are you in the market for, Riley?
A new girlfriend?
Hey, honey.
You're doing it again.
Honey. Honey.
He's giving out free honey samples.
I mean, come on, Alex, this is crazy.
I don't think we should go out anymore.
What?
You're breaking up with me?
But we're so good together.
I mean, we have so many good memories.
Remember, you, me and the penguins
at the zoo?
- What are you doing?
- I'm acting out our favourite memories.
And then that one time
when we went for a walk.
And then we went down the stairs.
Alex, I'm breaking up with you.
Okay, I'm not a very good mime.
I'll admit that.
No, it's because
you're constantly jealous.
I'm not constantly jealous.
I just really like you.
Well, you have a funny way
of showing it.
No, I don't. I'm constantly jealous.
That's how I show it.
Okay, I'm done with my wizard homework.
Can I watch TV now?
Sit. Let me check it.
Yes. You might wanna look at spell five.
I got spell five wrong?
No, spell five is the only one
you got right.
You're meaner than Dad.
Thank you.
You're dumber than I thought.
Well, then you should've thought
that I was dumber. Now who's dumb?
Okay. You need to think harder
about the murrieta-animata spell.
If you leave an animated object animated
too long, then it develops emotions.
You mean,
if I turned this doll into a person,
it'd feel bad
about being stuck in the box?
Don't touch that!
That's Calico Woman
in her Legion of the Superladies uniform.
They only made 1000
of these lovely ladies.
Isn't that right, Calico Woman?
So, what you're saying is,
there's 999 other guys
who couldn't get a girl to talk to them?
Don't listen to him.
- Riley broke up with you?
- Yeah.
- But I'm being really strong.
- Well, that's good.
- You want some churro?
- Sure.
Riley used to buy food
and let me eat some of it.
You guys were so good together.
Remember that time
you went to the penguins?
Oh, that did look weird.
Hey, Alex,
I heard that you and Riley broke up.
What do you say you and I go out?
Excuse me, Ken? Hi.
We're going out. Like, right now.
Yeah, I've been meaning
to talk with you about that.
This will only take a second.
Wait for me.
I can't believe Riley thinks I'm jealous.
You know, Riley would be jealous too
if I were looking at other guys all day.
You know what you should do?
You should have an open and honest talk
with Riley to establish trust.
Then you'll have a firm foundation
for the future.
That sounds like something
old couples in their 20s would do.
Then what are you thinking?
I'm thinking I'll find a boyfriend
who's cuter than Riley,
make him jealous, and then
he'll wanna get back together with me.
Yeah. What am I thinking?
We're not in our 20s.
We don't watch the news.
So see any cute guys around here?
I see a lot of cute guys.
Hey, Harper, did you see that booth
where they sell rock families
with the eyes glued on them?
- Where?
- Around the corner...
Did they have any with two parents,
one teenage girl
and a smallish, shriveled-up grandma?
I don't...
Murrieta-animata
That pole hurts.
Well, hello, handsome.
Hello. Hello to you.
Hello. Hello.
I can say hello.
Why can I say hello?
I'll explain that later.
The important thing is,
is I'm Alex and your name is Manny.
Yeah, Manny. Last name Kinn.
Manny Kinn. Okay.
And you're my new boyfriend.
Whoa, this is moving too fast.
- I just got off that pole.
- Let's go.
No.
You know, you look so familiar.
Where do I know you from?
You know, you look just like my uncle.
But they took him away a long time ago.
I mean, that's okay, because it was
just me in the window then for a while.
What did you put in there? And why?
- Why?
- I don't know.
This is my mom, my dad,
my grandma and me.
Your dad's a pirate?
Oh, my gosh.
One of my dad's eyes fell off.
Nobody move. Nobody move.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning Calico Woman
because I'm selling her on the Internet.
Well, her and Man Boy.
Even the box has to be
in mint condition.
Oh, by the way, did you clean your room
or just shove everything under the bed?
Cleaning my room
is shoving everything under my bed.
That's why beds have an underneath.
Think.
Hey, everybody.
This is my new boyfriend, Manny.
Hey, everybody. I can say hello.
Hello. I'm Justin.
Alex, what happened to Riley?
We broke up like an hour ago.
Where have you been?
After grieving over Riley for 15 minutes,
I met Manny and it was love at first sight.
- Right, Manny?
- Right.
No.
I didn't even know what it was like
to feel alive until I met Alex.
Oh, that's so sweet.
You guys make such a cute couple.
Alex, it's like Manny was made for you.
You have no idea.
- Manny, this is Harper.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm looking for an eye.
No.
And my brother Max.
And my older brother, Mr. Russo.
And those are Mr. Russo's dolls.
Found it.
Oh, this isn't my dad's eye.
It's a button.
Wait, buttons don't have legs.
It's a bug!
Alex.
Can I talk to you for a second?
I don't know, Manny and I are pretty busy
talking about how I don't get jealous, but...
Sure.
I feel horrible about our breakup.
I was stupid.
I didn't know what it felt like to feel jealous
until I saw you with that guy over there.
His name is Manny.
I prefer to call him "that guy over there."
What are you saying?
You wanna get back together?
I would.
Yes.
Well, I don't... Okay.
Really?
Well, what about that guy over there?
Oh, don't worry.
Manny's used to being stood up.
It's an inside thing.
Stood up.
You're breaking up with me?
Yes.
And you're okay with it, because
I'm gonna turn you back into a mannequin.
All right.
Garibay-immobilitay
Okay, one more time.
Excuse me.
Stay.
Justin, a question
completely out of the blue.
But what's the spell to un-animate
something you've brought to life?
Garibay-immobilitay.
Well, I tried.
So, Manny, this is your lucky day.
You're free to live your life.
You'll do great out there,
a handsome kid like you. Okay.
- You enjoy.
- All right.
You know, that's too bad.
I really liked Manny.
And he wears the same sweater as me,
which I saw on a mannequin
that looked a lot like Manny Kinn.
Manny Kinn.
Mannequin.
Yes, I animated the mannequin
from the store.
God.
What's the big deal?
You can't be using magic
without my permission.
That's complete disrespect
of my authority.
Hey, I tried to change him back,
but it didn't work.
What?
If you bring something to life
and it develops emotions,
you can't change it back.
Manny's in love with you.
Don't be ridiculous. He's a mannequin.
He can't be in love with me.
Alex, look, I brought you one flower
for every minute that I've loved you.
Oh, no.
Manny, we broke up,
don't you remember?
You have to stop following me.
I can't, Alex. I'm in love with you.
You get me.
You taught me how to drink from a straw
without poking myself in the eye.
Remember the time I kissed the duck?
But what if someone else got you?
And then you could have
even better times with them.
Really? Do you know that someone?
I think I do. She's a real doll.
She's a friend of my brother's.
More wizard homework?
Dad doesn't even make me
do homework on Friday.
Max, if you put it off until Sunday night,
then I won't be able
to put you kids to bed early.
Have a little quiet time for myself.
What are you gonna do,
light some candles and take a bath?
My quiet time is my quiet time.
Okay, so you're a teenage boy
who drinks tea
and likes to take baths.
Like I'm not gonna tell anyone about that
on the Internet.
Hey. You get down here, young man.
That's it.
Okay.
Murrieta-animata grande
Oh, those twist-ties really hurt.
Manny, meet Calico Woman.
Calico Woman, meet Manny.
You two have a lot in common.
I don't have anything in common
with a superhero.
You're so wrong, Manny.
Who likes to say hello?
Hello.
Who here is dishwasher-safe?
That's the only thing about me
that's safe.
See? You two are gonna be
so happy together.
I'm still in love with her.
When you say that,
that makes me really mad.
Yeah, that's called jealousy.
I don't like that feeling.
There. See? All done.
He's perfectly happy with her.
Now nothing could go wrong.
Oh, I hope I didn't jinx that.
And right after dinner, you have to take
a shower and then get in your pyjamas.
Can I take a shower in my pyjamas?
Then you would be wet,
your pyjamas would be wet
and your entire bed would be wet.
But if everything's wet,
is anything really wet?
Like when you're totally underwater,
you're not really wet.
Yes, you are.
Calico Woman's gone. Where...?
Well... it says right here,
"No chains can hold her."
Chains are a lot stronger
than a cardboard box.
Alex.
See?
Max! What are...?
Alex, don't leave me.
Look, look, I won you a stuffed gorilla.
All right, enough.
This has gotta stop, Manny. It's over.
- But I'm in love with her.
- Seriously, it's over.
Otherwise, that pretty face
ain't gonna be so pretty no more.
Oh, no, you're not gonna change my head
into that featureless knob.
All right, that's it.
Wait. Wha...?
Riley, wait.
Manny!
Manny, I love you.
Okay, let's split up and find Alex.
Because where Alex is,
that's where my Calico Woman doll is.
Well, there's Manny.
Oh, and there's Riley.
Oh, found Alex.
Manny!
And Calico Woman.
Man, she is huge.
And alive.
Manny. Manny.
We were both made in China.
We need a volunteer.
Who wants to sit in this dunk tank?
- I'll go in.
- Excellent. Excellent.
Just climb right up there.
Okay, who would like the first shot
at sending this handsome fella
into this dunk tank?
I would.
Riley.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna teach Manny that no one
comes between me and my girl.
I know you don't like jealousy on me,
but on you, it is so hot.
No!
Oh, my God.
Wait up.
- Alex.
- Oh, no, what happened to Manny?
Well, it looks like he got wet.
You know, sometimes
water can make a spell wear off.
How do you know that?
Because the spell just wore off.
Manny?
What have they done to you?!
What's going on here?
Alex, that guy over there
just turned into giant doll pieces.
That's it. I'm calling Waverly Place
Street Fair security.
No, no, no. No need to do that, okay?
I have to tell you something.
I have to tell everybody something.
Ladies and gentlemen, the man
you just saw in the dunk tank is really a...
- Alex.
- Magician.
The Great Manic-keeny.
And for his big trick,
he has disappeared in the dunk tank,
leaving behind
a disassembled mannequin in his place.
Ta-da.
Oh, yeah.
And how about a hand
for his lovely assistant?
Yeah.
All right.
Watch the outfit,
you're going back in the box.
I never liked you.
Hey. Hey. Hey, you get back here.
I thought Manny was just a mannequin
who got turned into a person
and then back into a mannequin.
But he was really just a magician.
Great show. Great show. Great show.
Look, Alex, see what happens
when you break the rules?
Things end up working out for me?
No.
You almost exposed us as wizards
and I lost Calico Woman.
She was worth 100 bucks.
I got my boyfriend back,
and I'll give you 100 bucks. Who got hurt?
I did because you didn't respect me
being in charge.
Why is that so important to you?
What about living? Having fun?
Doing stuff to tell stories about?
Like this.
This is gonna be a great story to tell.
The only people you could tell the story to
would ground you.
If you'd calm down every once in a while,
I would tell you stories.
Like, I bet you've always wondered what
happened to your lightsaber and cape.
Alex, how am I supposed to be calm
when you tell me stuff like that?
Oh, come on, you grandpas.
Can't anyone dunk me?
You know, it's really hot out here.
I could really use a dip.