(quirky music)
- I cannot believe this
many people showed up.
- I can't believe it's not butter
but I am!
- Get out of here, Butter Man!
- It's pronounced Butterman.
I wasn't planning on staying.
The cry of a dry crumpet calls to me.
Til we melt again!
- How don't we just change the
law so that only I can stay?
- Mhmm.
There, Jack, look at this crowd.
The public are coming around,
this isn't a lost cause
so just get up there and say something.
- Okay, okay, okay, just gotta
get that butter guy out of my head,
it's a fucking dude, man.
- [Butter Man] You butter believe it!
- Quiet!
- Hey!
Jackie, Jackie Chan, yeah yeah yeah yeah!
I didn't know you were having a party.
It's really cool, man (laughs).
- Hello.
- Oh good day, love.
(woman shrieks)
- Skulldrich, did you
come here just to mock me?
- Is that popcorn?
- Yes and no.
Yes I am here to mock you but
no, these are scarab beetles.
Sorry, mate, they're a little dry.
- But of course!
- Neat-o, neat-o petit-o.
But I've got a little speech to make
so maybe you could just
butter off, bugger off.
- Good on you, Jack.
Break a leg.
- Yeah, leg, spine.
Hell, break it all.
Yeah.
You texting?
That's cool.
(marching music)
- Okay.
Hi.
- Hey!
- Guys, girls.
Whatever that is.
(baby crying)
Thank you so much for
coming, what a turn out.
It really means so much that
you all care about my cause,
this cause, our cause, really
matters to this many people.
I'm Jack.
- Boo!
Boo, am I right?
- You might remember
me from Fishy Thursday
or the time I blew up Morgan
Wright's eardrum on television.
- Yeah, nice one ya dickhead!
- Or a positive example...
- What'd do ya think of that?
- And I have run out of words.
Lotus.
- Hello, he tried.
Okay, guys, well we
all know why we're here
so let's just open the
floor for public discussion.
- Hi, Marvolo Loprego.
- [Woman] Get up.
- Sorceror, level 16.
- Hi, Marvolo.
Enjoy that level sweet 16, mate,
it'll be over before you know it.
- What level are you?
- Oh, I'm level...
- You know, you're not
the only wizard in town.
Some of us have been here for centuries,
going completely unnoticed
and then you turn up,
turn a railway station into a fish
and suddenly we're all
being told to fuck off.
- I am (stutters).
- I uh, I uh (spits).
What a cunt!
(dramatic sting)
- Hey, Zandark, necromancer.
- Hey, Zandark.
- Hey, Skulldrich.
So Zach, so Jack, my bad.
It seems your petition calls for any acts
of raising the dead to cease forthwith.
I think that's pretty unfair considering
some of our professions, fetishes.
- Gross.
- And what's with no murdering people?
- What?
- Aw, boo!
(crowd heckles)
- Stick it up your...
- Beanbag.
- Cool it, guys, come on.
- Hello, I'm Snot-beak Fuck-Nuggs,
spokesgoblin for Saint
Cook's Wizards Council
for Equal Rights for the
attractively impaired.
- Hello.
- Oh yes, your documentation,
you have no options for
aesthetically-challenged members
of the magical community whatsoever.
What's the story there, mate?
- I didn't think of it.
I don't know man, look,
if you wanna fit in
why didn't you change your
name from, what was it?
Shitbird Dicklips, into
something like Tim.
- I'll have you know that
Fuck-Nuggs is a proud goblin name.
- You gotta tick on you, mate.
(crowd heckles)
- Boo!
- You fraudulent poet.
- I hate this man.
- Oh, I've got such a
hard-on right now, man.
Fucking Medusa, she took a
peek of this and (sputters).
(dog barks)
- He hates them.
Look at his shirt!
- What?
- Skulldrich.
(laughs)
- Now that is very offensive.
- He tried to get me to stop Barbie.
Hell, what Australian is that?
- She just wanted to be an astronaut.
You murderer!
- Won't anyone think
about my poor baby bones?
- And he can't even keep
it up, unlike Enrique.
- And my hot water hasn't
been working for days!
- That's right, he's a pervert!
- He got me so wet in a
restaurant that I was late
for a date with Brendan
Frazier and Rachel Weisz,
star of The Lovely Bones and
Monkeybone, respectively.
- I like him.
- Thank you, Terry.
- Fuck you, Terry!
- Why don't we just send him back?
He caused this whole mess.
Why blame the majority for
the actions of a minority?
- Yeah, what a dickslit.
Send him back!
(crowd heckles)
- This has been, like
a complete and utter,
what's the expression,
like a locomotive disaster,
like a bunch of people on
the metro who die in a crash.
- A trainwreck?
- No, anyway, why did I
think this was a good idea?
I left home to escape these lunatics,
and now I've given them
a rallying point, me.
- Jack, this was a good idea.
And granted, it maybe against you now
but for good reason (mumbling)
but they all need this vote to go through
so just get them on side.
- I can't do that, they hate my guts.
I'm pathetic.
- You're not pathetic.
Okay, look, you've made some mistakes
but you're a good guy.
Just
stand up and speak from the heart.
You've got this.
I believe in you.
Be charming.
(laughs)
You can do charming.
- [Voiceover] Boo!
(melodramatic music)
- Hey, this baby-eating fuck is...
(dramatic music)
- Hey!
Listen, I know I'm nobody's
favorite person right now
and I know that I got us into this mess
but please let me get us out of it.
Why are you all here?
Why would anybody leave their home
for somewhere so different and so strange?
I can tell you why I came here
and it's cheesy but I came
here 'cause I love this city
and I love this country.
I love that I can check my mail without
being buried in owls, I love
that I can go to the beach
without fear of kraken attack.
I love, that by and large,
there aren't many butter people
here trying to assault my toast
with slip-free cholesterol.
- I'll get you yet.
- But what I love the most is
that in spite of my accidents,
in spite of all the times I've fucked up
I've actually felt pretty welcomed here.
And for someone like
me, that's everything.
And do you not all feel welcome?
All of us, outsiders,
black sheep, eye kings.
- Aye!
- Wizards.
- Necromancers.
- Aye!
- Terries.
- Goblins and mummy lords.
- He and I once strangled a
puppy to death for no reason.
We were just bored.
- And assorted others.
- [Butter Man] You're churning me on!
- Fuck you, Butter Man!
New settlers have always
been welcomed in this country
but let's show them that
we're worth the effort.
Let's show 'em that we
can be Australians too.
(crowd cheers)
(dramatic music)
(dogs barking)
- Well, Jack, I never
knew how passionately
you felt about this place.
I mean, look, I feel
like a bit of a bloody
dill pickle saying this, but, the reason
I wanted you back home
was because I miss you.
I miss having someone
around that I could just
fucking hate, you know, and I do.
I hate you.
- I hate you too, man.
(laughing)
- Gotta admit though, I did
get you to use magic again.
- Yes, you did, you cheeky fucker.
(laughing)
- Watch your language you cunt.
Alright, I'm outtie (sighs).
(light melodic music)
(woman laughing)
- You did it, Jack.
- We did it, Kylie.
This is the start of something great,
a long life here in Melbourne.
It's beautiful.
Allow me.
(twinkling sound)
- Yeah, okay, stop it, stop it, Jack.
I know how to eat.
(laughs)
I am happy for you, though.
And I'm proud of the
small part that I played
in helping you find a home.
- Small part?
Thanks to you I found a new home
and I think I've found
someone I wanna share it with.
- Oh! (laughs)
(light melodic music)
- Jack, Jack, what do you
think you're doing, Jack?
- What do you mean?
We won, now we kiss, that's how this ends.
- No, no it isn't.
Look, you're a really nice guy
but I'm aggressively unattracted to you.
- But where I'm from, we win the quest,
we kiss the maiden.
- Oh, well that's fucked up!
Just because I'm the only
woman you know, Jack,
doesn't mean that we are
destined to be together.
If I was interested, I
probably wouldn't have
taken you speed dating.
- But you kissed me.
- Jesus Christ, there is
a big difference between
a kiss on the cheek
and a cock in my mouth.
- What?
- What do you mean, whoa, what?
- It's gross.
I don't know, it's weird, it's vulgar.
- Fuck you, it's vulgar!
You just pulled me against my will
to your gaping moor and I am not
into wispy, beard mouth.
- I'm not sure I understand
what's happening right now.
- Typical.
Look, Jack, I'm really happy that
I could help you, really I am.
Maybe I'll see you around.
(melancholy music)
- Well, at least wizards
can live in Melbourne now.
Yay!
Well, at least I haven't
ruined everything.
I have ruined everything.
(exploding sounds)
- Good question.
I think Melbourne has
changed since the wizards,
you know, showed up
now that you mention it
but it's always been a hectic city,
so much hustle and bustle, you know?
I love it.
- As a vegetarian, I couldn't be happier
since my husband was
turned into a cauliflower.
- As a pescatarian, I couldn't be happier
with my new neighbor.
- Good day.
- Since the wizards took
over, metro trains have been
running on time if not
slightly in the future.
(mumbles)
- Good day, hello, good to see you.
Yeah, look, alright I'll admit
when the johnny-come-latelies
first turned up
I was on serious bloody tender
hooks, you know what I mean?
But when they showed me the beauty
of the self-battering fish
well I've been making
some yahoo serious dosh.
- Why must everything I love die?
I mean, I finally got a
place that I fit in, sort of.
I left to escape this bullshit
now I'm knee, no cock, no
neck fucking deep in it!
It all followed me over, all of it!
Huh.
(light pleasant melodic music)
At least it's peaceful.
I mean, fucked up a good
city, ruined a lot of lives
(sighs) but hey, this is nice.
(light pleasant music)
- Well, everyone else is gone but
I'm glad you changed your mind.
It feels right, doesn't it?
Like old times.
- I don't know, man,
it's been a weird month.
I mean, everything I have ever loved
has either died or turned to shit.
Maybe I should just
embrace something I hate.
- I hate you, Jack.
- And I hate you, Skulldrich.
Now and forever.
(dramatic music)
(moaning)
(vomiting sounds)
(screaming)
(light pleasant music)
- Thus, the circle of life continues
its dance into eternity.
- That is a beautiful thing.
- I cannot articulate how
much I regret this decision.
(spaghetti music)