(serious music)
- Sticks and stones may break my bones
but this story may break your heart.
Good evening and welcome to a very special
edition of No Nonsense.
This past month has been
dominated by a single story,
the fate of one little boy, Baby Bones.
The product of a dark wizard's curse,
Baby Bones was rejected
by his biological parents
simply because he was born without skin.
On tonight's episode we
take an exclusive look
at the life of Baby Bones
and his adoptive parents.
A Channel Bueno exclusive,
let's take a look.
- Me and Harry had been trying for a baby
ever since the wedding,
but it just wasn't happening.
Adoption seemed like the only way
for us to have a real family.
And the orphanage just broke our hearts.
So many beautiful children who needed
the loving care of parents.
But there was one child who needed love
more than any other.
That child was Baby Bones.
- Yep.
- [Deborah] It's been a
little over two months
since the couple adopted
the innocent child,
unaware of the celebrity
status the media had
cruelly forced upon him.
- We would like to go up.
- Hopefully.
- Baby Bones get down from there.
(screeching)
That's our Baby Bones.
(phone ringing)
- Hello this is the
mobile telephone of Jack.
May I ask to whom that I speak?
- Hey Jack, I'm at the studio already.
Where are you?
- I'm sitting in my motorized vehicle
in a seemingly endless queue of other
motorized vehicles, and it is boring
and it feels natural
and it just feels right.
- Okay yeah, they have run
the Baby Bones retrospective.
- Oh fuck.
- Oh fuck is right Jack.
Look, wizards aren't in the
public's good graces right now
and if you don't get to
this interview on time,
Quinn is gonna tear you a new one.
Are you sure you can't
get here any faster?
They've got fish and chips.
- I don't know what to do.
I'm stuck in a traffic jam.
Fuck okay, so Baby Bones has
reared his ugly head again.
Did the show make us look that bad?
- Of course his life
would be easier with skin.
Of course I wish those damned
awful wizards hadn't cursed
an innocent child to live without skin.
But he's my Baby Bones.
I wouldn't change him for the world.
Excuse me.
Baby Bones stop eating
the cat this instant!
(screeching)
- Look um, I'm not gonna lie.
Hilde was more on the
Baby Bones bandwagon,
the triple B.
However, I love my wife.
And now I love my son.
My son who is a Baby Bones.
Nutritionists weren't quite
sure what would sustain
Baby Bones, but after some
research into the occult,
Hilde and I discovered that
he really likes something
we like to call four blood salad.
Basically you take the
blood from an animal,
put that in a bowl, and
you take the blood from
another animal, put that in a bowl.
Followed by two more types of blood.
A little pinch of nutmeg, give it a stir,
and you've got yourself a salad.
It's actually a recipe from
Curtis Stone's new book.
It's a weird shift from
his previous books.
- Aww, my two boys.
(screeching and squealing)
- I was hoping they had
forgotten about Baby Bones.
I mean well that's it. I'm fucked.
I'm completely, utterly,
shittingly fucked.
- Just get here ASAP Jack.
- I'm stuck in fucking traffic.
- Technically you're not in
traffic, you are traffic.
What possessed you?
- What possessed you to
turn that baby into a bones?
I mean of all your plans to fuck me,
that one's fucking me rotten.
It's fucking me frontways.
It's fucking me sideways.
Thanks to you I'm pretty much a big soggy
fuckbag of cum.
- Well you're very welcome, Jack.
I don't do that for everyone.
- And now on the one nationwide interview
that I've booked, my one
chance to redeem myself,
I'm gonna miss it 'cause
I'm stuck in traffic.
- Aw yeah I heard there was
a big accident up there.
It's caused all this traffic.
Also I saw it.
Also I did it.
(laughing)
Why don't you just teleport there?
I mean use a bit of, you
know, as the French say
they'd just say magic wouldn't they?
I mean they're French.
They're people.
They're fucked but they're people.
- Or I could just sit down
like a civilized person and wait.
- Because you're an idiot.
And just to show you how idiot you are,
I'm gonna skip across the globe.
Excuse me.
I'm back.
Gee whiz I had a lot of fun.
Glad I'm not stuck in
traffic like a bloody drongo.
Oh and by the way, the rain in
Spain falls mainly on nothin'
'cause I evaporated Spain.
It's gone. Cha cha.
No jamon for you.
That's Spanish ham.
Fuckin' buy it in a Safeway.
Buy a whole leg into your cart now.
- We love you Baby Bones!
- He may not have skin, but certainly
he has fans.
- I love his bones.
- If I have a baby, I'm gonna
rip off all his skin too.
- Appeared on tee shirts,
mugs, his hip-hop single,
or the wildly successful
line of children's toys.
♫ Baby Bones Baby Bones Schmampftz ♫
- Baby Bones merchandise
is a must-have accessory
for kids this summer.
- I like Baby Bones because
he doesn't listen to teachers.
(screaming)
- I love those bones!
- Baby Bones has become a media darling.
Mr. and Mrs. Pottinger
have faced harsh scrutiny,
forcing their child to undergo
a life-threatening procedure
to have its bones surgically removed.
Needless to say, Baby Skin has failed
to capture the imagination
of the Australian public.
But is it all too much?
Child Psychologist and mother
of four, Miranda Merhtens
believes Baby Bones should
be Baby Left Alones.
- I just don't think it's healthy
that the youth of our
country is so obsessed
with what is objectively
a spooky, scary skeleton.
- And do you have any words tonight
for all those fans watching you?
(screeching)
- All your skins shall cast asunder
and all that will remain will be bones!
(laughing)
- What a darling little trooper.
- He may not look like a normal baby.
But he's an extraordinary Baby Bones.
- [Deborah] And what do you
think of the media's obsession
with your Baby Bones?
- I consider it an invasion
of my family's privacy.
I beg of everyone please,
stop making my family
into a media circus.
(disturbing rasping and whispering)
- Well we thank you for letting
our crew into your home.
- Oh you're welcome.
It's been my pleasure.
(horns honking)
- Whew these Cubans are delicious.
Cigar's not bad either.
Yak yak yak yak yak yak yak.
Seriously bud, I ate
a lot of Cuban people.
And most of them were delicious,
except Diego.
- Shut up!
I'm trying to listen to this
interview that I am missing.
- [Voiceover] Talk about
Jack the Ripper, Ripoff.
Jack the Ripoff.
This is typical.
This is the mark of a coward.
They're good aren't they.
You create a level playing field.
And he hasn't got the guts to turn up.
Why? What's he hiding?
It's disrespectful to
your wonderful listeners
whom I adore.
It is rude, crude, it's kangarooed.
It's absolutely fair
dinkum, unfair dinkum.
He's a dirty, rotten coward.
This is appalling, Paul Hogan.
(screech snoring)
- And now for some unfortunate news.
Since we recorded that
episode, there have been
some alarming developments
in the Baby Bones saga.
Two days ago, Baby Bones's adoptive father
Harry Swinton disappeared.
While no full body has been
recovered, his undamaged skin
has been found in the crawlspace
beneath the family home.
The whereabouts of Baby Bones
is currently Baby Unknowns.
However the police have
released this security footage
taken from a mechanic's mere blocks
from the Swinton residence.
(creepy music)
Baby Bones is considered
at large and dangerous.
Here at Channel Bueno, we
strongly urge all our viewers
to keep children and pigs inside,
doors and windows firmly
fastened, and please
lock up your bones.
(reporters shouting at man on television)
- I have no official comment tonight.
But I will say this, this latest business,
the quadruple B, the
bigger Baby Bones business,
this is disgusting.
It sticks in my craw.
They've gone too far this time.
They went too far the other times as well.
But this time they've gone even further.
It's time for us to do
a little bit of magic
and make the bastards disappear
next Saturday at the ballot box.
We've had enough!
- I'm totally boned.
(screeching)
(gentle music)