Subs created by: David Coleman.
Alex Russo, you kneel before
the Crystals of Justice
where you are charged with treason for
attempting to destroy the mortal world.
I'm telling you, you have the wrong wizard.
Silence!
Ok, I am right here. You
do not have to yell.
What I was trying to say is that,
ok, maybe some bad things happened,
and maybe it was because of me, but
that doesn't mean it was my fault.
I'd make a terrible lawyer.
Your fate has been decided.
The Crystal Cavern of Justice
hereby find you guilty!
Wait! No! Isn't there some way
we can replay what happened
so you would know I'm innocent?
Well, almost innocent.
You're not speaking of the
time vortex, are you?
Well, if that's what you call
a rewind button, then yeah.
Very well. We will send you back
to the moment this incident began.
All right. Well, get your
popcorn and licorice
because you're going to
like how this got started.
I just love drive-in movies. You can
yell at the screen and nobody cares.
Hey, genius, the walls are oozing
maggots, why are you taking a shower?
Alex...
Your own personal drive-in?!
Get rid of it now.
Come on, dad. I can get you your own car
and you can watch the movie with us.
I can get you a Churro truck.
Lose it.
Fine.
And whose car was that?
I don't know, but there's
some guy out on Waverly Place
who's been looking for his car for about
an hour, show me some love, Harper.
- Yeah.
- Harper, don't high-five her.
What she did was wrong and
unbelievably selfish.
Well, we left the guy
half a pack of licorice.
No, we didn't.
Dad, what's the big deal? I've
always done stuff like this.
Right, but now that
you're The Family Wizard,
it's time to stop using
magic for selfish reasons.
Now give me that popcorn.
Thank you so much, Mason.
Ok, you and Alex can hang up the banner.
Harper, get the ice cream
cake out of the freezer.
Jerry, stop eating popcorn off the floor.
Wait, did you say party? For who?
I have a fair inkling.
Another party for Justin?!
We're just so excited about
him taking over WizTech.
It's a big deal.
Yeah. I guess you're right.
It's not like, you know,
actually winning the
family competition and
becoming the full wizard.
Since nobody ever threw me a party.
Hey, I didn't get a party
or get to become a wizard.
I just got these all-you-can-eat
bologna scraps.
Mm-mm. Maybe I am the winner.
Come on, everybody. We've
got a lot of work to do.
Justin's going to be here soon.
All right, I'm done. Where's my magazine?
Mason, rub my shoulders.
That was hard work.
Hey! I just told you,
magic is not for getting what you
want or using it for selfish reasons.
Mason, stop rubbing her shoulders!
That's right, Mija, you should use your
magic to make other people's lives easier.
I know a pretty Latina who would love
to never have to do laundry again.
Theresa.
Sorry. Your father's right.
It's time to grow up.
"Grow up?" Everybody knows people
who grow up too fast are miserable.
I mean, look at Harper.
She's been doing her parents' laundry
since she was in the second grade.
Oh, see, the laundry I didn't mind so much.
It was rotating the tires
on the minivan that just...
Really got to me.
Where's Justin? He should've
been here by now.
You mean he's not here?
I'm so bored I thought he was here
telling one of his nerdy stories
that always ends with "hey,
wake up, everybody!"
I'm so sorry for the intrusion.
I'm Justin's friend Dominic.
He asked me to give you a message.
He is too busy at WizTech and
unfortunately cannot come.
Ok. Give us the message.
Uh... that was the message.
Ok. Can we start from the top? Because
this guy is all over the place.
- So is Justin all right?
- Oh, yes, Mrs. Russo. Justin is fine.
It's just more difficult for someone with
his spectacular talents to get away.
Now, I don't usually use
the word "spectacular,"
but in Justin's case, spectacular.
Justin isn't coming? What are we
gonna do with the ice cream cake.
Oh, I'm sure you'll think
of something, Jerry.
Excuse me, you must be Alex Russo.
You're quite famous in the Wizard World
but I had no idea you were so...
Beautiful.
Oh, come on. I'm not that famous.
Dominic. Nice to meet you, mate.
I'm Mason Greyback.
Perhaps you've heard of me,
Alex's Werewolf boyfriend.
Boyfriend? You're a lucky man.
Yes, I am. A lucky Werewolf.
Well, it seems like I've made
this awkward, forgive me.
It was an honor meeting you, Alex.
So long, everyone.
Werewolf.
Boy, he was the most polite
wizard I have ever met.
And easy on the eyes.
Reminded me of a young me.
You know, I think he was into you, Alex.
Oh. No, no, no, no.
Yeah. No, no, no, no.
I can't believe Justin's not coming.
I wanted him to be here
for my big announcement.
A while ago, I got an invitation
from my cousin, Carmela, in Italy,
inviting us to a Russo family reunion.
It's ok, dad. What's your announcement?
- That was the announcement.
- Oh, great, now dad's all over the place.
Aw, Jerry, you're taking me on a
romantic trip to Italy, I love you.
Well... actually, I'm
taking the whole family.
Why? They don't know we have kids.
But, Theresa, it's a family reunion.
Or should I say...
Riunione di famiglia?
Please don't do that, dad.
It's almost as annoying as
when you say "mootsa-rella".
Well, you guys have fun.
I'll just stay here and read or something.
Yeah, and I'll just stay here
and chew up the furniture.
This couch looks pretty fruity.
You guys are family, too. I got
tickets for all of us to go.
- Oh yay!
- All right!
Tickets? Dad, if you want to go to
Italy, I can be our travel agent.
No time for that travel confusion. Show
me the door to our Italian reunion.
Ok, I don't know how to say
"Wizard Speed Pass" in Italian,
so I'm just going to go with "Mamma Mia!"
Or at least I think that's Italian.
A door to Japan? How cool.
It's Italy.
I don't know all the towns in Japan, dude.
Alex, you're not going to turn this trip
into one of your selfish shortcuts.
I want us to experience the whole journey.
Getting there is half the fun.
Now, get rid of this thing.
Whoa.
Did you just see that girl?
Alex, I have to get her number first.
Max, get back here!
Would you please grow up?! Max!
Ok, let's just find Max and go home.
So we can fly back here.
Wow! Look at this place.
Oh. It's beautiful.
Your family lives here?
Villa di Russo.
I don't know who "Villa di" is,
but Russo is definitely me.
I don't think he's mad at you anymore.
Oh, don't be fooled. He's happy
anywhere there's cheese hanging.
Man. I lost her.
I didn't even get her name,
but she looked like a Tomiko.
Tomiko! Tomiko!
Max. Forget the girl. We've
got girls back home.
Yeah, but there's no
Italians in New York, Mom.
Oh, come on. Can't we stay a little longer?
This is the first time Alex's magic
took me somewhere that didn't scare me.
No. We're not coming to Italy this way.
We're going to experience a
family trip the real way.
You mean on a discount flight in
cramped seats with bad food and
an obnoxious kid in front of you
saying, "peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo".
Ciao, bella.
Are you here for a tour
of the Russo vineyard?
Well... I, uh...
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
We're not here for the tour, paisan.
Go back to work.
And put a shirt on! All right, let's go.
Ok, fine. But you'll only
have yourself to blame
when that peek-a-boo kid uses
your lap for a barf bag.
All right, is everybody here?
Good. Now, Alex, get rid of this thing.
Ok.
Hmm... the spell I need is
like things in my bedroom.
It's buried under the
dirty clothes of my mind.
You see? Justin would never do a spell
that he didn't know how to undo.
Oh, I get it. I get this
whole "grown-up" thing now.
You think Justin should've
been The Family Wizard.
Honey, I'm sorry. I
didn't mean it that way.
No. I'm sorry I'm not the grown-up
Family Wizard you want me to be.
Well, up until then, that was the best
five-minute vacation I've ever had.
Ahem, excuse me, is this Jumbotron taken?
Dominic? What are you doing here?
My night job is cleaning
the back of the Jumbotron.
You being here is just a bonus.
Look, you seem really nice,
but I have a boyfriend.
And to be honest I don't think I'd
be really good company right now.
Unless you're a fan of big,
sloppy emotional meltdowns.
You know, I was just saying this morning,
I haven't seen a big, sloppy
emotional meltdown in a while.
Let's see what you got.
Ah, a smile.
Have you ever considered
joining The Wizard Council?
The Wizard Council?
Isn't that for old geezers who wear robes
because they're tired of shopping?
I just believe you have the
potential to be the most,
powerful wizard of your generation.
Trust me. You have no idea
what you're truly capable of.
Well, if you ask my family,
I'm not capable of anything
except refusing to grow up.
They're mortals. They can't
understand wizards with your power.
Besides, if their opinions
really bothers you,
you're powerful enough to create your own
spell to smooth out your little edges.
Why are you telling me this?
Because where everyone else
sees trouble, I see magic.
And beauty.
Ok, now you're just flirting.
Yeah, a little bit.
- Here. It's a small gift.
- Oh, no. I can't take that.
It's simply a friendship bracelet.
Everything ok up here?
Oh, yeah. Mason, sorry. I just had
to get away from home, you know.
And I just came to check on her.
I apologize if I've overstepped.
You have, mate, and I'm here now.
Werewolf.
- Good-bye, Alex.
- Bye.
Werewolf.
I do not like that guy.
Anything I should be worried about?
Not a thing.
Good. Well, I've got a
surprise to cheer you up.
I thought we would have a little picnic.
Don't say Italian, because I've
had enough of that, today.
No. I was thinking
something sophisticated...
- Poached salmon.
- Oh, Mason...
That's so sweet.
But can I make a little tweak?
Of course, darling.
Check it out, finger food feast.
I call the wing.
No, Alex! Alex, you know
this food is bad for you.
Besides, I cooked that salmon,
two hours over a hot poacher.
Why? You know it only takes
me like two seconds.
I see. So, this is how it's
going to be from now on.
- What?
- Just you, me and your wand.
Just using your magic selfishly
no matter who it hurts.
Mason, where are you going?
I did all this for us.
So did I.
So you turned Mason's classy picnic
into a county fair fry-fest?
Well, everybody knows that
my favorite food comes in
cardboard containers with
some kind of dipping sauce.
Ewe.
Oh, hi, Alex. Can you tell me
what's wrong with this picture?
Everything you're wearing
is from the nineties.
Oh, but if you guys wear
it, it's "vintage".
Have you figured out how to
get rid of this thing yet?
Uh, no. I've been a little busy.
But don't worry, I'll figure it out
something before Max can use it again.
Hey, who wants to help me
make a hot tub out of this?
I bet I know how he's going
to make the bubbles.
Max, stop going to Italy. And, Alex, you...
I know, I know. Grow up.
You're right, pop. I'll
just take this back.
Max, you forgot the barrel!
Max!
He's not coming back, is he?
Theresa, we have to find Max again!
What?! I was about to make dinner.
It's just Italy, we'll be right back.
Hey, are you ok?
It's just that, I thought once
I became The Family Wizard,
all of this pressure would be off of me.
But no, it's like everybody
still wants me to change.
Well, that doesn't make a lot of sense.
It's who you are in the first place
that made you The Family Wizard.
I know, but maybe growing up
would make me a better person.
I mean, I can't even say anything nice
about my best friend's
hideous clambake outfit.
I'm sorry, Harper. I held
off as long as I could.
But you see? That's what I mean. You
making fun of my outfit is you.
And me loving this outfit is me.
People should appreciate
you for who you are,
not for what they think you should be.
Right. And I am a powerful wizard
who can change if I want to.
Just smooth out my little edges.
Wait, hold up. Ok, so,
after my great speech,
you're still going to change
your personality with magic?
Well, just the parts that nobody likes.
So, you're going to change
your whole personality?
I owed you for the clambake comment.
- All right.
- Yeah, that's good.
Selfish, mean and tired of rejection.
Take these parts to a place of reflection.
Alex, are you ok?
I think so. Did it work?
I don't know. You look the same.
Here, let me test you.
What do you think of my clambake outfit?
Mm. It's horrible...
That you didn't make me one.
- Oh, it worked!
- I'm totally nice!
Wait.
If you still have all your good parts,
where did all your bad parts go?
Hey! Let me out of here, you ugly hags!
And I found my bad parts.
Oh, come on. She doesn't seem that bad.
I can smell that nasty outfit
all the way from here!
- Oh, I am not afraid of you!
- Well, come and get me, lobster girl!
Harper, don't let me taunt you.
Hey, maybe she's like a bird.
She'll be quiet if we cover her up.
Hey! Take this off!
Oh, Alex. You have no
idea what you've started.
Did you find Max?
No.
But I found out where my
cousins keep their cannolis.
Jerry, you're supposed to be
looking for your son, not dessert.
Let me have a bite of that. Come on.
- Oh, Max!
- Where?
Oh!
Mmm.
Let's just go home and try to
lure Max back with this cannoli.
- Ok.
- What I'm saying.
There's not going to be any left.
- Let's get a couple to go.
- Ok.
Where are you going? Thieves!
Buon giorno. We're just
looking for our son.
We're not stealing.
Carmela? Cousin Carmela?
Jerry Russo!
Bianca, Gino, put your wands down.
Geraldo!
Cugino Geraldo!
Look at you. You still have a baby face.
It's so smooth.
Oh, that's just the
grease from the cannoli.
- Carmela, this is my wife, Theresa.
- Oh, Theresa!
Nice to meet... too tight.
Too thin. This one is like a bread stick.
Hey, Geraldo, what are you doing here?
The reunion isn't for month, huh?
Oh, who cares? Let's eat.
- Benvenuto!
- Max.
I'm sorry. I just love meeting people.
Hi, Max Russo.
We have been looking all over for you.
This is our son, Max. I'm sorry.
He saw a pretty girl through the Wizard
Speed Pass and came to find her.
You have a Wizard Speed Pass?
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Only the most powerful
wizards can create those.
Ah, but your Family Wizard, Alex Russo.
Yes. Alex is very powerful, and very...
Irresponsible!
Just because you say it loud and weird
doesn't make it Italian, Jerry.
There's that girl. I have to meet her.
She might be the future Mrs. Max Russo.
Mrs. Russo! Mrs. Russo!
Your son likes Francesca?
What's so funny?
Francesca is his cousin!
Ewe.
Theresa, did Geraldo tell you that we were
wizards in training at the same time?
We had so much fun.
Geraldo, remember I used to tickle you?
Stop, stop! Get the bread stick.
Get the bread stick.
No. No, oh no.
So, what do you think about
taking accordion lessons with me?
Well, why wouldn't I?
You're my best friend.
It's like a dream come true.
Ok. I'm ready!
- What do you think?
- I think it's missing something.
- Come here.
- Oh.
- Oh, this is the best day of my life.
- Oh, I'm so happy you're happy.
Thank you, Alex. You're such a good friend.
- Now, take it off.
- What, why?
Because even though I love that you finally
appreciate something I like to do,
it's just not you and,
I don't need it to be.
Thank you.
Besides, I can pull off a clambake outfit.
On you, it just looks stupid.
What was that?
Oh! Something I think is going
to take up the rest of the day.
Harper, grab the fishing net.
We might need it to catch me.
Yup. I broke out.
Ok, where would a Bad Alex go?
Usually, only as far as the
couch, but that door is open.
Oh, gosh.
What are you doing?
You know, I really should have
made a shawl out of this net.
Carmela, this cheese is amazing.
Oh yeah, Papa Fabrizio makes it.
Eh.
We need find me before
I do something bad...
Hi, Mom and dad. Guess what? I've changed.
Yeah, into a third grade art project.
No, no, no. Not that, dad. Guess what?
All the part of me that has all
of those bad things is gone.
Yup. Gone. Nowhere to be seen.
Unless of course you've seen it.
Mom, dad, from now on I promise...
To be the unselfish grown-up
you expect me to be.
I don't believe her.
Me neither.
Seriously, why are you
wearing a clambake outfit?
Because my best friend asked me to.
Dad, sometimes you need to do
things to make others happy.
Now, I definitely don't believe her.
Look, I still don't like
the way we got here...
But they're feeding us. So you
might as well meet the family.
Everyone, I'd like you to meet our friend
Harper, and our Family Wizard, Alex!
Oh.
So cute.
Pooka-pooka-pooka!
Just like your father!
- Why is she tickling me?
- Pooka-pooka-pooka!
Excuse me, I'm looking for a girl that's
about this tall and this beautiful...
Hey it's you.
You know my name?
Or, wait, does it just take that
long to say my name in Italian?
I don't understand what
you're saying right now.
I'll try the language of love with you.
Ok, maybe you don't speak that language.
Oh, Max. I'll save you.
Not really.
Thanks, Alex. They kiss really weird here.
All right. I'm safe in a bracelet. Thanks.
Safe or trapped?
By that evil chuckle, I'm
going to go with "trapped".
And this is where we press the
finest grapes in all of Tuscany.
Oh, that looks like hard work.
Please. Stomping your feet isn't hard work.
Yeah, filling bread rolls
with cold cuts all day.
That's hard work.
Geraldo...
Why don't you try it?
- Oh, no. No, thanks.
- Ah...
- Pooka-pooka-pooka!
- Ha-ha-ha! Ok. Ok.
- You too, Theresa.
- Oh, no, no, no. I'm ok.
- Get in.
- No, no, no.
- Theresa, get in.
- No thank you.
Get in!
Si, senora.
It's nice to appreciate my Mom and
dad doing something together.
Old me would've just been thinking
of ways to make fun of them.
- Oh.
- Oh, it's so squishy.
Ugh. And the worst part
is, I kind of like it.
Thanks a lot, Jerry. You know
what this reminds me of?
The time the bathtub backed up and you
made us take showers in there anyway.
Don't blame me. You were the one who
said, "oh, handsome vineyard guy"...
"You're so strong, the way
you squash those grapes".
I never said that.
- Oh, yes, you did.
- Oh, please.
- You imagined it.
- Oh. Oh, really?
Your insecurities imagined it.
Aha!
Ooh.
Hey, you know, they should
really have machines for this.
- Don't you think?
- Oh!
You know what? Yes, I do.
I would never disrespect you like that!
- Oh, honey, wait.
- What?
You love me so much you got so jealous?
- Oh, honey...
- Good!
Aw. They found a way to make it worse
for themselves without my help.
Changing me was great.
My cousins! Where did they go?
Oh, no. Harper, do you think my bad side
could've done something
terrible to my parents?
Hmm, let's see. All of your bad
is concentrated into one you.
- Do you want to finish where that's going?
- I get it, I did it.
Where are we?
Dad. You're not going to like this.
Oh, it's just Alex. Thank you
for cleaning me up, Mija.
Now, get me out of here. It's stuffy.
What's your hurry? Handsome
vineyard guy waiting for you?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who had to prove what a big
macho man you were with your cold cuts.
Yeah-ha! They're delicious!
Hey, hey, hey, hey. I can't
concentrate on the evil
plan we have going here if you
two are flappin' your yappers.
Evil plan?
You remember when I said, "you're
not going to like this?"
This is what I was talking about.
Who's "we?"
Excellent, Alex.
Hello, Russo's.
Hey, it's that guy. Hey, did you ever
remember that message from Justin?
Just as I thought.
Alex! You don't have to do this.
So, what's next?
How would my partner like a little
road trip to the Tower of Pisa?
Dominic is evil?
Is it weird he's even more attractive now?
- Harper. He took my family.
- Oh yeah, right. I won't date him.
Even as a young wizard I knew
that some day my dreams...
Though disturbing, would come true.
And so, from this high vantage point, we
will launch the final steps to my plan
to rid the world of mortals and then...
You know, it's really kind
of killer on the calves.
That's a nice story, can we
get to what this thing does?
Right. This device...
Replicates spells.
Once energized with
sufficient wizard power,
it will cast a spell
repeatedly across Earth.
I call it the "Dominic One Thousand".
Is that too self-centered?
You're asking the wrong girl.
I designed the Dominic One
Thousand to imprison every mortal,
thereby paving the way for a new
Wizard World that I will rule.
- Uh, that last part again?
- That we will rule.
All that is needed is a spell cast by our
generation's most powerful wizard...
Alex Russo.
All right. Well, then let me at it.
No offense, you're just a knock-off.
You don't have all of her powers.
I have enough powers to scorch a hole
in your little purple jacket there.
Point taken.
All right. So, what if your "all
powerful" Alex doesn't come?
Oh, she'll come...
To save her family.
Wait, wait, wait. I'm confused.
Are we tiny or are they giants?
So if it's called the Leaning Tower
of Pisa, where is all the pizza?
What?
Alex, you need to come up with a plan.
I'm not good with heights.
Or substandard architecture.
You're fine, Harper. Just don't
look down, it'll make you dizzy.
Oh, Too late. Dizzy. Going down.
Wait, Harper!
Oh. All right then. Ha ha.
So, this is the top of the Tower of Pisa.
Woo. Would you check out that view.
That is breathtaking. My
breath has been taken...
- From my lungs.
- I know, right?
- We should post this on Wiz-agram.
- We should.
- Can you take a picture?
- Yeah, let's do that.
Ready? Say, "cheese".
- Harper, run!
- Ah!
Yes.
Harper has joined your family in captivity.
- You let them go right now or I'll...
- You'll what?
Don't forget, I have all the bad.
Yeah, well...
I look really cute in that outfit.
I know. I wasn't really sure
about the boots at first but...
Focus on the mission.
Yeah, I heard all about your mission.
Clear out the mortal world so that you
can make room to rule all evil wizards.
Good. You're up to speed.
Now, for that spell...
- Never.
- Why would you underestimate me, Alex?
Perhaps you remember my
very determined uncle.
- He had wings.
- Gorog.
I came to finish what
you took from my uncle.
But where he failed, I will succeed.
My own wizard empire right here on Earth!
Ow! Why are these stupid bells here!
Maybe to knock some sense into you
because I'm never doing that spell.
My family is more important than anything.
Now give me the bracelet.
You're so stubborn with that spell.
Perhaps if I fill up one more
charm, it will convince you.
Mason!
No!
Mason. You're ok.
Get tired of Dominic already?
What? I don't care about him.
He's some crazy wizard who's weaving some
sort of wicked web to take over the world.
Well, you're some kind of
wicked web weaver yourself.
What are you talking about?
I saw you at the Villa with Dominic,
you two looked quite chummy.
No. That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Dominic tricked me into
casting out my bad side.
That's who you saw. There's
another me walking around.
And I have to get you out of here
before she finds you. Let's go.
I knew I wasted time with that hug.
- Two Alex's?
- Mason, get away from her.
She's with Dominic, and they're
trying to take over the world.
Nice try, me. Mason, she's the bad one.
Let's go.
No! Don't listen to her. I'm the good one.
She's the bad one.
Well, isn't this a sticky wicket.
Mason, please believe me.
She's trying to trick you.
She doesn't even know how I dress.
That is something Harper would wear.
No, no, no, no. I'm wearing it
because Harper asked me to.
Ok, that doesn't even sound like me.
Thank goodness. I hope you and Dominic rot.
Mason, no!
- Where are we?
- The Leaning Tower of Pisa.
Oh. Very romantic.
I think so.
Dominic.
Oh, no.
Aw. You picked the wrong Alex.
Oh. Now, this is what I call a
"take over the world" look.
As for you...
Max, who joined us over there?
Hey, it's Mason.
What have I done? I can't even
"grow up" when I try to grow up.
I don't even deserve to
be The Family Wizard.
Justin does.
And he'd know what to do.
Beep, beep, boop, beep, beep...
Professor Justin Vincenzo Pepe Russo is...
People should appreciate
you for who you are,
not for what they think you should be.
Harper's right.
Everybody should just get over it.
I'm not perfect, I'm just...
A wizard who has to save the world, again.
Ugh!
Ok, Dominic wants a spell?
I'll give him a spell...
With a little bit of a surprise.
Ok, I'm here to get my family back.
Let's do this.
Excellent.
Aw, she's here to save the family.
How sweet. Ugh.
Dominic, give me the bracelet, and
I'll do the spell for your machine.
Agreed. Give it to her.
Wait...
I know me.
We'll give her the bracelet and she'll
flash out without doing the spell.
Right. Spell first then the bracelet.
Nice try, but I know me, too.
I'll do the spell and you'll
keep my family anyway.
No bracelet, no spell.
- Spell first!
- Bracelet first.
- Not doing anything...
Spell first! Spell first!
Stop it!
Tower of Pisa that hurt!
Alex will cast the spell at the same time
Bad Alex gives you the bracelet, agreed?
- That's a good idea.
- Well, why didn't you think of it first?
One wave, two waves, three waves, four.
Every mortal be no more.
Excellent. The world will now
be wiped clean of mortals.
Ow! And then we wipe it clean of bells.
Was this how you wanted it to work?
Ok, the Leaning Tower of Pisa may
not have been the ideal place
for my Dominic One Thousand,
but it's working.
Every mortal will be
imprisoned in these beads.
Are you sure you don't want
a bucket or something?
The bracelet, please.
You know, Alex, now is the time to join us.
With your powers, we can rule
more than just this world.
Thank you for remembering
I'm a powerful wizard.
Powerful enough that I can
undo any spell I create.
No!
The mortals who were
gone before, can now...
What are you doing? I was
about to fix everything
before you guys swirled me out of there.
Well, if you're looking
for someone to blame,
you can just point your
fingers at yourself.
If you had fingers, I mean.
- Told you it was too soon.
- It wouldn't have mattered.
She's obviously stalling.
Don't you understand? The spell
replicator is still capturing mortals.
You have to let me go, so I
can save the world, again.
There he is! Grab him, get him!
Dominic, the Crystals of Justice recognize
you as an esteemed member of WizTech.
Do you have any testimony?
I most certainly do.
Alex Russo had no intention
to undo her spell.
She is a powerful, but selfish wizard.
Why does everybody keep saying that?
So powerful that she put me under her
spell to take the blame for her crime.
Spell?! He's lying!
You need look no further than the fact that
she extracted her own evil personality
and cast the spell into
the Dominic One Thous...
Alex One Thousand.
That's what she called it.
Alex Russo, do you deny this?
He's twisting things. He set me up.
Silence!
The evidence against you is overwhelming.
After careful deliberation,
we, the Crystals of Justice,
find you guilty as charged and
sentence you to no dessert for a week!
Oh.
Well, that's not that bad.
Oh, no, sorry. I was reading
the wrong subsection.
It's actually death.
Death by chocolate?
No! Death by death!
What?! No! It's Dominic you want, not me!
You will be incarcerated until
your sentence is carried out.
Wait! No! Please! You have to believe me!
I didn't do anything! He has my family!
I hope you got a last glimpse of
Alex before she meets her end.
You won't get away with this!
Already have.
You have a girl's bracelet on!
No! It's a uni-bracelet.
Dominic, if you had a spine,
you'd let me out of here,
so you and I can settle
this like gentlemen.
This just in, it's been reported
that people around the world
have been mysteriously disappearing.
As of now, there is no official...
Uh...
In other news, the people of
the world are becoming...
This is bad. We should eat.
Why did I choose the Tower of Pisa?
I'm wondering the same thing, dude.
Nonetheless, Alex is now doomed.
And best of all, her loved ones had
a front row seat to her conviction.
Dominic, one of those charms is broken.
- Mason.
- Yep.
This is ridiculous. I've got
to try to get out of here.
Hello! Hello!
I'm going to use magic to blow this
door down, so you better stand back.
And let me apologize in
advance for the mess I make.
I am really nice.
Double-Decker bus, that was close!
Mason, I'm so glad you're here.
Look, I just want to say
I'm so sorry for ruining
your picnic and being
selfish and immature...
Alex, there's no time for that now. You
must save humanity from Dominic and...
Well, you.
But I can't. I can't get out.
This dungeon is magic-proof.
Well, then, let's find out
if it's Werewolf-proof.
Thank you.
If you're really grateful,
you'd scratch behind my ears.
Oh. That's the spot. All right.
- Come on, we gotta go.
- Oh.
And more people are mysteriously
disappearing around the globe.
The government asks that everyone
remain calm and in there houses.
And now for the sports.
Antonio, por favor tell all
the workers to come inside.
Eh!
Tall, skinny guy, girl in a
bikini, Italian newscaster...
Ryan Gosling?
Hey, guys. Don't mind me, I just
dropped by to give myself a beat down.
Alex?! How did you get out?
Take a guess.
Dominic, it's over.
You're not gonna take over the world
because I'm here to save it, again.
You're not going to be
able to save it this time.
Oh, yeah?
- Here...
- No, I got it. I got it.
You're ruining my moment.
Get her out of here before
she stops the replicator!
I'm not going anywhere.
You will to protect your family...
and your home.
Oh, no. Mason, I'll be right back.
No worries, love. I'll just
stay here and have a snack.
What am I up to?
It's kind of hard chasing
me without my sneaky side.
Oh, I wish I could just rest here.
Ok, maybe I don't care about the kitchen,
but now you've messed with my couch.
- That's weird, right?
- It's really weird.
Hey!
You are a very ugly side of
me and it is time to go.
Sure.
Oh! Why didn't I see myself doing that?
Watch out for the bars.
Don't get cute. I'm the cute one.
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
You're right. This is fun.
Psst. Over here.
I didn't think it'd be that
hard to kick my own butt.
Always underestimating me.
Mason! Mason, wake up! I'm so sorry.
- What did you do?
- I put your dog down.
This is for Mason.
Guess who?
I'm back? Darn I'm good.
Drop it.
And I'll take the bracelet.
Oh. Finish her.
Ok, that definitely got rid of me.
I think.
All right. Now time to get rid of this.
Alex!
Don't you think your time would be
better served saving your family?
Hey, I think I can see Tokyo from here.
Are you guys all right?
- Yeah, we're ok.
- Good job Mija.
Got a little steamy in my bead.
Clearly I can't defeat
the great Alex Russo.
But think of the world I am creating.
It needs you.
I need you.
No surprise. You all
knew I did not like him.
Mason! I was so scared I lost you.
Ugh. Wouldn't it be nice if I was
this determined in everyday stuff?
Haven't we had enough of this?
Can we just call it a day
and get back together.
No way. Dominic went bye-bye, so that
leaves more room at the top for just me.
And thanks to this, I'm going
to take over the world.
You're really bad.
I have no choice.
Oh. Just as I thought.
Too good for your own good.
No one wins if we both lose everything.
What do you mean lose everything?
By all my power is to go.
- No. No, no, no. You can't!
- Alex, what are you doing?
She's casting the spell
to cancel all her powers.
A wizard's essence, spirit and soul
will be nothing but a lump of coal.
- Alex, stop! Don't do it!
- Honey, don't do it!
By all the power vested in me my power
be wrested out and forever free.
Alex Russo...
Once again, you've shown immense
bravery in saving the world.
Consequently, your guilty
verdict is hereby overturned.
Ha! All right.
However, we cannot ignore
the fact that this,
as in every time in the past,
you were involved in bringing the
world to the brink of disaster.
Oh, come on. This was a good moment.
We don't need to dig up the past.
How about you just give me my magic back,
and we can all go home with a warm feeling?
We have been patient, but
you have failed to show the
maturity and responsibility needed
to handle being The Family Wizard.
Therefore, we have decided that it is in
the best interest of the Wizard World
that your powers not be reinstated.
Wait. Wait, please. I've been
trying to help her grow up.
Just give her another chance to change.
No.
I'm tired of everybody wanting
me to grow up, or to change.
Or to not be selfish.
No one is happy for just who I am.
Except for one person.
This is so embarrassing.
She's talking about me.
Harper.
I'm sorry, dude. I thought
she was gonna say you.
You're the only one that
accepts me with all my flaws.
And I know that I have a lot of them.
And even though that there have been times
where you wanted me to
change and I didn't...
You stood by me anyway.
So it's ok if you don't give me my magic.
My best friend Harper is my magic.
Oh, Alex.
I am so proud of you, honey.
Even though you don't have your powers,
you still deserve to be The Family Wizard.
Here.
All right. Let's go home.
Perhaps...
The appreciation you have for
others is in itself very mature.
It seems you have other qualities
that can make a great Family Wizard.
I don't like where this is going.
There still may be hope
for you, Alex Russo.
We grant you one more chance.
I have my magic back.
Thank you.
I'll see you the next time I mess up.
Carmela, grazie for this
beautiful family reunion.
Please come visit us anytime.
Except you.
Can I come back and visit you sometime?
"Stupido". I'm wearing her down.
Alex, before you go, please give
some advice to Bianca and Gino.
- They're our wizards in training.
- Mmm. Yep.
All right. Look, guys, there's gonna
be a lot of work ahead of you.
And it won't really be easy.
And one day, only one of you will
get to become The Family Wizard,
but until then, the most important
thing to remember is...
Have as much ridiculous fun
with magic as you can.
All right. Guys, this has been a great
trip but there's no place like home.
Let's go.
Uh, hang on, Harper.
What happened in here?! The kitchen!
My couch!
Alex!
I think we should stay in Italy a while.
Action!
You say, "here we go".
What?
- You say, "oh, here we go".
- Oh.
Action!
I still don't like the way we got here.
But they're feeding us.
Your own personal drive-in?!
What? What did I do?
Come on, dad. I-I... I spit popcorn.
I'm sorry. Ok.
I don't know how to say wizard...
I got an invitation from
my cousin, Carmela,
in Italy, inviting us to a re-usso...
Russo.
I got an invitation in Italy
for a re-usso family reunion.
A while ago, I got an invitation
from my cousin, Carmela, in Italy...
I got an invitation from
my cousin, Carmela,
in Italy, inviting us to a re-usso...
I'm not doing it!
Sync & corrections by P2Pfiend.
Www.Addic7ed.Com.