Welcome to the grand
re-opening of wiztech.
We owe a big debt of gratitude to
justin russo for saving wiztech
By removing the plastic balls
from our hallowed halls.
And we know how dangerous
plastic is to wizards.
we hate plastic! We hate plastic!
Thank you, thank you. We're wizards.
We all hate plastic, right?
Saving wiztech wouldn't have been possible
without the generous financial support
Of the wizworld industries,
so let's...
I, uh, hope that's ok
with you, professor.
Of course. A few advertisements
is a small price to pay
For the reopening of
our beloved school.
As long as the sign
isn't made of plastic.
Ahh.
Now, I would like to invite
wiztech student, hugh normous,
To cut the ceremonial ribbon.
Oh, no thanks. My giant hands
will never fit in those scissors.
I'll have to use my own.
- Gee...
- Oh, are you kidding me?
Whoa. Finally.
Tv how I want it.
All commercials.
Thanks for coming
back with me, alex.
And I promise I'll make you forget about
that boyfriend who broke your heart.
Yeah.
Dean.
Almost forgot about him.
Thanks for hitting the
reset button on that.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No, this is a new start for you.
You have no idea
what's possible here.
And you're a very special girl.
very, very special.
More special than
you will ever know!
Um, I'm sorry. I can't hear you
with all this evil thunder.
- Oh. I said you're special.
- Oh, thank you.
ominous thunder and
lightning brought to you by
The wizworld weather channel.
Now, that could get annoying.
You think this would look
good with my board shorts?
- I'm gonna get it anyway.
- Ok. You do that.
* well, you know everything's
gonna be a breeze *
* that the end will no
doubt justify the means *
* you can fix any problem
at the slightest ease *
* yes, please *
* well, you might find out
it'll go to your head *
* when you write a report
on a book you never read *
* with a snap of your fingers
you can make your bed *
* that's what I said *
* everything is not what it seems *
* when you can get all you
wanted in your wildest dreams *
* you might run into trouble
if you go to extremes *
* because everything
is not what it seems *
* everything is not what it seems *
* when you can have what you
want by the simplest of means *
* be careful not to mess
with the balance of things *
* because everything is not *
* what it seems *
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Junior, I cursed the castle
So I could turn the whole
place into a ball room
For the best birthday ever.
Now it's ruined.
Dad, I have a better evil plan.
To restore our
family's evil powers.
Oh, now, that is a
fantastic birthday gift.
But you know, I'd rather have
some of those shoe skates.
Size ten.
Dad, focus.
- All right.
- All we need to do
Is get alex russo up to
the tower of evil with me.
And then we can turn this place
into an evil wizard school.
- Dad?
- Hmm?
That is a great evil plan.
I am proud of you.
yeah, well, actually,
I didn't think of that.
Justin russo gave me the idea.
Oh, well, take credit
for it, anyway.
And that's evil.
Now, in the meantime,
Make sure no one sees this.
Jiggly fruit dessert!
My party's back on.
No!
No, this is alex's boyfriend.
I hid him in here
in the supply closet
So we can get alex up
to the tower of evil.
That sounds delicious.
Dad, I know what you're thinking.
Don't eat it!
Stop it!
Oh. And, um, also,
I need you to get rid of this silly
wooden card alex's boyfriend made for her.
Oh, isn't that sweet?
- Dad, you're evil.
- Right.
Oh, hey. Cool booth. Who's this?
- My father.
- The evil one?
Yes, I am.
But defeated.
- By your brother?
- Oh, right.
I'm horribly defeat...
I'm terribly defeat...
I'm a mess. Just
selling t-shirts here.
Not hiding anything back there
in jiggly, fruity dessert.
You are not good at hiding things!
And by hiding things,
I mean hiding......What amazing
deals these t-shirts are.
- These are pretty good deals.
- Yeah.
- Do you have this in blue?
- I'll look in the supply closet.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Let's just, uh...
Oh, look. It's a blue.
Thank you.
You better get to class. - When I was
with dean we never went to class.
Well, I'll try and be a
better influence on you.
Oh. A lot of people have tried.
Good luck with that.
Well, uh, hey,
how about after class
We have a picnic in this great place I know,
on top of the tower of evil.
Oh. I was told to never go
to places that are evil.
Oh, it was just named after...
...William. Evil.
The architect.
He's famous for a lot of buildings.
- Oh, yeah, I've heard of him.
- You have?
No, I was just trying
to impress you.
Hey, hugh.
That's funny.
It sounded like I said, "hey, you."
Anyway.
What are you doing there,
pulling a cereal box on a wagon?
No, it's not cereal.
- It's a massive billboard.
- Oh.
Wizworld industries picked
me to haul it around.
You know, 'cause I'm a giant.
Well, if I order the cool binoculars
on the back, maybi could see it.
You think all these advertisements
around here are a bit too much?
Well, if by "a bit too much"
you mean "a bit too terrific,"
Then yes! Check this out.
"why buy wizworld? Why not?"
I, uh... I wouldn't wear
that in class if I were you.
Oh, I'm wearing it for class.
Sign wearing 101.
- That's a class?
- Uh-huh.
What about learning wizardry
and spells and potions?
All the things that I
love about wiztech.
whoo!
Wizworld industries!
They've got products, yes, they do.
They've got products
to sell to you. Whoo!
Wizworld!
I could learn to love that.
No! All this advertising
is corrupting my school!
Whoo!
Oh. Sorry.
I'm working on this for my advertising
class, called "blimp-ertising."
That's it!
Wizworld said they'd put
up a couple of signs.
Those tiny little
executives lied to me.
I need to speak to
professor crumbs.
Here we are.
The entrance to the tower of evil.
Shall we? - I thought you
said we were gonna picnic.
- Where's your basket?
- Um...
A bear took it.
Look, if you're trying to make
me scared of some pretend bear
So you can put your arms around m
I'll play along. Watch.
Oh, no. A bear! Protect me.
Real cute. Well, come on.
There is a wicked view up there.
Although it's nothing
compared to this view.
Why are you looking at me?
Oh, I get it. I'm the view. Duh.
Oh, professor crumbs, look,
I know I brought wizworld industries in,
But nobody's learning anything
except how to buy wizworld products.
Well, wizworld products are
high-quality and affordable.
Hi. This professor has been brought
to you by wizworld industries.
What was that? - Wizworld
industries is sponsoring me.
Kind of like a walk-a-thon,
except I get to keep the money.
This has gone too far.
Hey, justin!
I heard that alex went
to the tower of evil.
Where did you hear that?
That's what everybody's
talking about.
Well, that, and my
awesome sign flipping.
Not to worry.
Alex is perfectly safe
As long as she doesn't go up
there with ronald longcape.
That's exactly who she
went up there with.
- Oh, no.
- What do you mean, "oh, no?"
I mean, if alex goes up to the tower of
evil and plays the tetherball of evil,
- She'll become evil.
- Oh, I love tetherball.
It's the only ball that
you can never lose.
If ronald and she become evil,
then they have the evil strength...
To take over wiztech
and make it evil.
I knew that guy was evil.
But then he talked me into
believing that he wasn't evil.
Which is totally evil of him.
Come on. We've got to go stop them.
I'll stay here.
Ooh, lovely.
This is the strangest
greeting card I've ever seen.
I like this one, yes.
I don't think anybody's
gonna mind that.
Oh, wow.
It's so romantic up here.
We should look at the stars.
It's kind of our thing.
Yeah. And you know what else is
our thing? Playing tetherball.
Playing tetherball? No, it isn't.
Well, can it be?
Uh, no. I think looking at the stars
is more romantic than tetherball.
Well, then,
how about we stand here.
Next to this pole and
look up at the stars
And maybe just bat the
ball around a little.
I gotta tell you, ronald,
I'm not all that into playground games.
I'm really into
just being with you.
Come on, alex. Just one game.
I don't even know how to play.
You just keep hitting it
back and forth for a while.
Sounds complicated. No.
- Hit it.
- No.
- No!
- Hit it!
- Hey, I'm doing it.
- Good. Keep going.
It's glowing. It's working!
- Why is it glowing?
- This is good. This is good!
Why is this good?
- 'cause it's our thing.
- It's not our thing.
alex, no!
Whoo! That was a lot of stairs!
I should really run instead of
hiding under the bleachers during pe.
why didn't you guys
just take the elevator?
There's an elevator?
There needs to be better
signage in this tower of evil.
What are you guys even doing here?
Alex, you gotta stop playing
tetherball or you're gonna turn evil.
You're too late, justin.
In less than a minute,
alex and I will have turned evil,
To destroy wiztech and begin
our evil lives together.
- What?
- Oh, I heard him.
He said that you and
he are gonna start
Your evil lives together.
Congratulations.
It's too late to stop
the evil, justin.
Your sister has served her purpose.
Wait. Is that why you
brought me up here?
For evil? You used me to
complete your evil plan?
Well, it could have been any russo.
Come on, justin,
let's go spit over the edge.
I guess it had to be you.
Max, we're trying to stop evil.
You fight evil your way,
I'll fight it mine.
You lied to me, ronald. You told me
that I was special and I fell for it.
- I can't believe I broke up with dean.
- He broke up with you.
Look, the story we're telling everybody
is that I broke up with him, ok?
Maybe you won't turn evil.
Maybe it's not too late.
wizworld industries
is proud to announce
That evil will commence in three,
two, one...
Evil.
Yeah, it's too late.
I don't look like him, do I?
Professor, we're too late. - I would have
been here sooner, but somebody spit on me.
I had to change my robes.
Bull's eye! - yeah, well,
you didn't make it.
My evil powers have been restored.
I am taking over wiztech
and making it evil!
and professor crumbs,
Um, I'm firing you.
And just to prove that I am evil,
I'll take that beard.
Thank you.
Before I go, I'd like
to give alex something
That I believe belongs to her.
I can't get used to looking
at him without the beard!
It's from dean.
That's impossible!
"dear russo,
I was thinking, maybe I
should start calling you alex,
So here it goes.
Dear alex, I like you.
Signed, moriarti.
I mean, dean."
Aw, dean.
And there's not a grade on it.
It wasn't an assignment.
- Then why'd he break up with me?
- He didn't. I did.
And you fell for it.
I'm stopping seeing you.
See you in school.
It was you?
Absolutely.
And now, evil is mine.
Oh, my gosh, evil has taken over.
We've got to warn the others.
There's an elevator.
These things are slow.
Wait a minute.
There is a way evil can be undone.
If one of the tetherball
players is in love,
Then evil is cancelled.
- Ronald?
- Hm?
Are you in love with anyone?
Yes.
Is that someone yourself?
Doesn't count.
Alex russo, are you
in love with someone?
Oh, my goodness.
I guess I am.
I'm in love with dean.
I believe you are.
What's happening to me?
The natural power of love!
Ew. I found him attractive?
Well, you can love dean,
- But he can't love you back!
- What are you saying, ronald?
That I have trapped your precious
dean in a jiggly fruit dessert.
And I have hidden him somewhere
you will never find him.
finally.
Oh, hi, son.
Having all this jiggly fruit dessert
around is just too tempting.
I thought I'd better hide
your encased boy up here.
Dean!
Oooh, no.
Dad, this is why
We've failed at being an
evil family all these years.
Evil is one thing but mean is
a hurt that never goes away.
All right!
No one try and follow
us or loverboy gets it.
No, wait, dean!
Justin, we have to take the stairs.
Couldn't we just wait for
the elevator to come back?
Justin, even I know
that's a bad idea.
Fine. Grab my hands.
We're wizards.
We'll take our own way down.
Pillows for feet spell.
Nice one, justin.
I know. Pillows for feet.
Never thought I'd use it.
Oh, man, I got hit
with my own spit.
not your spit. Bull's eye!
- There they are. Let's catch them.
- You'll never catch me.
I think we're gonna catch him.
Never!
We just caught you, dude.
Curses.
I almost got away.
Oh, great.
I was with a guy that
said "curses." not hot.
I'll take my beard back.
Higgly wiggly,
get out of that jiggly
Hey, russo. I came by
to give you something.
Oh, no. I lost it.
- I'll go make you another one.
- No.
I think you dropped it.
Read it to me.
"dear russo,
I was thinking maybe I should
start calling you alex.
So here it goes. Dear alex,
I like you.
Signed, moriarti.
I mean, dean."
- Aw. I love it.
- You do?
Yes.
And I love...
...This card.
- You just said that.
- Well, that's how much I love it.
I love it so much.
more than you will ever know.
Why did you say it like that?
I don't know. I thought I'd give
it a shot but it's not really me.
All right. First one
down the staircase wins.
I'll even give you a
ten second head start.
You're on.
- Go!
- Go. One, two...
...Three...
I knew you were gonna do that
and I'm still gonna beat you.
No! No, no...
wait, wait!
No!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com