Oh, hi, alex. I'm sure you'll be happy to
hear that you and dean broke the school
record
By dating two months,
four days and three periods.
Yep. I know. I saw your banner
in the cafeteria. Thank you.
Oh. You saw that?
Then I guess I wore this "check out
my banner" shirt for no reason.
Hey, you should have
told them where.
"in the cafeteria." ok.
Wow, harper. Sometimes I
feel like you put more effort
Into my relationship
with dean than he does.
I'm sorry. Are you creeped out?
No. You haven't creeped
me out for weeks.
Oh, wait, here he comes.
Hey, russo, I got a
gift for my girlfriend.
Oh, let me guess. Something
you made in woodshop again?
- I love how you know me.
- Oh.
Oh, look. It's a birdhouse.
Or a mailbox.
Wait, which one is it?
Both.
Oh, dean.
These aren't really gifts.
They're assignments.
Just like all the other ones were.
It's just... It'd be nice if you
gave me something more special.
Well, this is my first b-minus.
- It's pretty special to me.
- Wait a minute.
Is that a d turned into a b?
Busted.
* well, you know everything's
gonna be a breeze *
* that the end will no
doubt justify the means *
* you can fix any problem
at the slightest ease *
* yes, please *
* well, you might find out
it'll go to your head *
* when you write a report
on a book you never read *
* with a snap of your fingers
you can make your bed *
* that's what I said *
* everything is not what it seems *
* when you can get all you
wanted in your wildest dreams *
* you might run into trouble
if you go to extremes *
* because everything
is not what it seems *
* everything is not what it seems *
* when you can have what you
want by the simplest of means *
* be careful not to mess
with the balance of things *
* because everything is not *
* what it seems *
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Ok, today's lesson will
be on shape shifting.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Demonstrating shape shifting.
Thank you, justin.
Yeah, could we have a lesson on how to get
your boyfriend to treat you more special?
Do I need to shape shift
back into your mom
And give you one of her
eye rolls and hip twists?
No, wait. I can do it.
- Work it, sister.
- Ooh.
Professor crumbs, to what do
we owe this... This honor?
I need to ask a favor
of your father.
Unfortunately, wiztech has been
completely infested with these.
Ooh!
A school full of wizards
can't deal with those?
Alex, if you had
studied your wizardry,
You would know plastic is impervious
to even the most powerful magic of all.
Because of the plastic
ball infestation,
We can't occupy the
castle or teach magic.
But removing plastic balls is a pricey
proposition wiztech cannot afford.
Well, why don't you sell some of those fancy
words like "proposition" and "afford"?
We need to figure out a way
to get wizworld industry's
Plastic ball removal
specialists to help us.
Plastic ball removal specialists?
- yes.
- Sounds dangerous.
In the meantime, jerry, I was hoping you
could house a few of the wiztech students,
Just for the time being. - I don't see
any problem with housing a few students.
Hey, that's not a few.
No taksies backsies.
Wow. I barely fit
through that door.
Hugh, how many times do I have to tell you,
you're not a giant. All right? I'm bigger
than you.
Well, my overnight
bags beg to differ.
- Hey, hugh.
- Oh, hi, alex.
This is my friend, ronald.
Hello. Alex,
I'm ronald longcape, junior.
Ok.
I'm alex russo, sophomore.
I should be a junior
but I don't test well.
You gotta show up to not test well.
- Oh, hi. Ronald, right?
- Yes.
Thanks for remembering. - I didn't
really remember. That's why I was asking.
But I did remember your order.
Half of a chocolate shake
and two onion rings.
Wait, that's um...
That's not my order.
That's from the table
you just cleared.
Who can keep any of that straight,
right? - Wait, wait.
Oh, I'm sorry. Do you want
me to take your order?
No, I just want to
keep talking to you.
Oh. Oh, that's sweet.
If I weren't working I would
sit down and talk for a while.
Oh, come on. You look like somebody
Who's always looking for an
excuse to get out of work.
What?
No, I am not.
Here, let's discuss it.
So, how's it going out here?
It's a bunch of rambunctious
teenagers with wizard powers.
How do you think it's going?
Sure, you're angry now.
But I promise, in a year
from now we're gonna laugh.
Hey, let's start now.
No.
Ah, professor crumbs.
Just the guy I'm looking for.
While you're staying with us I got
you a track suit just like mine
- So you'll fit in.
- Thanks.
I'm an 850-year-old wizard.
I think I know how to fit in.
- It makes you look skinny.
- Where's the dressing room?
No need.
Right, sweet. Now, when you walk the
swishy sound makes static electricity.
Go find someone to prank
and shake their hand.
Hey, justin, good to see you.
Oh, professor...
Swishy pants. Gotcha.
I'm glad you all think
that's so funny.
Now, what are we gonna do about the
plastic ball infestation at wiztech?
Oh, justin, don't worry.
Everything will work itself out.
- It sounds like you're doing nothing.
- I'm learning to shock people
With my pants.
I'd hardly call that nothing.
I didn't expect to
see anybody here.
Neither did I.
You must be doing what I'm doing.
Trying to figure out what's
going on with wiztech
And who cursed it.
That's exactly what I'm doing!
So, what have you found?
Oh! You got me!
Oh, you're one smart cookie,
figuring out that
I was the one who infested
wiztech with plastic balls.
You did this?
Why?
For a whole bunch of evil reasons.
Here's my list.
Color balls: Evil.
Check.
Taking over wiztech: Eviler.
Throwing the birthday
party I never had...
Not so evil, but I'm doing it.
And then what,
are you gonna open up
Like, a totally evil wizard school?
I like that!
After the birthday party.
The only bummer is, my son isn't here.
He got sent off with the wiztech students.
- Who's your son?
- I'm never gonna tell you.
what's your name?
Ronald longcape, senior.
Is your son ronald
longcape, junior?
Are you a detective? - No,
just a smart boy with a curious mind
And the power to stop you.
Spandau ballet tell me it's true
Take this evil man
you know what to do
Aren't you forgetting something?
If we weren't standing knee-deep in plastic
balls I would use magic on you so bad.
Don't go. I... Um...
You! You! Ronald longcape, junior.
I met your father and he's evil
and my guess is, so are you.
Ronald, have you met
my brother, justin?
It's ok, alex. Um... He's right.
My father is evil. - And you know what
he's gonna do now that wiztech is vacant?
He's gonna open up a
totally evil wizard school.
It's ok. Trust me.
My father always thinks big
but he can never deliver.
And look, I'm telling you that.
It's proof that I'm not evil.
Oh, good enough for me.
Justin, can we have a couple menus?
Not good enough for me. The flame
doesn't fall far from the inferno.
If you knew your father was evil then
why didn't you say anything, huh?
Well, because I was afraid.
I thought if people knew my father was evil,
they'd treat me, well,
Kinda like how you're treating
me now. - Yeah, justin.
You're being very rude.
And what are your specials?
We have the turkey pastrami on
rye and a philly cheese steak.
Now listen up!
I'm gonna fix the problems
your father created at wiztech
And if you try and stop me
I'm gonna know you're evil.
Come on, ronald.
I'm sure we can find a restaurant
Where the wait staff
won't call you evil!
That was a really fancy restaurant.
I mean, you got great food,
you got great bowling.
So, maybe we should go back
there again on our next date.
What?
Oh, no, no. This wasn't a date.
Please don't say "date" because I
have a boyfriend and his name is dean.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
I haven't seen him around.
Well, yeah, 'cause he's probably
in shop class right now,
Making me something that won't
express his true feelings.
Well, let's see how I do.
* there's a rainbow up in heaven *
* and that rainbow spells alex *
* ronald really likes you, girl *
Thank you for a
wonderful day, alex.
Alex, what was going on
out there? Where's dean?
That boy was well inside your
"kiss or clobber" radius.
Oh, um, him? No, no.
That's just a family friend.
He's visiting from wiz...
Uh...Wisconsin, and he said
that we were on a date.
And I said, "no, because I
have a boyfriend, dean."
You do. - Who's not great
at expressing feelings.
- He's not.
- Doesn't mean I don't like him.
- You like him.
- Then ronald left.
- His name's ronald?
- Yes, and I was just with him
And now I kind of miss him.
- You do?
- I do. What am I gonna do?
I'll tell you what
I'm not gonna do.
Study for my history final.
My friend needs me.
Yeah.
Alex, you and dean just broke
the longest relationship record.
I don't know much
about relationships,
But I don't think dating another
guy is the way to celebrate.
I'm not dating ronald.
We just went out to dinner.
Well, it may have
started out as dinner,
But when you guys came back you're all, "I
miss him, I love him, he's the love of my
life."
I never said he was
the love of my life.
I'm sending your story into
a teen magazine for advice
And if you don't let me juice
it up they'll never publish it.
You've got to break up with ronald.
I can't break up with ronald.
I'm not even going out with him.
I see the problem.
Ronald has to go away
for a long, long time.
I'm on it.
Harper, forget that.
Dean's gonna come over so I can tell him I
made a mistake before he finds out from
somebody else
- And it becomes this whole big thing.
- Ok, but if that doesn't work,
I can still make ronald go
away for a long, long time.
What are you gonna do?
Start making him
really uncomfortable
With some of my staring until he goes away.
You know the stare.
Stop it.
You're uncomfortable, aren't you?
Please, harper, stop.
Oh, justin, honey, you'd really
have an easier time in school
If you just dressed
like everybody else.
Mom, please.
I'm dressed for success.
I'm gonna give the wizworld
industry executives
A tour of wiztech so I can convince
them to remove the plastic balls.
Great! Who's gonna
cover your shift?
Me.
Hey, justin, where's your sister?
She told me to come over so I
made her this card in woodshop.
I think I'm finally getting
what she's trying to say,
So I'm trying to say something
I think she might get.
I don't know. She was hanging
out with some dude. Ronald.
Whoa. Ronald?
Yep. His name was
definitely ronald.
Thanks.
Now, 'cause I date your sister I
tell people not to laugh at you.
But you're not
helping me right now.
I'm going on a business trip.
We're gonna tell people you've
got a court date. - All right.
Tell those people I was defending you.
Do you do that?
'cause I need someone. All you have to do
now is prove there's no way I could throw
that far.
I didn't hear that.
I can't be associated with this.
Excuse me.
Are you looking for alex?
Who are you?
I'm ronald longcape, junior.
Dean moragardi. Supposed to be
a junior but I'm a sophomore.
I don't test well.
Hey, hold on.
Alex is off with a
guy named ronald.
- Are you him?
- Um, I'm here with you.
Ah-ha. Exactly. You get that
I don't test well, right?
Look, I think I know where alex is.
- Why don't you come with me?
- All right. Thanks.
Hey, you're ok, ronald.
Let me know if you see that other ronald.
That guy's in big trouble.
Will do.
So, you say you don't
test well? - Nah.
now that you've seen
our wonderful facility
Don't you want to help us
so that we can reopen it
For wizards present and future?
Now, are there any questions?
Can we play in the balls now?
You're the executives
of wizworld industries.
We're not here to
play in the balls.
We're here to see if your company
will help us by removing them.
Ok. We'll help you
clean up the balls
If you let us put up a couple
of wizworld signs around here.
You mean like when sports
drinks sponsor sports arenas?
Yeah, exactly like that.
So, are we gonna play
in these balls or what?
Uh...
Well...
Then, yes. Sure, yes.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
So does this mean we're
getting our school back? Yeah!
Make way! Ow! Ow!
This is unprofessional.
Dean, I'm glad you came over. - Me, too.
There's something I need to talk to you
about.
No, there's something I need to talk to
you about. I wanted to do it in person.
Oh, here, let me
text you right now.
"it's just not working out.
I'm breaking up with you."
What? Wait, what are you saying?
"I can't believe this, dean."
"well, you should,
because..." what are we doing?
You can't be breaking up with me.
Is this because somebody already told
you I was hanging out with this guy?
You mean ronald,
'cause I heard all about that.
Dean, it's true, but it was
just a big misunderstanding.
Ronald's a nice guy and he likes
me and he treated me special,
- But you're my boyfriend.
- Not anymore, I'm not.
Maybe you should make that ronald your
boyfriend. - What are you doing? Stop.
I am stopping. Stopping seeing you.
Forever.
See you in school.
I know you. You're ronald and you better get
out of here, because dean's coming over.
I'm not too worried about dean.
Hey, look. I think I
know where alex is.
Why don't you come with me?
All right, thanks.
Hey, you're ok, ronald.
Let me know if you see
that other ronald.
That guy's in big trouble.
Will do.
So, you say you don't
test well? - Nah.
- Alex isn't in here.
- That's weird.
I thought she was.
Hold on a minute.
You'rehat other ronald.
Piggly wiggly, get in the jiggly
All right. Now, time for
my little dean impression.
Yeah, it's gonna go a
little something like this.
I'm dean. I don't test well.
That'll do.
- That makes me uncomfortable.
- Because it's working.
Guys! Guys!
Guess what?
I saved wiztech. You're welcome.
- How'd you do it, justin?
- It's complicated,
But I got wizworld industries
to remove all the plastic balls
And all we've got to do is let them put
up a few signs advertising their products.
Ooh, like sports drinks
do with sports arenas.
Yes.
Ahh!
Swishy pants gotcha.
You're the one with the beard
and I'm the mature one.
I just wish I could stop
thinking about dean.
See, I know that if I
was your boyfriend,
See, I wouldn't give you
stupid wooden gifts.
How did you know he
gave me wooden gifts?
Um...
It's a classic stupid guy move.
But this is what a
good guy would do.
"I like you. Do you like me?
Check yes or no."
Yes.
Oh, alex, this is perfect.
more perfect than you
could ever imagine.
Wait, why did you say it like that?
No reason.
Well, thanks for taking my
mind off things tonight.
You kinda make me feel special.
Now that your brother
saved wiztech,
And we're going back,
I'm gonna miss you, alex.
And I know it's only been two days,
But it seems like I've known you...
...At least a week.
I'll miss you, too.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't you come back
to wiztech with me?
Really? That seems so sudden.
Yeah, but doesn't it also
seem romantic? - Yeah.
And we can be that couple at
wiztech that everyone looks up to.
Maybe we can even break the
record for longest relationship.
Two months. - I know where
we could get a banner.
You know what?
Maybe change is good.
I'll go back to wiztech with you,
And we'll see about you and me.
That's perfect.
oh, more perfect than
you will ever know.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com