''And that's when the great Chinese
wizard Li first used dragon scales
to build an impenetrable box
for safeguarding one's wand.
And then in the 12th century,
there were nine native--''
Time.
You're supposed to keep your oral reports
under 45 minutes.
Otherwise, you start losing people.
Okay, Alex, you're up.
- Alex?
- Oh, yeah.
Your report on crystal balls:
history, usage, and manufacturing.
Crystal balls: usage and manufacturing.
Oh, l did mine on how to use
the really little ones for earrings.
Cute, huh?
End of report.
You'll try it again tomorrow.
- Max, you're up.
- Okay.
Caldrons:
proper use and maintenance.
How did all these people
get in my room?
- Oh, Uncle Kelbo.
- Uncle Kelbo.
Hello, future voters.
Sorry for dropping in unexpectedly.
Wanted to see my niece and nephews.
Kelbo, what did l say about poofing in
when you visit?
Oh, right, right, right.
lt sets off the smoke alarms.
So, what are you guys up to?
We're doing boring oral reports
without magic.
You know you're wizards, right?
Well, lots of times, Dad wants us to study
magic without actually using magic.
Well, that's because he can't do magic.
You know what l say.
Those who can't take hamburger
and turn it into delicious filet mignon,
teach.
Okay, fine.
l didn't become the family wizard.
But the things l can do
with plain hamburger will blow your mind.
He puts cheese in the meat.
Hey, l've had many, many, many
of his inside-out cheeseburgers.
Tell me about it.
So, what are you working on?
Oh, well, l'm doing a report
on the great Chinese wizard Li.
Chinese wizard Li? He's in my fave five.
He'll come here,
he'll teach you all about his life.
He'll do anything to get away
from his witch of a wife, okay?
By the way,
his wife, she really is a witch.
Li, baby, how's that wife of yours?
Look, l would appreciate it
if l could teach them my way.
Yeah, you're right.
- No more distractions.
- Thank you.
- Oh, l've got presents.
- Oh, presents.
Justin, l got you some opera gum.
Oh, sweet. What's it do?
lt's opera gum. Try singing.
- l think l'll save that for the talent show.
- Great.
Max, for you,
l've got the leprechaun answer blower.
Ask it a question, blow a bubble,
bubble pops, there's your answer.
- Give it a drive.
- Awesome.
Come on, baby. What are the answers
to my social studies test?
Yes-or-no questions only.
But l love that you think big.
And for my favorite niece who l love.
l have for you an Emoto-scope.
Okay. Look through it,
you'll see how people are really feeling.
Oh, cool. l've always wanted one.
Wow, either you're really excited
or your underwear is on too tight.
And Max has no idea what's going on.
Big shocker.
Wow, you're mad inside and out.
Because no one wants to finish
the wizard lesson.
He's right. Who wants to go the zoo?
- The zoo?
Let me rephrase that.
Who wants to go to the zoo
as a monkey?
- You're gonna turn into a monkey?
- All of us are gonna be monkeys.
Sorry, Kelbo.
We frown on random uses of magic.
Okay. Let's talk about it.
l--
Great conversation.
Where are they? You know,
the burgers are almost done.
Kelbo does this every time.
Jerry, they're out having fun
with their uncle. lt's a good thing.
Do you really trust him
to watch our children?
No. But l trust our children
to watch him.
- We had so much fun at the zoo.
- Oh, yeah?
l didn't even turn them into monkeys,
just like you asked.
Oh, good.
So then those aren't monkey tails.
Chocolate?
Oh, man, l wanted to find out some stuff
with my leprechaun answer blower.
Oh, hey, let me ask it a question.
Who is my secret admirer?
l've been getting notes in my locker every
Wednesday for the past three weeks.
Oh, you can't ask it that.
lt only answers yes, no or l don't know.
ls it Cathy Antinocci?
ls it Corrie Montanio?
There's, like, 300 girls in my class.
This might take a while.
Okay. But just don't suck in,
because the answer juice tastes nasty.
Well, l'm glad you're back in time
to watch the basketball game, honey.
Dad, l don't wanna watch basketball.
Basketball?
l got tickets tonight for the basketball
game, up in the wizard luxury box.
You wanna go, Alex?
- What--? The wizard luxury box?
- Yeah. The wizard luxury box.
You know the scoreboard
over center court?
The wizard luxury box is in that.
That sounds amazing. l have to see it.
Dad, can l go?
Wait. You don't wanna watch
the game with me
but now that Kelbo is gonna take you
to some fantastic wizard box, you wanna?
Well, but l don't think you'll be able to,
because your mother has a lot of stuff
for you to do around the house.
No, l don't.
Of course, she should go.
Sounds like a great way
to spend some time with your uncle.
Great. We gotta get going,
because we gotta beat wizard traffic.
- Oh, wait. Let me get my sweater.
- You're a wizard.
Thanks for reminding me.
Cashemerus-appearus
Soft.
- Hey, that's my sweater.
- Oh, l'm sorry, Mom. Let's talk about it.
Great conversation.
So we're in the scoreboard
and we can see everything and everybody
and they can't see us at all?
Yeah.
That's the beauty of the wizard box.
Except it's got one drawback.
- Time out on the floor,
- Cover your ears.
We're trying to get that removed.
So tell me more about this whole
secret admirer thing with your brother.
- You're the secret admirer.
- Yeah.
For the last three weeks,
l've been dropping notes in his locker
saying that he's cute and sweet,
and a bunch of other stuff he's totally not.
- You won't tell Dad, right?
- Of course not.
lt's a classic gag.
l got a finish for you.
Here's what you do.
You get yourself a genie, all right?
Dress your genie up
like his secret admirer.
The minute he spots the genie,
you capture his soul, put it in a lamp.
l love that one.
l wasn't gonna go that far.
Well, you're young.
You got a lot to learn.
- And l bet you could teach me a lot.
- Of course l could.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You have so much more fun with magic
than Dad does.
Okay. Here's a good one.
Hold your head like this.
Cranium revolvus
l love that.
l can't wait for our next school assembly.
- And that's the half,
- Cover your ears.
You're the best, Uncle Kelbo.
Hey, what you got there?
l got another note
from my secret admirer.
They're coming every day now.
Wow, that's exciting.
Do you have any idea who it might be?
No. But she's probably pretty cute.
You see, she dots her l's with hearts,
and that always says cute.
And perfume.
Oh, l can't even smell it,
because of my allergies.
Yep, you're someone's dream.
Someone without pets, grass,
or common house dust.
You know, it's too bad
you don't know who she is.
Hey, l got a great plan to figure it out.
l'm gonna--
You don't wanna hear
my stupid plan, do you?
Oh, no, l wanna hear
all about your stupid plan.
Okay.
l'm gonna hide in this trash can
and stake out my locker.
- Brilliant.
- Yep, and Max is gonna help me.
- He's gonna be your lookout?
- No.
He's gonna stop the wrestling team
from shoving Eugene Troobnick
into the trash can
like they do every day at 3.
- l thought Eugene was homeschooled.
- He is. They go home and get him.
Where is she? l don't wanna teach
the magic safety course twice.
We don't wanna hear it once.
Sorry, we're late. But you know
how much l love the Old West.
lt was great. We went on a cattle drive,
and we took turns branding.
Wanna see mine?
Just kidding.
l'm gonna get me a sarsaparilla
and a nice hot bath.
Partner, l'd love me a sarsaparilla.
Whatever that is. l hope it's root beer.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, you were late, young lady,
and we've all been waiting.
And we're about to start
the magic safety lesson.
Did you guys know most wizard accidents
happen within a mile of the home?
That's because some people
have brothers, and they're not accidents.
Daddy, it's okay that l'm late,
because Uncle Kelbo's been teaching me
magic for the last few days.
ln fact, he and l were talking,
and he said that he could be
my wizard trainer instead of you.
- He did?
- l did?
- You did.
- Hold on.
You--
l did?
- Kelbo, was this your idea?
- No.
Usually, when a guy goes to get a glass
and does a spit take, it says, ''Surprise.''
But at the basketball game,
you said you would teach me.
Yeah, but l was talking more about,
like, pranks and things like that.
Oh, like, Dad has those birthday candles
that never blow out.
No, more like 50 wizards' heads
spinning completely around their bodies.
Oh, that's way better
than the burning-candles thing.
But you guys
love the candles with the:
And the:
Look, l'm honored that you want me to be
your teacher, but that's your dad's job.
Dad's great with Justin and Max,
but l don't think l'm reaching
my full potential with him.
Well, l don't wanna stand in the way
of your full potential.
Maybe Kelbo should teach you.
Maybe you'll actually show up on time
for his lessons.
l will, Dad,
because you know what l was thinking
is that l learn more by doing
than l do by learning.
Then it's done.
Wait a minute. We get to pick
our wizard teachers? Oh, l pick--
Dad.
Excuse us.
We got a reservation for this garbage can.
Oh, this one's full.
There's a stinkier one upstairs.
See you tomorrow at 3, Eugene.
l don't know
how much longer l can hold out.
l'm the one in the trash can.
My leg was asleep, woke up,
and now it's asleep again.
And l'm claustrophobic.
- Someone's coming. l'll act natural.
- Oh, yeah.
Yep, standing here,
being natural, whistling.
Oh, my gosh.
The lunch lady loves you.
lt makes sense.
My milk's always a little bit colder
than everyone else's.
But what are you gonna do?
l'm gonna write her a letter
and tell her l'm flattered
and if l was 20 to 30 years older
and out of options,
maybe our love could flourish.
Okay. Let her down easy.
You don't want warm milk.
Hey, thanks for doing that for me, Doris.
Here's the left-handed mashed potato
scooper you wanted.
Thanks. A lot of people think they're
the same as an ice-cream scooper.
Those people would be wrong.
That was totally an ice-cream scooper.
So that's how you disappear and reappear
ten feet away. Pretty fun, huh?
That's about as magical as walking.
See? What did l tell you?
Not as much fun as poofing in.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, Alex.
You missed a good one today.
We disappeared and then reappeared
ten feet away.
- Wasn't it fun, guys?
- Yeah.
A little more exciting
than that ripening-fruit spell you taught us.
Okay. Well, have a good lesson.
The lair is yours, Kelbo.
Please, leave it how you found it.
Come on, guys.
Oh, hey, Max.
Does anybody want some salted nuts?
Sure, Dad.
Snakes of all different colors.
lt was--
- So, what's our lesson gonna be?
- Oh, l thought we'd take a nap first.
Well, l'll tell you what it's not gonna be,
and that's fruit ripening.
Because it's easy.
All you do is you buy the fruit,
you go into the future,
fruit's ripe, you eat it.
You're gonna teach me about time travel?
l've always wanted to learn that.
Oh, look, the wizard mail's here.
Uncle Kelbo,
can we please focus on the lesson?
Look, we'll read it.
We'll go back in time to before we read it,
and it will be like we haven't even read it.
A sea chimp sample? We used to get
these all the time when we were little.
They're just pets you put in water
and you don't have to feed
or play with them.
They're great. They die before your mom
makes you throw out the smelly water.
Open them up. Come on.
l don't know.
These aren't regular sea chimps.
They came in the wizard mail and Dad
doesn't like us to open the wizard mail.
Some of the stuff
can be dangerous.
Okay, l understand.
But your dad's not your teacher, l am.
And whatever goes wrong,
we can fix with magic.
All right.
But don't you need water
for sea chimps?
Apparently, not.
What--?
That's not gonna work.
Fix it with magic.
Okay, okay, okay. All right. l got it.
Okay. That's what l use in the shower
at cheap motels.
- Sorry.
- Well, use another one.
l can't. l'm panicking.
Guess who l am.
l'm the lunch lady.
l'm in love with Justin.
Give me a kiss, doll face.
Hey, why is Coach Gunderson here?
And why does he look so mad?
Which one of you is Justin Russo?
l think it's you.
You don't shower after gym
because you don't sweat.
Because you walk the mile.
Hey, coach.
What are you doing writing love letters
to my girlfriend, the lunch lady?
She was putting letters in my locker
and l was just trying to let her down gently.
Excuse me. What's going on here?
Your son is trying to tell me
that he's getting love letters
from my girlfriend, the lunch lady.
The lunch lady?
May l see one of these notes?
l have one.
''l love your lightsaber nightlight.''
How would the lunch lady know
you have a lightsaber nightlight?
Alex.
Alex is my 1 4-year-old daughter
and she kind of torments him.
Well, really all of us.
l get it.
You still sleep with a nightlight?
Good.
The dark can be very, very scary.
Keep walking the mile.
And sorry l barked at you.
Lunch lady says l get pretty jealous.
Dad.
- Honey, are you all right?
- Yeah.
l don't know what happened.
l know.
There's water coming out of the lair.
Oh, who's in the lair?
Alex and Kelbo.
They're doing their lesson in there.
Somebody's gotta get into the lair.
We don't know how much water.
lf we open it, it could flood the restaurant.
l know. Hey, you remember the spell
from today, transporting ten feet?
- Come on.
- l'm on it.
Whoa, wait, wait.
l'll be right back.
Okay, okay, l'm ready.
Better safe than sorry.
Justin, get me in there.
Threemetrus-movetrus
Hey, why can l breathe underwater?
lt's due to the fact
that we're sea chimps.
Oh, right. Do something.
Relax. l've been in way worse situations
than this.
lmagine the exact same thing,
except hot lava.
Why were you in hot lava?
Suffice it to say,
l don't know how to make hot coffee.
You opened
the magic sea chimp packet, didn't you?
A little.
l know a spell that will fix this.
Alex, repeat after me.
- l'm a big knucklehead.
Wait a second, that's not a spell.
No, l know.
l just wanted to hear you admit it.
Hey, if anyone here's a big knucklehead,
it's this sea chimp.
Gee, who knows a spell
that will get us out of this mess?
Anyone? Anyone?
Oh, wait. l do.
All right. Alex, say this:
Dehydratus-lougaines, apus-escapus
l just don't get it.
Kelbo said that he could fix it,
but he couldn't and Dad could.
But Dad's not even a wizard anymore.
Well, your dad was always
a much better wizard than l was.
That can't be true. Only one wizard
in each family can keep their powers.
lf Dad was the better wizard,
he'd keep his powers.
- You never told them, huh?
- Told us what?
Honey, l think they're old enough.
We're all getting go-carts?
No.
When Kelbo and your father competed
to see who'd keep their wizard powers,
it was your dad who won the contest.
What?
But wizards can't marry non-wizards,
so your dad gave Kelbo his powers
so that he could marry me.
l think that's the sweetest thing
l've ever heard in my life.
Give your powers up for a girl?
- Yeah, right.
- What?
l can't be--
You guys,
if Dad hadn't given up his powers,
none of us would be here.
Yeah, l made the right decision then,
and l stand by it.
And l should've stood by you, Dad.
Will you still be my wizard teacher?
Please, l beg of you, okay?
Take her on.
You know me. l can't handle it.
l get distracted, and then l get careless,
and then--
This towel is so soft.
Oh, and distracted.
You know, l get distracted.
We get it.
Honey, honey, l'll be your teacher.
But you're still my fun Uncle Kelbo.
l mean, who else gets to say that they
were a sea chimp even for a little while?
Actually, everyone l know.
l've made them all open up
that same packet
because l just love the pretty colors
on the outside.
- The basketball game is on.
- Oh, can l watch it with you?
Yes. l'd love that, honey.
Wait, wait, wait. l've got an idea.
We can all watch it.
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, guys, wanna see something cool?
- Hold your heads like this.
- Oh, what are you talking about?
Cranium revolvus
Oh, this is bunk.
- Okay. You remember what to say, right?
- Yeah.
Excuse me. l was just checking to see
if your refrigerator's running.
As a matter of fact,
my refrigerator is broken.
lt's not running.
What do l do if it's not running?
She's onto us. Run.