1
00:00:26,609 --> 00:00:29,987
DARYL HANNAH: The oceans
<i>are the source of all life on our planet.</i>

2
00:00:31,322 --> 00:00:36,827
<i>Without healthy oceans, no life,</i>
<i>even on land, can continue to exist.</i>

3
00:00:38,371 --> 00:00:42,041
<i>Cetaceans, better known</i>
<i>as dolphins and whales,</i>

4
00:00:42,125 --> 00:00:45,044
<i>have been roaming the oceans</i>
<i>for millions of years.</i>

5
00:00:45,754 --> 00:00:47,546
<i>Yet in only one century,</i>

6
00:00:47,630 --> 00:00:51,050
<i>we have slaughtered many of them</i>
<i>close to extinction.</i>

7
00:00:54,220 --> 00:00:56,764
<i>Despite some efforts to protect them,</i>

8
00:00:56,848 --> 00:00:59,558
<i>human activity has forced</i>
<i>these weakened populations</i>

9
00:00:59,642 --> 00:01:02,311
<i>to face the greatest danger of all,</i>

10
00:01:02,395 --> 00:01:05,773
<i>the destruction of their habitat</i>
<i>and food resources.</i>

11
00:01:07,275 --> 00:01:10,402
<i>We live on land. They live in the oceans.</i>

12
00:01:10,487 --> 00:01:13,197
<i>But we all breathe the same air.</i>

13
00:01:13,281 --> 00:01:14,740
<i>We share the same planet,</i>

14
00:01:14,824 --> 00:01:18,535
<i>yet only a few of us have had</i>
<i>the privilege to meet them underwater.</i>

15
00:01:19,329 --> 00:01:23,874
<i>Let's share their worId for a while</i>
<i>and meet these tribes of the oceans,</i>

16
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:26,293
<i>the dolphins and the whales.</i>

17
00:02:07,877 --> 00:02:11,588
<i>Cruising through the sparkling waters</i>
<i>of the Azores Islands,</i>

18
00:02:11,673 --> 00:02:16,593
<i>these sperm whales can reach 60 feet</i>
<i>in length and weigh up to 45 tons.</i>

19
00:02:17,303 --> 00:02:20,514
<i>They are the largest of all the toothed whales.</i>

20
00:02:22,475 --> 00:02:24,893
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)

21
00:02:40,869 --> 00:02:45,247
<i>Sperm whales are social creatures,</i>
<i>enjoying companionship.</i>

22
00:02:46,040 --> 00:02:49,918
<i>They take care of one another</i>
<i>and even look after the injured.</i>

23
00:02:59,137 --> 00:03:02,014
<i>The females raise their young in nurseries,</i>

24
00:03:02,098 --> 00:03:07,019
<i>one female caring for another's baby</i>
<i>while she dives into the abyss to feed.</i>

25
00:03:13,735 --> 00:03:16,862
<i>The sperm whale, like all marine mammals,</i>

26
00:03:16,946 --> 00:03:19,531
<i>must surface regularly to breathe.</i>

27
00:03:20,742 --> 00:03:22,075
(INHALING)

28
00:03:33,463 --> 00:03:38,759
<i>They also have the ability to dive</i>
<i>up to 7,000 feet for as long as an hour</i>

29
00:03:38,843 --> 00:03:42,512
<i>while searching for their favourite food,</i>
<i>the giant squid.</i>

30
00:04:08,706 --> 00:04:13,502
<i>The scars on his head were most likely</i>
<i>received during fights with his prey</i>

31
00:04:13,586 --> 00:04:16,588
<i>or from an encounter with a jealous rival.</i>

32
00:04:35,066 --> 00:04:38,819
<i>Sperm whales once roamed the Earth</i>
<i>in vast numbers.</i>

33
00:04:39,696 --> 00:04:43,031
<i>They were hunted almost to extinction</i>
<i>during the last century,</i>

34
00:04:43,116 --> 00:04:47,494
<i>mainly because of the precious oil</i>
<i>that fills their huge square heads.</i>

35
00:05:14,397 --> 00:05:18,775
<i>This creature, while hunting,</i>
<i>used to lead fishermen to squid,</i>

36
00:05:18,860 --> 00:05:22,070
<i>thus becoming commonly known</i>
<i>as the pilot whale.</i>

37
00:05:25,158 --> 00:05:28,785
<i>At only 1 5 feet,</i>
<i>this toothed whale is relatively small.</i>

38
00:05:36,127 --> 00:05:39,671
<i>These social creatures live in small,</i>
<i>very organised pods</i>

39
00:05:39,797 --> 00:05:43,592
<i>and will, in turn, join larger pods</i>
<i>headed by one leader.</i>

40
00:05:44,469 --> 00:05:47,346
<i>They will blindly follow that leader anywhere,</i>

41
00:05:47,430 --> 00:05:49,890
<i>sometimes to their own detriment.</i>

42
00:05:50,975 --> 00:05:54,603
<i>When one strands on a beach,</i>
<i>the others will follow.</i>

43
00:05:56,564 --> 00:05:59,107
<i>Why? We don't know for sure.</i>

44
00:06:01,069 --> 00:06:04,112
<i>Sadly, still slaughtered in some places,</i>

45
00:06:04,697 --> 00:06:08,950
<i>only about 1 85,000 pilot whales</i>
<i>remain in the world today.</i>

46
00:06:23,049 --> 00:06:26,968
<i>They seem to be smiling at us,</i>
<i>the spotted dolphins.</i>

47
00:06:28,179 --> 00:06:32,307
<i>Of all of the tribes of the ocean,</i>
<i>they've become our best friends.</i>

48
00:06:36,312 --> 00:06:38,105
(DOLPHINS SQUEAKING)

49
00:06:39,524 --> 00:06:44,027
<i>Like the sperm whale,</i>
<i>dolphins are actually toothed whales,</i>

50
00:06:44,487 --> 00:06:47,656
<i>grabbing and tearing at prey with their teeth.</i>

51
00:06:54,497 --> 00:06:56,206
(DOLPHINS CLICKING)

52
00:07:08,678 --> 00:07:12,848
<i>These spotted dolphins were grey</i>
<i>when they were born and spotless.</i>

53
00:07:13,683 --> 00:07:16,476
<i>Very social, they, too, live in pods.</i>

54
00:07:27,613 --> 00:07:30,699
<i>Dolphins love to interact with each other.</i>

55
00:07:30,825 --> 00:07:34,953
<i>They play, touch, fight, hit and caress.</i>

56
00:07:39,417 --> 00:07:40,667
<i>Check this out.</i>

57
00:07:40,751 --> 00:07:45,714
<i>Displaying amazingly intelligent behaviour</i>
<i>and a wonderful facility for teamwork,</i>

58
00:07:45,840 --> 00:07:50,343
<i>these adults have intentionally picked up</i>
<i>some algae from the sea floor</i>

59
00:07:50,887 --> 00:07:52,554
<i>to start a game.</i>

60
00:07:58,102 --> 00:08:00,812
<i>They play for fun, not fighting for the piece</i>

61
00:08:00,897 --> 00:08:04,524
<i>but cordially passing it around</i>
<i>like a game of catch.</i>

62
00:09:29,569 --> 00:09:32,195
<i>One of the great mysteries</i>
<i>of the animal kingdom</i>

63
00:09:32,280 --> 00:09:35,615
<i>is the spine-tingling humpback whale song.</i>

64
00:09:37,868 --> 00:09:39,494
(SNORTING)

65
00:09:47,795 --> 00:09:49,379
(SCREECHING)

66
00:10:03,853 --> 00:10:05,186
(SQUEAKING)

67
00:10:21,370 --> 00:10:25,373
<i>The male humpbacks create eerie,</i>
<i>hauntingly beautiful tunes.</i>

68
00:10:25,958 --> 00:10:30,670
<i>Are they mating calls to females</i>
<i>or warning calls to ward off other males?</i>

69
00:10:31,422 --> 00:10:33,381
<i>We don't know for sure.</i>

70
00:10:50,399 --> 00:10:51,816
(VOCALISING)

71
00:11:20,805 --> 00:11:24,766
<i>These complex communications</i>
<i>can be heard from great distances</i>

72
00:11:24,850 --> 00:11:27,602
<i>and may be repeated for several hours.</i>

73
00:11:40,282 --> 00:11:42,242
(VOCALISING CONTINUES)

74
00:12:25,244 --> 00:12:29,956
<i>This graceful and elegant underwater ballet</i>
<i>is one of the most beautiful shows</i>

75
00:12:30,040 --> 00:12:33,334
<i>we will ever see</i>
<i>below the surface of the ocean.</i>

76
00:13:17,713 --> 00:13:20,298
<i>The humpback is a baleen whale.</i>

77
00:13:20,382 --> 00:13:25,220
<i>Instead of teeth, they have baleen plates</i>
<i>that filter food out of the water.</i>

78
00:13:30,226 --> 00:13:32,811
<i>They have an appetite to match their size,</i>

79
00:13:32,895 --> 00:13:37,899
<i>eating an average of 5,000 pounds of krill</i>
<i>and small schooling fish every day.</i>

80
00:13:59,964 --> 00:14:02,715
<i>With a life expectancy of 50 years,</i>

81
00:14:02,800 --> 00:14:08,096
<i>a humpback whale can reach over 60 feet</i>
<i>in length and weigh up to 50 tons.</i>

82
00:14:13,102 --> 00:14:14,978
<i>Humpbacks are nomads,</i>

83
00:14:15,604 --> 00:14:19,607
<i>migrating to the icy polar waters</i>
<i>for the summer where they feed.</i>

84
00:14:20,109 --> 00:14:24,612
<i>Summer's gone, they will make the 3 month,</i>
<i>3,000 mile journey</i>

85
00:14:24,697 --> 00:14:27,782
<i>back to tropical waters to breed and calve.</i>

86
00:14:35,165 --> 00:14:37,792
<i>Today, despite some recovery,</i>

87
00:14:37,918 --> 00:14:41,379
<i>the humpback whale is still a victim</i>
<i>of human activity,</i>

88
00:14:41,463 --> 00:14:43,715
<i>and its future is precarious.</i>

89
00:14:59,857 --> 00:15:03,610
<i>The beluga whale</i>
<i>lives in the frigid waters of the Arctic.</i>

90
00:15:07,531 --> 00:15:11,492
<i>Born grey, they don't turn white</i>
<i>until six years of age.</i>

91
00:15:18,500 --> 00:15:19,834
(SQUEAKING)

92
00:15:25,716 --> 00:15:29,761
<i>It is also called the sea canary</i>
<i>because of its bird-like sounds.</i>

93
00:15:37,478 --> 00:15:41,189
<i>The beluga is the only whale</i>
<i>that can move its head in all directions.</i>

94
00:15:42,358 --> 00:15:46,861
<i>This friendly-looking creature</i>
<i>can appear to have very human expressions.</i>

95
00:15:55,871 --> 00:15:59,999
<i>Human activity has resulted</i>
<i>in massive pollution of their habitat</i>

96
00:16:00,376 --> 00:16:04,379
<i>and has put some of these tribes</i>
<i>in great danger of extinction.</i>

97
00:16:04,964 --> 00:16:09,509
<i>The beluga whale may soon become</i>
<i>a ghostly shadow of the Arctic,</i>

98
00:16:10,594 --> 00:16:12,220
<i>a mere memory.</i>

99
00:16:24,149 --> 00:16:25,191
(SQUEAKING)

100
00:16:25,275 --> 00:16:28,403
<i>Now, here's a very difficult tribe to approach.</i>

101
00:16:28,988 --> 00:16:33,366
<i>Risso's dolphins are fairly large,</i>
<i>weighing up to 1,100 pounds.</i>

102
00:16:35,619 --> 00:16:39,414
<i>Their battered look comes from</i>
<i>the numerous scars that cover their bodies.</i>

103
00:16:40,499 --> 00:16:43,668
<i>The older they are, the more scars they have,</i>

104
00:16:43,752 --> 00:16:48,381
<i>and over time, their naturally</i>
<i>dark grey bodies turn nearly white.</i>

105
00:16:50,843 --> 00:16:53,970
<i>They get those scars</i>
<i>during rough social play.</i>

106
00:17:13,699 --> 00:17:15,908
<i>As belligerent as they can be,</i>

107
00:17:15,993 --> 00:17:19,787
<i>these fascinating dolphins will remain</i>
<i>in a tight-knit social structure</i>

108
00:17:19,872 --> 00:17:22,206
<i>enjoying strength in numbers.</i>

109
00:17:59,703 --> 00:18:02,246
(SOOTHING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)

110
00:18:07,002 --> 00:18:12,423
<i>In the shallow coastal waters of Florida</i>
<i>lives the most peaceful of marine mammals,</i>

111
00:18:12,508 --> 00:18:14,092
<i>the manatee.</i>

112
00:18:22,351 --> 00:18:26,729
<i>It may look something like a cetacean</i>
<i>but this is a sirenian.</i>

113
00:18:29,733 --> 00:18:33,903
<i>Manatees, much like dolphins and whales,</i>
<i>evolved from land mammals</i>

114
00:18:34,029 --> 00:18:36,364
<i>and later returned to the sea.</i>

115
00:18:43,831 --> 00:18:48,126
<i>The curious-looking manatees</i>
<i>are more closely related to elephants</i>

116
00:18:48,210 --> 00:18:50,419
<i>than any other living animal.</i>

117
00:19:02,391 --> 00:19:04,725
<i>Despite the corpulent look,</i>

118
00:19:04,852 --> 00:19:06,769
<i>their layer of blubber is so thin</i>

119
00:19:06,895 --> 00:19:10,356
<i>that it cannot protect them</i>
<i>when the temperature drops.</i>

120
00:19:11,066 --> 00:19:13,734
<i>They won't survive in water</i>
<i>below 68 degrees,</i>

121
00:19:13,861 --> 00:19:17,155
<i>so in winter, they will seek out warm springs.</i>

122
00:19:33,088 --> 00:19:35,882
<i>The manatee is also called the sea cow.</i>

123
00:19:36,300 --> 00:19:40,011
<i>In fact, it's the only marine mammal</i>
<i>that eats vegetation.</i>

124
00:20:42,658 --> 00:20:45,159
<i>The manatee's diet causes fIatulence.</i>

125
00:20:47,829 --> 00:20:49,956
(CHUCKLES) Look at aII those bubbIes.

126
00:21:07,557 --> 00:21:11,102
<i>A manatee calf will live with its mother</i>
<i>for five years.</i>

127
00:21:11,853 --> 00:21:16,357
<i>They'll nurse from the long teat</i>
<i>located at the base of her pectoral fins.</i>

128
00:21:24,533 --> 00:21:26,284
<i>Just to keep their bodies warm,</i>

129
00:21:26,368 --> 00:21:30,204
<i>they have to eat</i>
<i>more than 100 pounds of water plants a day.</i>

130
00:21:35,210 --> 00:21:37,837
<i>The 3,000 manatees left in Florida</i>

131
00:21:37,921 --> 00:21:41,841
<i>are one of the last surviving</i>
<i>sirenian tribes in the worId.</i>

132
00:21:43,135 --> 00:21:44,802
<i>But for how long?</i>

133
00:21:45,220 --> 00:21:48,472
<i>Every day, human development</i>
<i>takes a little more of their habitat.</i>

134
00:21:49,891 --> 00:21:52,768
<i>Soon, they may have nowhere left to live.</i>

135
00:22:04,072 --> 00:22:08,367
<i>The orca, or killer whale,</i>
<i>is the king of the ocean.</i>

136
00:22:09,619 --> 00:22:12,455
<i>It is the largest of the dolphin family.</i>

137
00:22:12,664 --> 00:22:16,375
<i>It can reach 32 feet in length</i>
<i>and weigh up to 10 tons.</i>

138
00:22:22,049 --> 00:22:23,299
(SCREECHING)

139
00:22:25,260 --> 00:22:29,722
<i>They will spend their entire lives</i>
<i>in pods as large as 25 individuals.</i>

140
00:22:30,474 --> 00:22:32,933
<i>The eldest female will always lead.</i>

141
00:22:34,311 --> 00:22:36,020
<i>Mother knows best.</i>

142
00:22:41,026 --> 00:22:43,778
<i>This extraordinarily intelligent animal,</i>

143
00:22:44,112 --> 00:22:46,614
<i>probably the smartest of them all,</i>

144
00:22:46,698 --> 00:22:49,867
<i>exhibits highly sophisticated</i>
<i>social behaviour.</i>

145
00:22:50,952 --> 00:22:52,286
(WHISTLING)

146
00:22:53,789 --> 00:22:57,291
<i>They have their own dialects,</i>
<i>varying from pod to pod.</i>

147
00:22:58,126 --> 00:22:59,585
<i>They will work as a team,</i>

148
00:22:59,669 --> 00:23:04,298
<i>and are able to adapt their hunting strategy</i>
<i>when faced with new situations.</i>

149
00:23:08,470 --> 00:23:11,514
<i>The orca</i>
<i>is the greatest predator of the ocean</i>

150
00:23:11,681 --> 00:23:14,642
<i>and will even attack the great white shark.</i>

151
00:23:22,734 --> 00:23:25,486
<i>Their frightening nickname, killer whale,</i>

152
00:23:25,987 --> 00:23:30,574
<i>derives from the fact that they are</i>
<i>the only whales that kill other whales.</i>

153
00:23:36,123 --> 00:23:40,334
<i>Orcas, too, are suffering from pollution</i>
<i>and depletion of their prey.</i>

154
00:23:42,295 --> 00:23:43,921
<i>At the head of the food chain,</i>

155
00:23:44,005 --> 00:23:48,175
<i>they have become one of</i>
<i>the most contaminated of all the cetaceans.</i>

156
00:23:48,385 --> 00:23:52,847
<i>They are slowly being poisoned</i>
<i>by the polluted prey upon which they feed.</i>

157
00:23:54,099 --> 00:23:56,767
<i>Another tribe losing ground.</i>

158
00:24:13,994 --> 00:24:17,413
<i>The fin whale is one of the largest creatures</i>
<i>on Earth.</i>

159
00:24:17,956 --> 00:24:20,499
<i>Only one, the blue whale, is larger.</i>

160
00:24:23,962 --> 00:24:25,713
<i>Looking at these dolphins,</i>

161
00:24:25,797 --> 00:24:28,924
<i>it is easy to imagine</i>
<i>how big this fin whale is.</i>

162
00:24:29,759 --> 00:24:33,596
<i>It can reach up to 88 feet in length,</i>
<i>and weigh up to 70 tons.</i>

163
00:24:43,064 --> 00:24:46,734
<i>Are these spotted dolphins</i>
<i>hunting with the fin whale?</i>

164
00:25:05,921 --> 00:25:09,924
<i>After a large school of fish</i>
<i>has been herded into a tight ball,</i>

165
00:25:10,133 --> 00:25:12,092
<i>many predators appear.</i>

166
00:25:27,943 --> 00:25:29,527
<i>The large bait ball of fish</i>

167
00:25:29,611 --> 00:25:33,072
<i>is first being attacked from above</i>
<i>by shearwater birds.</i>

168
00:25:56,888 --> 00:25:59,473
<i>Now, the spotted dolphins from below.</i>

169
00:26:17,617 --> 00:26:22,580
<i>And finally, here comes the giant fin whale,</i>
<i>taking its turn.</i>

170
00:26:29,421 --> 00:26:31,338
<i>In one fantastic gulp,</i>

171
00:26:31,423 --> 00:26:35,259
<i>it takes the entire school of fish</i>
<i>into its enormous mouth.</i>

172
00:26:43,685 --> 00:26:46,645
<i>Look how the ventral grooves</i>
<i>below its mouth have expanded,</i>

173
00:26:46,730 --> 00:26:49,481
<i>like a giant balloon, to hold the catch.</i>

174
00:26:51,359 --> 00:26:54,194
<i>The water will be filtered out</i>
<i>through the baleen plates,</i>

175
00:26:54,279 --> 00:26:57,239
<i>and the entire school of fish, trapped inside,</i>

176
00:26:57,324 --> 00:26:59,867
<i>will become this fin whale's dinner.</i>

177
00:27:01,202 --> 00:27:05,372
<i>They will eat up to 3 tons of krill</i>
<i>and small fish each day.</i>

178
00:27:09,544 --> 00:27:13,881
<i>Although supposedly protected,</i>
<i>the fin whale is still hunted today</i>

179
00:27:14,299 --> 00:27:16,508
<i>and is extremely vulnerable.</i>

180
00:27:16,885 --> 00:27:21,221
<i>In addition to modern commercial whaling</i>
<i>and collisions with ships,</i>

181
00:27:21,598 --> 00:27:25,309
<i>the fin whale is now also</i>
<i>being impacted by climate change.</i>

182
00:27:25,685 --> 00:27:31,732
<i>Indeed, krill, its primary source of food,</i>
<i>depends on the cover of sea ice,</i>

183
00:27:32,525 --> 00:27:34,318
<i>which is now melting.</i>

184
00:27:48,124 --> 00:27:49,917
<i>The common dolphin,</i>

185
00:27:51,044 --> 00:27:54,546
<i>creature of legend, art, poetry,</i>

186
00:27:55,507 --> 00:27:57,925
<i>from ancient times to the present.</i>

187
00:27:58,426 --> 00:28:00,511
<i>Why this mystical appeal?</i>

188
00:28:01,137 --> 00:28:05,265
<i>What about these magical tribes</i>
<i>so captures the human imagination?</i>

189
00:28:10,939 --> 00:28:12,648
(DOLPHlNS CLlCKING)

190
00:28:12,816 --> 00:28:15,734
<i>The clicks we hear are used for echolocation,</i>

191
00:28:16,069 --> 00:28:19,363
<i>a sixth sense that allows them to see,</i>
<i>so to speak.</i>

192
00:28:20,240 --> 00:28:23,450
<i>They use it to detect objects,</i>
<i>track down prey,</i>

193
00:28:23,576 --> 00:28:27,621
<i>locate one another, avoid predators</i>
<i>and orient themselves.</i>

194
00:28:47,308 --> 00:28:49,977
<i>They use squeaks as a form of language.</i>

195
00:28:50,979 --> 00:28:53,188
<i>These sounds enable them</i>
<i>to communicate with each other</i>

196
00:28:53,273 --> 00:28:56,817
<i>when hunting, playing</i>
<i>or keeping track of their young.</i>

197
00:29:07,203 --> 00:29:10,998
<i>Today, common dolphins</i>
<i>are still hunted for their meat,</i>

198
00:29:11,708 --> 00:29:16,920
<i>and around 300,000 dolphins and whales</i>
<i>die every year entangled in fishing nets.</i>

199
00:29:17,881 --> 00:29:19,673
<i>Eight hundred a day.</i>

200
00:29:40,695 --> 00:29:43,238
<i>A mother right whale and her baby,</i>

201
00:29:43,490 --> 00:29:48,327
<i>nurturing, nurtured,</i>
<i>a bond formed over several years.</i>

202
00:30:01,049 --> 00:30:04,343
<i>She will have one offspring</i>
<i>about every three years</i>

203
00:30:04,636 --> 00:30:08,180
<i>and will nurse it with her rich milk</i>
<i>for roughly 12 months.</i>

204
00:30:15,396 --> 00:30:19,691
<i>The right whale's mouth contains</i>
<i>about 250 baleen plates,</i>

205
00:30:20,151 --> 00:30:23,070
<i>enabling it to filter tons of zooplankton.</i>

206
00:30:30,703 --> 00:30:34,039
<i>The huge, pale growths on the head</i>
<i>and the lower jaw,</i>

207
00:30:34,123 --> 00:30:37,084
<i>called callosities, are home to whale lice</i>

208
00:30:37,669 --> 00:30:40,921
<i>that tint them with white, pink,</i>
<i>yellow or orange.</i>

209
00:30:41,589 --> 00:30:45,008
<i>Unique formations,</i>
<i>their own kind of fingerprint.</i>

210
00:30:56,312 --> 00:30:58,605
<i>Looking into the eye of a whale</i>

211
00:30:58,940 --> 00:31:02,484
<i>is said to be</i>
<i>like looking into the window of one's soul.</i>

212
00:31:06,489 --> 00:31:09,408
<i>For the few humans</i>
<i>who have come this close,</i>

213
00:31:11,244 --> 00:31:15,414
<i>the whale's gaze has provided</i>
<i>a moment of true emotional connection.</i>

214
00:31:24,299 --> 00:31:29,970
<i>Whalers dubbed this creature the right whale</i>
<i>because their entire body could be used.</i>

215
00:31:30,763 --> 00:31:34,099
<i>In addition to their long baleen plates</i>
<i>and their blubber,</i>

216
00:31:34,183 --> 00:31:37,769
<i>they were also slow swimmers, easy to catch,</i>

217
00:31:38,271 --> 00:31:43,191
<i>and once dead, kept floating at the surface,</i>
<i>so it made their processing easier.</i>

218
00:31:43,735 --> 00:31:46,862
<i>Thus, they were the right whales to hunt.</i>

219
00:31:53,786 --> 00:31:55,787
<i>Most southern right whales are born dark,</i>

220
00:31:56,539 --> 00:31:59,833
<i>but this one is white, a rare occurrence.</i>

221
00:32:19,687 --> 00:32:22,272
<i>There are very few right whales left.</i>

222
00:32:23,983 --> 00:32:26,985
<i>Southern right whales have shown</i>
<i>some signs of recovery</i>

223
00:32:27,070 --> 00:32:29,321
<i>thanks to protective measures.</i>

224
00:32:30,365 --> 00:32:33,617
<i>However, we can only remain</i>
<i>cautiously optimistic</i>

225
00:32:33,701 --> 00:32:36,995
<i>about the future</i>
<i>of these last 9,000 individuals.</i>

226
00:32:38,247 --> 00:32:41,708
<i>As for their cousins,</i>
<i>the Northern Atlantic right whales,</i>

227
00:32:42,335 --> 00:32:46,296
<i>it is estimated</i>
<i>that a mere 300 are left in the worId.</i>

228
00:32:47,048 --> 00:32:50,384
<i>They are very, very close to extinction.</i>

229
00:33:43,271 --> 00:33:45,188
<i>The bottlenose dolphin.</i>

230
00:33:46,149 --> 00:33:49,026
<i>This tribe of dolphins is usually nomadic.</i>

231
00:33:49,610 --> 00:33:52,988
<i>Sometimes, though, they prefer</i>
<i>to reside in one location,</i>

232
00:33:53,072 --> 00:33:56,241
<i>like these,</i>
<i>swimming in the waters of the Bahamas.</i>

233
00:33:58,578 --> 00:34:02,247
<i>Dolphins stick together.</i>
<i>Their pods are tight family groups,</i>

234
00:34:02,331 --> 00:34:05,834
<i>well-structured, and come</i>
<i>with an established hierarchy.</i>

235
00:34:09,756 --> 00:34:11,089
(WHlSTLING)

236
00:34:11,632 --> 00:34:15,010
<i>The remarkable bottlenose dolphins</i>
<i>are able to develop</i>

237
00:34:15,094 --> 00:34:19,639
<i>and teach their young different individual</i>
<i>and group hunting strategies.</i>

238
00:34:20,308 --> 00:34:23,560
<i>They can then adapt these strategies</i>
<i>to varying situations.</i>

239
00:34:29,275 --> 00:34:32,235
<i>They can chase through schools of fish</i>
<i>in the open sea</i>

240
00:34:32,320 --> 00:34:35,238
<i>or corner a hapless prey against a sandbar.</i>

241
00:34:37,658 --> 00:34:41,411
<i>A hungry adult bottlenose may consume</i>
<i>up to 30 pounds of fish,</i>

242
00:34:41,496 --> 00:34:43,747
<i>squid and crustaceans each day.</i>

243
00:35:02,350 --> 00:35:05,352
<i>Their brain is proportionally as large as ours.</i>

244
00:35:06,354 --> 00:35:08,855
<i>They communicate with a complex language</i>

245
00:35:08,940 --> 00:35:12,275
<i>and, amazingly,</i>
<i>have individual signature whistles</i>

246
00:35:12,360 --> 00:35:16,321
<i>they use the same way we use names</i>
<i>to identify one another.</i>

247
00:35:33,714 --> 00:35:38,885
<i>Dolphins, when in the intense</i>
<i>throes of passion, become very playful,</i>

248
00:35:39,554 --> 00:35:42,973
<i>swim in an agitated manner</i>
<i>and mate indiscriminately.</i>

249
00:35:50,523 --> 00:35:53,859
<i>It's quite common for the bottlenose</i>
<i>to scratch each other with their teeth</i>

250
00:35:53,943 --> 00:35:56,153
<i>during courtship and mating.</i>

251
00:36:36,694 --> 00:36:38,195
<i>Time to play again.</i>

252
00:36:38,279 --> 00:36:39,571
(SQUEAKS)

253
00:36:40,656 --> 00:36:41,865
<i>Catch it.</i>

254
00:36:52,126 --> 00:36:53,668
(SNORTING)

255
00:36:54,837 --> 00:36:56,630
<i>A year has gone by.</i>

256
00:36:56,714 --> 00:37:00,967
<i>This female is back in the tropical waters</i>
<i>of the kingdom of Tonga.</i>

257
00:37:01,802 --> 00:37:04,930
<i>Here, sheltered from predators</i>
<i>and bad weather,</i>

258
00:37:05,348 --> 00:37:08,558
<i>she will give birth to a beautiful</i>
<i>1 4-foot baby.</i>

259
00:37:26,827 --> 00:37:30,622
<i>This newborn baby is so young</i>
<i>that his eyes are still closed.</i>

260
00:37:35,253 --> 00:37:38,421
<i>His body doesn't yet know</i>
<i>how to stay in balance.</i>

261
00:37:49,267 --> 00:37:53,186
<i>Every four minutes,</i>
<i>for several days and nights,</i>

262
00:37:54,188 --> 00:37:58,191
<i>the mother will gently nudge her baby</i>
<i>to the surface to breathe.</i>

263
00:37:59,735 --> 00:38:03,530
<i>During this period,</i>
<i>mother and baby are extremely vulnerable.</i>

264
00:38:06,242 --> 00:38:09,536
<i>Even a big storm can be fatal to a newborn.</i>

265
00:38:55,583 --> 00:38:57,500
<i>A few days have gone by.</i>

266
00:38:58,252 --> 00:39:01,671
<i>This calf can finally swim</i>
<i>and breathe on its own,</i>

267
00:39:03,382 --> 00:39:07,093
<i>though it still takes shelter</i>
<i>under its mother's large fin.</i>

268
00:39:19,815 --> 00:39:23,360
<i>Weeks have gone by.</i>
<i>The baby has grown stronger.</i>

269
00:39:23,986 --> 00:39:25,695
<i>Its skin is darker.</i>

270
00:39:26,280 --> 00:39:29,074
<i>From this point on for about two years,</i>

271
00:39:29,158 --> 00:39:33,119
<i>the mother will teach her youngster</i>
<i>how to survive in the ocean.</i>

272
00:39:36,457 --> 00:39:39,000
<i>Mother and baby</i>
<i>will often touch one another</i>

273
00:39:39,085 --> 00:39:42,128
<i>in what appears to be a gesture of affection.</i>

274
00:39:47,593 --> 00:39:48,885
<i>It will take about eight years</i>

275
00:39:48,969 --> 00:39:53,223
<i>before this young calf will be old enough</i>
<i>to produce offspring of his own.</i>

276
00:39:54,266 --> 00:39:56,393
<i>Will he survive that long?</i>

277
00:39:59,021 --> 00:40:03,983
<i>Hope this young calf will grow old enough</i>
<i>to sing his own unique and lovely song.</i>

278
00:40:05,152 --> 00:40:08,321
<i>Hope his song</i>
<i>will not be the last one we hear.</i>

279
00:40:10,616 --> 00:40:14,327
<i>Dolphins and whales</i>
<i>are one of the Earth's living wonders.</i>

280
00:40:15,621 --> 00:40:19,749
<i>Some assume they have the right to destroy</i>
<i>our children's heritage.</i>

281
00:40:20,042 --> 00:40:23,461
<i>We can stop vandalising</i>
<i>and plundering the oceans.</i>

282
00:40:24,171 --> 00:40:26,339
<i>We can change our way of life.</i>

283
00:40:27,550 --> 00:40:30,343
<i>Make no mistake, it's not too late.</i>

284
00:40:30,761 --> 00:40:32,345
<i>If we all join together,</i>

285
00:40:32,430 --> 00:40:35,849
<i>we have the power to save</i>
<i>the dolphins and the whales,</i>

286
00:40:35,933 --> 00:40:37,308
<i>the tribes of the ocean.</i>

287
00:40:41,480 --> 00:40:43,231
(GRUNTING)

288
00:40:47,445 --> 00:40:48,736
(CALLING)

