♪
Is that Garcia?
Dead.
Lock off all the exits now!
Copy that. Locking it down.
Son of a bitch!
Hey.
It's okay. I'm a cop.
I come up here to take naps
between making pickups.
I hear these guys shouting.
I wake up.
English or Spanish?
Both.
They're going back and forth.
It's getting kind of loud.
They're getting kind of mean.
I drop my keys.
I go down to pick them up.
They start--
p-pow, p-pow-- shooting.
Did you get a good look at
the guys who were arguing?
Yeah.
I got to throw up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get this guy
to a toilet!
Your mother killed Christmas.
She killed it dead, Clyde.
Every year, it's the same.
"You're coming to
Pittsburgh, right?
I don't want to be
alone for the holiday."
Well, she is alone.
In-laws.
Even when they're not
in the same time zone,
they can ruin your day.
Yes, in-laws are a
universal problem.
But one of the
benefits of group
is that we all get to
share our experiences.
Does anyone
have anything?
Change your phone number.
Or move, don't tell
them where you went.
Wes, you disagree?
Hmm?
That's just
his default state.
Clyde, Rozelle, look.
When I was married to Alex,
my mother was a problem.
Didn't get better until I
confronted her about it.
And that's what you got
to do here, Clyde.
It's got to be you;
otherwise, Rozelle
is just the harpy who stole
her son away from her.
That's what I keep telling him.
Call her up. Say, "Mom,
"I'm the decider now.
"You don't pay
my bills anymore.
"You don't clothe
me anymore.
"I make my own choices.
That's the way it is."
She does help us with money.
Wes, how did that
strategy work for you?
Great. There's a beautiful
relationship there now.
Between my mother and Alex.
Neither of 'em
really got over me
quitting the law.
And, uh,
my mom and I e-mail
occasionally.
It's... cordial.
Yeah.
Sorry, Dr. Ryan.
I got a text message
from my old boss.
Dan Noone?
What's he want,
a designated driver?
It's not funny.
We-we got to go.
Excuse me. Sorry.
You know you're lucky, right?
Yeah?
You get to watch a legend
at work.
Yeah, I heard
the stories.
Now you get to live
the Dan Noone experience.
He made me the finely-tuned
investigative machine that I am.
Yeah? Well, in that
case, I am lucky.
Got a few things
I want to say to him.
Nooner!
Hey, T!
How they hangin', jefe?
Ah, they're headin'
for the knees,
and I wish to Christ
that was my only complaint.
This is my partner,
Wes Mitchell.
Hey, Wes.
How are yours hangin'?
They're hang...
Just... I can't.
Nah.
So, what happened?
It's a mess.
We had an informant
inside of Los Ladrones.
You know, the
Guatemalan outfit
that holds down all the
corners in Glassell Park?
Our guy said he was
making a wholesale buy
first thing this morning,
so we set up surveillance
about a block away, and soon
as we got audio, well...
all hell broke loose, and the
rest you can see for yourself.
We got four bodies, and
one of 'em's my snitch.
I guess someone wanted those
corners for themselves, huh?
Looks like it.
We'll get a description
of the shooters
as soon
as my witness stops puking.
So, you have a witness?
How's he doing?
Still going,
last I checked.
I don't know how
he got anything left.
How long has he been
in there?
15, maybe 20.
What's his name?
Charlie Perez.
Mr. Perez, open up.
Well, you had a witness.
Had.
♪Common Law 1x10 ♪
In-Laws vs. Outlaws
Original Air Date on July 27, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Out of my way!
Thanks for coming in.
Here's what we got.
We got a dead informant,
we still got three bodies
on a rooftop down in skid row,
and the only guy who knows
what happened is in the wind.
Okay, what do we know
about this guy you lost?
The guy I let get away
introduced himself
as Charlie Perez.
That was his limo that
got shot up in the gunfight.
We checked the registration.
It's under a Charles Perez.
He owns a car service.
Any address on file?
No.
Tidy up those papers, son,
and lose that picture.
If I didn't know better,
I'd swear a woman
works at your desk.
How do we not
have a home address
on this guy?
He owns a limo service.
He's got to be
registered with the DMV.
He's got to have
a driver's license.
There are 68 Charles Perez's
registered with the DMV in L.A.
We checked 'em all,
and none of 'em are our guy.
Did you look up any names
besides Charles Perez?
Fred Bandak?
Who the hell
called you in?
I did.
Perez is a missing person.
Why not bring in
the head of the department?
Missing Persons hasn't been
the same without you, buddy.
I appreciate that, sir.
Look, I'm sorry for your loss.
I heard about Snowy.
Fallen soldiers, son.
Fallen soldiers.
This is Snowy Two.
Our runner
introduced himself
as Charlie,
but that doesn't necessarily
mean that his name is Charles.
The man that
we're looking for
is Carlos Perez.
Here is his photo.
That's him. That's our guy.
I just said that.
Now, Carlos
has his business registered
under Charles Perez
because he's a two-time felon.
Grand larceny and possession
of stolen property.
All right, so, an ex-con
is there for a drug deal
that becomes a massacre.
He then flees the scene.
Anybody thinking
what I'm thinking?
Yeah. He might not be a witness.
We might be looking
for a shooter.
All right, guys.
Uh, yeah.
RHD's got it from here.
Thank you.
T?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah. What's up, Nooner?
Listen, this whole thing's
getting ugly.
I mean, I got a dead informant,
I let this Perez guy slip
right out from under my nose.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're in Narcotics.
It's not a cut-and-dry
operation.
You got to take risks.
You taught me that.
Yeah, I did. I did.
You see, we got this new major.
It's a 35-year-old chick.
She keeps telling me the era
of the cowboy cop is over.
I know this is your case,
but, you see, my boss--
she's just itching
to find a reason to suspend me.
If somebody else makes
the collar,
well, she's gonna have
a reason.
You want to put cuffs
on the shooter, I got your back.
You'd do that?
Yeah.
I'll be there for you any time,
any place, any way. Uh...
Stay ready.
So you don't have to get ready.
Hi.
I'm Travis Marks.
This crime scene hasn't been
adequately photographed.
Well, we'll, uh...
we'll be sure
to send the techs
a harshly-worded e-mail.
First principles, son.
If your techs can't
process a crime scene
thoroughly, then,
the entire investigation
is nothing but a leaky boat.
Your old boss
is a freak show.
Snowy Two?
He does know
it's weird to name your new dog
after your old dead one, right?
Look, Fred Bandak has a long
and distinguished career.
He's entitled to
a few... quirks.
Yeah. Whatever.
This is our case.
Can we ditch him now
and go get some work done?
Be patient.
Hey, Fred?
Don't, don't. Don't.
Uh, hey, Fred, is there
anything we can do,
help save some time?
Good investigation takes
as long as it takes.
You know that.
Yes, sir.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's onto something.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Now, watch this.
What are you doing now, Fred?
I'm waiting, son.
Waiting for the truth.
Okay. Okay, that's
an expression.
He analyzes everything, doesn't
want to jump to any conclusions.
He's smart.
Let me ask you something.
Does he frighten you?
No.
No. Why would he frighten me?
He is the Ghost
of Future Wes.
If I were you, I'd be terrified
of winding up like...
that.
My guy doesn't lose witnesses.
Or suspects, or whatever
you call Charlie Perez.
No, no.
He just carries a dog around
like a man-purse.
Hey, Fred?
No, no, no, don't.
No, I'll be sweet.
I'll be sweet.
Listen, man,
uh, quick question.
Um, while you're waiting,
do you mind if we just go ahead
and, um, investigate?
If you can't refrain from
talking, I'd actually prefer it.
Okay, sorry, Fred.
Got it.
Got Fred mad at us.
Don't have to get
all snooty at me.
I mean, I'm just
asking a question.
Got the address on Perez.
Keep it locked and loaded, team.
Thanks, Noone.
Wait.
Should we wait for the truth
or knock on the door?
I don't know. What
would Dan Noone do?
Oh, wait, I do know.
Let's have a drink
and talk about it while
the suspect escapes.
LAPD! Open up!
Ready?
Yeah.
LAPD!
Behind the table,
come up.
Hands up right now.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Okay, okay, relax.
No one's gonna shoot,
all right?
Are you really police?
Yes, ma'am.
My husband said men might be
coming here to hurt us.
We were just about to leave.
Is your husband Carlos Perez?
Is he in the house?
Where is he?!
I don't know!
He came here an hour ago.
He said he was
in big, big trouble.
He gave us this,
then he said we had to run.
Charlie got away with some money
from the crime scene.
I warned him
not to get involved
with those people.
What people?
Ma'am, if your husband's
in danger,
we're your best shot
at keeping him safe.
Charlie wanted to start
his limousine company,
but he couldn't get a loan or a
license, 'cause he's an ex-con.
Changed his name to get around
the licensing thing,
then he went to them
for the loan.
Saavedra people.
The cartel?
Everyone around here knows,
if you want to borrow money
till payday, you go see
Miguel Avila at Safari Car Wash.
I knew something
like this would happen.
Something like what?
He said they made him
do something.
Okay.
We'll go to the car wash,
meet with this Miguel Avila,
see if he can tell us
where your husband might be.
In the meantime,
an officer's gonna come by here,
he'll take you and
your daughter to a hotel, okay?
You hear from Charlie,
you call us.
Thank you.
Okay, so this guy Perez
takes cartel money,
he starts a business,
so now he owes them a marker.
Looks like they called
it in last night.
But if Perez is the one who
mowed down the four guys
from Los Ladrones, why does he
think the cartel's after him?
He did what
they wanted.
I don't know.
Those guys don't look like
car wash employees to me.
Stay on your toes.
Hello?
Detective.
LAPD. Stay
right there.
Go!
LAPD!
Open up right now!
Travis, get down!
You all right?
Yeah.
On three, yeah?
Yeah. One, two, three.
He's going, he's going!
♪
Get in the car!
LAPD.
Put them down.
Drop the guns now!
Right now!
Drop them now, now!
Put the guns down!
Cops right here!
Hey, this is a misunderstanding!
Get on the ground now!
Get down!
A misunderstand.
They're my bodyguards.
They thought you were
gonna hurt me.
Miguel Avila?
Yeah.
You and your bodyguards
are under arrest.
I don't know anything
about a drug deal.
I told you, I'm a
legitimate businessman.
Oh, a legitimate businessman
whose employees carry Mac-10s?
Hey, it's a dangerous
neighborhood.
I only called
my bodyguards in
after that maniac bursted into
my office and attacked me.
Wait, are you telling us that
Carlos Perez threatened you?
Yeah. I lent
him money.
Something I do for
people in the community.
Well, your philanthropy
is very impressive, Miguel.
Look, Charlie always
paid on time, no problem.
But today, he
went crazy.
He attacked me.
He said that if I
hurt his family,
he would do the same to
my wife and my daughter.
Now, why would I
hurt his family?
Because your business is a front
for the Saavedra cartel, Miguel.
Because, no matter what happened
in that parking garage,
you know Carlos Perez
left with
a stack load
of your boss's money.
My boss.
I'm a legitimate...
Legitimate businessman.
Yeah, we heard you
the last ten times you said it.
Now you can tell
the booking officer
down at the station.
Oh, come on.
All right,
I got a text from Fred.
"Dear Wesley,
"I do loathe
these digital leashes,
"but they have their uses.
"Please come down to the
station when you have a chance.
Sincerely yours,
Fred Bandak."
He knows this is
not his case, right?
Well, I did... ask
him for a consult.
Which he gave to you.
Now it's time to take
Snowy 2 for a walk,
and get the hell
out of our business.
It'll be fine.
He's just excited
to be out in the field, all right?
Whatever.
Who signs a text message?
So, I analyzed
every aspect of this melee--
lines of fire,
avenues of escape--
and after four and a half hours,
I got it all
right here in my head.
And this is what I found.
Spot of blood
on one of the tires
of the limousine.
Your techs missed it.
You found a spot of blood
at a massacre. Congratulations.
What's he even doing here?
He's not on this case.
Well, this isn't your case,
either, Dan.
You're still here.
It says the spot of
blood doesn't match
any of the dead bodies.
Doesn't match
Charlie Perez, either.
Which means there was
someone else at that scene.
Exactly.
Someone else who got away.
Took the DNA
and did a search
of the VICAP database.
We found a partial match
with a degraded sample
at a crime scene
of the Cabo San Lucas massacre
in Mexico.
13 top lieutenants
of the Escamilla cartel
dead on a beach
at a resort.
Now, Escamilla's people
say that they think
that this is the work
of a Saavedra assassin
they call "El Ingeniero."
El Ingeniero.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
Of course you
heard about it--
'cause I told
you about 'em.
I'm in Narcotics.
I know about 'em.
El Ingeniero is "The Engineer."
He's a fairy tale.
Story that cartel goons
talk about
and sit around and tell
each other when they're bored.
Yeah? Well, I believe he's real,
that he's in L.A.,
that he's the gunman
that we're looking for.
Carlos Perez
is the gunman,
who's a real person
we can place at the scene.
Come on, T, tell him you're
not going on some snipe hunt.
Tell him you're not gonna ignore
an essential piece of forensic data.
Guys, guys,
let's just relax, all right?
Doesn't have
to be one or the other.
Uh...
Charles Perez's cousin
drives the other limo
for the service, right?
So if Charlie is looking
to skip town,
he's probably gonna get
in touch with him.
We could squat on the cousin,
maybe get a wiretap
on his phones.
Yeah. And while we check up
on Fred's lead,
we'll wait and see
if Carlos gets in touch
with his cousin, okay?
Hey, guys,
there is no boogie man.
You know, it'd really be
nice to work this case
without your greedy, needy
ex-boss in my ear.
I can absolutely relate
to how you feel.
Evening, sir.
Ah.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm just, uh,
giving Snowy a little exercise.
Okay, uh...
well, have a good night.
Uh, Wes?
I just wanted to thank you
for letting me saddle up
with you again.
This is gonna be one
of my last times at the rodeo.
What do you mean?
You haven't heard?
Missing Persons is being
consolidated out of existence.
All duties to be absorbed
by the other departments.
I'm being forced
to retire, buddy.
What?
Yeah.
Well, why don't
you just transfer?
No one wants me.
Look, you spend
your career
upholding the standards
of conduct, you're not gonna
wind up with many friends.
I'm sorry, sir.
That's all right.
It's life.
I'm not gonna whine about it.
Of course, if I were
to catch El Ingeniero,
that'd bring a lot
of headlines our way,
wouldn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah. A-And it'd
keep the lights on
for a few more years.
Yeah.
Well, let me see what I can do.
Hey, it's your theory, Fred.
You should get the collar.
All right.
Sir.
Snowy.
Come on!
So, you promised the arrest
to your old boss.
Correct.
And you promised the arrest
to your old boss.
He needs it.
I owe him.
Yeah, I did.
Look, Dan Noone may need the arrest,
but he doesn't deserve it--
we'd have our perp
in custody right now
if he hadn't blown it.
Like your guy's any better?
Yes.
He arrives uninvited,
he craps on everyone's work,
he hijacks the investigation
to go hunt for a ghost--
with his mind.
Well, at least his mind
isn't pickled,
like Dan's.
If Fred did more doing
and less thinking...
What? He'd live in the past,
have a record like Dan's?
Come on, man, you got
to look back at his career--
he's done more good than harm.
It's-it's not even close.
Oh. Oh, oh,
so we have to weigh
his whole career now.
Guys, it's interesting--
what you're dealing with
Please. All
due respect,
this is nothing like an argument over
whose in-law's house
we're going to
for Christmas.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're talking
about dead bodies,
drugs, stolen money.
All right, put the
particulars aside,
you're talking about
two parental surrogates,
important figures
in your professional lives,
both of whom are demanding
your time and attention,
and only one of whom
can be satisfied.
Okay. That's
a good analogy.
But, you know,
what-what do we do?
What, you're asking
me for a ruling?
Yeah. Why not?
You do a lot of clever
metaphor-making in here, Doctor,
and not much
solution-providing.
Then I say...
trust your instincts.
No. No. See,
that's not an answer,
because my instincts
are telling me to help Dan,
and his instincts are
telling him to help Fred.
Well, if that's
what you both think,
then you have
your answer.
I knew you were
gonna say that.
Hey, T! T!
Nooner!
Hey!
Got some good news, buddy.
We got the tap on Perez's
cousin's cell phone.
Charlie called him
two hours ago,
told him to dump his limo
down in Marina Del Rey
so Charlie could
drive it out of town.
We're headed
over there now.
Ready to go to work?
What...?
Morning, Wesley.
You ready to go to work?
Later.
Good luck.
So...
how, uh, how are we
gonna catch a ghost?
Start from the beginning.
Review the Cabo San Lucas
massacre.
And then we...?
Wait for the truth.
♪
So you've still got Trudy, huh?
Oh, yeah.
She's a little worn out,
but she gets me
from A to B in style.
That headlight flap just...
stays up like that, huh?
Uh-huh. They don't make
that part anymore.
You ever think about
trading her in?
You know? You got kids now;
maybe get something with a...
back seat?
Damn, T, you sound
like my ex!
Sorry.
Trudy's not
going anywhere.
She's O.G., brother, O.G.
Besides, I'm not...
a minivan type cat.
Okay.
Uh, uh, here we go.
Here we go.
We're in business.
♪
LAPD!
You're under arrest.
For what? I didn't do anything!
You ran from a crime scene,
Charlie Perez!
You're coming in with us--
we got a few questions.
About what?!
Four dead bodies!
And god-doggit!
You put a dent in Trudy.
What do you mean I can't
sit in on the interview?
We're the ones who
brought him in while these guys
were running around chasing
the Great Pumpkin!
Dan, this is our case now.
We brought him in!
It doesn't matter!
This isn't Narcotics!
This is a potential shooter.
He stole money
from a crime scene!
I'm not talking to you!
Fine! Travis, tell your old boss
I'm your partner now;
this is my case-- I'm not
gonna sit on the sidelines for it.
T, tell him what's up.
Guys, guys, guys.
Dan, Wes is my partner;
it's his case, too.
I can't cut him
out of it, all right?
Okay, look,
I wasn't just a witness,
I admit that.
But I didn't
shoot anybody.
What were you doing
fleeing the scene?
I got two strikes;
one more, I'm done.
I run a honest business
to support my wife and kid.
This was just a favor;
I had to do it.
Do tell.
When I borrowed that money
from Miguel Avila,
it came with
an understanding,
not only that I had
to pay him back,
but I also owed him a favor.
He didn't say what it was,
didn't say what it was
that I would have to do,
just that I owed him.
Two nights ago,
he cashed in that marker.
I get a call from somebody,
drops Miguel's name, tells me that I got
to pick up somebody at the,
uh, Wilshire Sands Hotel
out in Santa Monica
and take him wherever
he wants to go.
This guy gets in my car--
white guy,
about six feet tall,
blond hair...
two different-color eyes.
He's talking about
El Ingeniero.
This guy,
he barely said anything.
Just gave me the address
to the parking garage,
and that's it.
You know, he pulled up
the divider.
He gets out of the car,
starts shooting everybody.
Get a detailed description.
We need to make a sketch.
Fred! We got
this, okay?
So, tell us more
about this man.
Hey, Wes, why don't you ask him
how his wife ended up
with a bag full of drug money
if he's innocent!
Ask him that!
We got
it, Dan.
So, what do you want me
to talk about?
The man.
Okay. Look, it's all
part of the same thing.
I stuffed a few bundles of cash
down my pants leg
'cause I knew
I was gonna have to run.
Sorry, guys.
The public defender
just got here,
and he wants a couple
of minutes alone with his client.
Dan, this case is not about
cleaning up your mess.
This case is about the truth!
The truth is,
you just want to make this
collar so you can keep
that stupid dog of yours in fancy
treats for the next couple of years.
You leave Snowy
out of this.
Oh, I thought
it was Snowy 2.
Do we sound like that
when we fight?
Man, if we do,
we need a lot more therapy.
Drink it all in, boys.
Could always learn from
the guys who brought us here,
even when they're
not teaching us by example.
This anger is
a dark whirlpool.
Make note.
Perez says he's ready to
talk to you guys again.
His lawyer just
got in there.
Do we have to tell them
we're headed back in?
I'm of the opinion
that if we leave
these two out of it,
our lives will get a lot easier.
Agreed.
Hey, Charlie.
Where's your lawyer?
I don't need him anymore.
Um, I sent him home.
Why?
Sit down.
I want to talk.
I don't need a lawyer for that.
Okay.
There was no pickup.
I pulled the trigger
on those guys.
It was all me.
I'll tell you
everything.
Charlie...
what happened?
Why are your
hands shaking?
You guys didn't believe me.
It's time to stop
selling that line.
There was no one else
in that parking garage
except me.
I did it.
That's what you
want to hear, right?
That's a very bizarre and
sudden confession, Charlie.
Somebody got to you.
What'd your lawyer
say to you?
Why do you seem
so scared right now?
I'm not scared.
♪
Well, I just got off the phone
with City Services.
Charlie's lawyer signed in
with city credentials
under the name James Wilder.
They don't have any record of
a public defender by that name.
Look at this.
What?
This guy managed
to keep his face hidden
from almost every
single camera-- now,
that's no accident.
Hm.
Wait, stop. Right there.
Gotcha.
Ah, you're sly,
but so am I.
Yeah. Remember
Charlie's description
of the man he brought
to the parking garage?
Blond hair, six feet tall, and I'll bet
you if we had better resolution,
we'd see two
different-color eyes.
That's him. That's him.
That is the man who came here
and flipped Charlie Perez.
Yep.
Now we've got to figure out
what he said to him.
Charlie's not talking.
Yeah, not anymore.
Before he changed his story,
he said he picked up the gunman
at the Wilshire Sands.
Now, if that's El Ingeniero,
he's staying at that hot.
Sure, I remember him--
that's Mr. Coffey.
He checked out a few days ago.
I don't suppose he, uh,
told you his first name?
Um... I think it was Donald.
I hailed a cab for him a few times,
but he didn't talk much.
I remember
he had some wild eyes.
One brown, one blue.
How you doing, Charlie?
Well...
We know
who your lawyer is, Charlie.
We know that he's the man
that you picked up
from the Wilshire
Sands Hotel.
He's El Ingeniero, isn't he?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Whatever he told you
to get you to confess,
whatever deal
you think you struck...
Hey...
He's lying, man.
All right, Travis, take it
easy on him. Can't you see
he's having a tough day, okay?
He'll come around.
We can help you right now.
You know what,
you're a loose end.
And I promise you,
as soon as you get to county...
they'll take care of you.
We're trying
to help you.
It's not about me.
Who's it about?
You know who these people are.
You know what they do.
You really want
to throw in with them?
This guy, El Ingeniero...
he showed me a picture.
It's my wife and my kid.
He's got 'em.
Hi, you've reached Martha Perez.
Please leave a message,
and I'll get back to you
as soon as I can.
Okay.
You hear anything?
No.
Uniform has been swinging
by the hotel to check on him,
says the room's empty and they
have not checked out yet.
There you are.
Where the hell you guys been?
T, I've been calling your
cell phone...
Dan, Dan, not now.
El Ingeniero's got
Charlie Perez's wife and kid.
What?
Yes.
All right, look...
No.
Here's what we do...
No, no, no, no. Okay, w-w-wait.
I...
I am the decider now.
You don't have to boss
of me anymore; you don't...
get to solve this case,
and that's just the way it is...
man.
What the hell's
that all about?
I think Travis just had
a breakthrough.
We can analyze that later, okay?
El Ingeniero is
alive and well.
El Ingeniero
may be alive and well,
but we don't know
where he is, Fred.
we don't even know
his real name.
The Saavedra cartel
knows how to get in touch
with El Ingeniero.
Miguel--
from the car wash--
he's got a line to him.
You think he's gonna tell us
where to look?
He will if he's
properly motivated.
Dan...
No, T, T, T,
I'm cool.
I'm cool. I just want to help.
I really do.
Look, you two guys,
you know how
to get to the truth
by sitting on it and waiting
and waiting, and you did.
You did the right thing.
You got the answers
you were looking for.
You were right. I admit it.
What I want to know is...
Well, are you willing
to get your hands dirty?
You haven't even told me
why I'm here.
Here you go, gentlemen.
Signed, sealed,
and delivered.
I'm gonna sue you guys for this.
Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
What happened
to your hand, Miguel?
That stupid dog bit me.
Now will
somebody tell me
why the hell I'm here?
- I'm out on bail.
- Yeah, we know.
Your lawyer sprung you.
But here's the thing, uh,
my partner and I were
just talking about
this whole World War III
thing that happened
over at your car wash
the other day.
I don't know if you
know this or not,
but stressful situations like...
a bunch of men firing at you
with automatic weapons,
that just clouds up your memory.
Yeah.
Yeah, we talked about it.
And we realized
we had it all wrong.
But now we're clear.
See,
you were holding
one of those guns.
What?
No, that's a straight lie.
No, that's attempted murder,
two counts.
And you can
hire a lawyer,
you can complain
all you want,
but who
do you think
a jury is gonna believe?
You, a loan shark fronting
a business for a drug cartel,
or two
decorated detectives?
You can't do that.
I didn't shoot anybody.
We're gonna do it.
Yeah, we did it.
Oh, yeah, you're
going to jail.
Long time.
Done.
There it is.
See you in court.
Bye-bye.
No, w-w-wait.
Wait. Hang on.
Hang on.
All right, Miguel...
we're feeling generous today.
So you tell us
what we want to know,
we'll reconsider.
Where is El Ingeniero?
And where is Charlie Perez's family?
You tell us that,
we'll forget
about what happened
at your car wash.
He's leaving the country
tomorrow morning.
And I've never known
the man to travel
unless he's done with a job.
Shh.
Go.
LAPD!
Drop your weapons;
get your hands in the air!
But do not shoot,
he has hostages!
Go, go, go.
Dan.
Dan!
Got him?
Yeah.
You're okay.
Well, the EMT's saying
you're gonna be fine.
Just have to learn to shoot
with your left hand.
No, my shooting
days are over.
Why? What are you saying?
Eh, maybe my lieutenant
was right.
The era of the cowboy cop
is over.
Might be time
for me to settle into
a desk job, leave all this
to the new generation.
From what I can see,
you guys are doing okay.
We're trying, sir.
We're trying.
It doesn't mean
you're gonna get a minivan.
Hey.
T?
I know you promised
me the collar, but...
I think it should
go to Bandak.
He needs it more than me,
and besides that grumpy
son of a bitch was right.
Should I tell him
you said that?
Just the grumpy
son of a bitch part.
Stay ready.
Sir, you don't
have to get ready.
You said it.
Charlie's agreed to testify
against the cartel.
And in exchange,
the government has agreed
to put the Perez family
into the WITSEC program.
Give them a new start in life.
Nice collar, boys.
Nice collar.
Thanks, Cap.
This was not ours, though.
This one belongs to
the Missing Persons Department.
Sorry fellas,
but I'm gonna have to object.
It's not my arrest,
it's yours.
What are you talking about, sir?
You need this.
Missing Persons is a thing
of the past.
No collar's
gonna change that.
So what are you
gonna do now?
I have no earthly idea.
I guess I'll think
of something.
Wes,
you turned into
a fine detective.
Travis,
you're on your way.
Ha, funny guy.
Mike.
Fred.
You done good
with these boys.
Ah...
They were men before
they came here
because of guys like you.
I appreciate that.
Dinnertime.
See ya in the funny papers.
Wow.
You are so gonna end up
with a little dog like that.
You're so gonna wind up
with an old,
beat-up sports car like Dan's.
Trudy?
Yeah.
Come on, man.
Trudy's O.G.
O.G.? What does that mean?
Old and grimy?
She has one working
headlight.
Boys.
What?
Get out.
He started it.
But we waitin'.
Get out.
For the truth, Cap.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==