Good.
No, no, great.
Wes,
you go.
Take a deep breath.
Let every ounce of rage
bubble to the surface,
then let it all out
with one big, primal scream.
No.
This is your birth mother.
This, this is
your old therapist,
who strung you along
and then kicked you
out of her group.
Don't know if I'd put it
that way, but okay.
Crumple 'em up.
Wad them into a ball.
Then rip them into pieces
until you have confetti
for people to throw on you
at your "Travis Is Awesome,
And You Don't Need Any Woman
To Validate You" parade.
No.
Today, we're gonna go
through my ex-wife's files.
We're gonna be looking for
accounting irregularities.
Excuse me?
What is the therapeutic value
of this, exactly?
We're just helping you
with your divorce.
The value is
confronting your feelings
when you come upon a written
record of mendacity and deceit.
A forensic accountant is just
a fancy name for somebody
who can read a spreadsheet.
$200 an hour, my ass.
In this room, we say no to
the divorce industrial complex.
In this room,
we go through
the files ourselves.
No.
Absolutely not.
Could I talk to you two guys
for a second?
Rest of you dive in.
You know, I thought
it might be fun
to have a couple
cool cops around.
But we have to face facts:
you two suck at therapy.
We suck?
Yeah. You keep resisting my methods,
and I'll tell you
something else:
you really bring the energy
in the room down.
I-I don't want you here anymore.
We can't get
kicked out of another group.
I'm not throwing you out.
You've just seen
some things; there's
a couple new techniques
I don't want getting around.
So, I'm offering you
the deal of a lifetime.
You don't have to show up
anymore.
Couple months, I'll
call up your captain,
tell him your all better.
End of therapy.
Come on, guys.
It's a win-win.
So, how much you think
these guys get
for robbing a food truck?
Well, I think they robbed
three in the last two months.
They must be making
some kind of money at it.
So, this is good.
Hmm?
Huh?
We don't have to show up
for therapy anymore.
Oh, heck, yeah.
Of course, it's good.
I mean, you and me?
We're doing better, baby.
We're doing so much better.
Yeah.
Doing way better.
I feel great.
I feel... healed.
Feel much better.
It's just,
you know,
Pack-Man's birthday
is a few days away.
You think I don't know that?
I've been thinking
about it, man.
I-I just... I wouldn't mind
talking to Dr. Ryan about it.
Well, we don't have
that option, Travis.
Pack-Man's birthday-- it's gonna
come, and it's gonna go,
and neither one of us-- we're
not gonna do anything about it.
That's got to be them.
Let's go.
L.A.P.D!
On the ground!
What the hell?
You're under arrest!
Stay down!
Hey! What the hell are
you guys doing here?
Hey! Check it out.
R.H.D. in the house.
Sorry, boys,
this is an S.I.S. bust.
We've been tracking
these two all week.
Give us a heads-up
next time, okay?
We work undercover.
You know that.
Mitchell.
Marks. How you doing?
We're good.
We're just, uh,
moving out.
How's therapy?
You okay?
Hugging it out?
Crying on each other's
shoulders?
We're fine.
We're just leaving.
I only ask 'cause Pack-Man's
birthday's coming up.
Do not let him
get under your skin.
He ain't worth it.
Me and the fellas-- we're gonna
have a few beers in his honor.
You should stop by.
Do not...
Travis, no!
Travis, no, he's not...
Come and get it.
Come here.
Come here!
Relax and cut it out!
Oh, yeah, yeah,
you're doing fine.
Doing great.
Guys, thanks so much
for your help
with the chairs.
These yoga people
have been insisting.
Night, Dr. Ryan.
Good night.
I'll see you all in a few days.
Okay. Take care.
We need your help.
We're not as better off
without you
as we thought we'd be,
but other than that,
we're-we're good.
Look, uh,
you're the only doctor
that's been able to do
a damn thing for us,
and, uh... and we need you.
We need...
this.
We're sorry
that we broke your trust.
It wasn't just that.
I mean, you've been
reluctant to be here
since day one,
dragging your heels.
We'll do... better.
And what reason have
you given me to believe that?
None.
We want to change that,
and, uh, we've got
an offer for you.
If...
you'll take us back,
we'll answer the question
we've been dodging
the entire time
we've been here.
We'll tell you
why we were sent to you
in the first place.
We'll tell you
why I pulled my gun on Travis.
♪Common Law 1x12 ♪
Gun!
Original Air Date on August 10, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Travis.
Do not move another inch,
or I swear to God,
I'll shoot.
All right, stop right there.
What?
Stop interrupting me when
I'm trying to tell the story.
You're not telling
it right, okay?
First of all,
I was not wearing an ascot.
Are you sure?
Travis,
I don't own an ascot.
Why would you even
put that in the story?
All right, you're just
such a tightass,
I guess I picture you as an ascot guy.
Just tell it.
Fine, no ascot.
All right?
Travis.
Don't move another inch,
or I swear to God, I'll shoot.
No.
What?
No, no, no, no.
I said no ascot.
No. Trav, you're still not
telling the story right.
Are you denying you
pulled your gun on me?
No, but if Dr. Ryan's
gonna understand
why I pulled the gun on you,
we have to tell her
the whole story.
We have to start
from the beginning.
We have to tell her
about Pack-Man.
Yeah.
Who's Pack-Man?
Why are you even
bothering to enter
the sharpshooting
competition?
Why, the man asks.
Ain't no shame
in second place, baby.
Well, remind yourself that
when you're standing next to me
on the podium.
Damn it!
Something is
clearly wrong
with this weapon.
What's up with that guy?
Hey, you still working
the theory
that someone's killing
those working girls
who are disappearing
off Skid Row?
When I can, man. Why?
I was on a task force
with a guy from Missing Persons
who thinks the exact
same thing.
That's him right there.
Hey, Mitchell!
Yeah?
Hey, Pack-Man, what's up?
You got to relax, bro.
You're gonna give
yourself an ulcer.
Hey, get over here.
I want you to meet someone.
What's with the suit?
This is Travis Marks.
He works Narco and Vice.
This is Wes Mitchell,
from Missing Persons.
Yeah.
You, uh, you spoke when
I was a cadet at the Academy.
Well, meet for real.
What's the line from that movie?
"This is gonna be the beginning
of a beautiful friendship."
So David Paek
introduced you two?
No one called him David.
His name was Pack-Man.
Just Pack-Man.
But, yeah.
Travis and I teamed up
to catch the guy
who was killing
all those prostitutes.
- Oh, I remember that case, yeah.
- Kind of a big deal.
Wes and I, we got, uh,
we got promoted to R.H.D.
It was a good year.
Yeah.
A lot of good police work,
a lot of arrests.
You remember "Storm Front"?
"Storm Front"?
"Storm Front."
Oh, God.
It's getting cloudy in here.
Cloudy.
So what's "Storm Front"?
You idiot cops.
You really think two of you
will bring down Los Guerreros?
Oh, you think
it's just the two of us?
We're just the tip
of the spear.
We got cops all over
this building.
If you're smart, you guys
would drop your guns
and give up.
I don't see nobody else.
How about you drop your guns?
Now!
Any idea when
backup's coming?
Not soon enough.
Got an idea?
Now step back!
I think I see
a storm front coming.
Cloudy, cloudy storm front.
Got it.
Stay down.
I never would have guessed it.
Looks like Cuahtemoc's
a mellow high.
Yep. If you're going to jail,
that's the best way to do it,
right, guys?
- Don't make me laugh. Don't make me laugh.
- Stop laughing.
I'm gonna breathe this stuff in.
Well, it sounds like you enjoy
each other's company.
Well, for a while.
What happened?
We just kind of
went at each other.
And R.H.D. was different
back then.
You know, Captain Sutton
hadn't done therapy yet.
Damn thing never works!
Geez!
Travis, I can't read
this report
because you printed it
on three-hole paper.
Of course you can read it.
It's only like
five words cut off.
The burden is not mine to posit
what words might be.
It's right there...
Yo, boys.
You think you can put off
the catfight for a few minutes?
If you can, I'm buying.
Tacos, Wes, free tacos.
I can't believe it.
What is this?!
So, it sounds like
your friend was the only thing
that helped you get along.
At the time, yeah.
He pretty much was the only
thing we could agree on.
So, we decided
to help him out.
How so?
Well, Pack-Man introduced us,
and six weeks later,
we were working
Robbery-Homicide together.
And that's one of the best
assignments you can get.
Now, Pack-man, he was stuck back
in property crimes.
So we decided to throw
some busts his way.
Help boost his profile.
That's some solid shooting, kid.
You David Paek?
Pack-Man, yeah.
John Crowell.
S.I.S.
Nice to meet you.
I, uh, I wrote you a letter
when I was at the Academy.
Your name--
it keeps showing up
in these arrest reports.
It's impressive.
I just lost a guy
to desk duty.
I'm looking for someone.
If you're interested,
come and talk to me.
Gentlemen.
Oh, my God. Did he just...
Offer you a job
in S.I.S.? Yeah.
Welcome to the NFL, baby.
There ya go.
Uh, so, what is the S.I.S?
Special Investigations Section.
It's the other best assignment
you can get.
It's a covert tactical
surveillance team.
They do whatever they want,
whenever they want.
They don't have to answer
to anybody.
Wow, sounds like a great job.
Your friend must
have been delighted.
Well, we really didn't
see him much.
He was running undercover.
It was such a good gig,
we just assumed
he was fine until...
six months ago.
- R.H.D. Marks.
- You gotta help me, man.
These guys are bad news, Trav.
It's gettin' weird.
What are you talking
about, Crowell?
No, all of them.
I think they're lining
their pockets,
skimming from the busts
they make, maybe even
pulling jobs of their own.
Hey, Pack-Man, it's Wes.
You sure about this?
I'm pretty sure.
I heard them talking
about something big.
A score that's going
to set them up for life.
I don't know.
What's the score?
I heard them say two things:
"We bought off Henry."
August 22nd.
It's right before my birthday.
I think they know that I know.
Crowell's been looking at me
weird, I swear.
Okay, just calm down.
Where are you right now?
Staking out a check-cashing
place in the Valley.
Guys, I got to go.
That's Crowell.
Okay, sit tight.
We'll be right there.
What the hell
are you guys doing here?
Where's Pack-Man?
Whoa, slow down.
We've been tracking
a whole bunch of robberies.
Pack-Man was running
surveillance, all right?
Where is he?
By the time
we got here,
he had taken
two of these guys out.
Your boy--
he wasn't wearing a vest.
I'm sorry.
♪
Travis...
Do not move another inch
or I swear to God I'll shoot.
Okay, who's exaggerating now?
I'm trying to make
a point here, okay?
Guys, I think you're getting
ahead of yourselves.
What happened
after your friend was killed?
I, um, I just couldn't
let it go.
I mean, nothing about it
made sense.
Yeah, your friend said
he'd overheard them
saying they'd turn
some guy named Henry?
Did you ever find out
who he was?
There's no way
to know for sure.
We started looking into S.I.S.
And the more we looked,
the less we liked these guys.
We went to Sutton,
and by that time, you got
your hooks into him.
Are you awake?
Of course I'm awake.
It's called "shavasana."
Corpse pose.
Wow, Cap.
You really getting into
this therapy thing, huh?
It was either that
or lose Helen.
Now why are you two
disturbing my peace?
Pack-Man was shot six times.
But the shot
that actually killed him
came from behind.
He was murdered
by the guys
who held up
that check-cashing place.
How'd that happen?
Well, the driver
could have shot him.
Not possible.
Getaway driver was seen
parked right out front
of that store.
And there's no way
he could have flanked Pack-Man.
What are you trying to say?
Listen, Captain,
we've been looking
into these S.I.S guys,
and it's not good.
Financials don't add up.
Each one of them lives
in a place no cop can afford.
Well, you live in a house
that no cop can afford.
I don't have a bank account
in Curacao.
John Crowell does.
You make accusations against
four highly decorated cops,
you better be able to bounce
a quarter off the evidence.
Now, what you guys have got
is circumstantial.
You guys got
to be careful.
These guys are dangerous.
That's why we got
to stay on this.
I wasn't finished.
I said they're dangerous.
You get me something
that I can work with.
I'll go after them
with everything we got.
It's the hospital.
I told them to get
in touch with me
if the cashier ever came
out of his coma.
Can you work
with a witness, Captain?
He hasn't opened his eyes yet,
but he is responding to stimuli.
He's been mumbling
about getting shot.
What the hell is S.I.S.
doing here?
Hey...
What are you doing?
Hey, hey,
get away from him.
I'm bringing him flowers.
Carrano's our witness.
Relax.
Well, I think we can
take it from here.
You guys paranoid
about something?
You clear on who
the bad guys are?
Yeah, we're clear.
Good.
Oh, my God...
They must have known
you were on to them.
Uh... yeah.
How long have you been sitting there?
Sorry...
It's just technically
we're supposed
to have the room right now
and it's just such a good story.
I really appreciate
your understanding,
but these are my patients;
they need their space.
Can you at least tell us
how it ends?
Sorry.
You just said
we're your patients.
You are my patients
at this exact moment.
We will see where we are
when this is done.
Okay.
Well, Carrano
eventually did wake up.
He said he saw someone
sneak up behind Pack-Man
and shoot him in the back.
Couldn't give
an exact description,
but it was damn close
to John Crowell.
And that was enough
to start a formal inquiry.
That's great.
That's not good?
Counselor, I've granted you
two separate continuances.
Now, can you produce
your witness or not?
Your Honor, we're trying
to locate Damian Carrano.
He hasn't been to work
in over a week.
His apartment is empty.
That's unfortunate
for your case.
If you can find
Mr. Carrano,
you can refile
your charges.
Dismissed.
Easy, easy.
We had people
protecting Carrano,
and these guys are so good
that they must have
paid them off,
made them run,
or buried him somewhere.
We couldn't even
refile the case.
Wow.
That must have been painful.
Yeah.
The thing is,
John Crowell not only
needed to win in court;
he needed to gloat about it.
You ready to tell this for real?
Tough one, kid.
I've eaten it
plenty of times in court, too.
You must be feeling
like ass right now.
Let me tell you something
that might give you
some clarity
on the situation.
Now, I want you
to think about that
when you're rewinding
that one in your brain.
What'd the meatheads want?
Hey.
Hey, Travis.
Travis.
Travis, talk to me.
Travis? Hey, Travis.
Hey, hey, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, no. Talk to me.
Let's sit down and talk
about it, all right?
What did he say?
Travis!
You move one more inch,
I swear to God I'll shoot.
Mitchell!
Put it down, kid.
You got 30 cops
in this room.
If you don't stand down,
somebody's got to draw.
Come on.
Lower the gun.
What did he say to you?
He told me he killed Pack-Man.
I was suspended pending
an administrative hearing.
And when I told the trial board
why I pulled my gun
on my partner, that I did it
to keep him from
shooting John Crowell...
I wasn't gonna shoot him.
Damn it, Travis!
Yes, you were.
I saw the look on your face!
You cocked your gun.
There was no consoling you.
So what?
There was no restraining you!
When I told
the trial board
why I did what I did,
they ordered us both
to stay away from
John Crowell and his men.
And they let us
back on duty,
th two conditions.
One, we do this.
And two, neither one of us
could go anywhere
near S.I.S.
So it worked out perfectly
for John Crowell.
It seems that way.
It was a smart play.
He provoked a hothead
into coming after him.
And now that we know
Crowell and his buddies
are planning something big,
we're not even allowed to sniff around.
That shouldn't stop us.
That's not all
that's stopping us, Travis!
I'm not gonna let you throw your
life away and shoot this guy.
I just said I wasn't
gonna shoot him!
How do you know it?!
You're not even willing
to admit you were gonna
shoot him
six months ago!
I know!
You haven't even thanked me
for saving you from making the
biggest mistake of your life!
At great cost
to my own career, I might add.
Why should I believe you now?
Because they killed Pack-Man.
Do you understand that?
They killed Pack-Man!
I know that.
You don't have the market
cornered on grief, Travis.
When did I say that?!
Huh?
Guys.
When did I say that?
Guys, guys, guys.
You are so close
to making real progress here.
Don't start sniping
at each other.
Travis, have you
told Wes the truth
about what happened that night?
No.
I don't really know what was
gonna happen that night.
And I did have my gun.
Thank you.
I wasn't in a good place.
But that was six months ago.
I'm different now.
We're different now.
I promise you,
I'm not gonna shoot him.
Wes, do you believe
that Travis has changed?
Can you take his word for it?
Yeah.
Then, guys, I think
you're in agreement.
I've only got one
thing left to say,
and it really isn't
very therapeutic.
Go kick their ass.
♪
You wanted me to see
the Southern California
Expo Center?
Mm-hmm.
Why?
They come here.
Crowell, Reese,
Serra, Prince
come here at night,
take pictures
and walk around
the perimeter.
I'd say they're
casing the place.
You've been following them.
When I can.
You're not supposed
to do that.
They killed Pack-Man.
Why this place?
Well...
Captain? Captain?
Did you sleep here
all night?
Oh, geez.
I set the alarm
so I could get up
before anybody got here.
What are you guys doing here?
Well...
I already tried diamonds
with Helen.
It didn't work.
No, Cap, uh,
it's not about Helen.
There's millions of dollars
worth of stones
moving through
that trade show.
S.I.S. is planning
to rip it off.
And you know this how?
Pack-Man says that
they pulled jobs on
their own sometimes, Cap.
They been casing the place.
You go after these guys,
you're gonna roll the dice
with your careers.
Not to mention mine.
That's why we're here.
We don't move unless
you want us to move.
No, what I want you to do
is be right.
I suggest you get
the hell out of here,
let me get dressed, huh?
We don't know how they're
gonna hit the Expo Center,
so we have to be ready
for anything.
We need people on every
exit, every entrance.
These guys know what they're
doing; they will shoot back.
There's no guarantee
that this ends well.
You join this op, you put
your career on the line.
Does anybody want out?
Good.
Let's go.
Slip in through the side door,
gear up where nobody can
see you, and then pull the job.
They work fast.
All units, be advised,
we are going in.
Hey!
LAPD! Put it down!
Police!
Don't move.
Hands up.
Hands up. Hands up.
Up, up, up.
Hey!
You're not S.I.S.
What the hell?
Police!
Stay there!
Damn it!
- Hey! Get him up, now!
- Hey!
Why the hell are you
shooting at my men,
and why are you in the middle
of our bust again?
What are you talking about, "your bust?"
Yeah!
We've been tracking
the Huns for a year.
And all those people
you put in danger...
Then you take a shot
at my guy.
Your guy should have identified
himself, all right?
Before the operation!
You have no right.
This is harassment!
You're not gonna
survive this.
You're done.
Backing your men is one thing,
Captain, but when your men
are pursuing a vendetta,
somebody's gotta step in
and be a grownup!
Looks like
he's holding his own in there.
No, come on. He's getting
torn apart in there.
- These guys put a year of police work...
- I don't get it.
Pack-Man said they were planning
something big right
before his birthday.
Anthey were staking out
that Expo Center.
They were staking it out because
they were planning a big bust.
You believe Pack-Man was just...
Wrong?
I don't know.
How'd it go?
You're each going to get
a two-month rap,
and after your suspension,
you have a choice.
You stay together,
you go to Pawn Shop Division.
Or you split up
and you go back
to the respective departments
that you came from.
So... pick between
a crap detail
or split up?
You're lucky you have a choice at all.
Figure out what you
want to do, but...
you got to turn your shields in
in the morning, huh?
What's gonna happen to you?
My career's in the rear-view
mirror as it is anyway.
I'll be all right.
Oh, you're here.
Good.
Everything okay?
It, uh...
it didn't go our way.
I'm sorry.
Uh... I've got a few minutes
before the session starts,
but we could talk about it...
We're not here for therapy.
We just wanted to say good-bye.
If Wes and I want to stay
detectives, we have to split up,
so no more couple...
you know, no more
couples therapy.
I see.
You've been a good doctor.
So thank you.
I was a good doctor,
and I will continue to be one
until you walk out of that door.
Talk to me.
What happened?
Look, it doesn't matter.
We were wrong about this one.
Ha.
In the last two months,
I have seen the two of you
bet on the outcome
of therapy exercises.
I have seen you start
and finish
a spitball competition...
Yeah, listen,
we suck at therapy...
I'm not done.
But I have never, in that time,
known you to be wrong
about your work.
Not when it was this important.
So think about that
before you quit.
You need some help
cleaning all this up?
Nah, I'm good.
So, um...
I'll see you.
What if she was right?
Dr. Ryan. What if...
what if we aren't wrong?
You think I haven't
wondered that, Travis?
Maybe Crowell and his men were
gonna steal some of those jewels
after they arrested the Huns,
but we're not going to
know that for sure now.
Their plan changed
once they saw us there.
Wes, four guys cannot
set themselves up
for life off of
some of the jewels.
Okay.
I'll play.
Crowell and his men couldn't
have arrested the Huns
and then just had all
that evidence disappear
from the crime scene.
There's... there's
too many questions.
Those jewels have
not disappeared
off the face of the earth.
They might as well have.
To get at them now,
S.I.S. would have to get
into that evidence locker.
It could be done.
Once you pay off the right guy.
Henry.
We always assumed
Henry was working somewhere they
were planning to hit, right?
What if he works here?
Yeah, they make a big bust,
look like heroes.
Then, a little while later,
millions of dollars' worth
of evidence just....
disappears.
Or maybe someone breaks in,
holds the place up.
Another member of the Huns?
Make sure you check "Henry"
as a first and a last name.
Of course I'm going
to check it
as a first and last name,
Travis.
Please, it's our last day
together; don't be patronizing.
Ooh.
Ooh?
Look at this.
There are eight cops with the
last name Henry in the LAPD.
But look at this one.
"Derek Henry.
Evidence Collection."
♪
Storm Front.
Call it.
One... two...
threesie!
♪
Come on. Let's go!
Go ahead, boys.
Shake hands.
♪
One of the S.I.S. guys
has already turned.
Ronnie.
The quiet one.
Yeah.
He's already agreed to
testify against Crowell.
Crowell's going down
for killing Pack-Man.
And the two of you?
How are you doing?
Good.
Yeah.
We both got reinstated,
both getting
commendations.
And, you know,
once everyone realized
that we were right
about S.I.S. being bent,
they erased our
original suspensions
and lifted the terms
of our first reinstatement.
Uh... which means...
We don't have to
come here anymore.
Couples therapy,
no longer required.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
What Wes is
saying is that
it's not compulsory anymore.
But if you'll still...
take us back...
I'm sorry, you're volunteering
for another go-round?
I can't believe it,
either.
But the truth is, I'm actually
doing a little bit better.
And, uh, well, Travis,
he's got a long way to go.
You really haven't made any progress;
you still live in a hotel.
- Guys, welcome back.
- You're still a compulsive womanizer.
Well, define "compulsive."
No, we need to use words like "I" in here.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==