Wes, you're early.
Uh, do you need a minute?
'Cause I can just wait out
in the hall.
No, sit.
Come, sit.
I've been wanting to have a word
with you in private, anyway.
Okay.
How do you feel
it's going? Therapy?
Well, I hated it at first.
Mm-hmm.
But it is occasionally...
helpful.
I can't tell you
how happy I am
to hear you say that.
You are the most
complicated patient
I have ever had.
Do you think you're ready
to go to the next step?
Next step?
You and me.
Private sessions.
Because there is a
connection there, Wes.
Don't pretend
you haven't felt it.
I, uh...
Mm-hmm.
People are gonna
be here any minute.
Any minute.
What do you say, Wes?
We have to get you ready
for the first exercise.
(phone rings)
Travis, it's not even
7:00 in the morning.
Never too early
to catch a bad guy.
Come on, get up, man.
Get out of bed.
Just got a break
in the hijacking case.
Get up, get up, get up, get up.
TRAVIS:
That's Barry Kennefick.
His buddies at the Port
call him Barry Forty
because...
he likes malt liquor.
Anyway, Forensics has just
been scrubbing the computers
of all the dispatchers
at the Port.
Turns out Barry's been
sending off e-mails
from a private account,
one for every truck
that's been jacked
on its way out.
Okay, so Barry's tipping
off the hijackers. All right.
Yeah, giving up the routes
and describing the cargo.
I figure we
lean on him hard enough,
maybe he'll give up
the actual thieves.
So when's he getting here?
Well, he's
not working today.
I guess he'll
be home eventually.
Hmm.
Yeah.
You ever dream about Dr. Ryan?
No. Why?
No.
No!
You?
Never mind.
No, no, no.
What kind of dreams
you been having about Dr. Ryan?
Look, I...
I don't want to...
Fine.
They're just,
you know, they're...
dreams.
Okay.
You dirty dog, you.
It's involuntary, okay?
I mean, I can't help it.
Ever since she showed up
with that ring on her finger.
I can't help
but think about it.
Her personal life, you know?
Yeah, how many dreams?
What happened?
How's she smell?
How's she feel?
Leave nothing out.
Travis, that's between...
All right, that's
between me and her, okay?
No, it's between you
and the dream version of her.
You got to be so smart,
don't you?
I'm trying to confide
something in you...
Confide in me, brother.
And you're being smart.
Trust me. I want to hear
all the details
That's him.
Thank God.
This conversation isn't over.
Hey, Barry Forty?
LAPD.
Why do they always think
they can get away?
I don't know.
(gunshot)
Got him.
You might want
to consolidate those keys.
Just keep the
important ones.
Make them easier to find
when you're in a jam. Like this.
Put them down.
Get out of the car.
I'm cooperating here, guys.
I'll give you names,
phone numbers...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay,
we'll get to that.
So, these dreams--
did you have one last night?
Travis, I do not
want to talk about it.
You brought it up.
In a moment of weakness,
I brought it up.
You were confiding in me.
We spend a lot of
time together.
I think it's
perfectly natural
that she shows up in
my dreams, all right?
Was she naked?
She was naked.
Oh, man.
Wait, wait, wait.
Weird question: I'm definitely
awake right now, right?
Not dreaming?
Yeah. Ow.
TRAVIS:
Huh.
Dietz.
Yeah, what's up?
Hey, man, uh,
can you take this guy
to the box for us, please?
Yeah, you got it.
You're not gonna
say anything, right?
Travis?
Dr. Ryan.
Hey, Wes was just
talking about you.
What brings you down here?
Hey, guys, I'm, uh, I'm just,
I'm waiting for Captain Sutton.
You okay?
Yes. Fine.
Sorry.
I'm rattled.
Um, Robert, my fiancé,
was attacked last night.
♪Common Law 1x11 ♪
Hot for Teacher
Original Air Date on August 3, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Go ahead.
Sweetie,
it's all good.
Hey.
I keep telling her
it's not so bad.
You should see the
other guys, they got some
pretty serious abrasions
on their knuckles.
Detective Marks,
Detective Mitchell,
This is my fiancé
Robert Ewell.
How's it going, bro?
Travis.
All right.
God, you look different
than I pictured.
Not that I've been...
picturing you.
Hi. Hi.
I recognize you
from the news.
I saw you on the--
You were building malls.
On the east side, right?
Yeah, marketing people
prefer to call them
open-air retail communities,
but guilty.
So, um,
what happened to you?
(sighs)
I'm building this new
development in Atwater Village.
I was just working late last
night, and a couple kids jumped
me on the way to my car...
We talked about this.
Yeah, we did talk about this.
Guys, don't have to
get involved in this.
It's a conflict of interest.
What? Why?
Why is there a conflict
of interest?
Oh. Oh.
She does not talk about
her work at home.
I promise you that.
But I did know
that she was working
with a couple of cops.
I just assumed that it was
a man and a woman.
No, just us.
Okay, you're done
with your statement?
I am.
Thank you so much.
Guys, I will see you
both later.
BOTH: Yeah.
SUTTON: We'll do what we can
to catch these guys
that tuned you up.
I appreciate that, Captain,
but seriously...
Please do not break your back
on my account.
It was a mugging.
I got to go.
And honestly, I would not
even of come down here
to make a report if this one
had not insisted.
Nice to meet you.
Huh.
No. No "huh."
She's your doctor, huh?
You stay away from
this, all right?
I gave the case to
Stiefvater and Rafalski.
Stiefvater and Rafalski?
Captain, What are you,
mad at Dr. Ryan?
No.
They were working the night tour
last night.
So I gave them the case.
Plus, you guys have
a hijacking ring to break up.
Yes...
Hmm.
You're gonna e-mail your
contacts in this hijacking ring.
You're gonna tell them
there's a truck
headed out today
that they're
gonna want to rob.
What should I tell them
is in it?
What are they
looking for?
TRAVIS:
Air bags?
Why would anybody
want to steal 800 airbags?
Black market
for everything, man.
Does he seem
kind of like a...
weatherman?
Who?
Dr. Ryan's fiancé.
Robert.
You got a developer?
I always saw her
with someone more serious.
Yeah, yeah,
someone intense, huh?
Brooding?
Someone who nobly
fights his tendency
to irritate others?
You think you are so smart.
I'm not talking about me.
Hmm. Yes, you are.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I mean, listen,
subconscious doesn't lie.
Travis, that guy
blow dries his hair.
(laughs)
WES:
Dr. Ryan has substance.
She volunteers her time
to treat us.
Think about that.
Surprises me she'd be seeing
a guy who builds malls,
that's all.
Yeah, but...
I mean, really,
you don't really know her,
and you sure as hell
don't know him,
so why would you
be surprised?
You're a terrible
conversationalist,
you know that?
Here we go.
(indistinct shouting
in distance)
(cocks gun)
I think you
should tell her.
Hmm? What?
Dr. Ryan, I think
you should tell her
that you've developed
serious, passionate...
feelings for her.
What?!
Yeah.
No.
A: I haven't developed
any feelings,
and B: No.
LAPD!
Don't move.
Get down on the ground.
Right now.
Now!
Slowly.
Easy...
You okay?
Yeah. Go, go, go, go!
(sirens approach)
Put the cuffs on him now.
LAPD! Put your hands in
the air! Do it!
Whoo! You're out of there!
Whoa! Nice play at
the plate, baby.
You're under arrest.
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
All right!
(sirens approach)
You see that, Dietz?
Hey, you know what?
I think I'm gonna have to tell
Dr. Ryan about them dreams.
What?
Yeah, I'm gonna have
to tell her.
You can't do that?
Why not?
'Cause, you know-- Bro Code.
No, no. See, you don't
subscribe to Bro Code.
We already been
through this.
Are you guys gonna read me
my rights?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we'll get to that.
Let me ask you a question:
Catcher's mask?
What's wrong with the
catcher's mask? They're cool.
I can still see your
face, dumb-ass!
That's one hijacking
ring off the books.
(sighs)
Let's pull out
some open cases
and see what we can
attack next, huh?
Yeah, we could do that.
Should do that.
What else would we do?
Yeah, Mr. Mitchell,
I... this is...
Stiefvater's here?
Hmm.
What's he doing
working the day shift?
I don't know.
But we could ask him
how it's going
with Dr. Ryan's thing.
We're not supposed
to get involved.
We're just checking up.
No rule against that, right?
That's a business expense.
Yes, seriously.
I have a stressful job, i.e.,
I need a place in Ojai
to unwind,
i.e., business expense.
You know, I think
you're saying "i.e."
where you mean "ergo."
I-I gotta go.
What do you guys want?
Well, you caught a mugging.
How's it going?
Sutton told me not to
talk to you guys about that.
You make any arrests yet?
I got a full caseload,
and I'm getting audited.
You think we got time
to work a favor job for Sutton?
I think you caught a case.
You should work it.
I am working it.
I gotta go, guys.
That's fine. Okay.
Keep up the good work.
You got it?
Indeed, I did.
Dr. Ryan's is a
woman of substance.
She deserves a much better
class of detective.
Upstairs.
Downtown.
So, weatherman Bob goes
by his construction site
in the middle
of the night.
Not a weatherman.
He's one
of the most successful
builders in L.A.
Okay, fine.
So, the builder goes there
to check, make sure
his equipment's all stocked,
and he gets jumped by two
African-Americans
on the way back to his BMW.
Yeah. about that,
they just ran up
and clocked him?
He didn't even see their faces
These construction
site's have a lot
of valuable stuff
lying around.
I'm sure there's a
night watchman on duty.
Abort.
Hey, I got a captains' meeting
in here in a little while.
What are you guys
doing in here?
Well, we wrapped up
the hijacking,
so we're just reviewing
open cases.
And you can't do that
from your own desk?
Oh, it's too loud
out there, Cap.
Have a good meeting.
Yeah.
Whew!
TRAVIS: Robert Ewell
has you working nights?
Yeah, I was on
shift last night.
But I'm confused.
One guy hit Mr. Ewell,
and he wasn't black.
You're sure?
Positive. But I heard
a call coming in,
so I went to the front gate.
A guy had just let
himself in.
Had a key and
everything.
Why didn't you call
the police?
Mr. Ewell told me
not to.
Mr. Ewell lied to us.
I knew there was
something off about him.
What did the attacker
look like?
He was, like, mid-20ish.
Dark skin,
but like European dark.
Armenian, Turkish,
something like that.
Is this the spot?
Yeah. Everything
looks normal.
I don't think
he took anything.
Sorry.
You seeing what I'm seeing?
Yeah.
It's not even done setting yet.
This poured concrete, did one
of the workers lay this in?
No, I don't think so.
I've been absolutely dying
to use this thing.
The department
wouldn't spring for it,
so I finally broke down
and got it myself.
You paid for that
thing on your own?
One of the advantages
of flipping
your company before you're 30.
That's gonna tell us
what's in there, huh?
Yep. It uses ultrasound.
(device beeping)
Well, looks like nothing.
Wait, hold on.
There we go.
WES:
What is that, a face?
BASIL:
Hey, there.
Who are you?
Hey, what's going on?
Why'd you you guys call
me down here?
We need to talk to you
about last night.
Oh. I thought you weren't
supposed
to be looking into that.
Well, we were naughty.
But you know a little something
about that, don't you?
What's this?
There's a dead guy
down in there?
Who is he?
We were wondering if
you could tell us that, Robert.
I have no idea!
You lied about getting mugged,
Robert. Your word doesn't have
a whole lot of credibility
right now.
And I get that.
Look, I am sorry about that.
But...
but this?
Come on. I build things.
I don't get
involved in
this kind of thing.
Then who beat you up?
I don't know.
Honestly, I don't.
I am in construction.
I'm not a criminal,
but if I want
to get anything done,
sometimes I have
to do business with them.
Did you do business with
criminals here?
The head of the Steam and
Pipe Fitters' Union is a man
named Aram Parisyan.
He is not a great guy,
from what I've heard.
I had to issue him a payment
to ensure that my workers
would show up. Cash.
You bribed him.
This is the way the construction
business works, okay?
Now, Parisyan, he thought that
gave him the run of the place.
He wanted keys,
he told me his people
were gonna be coming
through day and night.
And I said no, but obviously
somehow they got keys anyway.
Was Aram Parisyan here
last night?
No, just that guy.
Tell us about him.
He was driving
a Mercedes.
And he held up his fist
before hit me,
he had tattoos, like,
letters on his knuckles.
"R.I.P." on one hand--
like Rest in Peace--
and "Anna" on the other.
Guys, guys,
know that
I'm not in a position to ask,
but you have,
you have to do me a favor.
I mean, Emma and I...
we're planning a wedding in
Descanso Gardens in two months.
You just can't tell her
about this. I know
I was wrong to pay
that bribe, I know that.
And the only reason
I lied about it to you was
that so Emma
wouldn't find out.
Really, I'm not
a bad guy, okay?
I just got in
over my head here.
I was specific when I told you
to stay the hell away
from this case!
Whoa, Cap.
Deep breaths, man.
Let's find your
little happy place, man.
How about some serenity?
I'll find my happy place.
I had my happy place until you
walked into this room and set
these pictures on my desk!
Okay, you're mad.
Really?
Just tell us what
you want us to do here.
You got a body.
You got to work it.
We are working it, Cap.
We got the medical examiner's
office is digging the body
out of the concrete. We're
trying to get an I.D.
We sent a description
of the ink on
the guy's knuckles
to Gang squads,
but what I'm asking is
what do you want us to do
about Dr. Ryan, Captain?
What about her?
Well, the man she's planning
to marry bribed some gangsters
who buried a corpse
at his construction site.
Everyone makes bribes
in the construction business.
It doesn't mean that
Ewell's a bad guy.
No, but maybe
Dr. Ryan should decide
whether or not
he's a bad guy.
Maybe you should let him decide.
Enough.
That's what I want...
That's enough!
I happen to know this guy.
He paid a bribe,
and then he lied about it.
I'm not saying that's
the right thing to do,
but we don't have the right
to put our noses
in Dr. Ryan's business!
When's your next session?
In about 45 minutes.
Later tonight.
Okay. Listen to me.
This girl's responsible
for changing my life,
and God bless her,
she's actually trying
to do the same thing
for you two guys.
Stay the hell
out of it!
Just go to the session and be
your usual stupid selves!
No problem.
Wes has got lots to talk
to her about, anyway.
No, I don't.
What's going on, kid?
Wes is having sex dreams
about Dr. Ryan.
No, no.
Oh, sex dreams.
What do you mean,
Yeah, the sex dreams"?
You having 'em, too?
Well, I did. It's, it's natural.
See? That's what
I was saying.
You should talk to her about it.
See? Now that's what
I was saying.
Travis,
you say a one word,
I'll kill you
where you're sitting.
Hey, Dr. Ryan.
How's it going?
Hi. Hey.
So...
what is on the
agenda for tonight?
It's up to the group,
isn't it?
How come we never talk
about dreams in here?
Travis.
Do you want to talk
about dreams?
I think Wes
would love to.
Okay, I not going
to be held hostage here.
I'm a cop, a cop knows
how to deal with
a blackmail threats.
You put it everything
on the table.
You reclaim your power.
So, I've been having
dreams about you.
Go on.
Yes, please,
go on.
They're are, uh...
Oh!
scintillating in nature.
And I can't help it.
I really would like 'em
to stop,
so please help me make
them go away.
Oh, Wes, you don't have
to be embarrassed.
It's very common.
In fact, it's probably my
favorite side effect of therapy.
You're happy about this?
Well, I'm flattered.
Haven't you been dreaming
about me?
Uh... no.
No?
You don't find me attractive?
(clears throat)
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, sure I... I do.
Ab-Absolutely.
Oh, good. Let's get to work.
Wes, would you excuse us?
Yeah.
Could you tell the others
that I'm gonna need 20
minutes alone with my patient?
(grunting and panting)
Damn it!
Oh, this is all your fault.
What?
What? I caught the
dreams from you.
They're dreams, Travis.
Not the flu.
Morning, Wes.
Just give me a minute
while I finish up
with our friend here.
No problem.
Hi, Jonelle.
Right.
(sighs)
So, they always
start in therapy.
What?
My dream.
Yeah?
Me, too.
Listen, no details,
but, uh...
it almost started just like
our last therapy session.
You got there early,
it's a little bit awkward,
then things start
happening... differently.
We started talking
about your dreams.
You sold me out
to Dr. Ryan?
You sold me out to
Dr. Ryan in your dream.
It was a dream.
No. Subconscious doesn't lie.
Okay, listen, okay,
okay, just hear me out.
(sighs)
(whispers):
This has to stop, okay?
It took me a long time
to accept the fact
that Dr. Ryan was
a no-fly zone.
I can't let my deviant
subconscious start
to mess with that.
What am I supposed
to do about the dream?
You boys getting are hot
for teacher.
How much of that
did you hear?
Only the
good parts.
(laughs)
(clears throat)
So, I guess I have you two
to thank so very, very much
for keeping me on my toes.
It's not every day
that I get to use a jackhammer
to identify a corpse.
It's exhausting.
Uh, what did you learn?
Your John Doe died
from blunt force trauma.
He was wearing a track
suit, so it looks like
somebody jumped him
while he was jogging.
I got some DNA
from the assailant
underneath his fingernails,
but no match to the assailant's
DNA, but, however, your
John Doe is in the system.
His name is Craig
Joseph Seward.
Craig Seward?
Yeah.
I know that name.
Of course you do.
He's one of the worst
lawyers on the planet.
Well, he was.
If you've been arrested
for a D.U.I.,
don't let the government trample
on your rights.
I'm five-star D.U.I. Defense
Attorney Craig J. Seward,
and I'm ready to go
to war for you.
I hate that guy.
Yeah. Everybody
hates that guy.
Why would the Armenian
mob want him killed?
You mean, besides
his commercials?
(phone chiming)
Have to find out if
there's a connection
between Seward
and the man
that Dr. Ryan's
fiancé was paying off.
Parisyan?
Yeah.
All right, we'll get
to that later.
Listen, the gang squad
found a match
for those R.I.P. Anna tattoos
in their photo file.
They belong to a guy
named Karl Rezian.
He did two years
for aggravated assault.
Okay, so where
do we find him?
He told his parole officer
he has a job
at a dog shelter
in Atwater Village.
(dog barking)
I guess Anna
was a dog.
Yeah, Anna was one of our best
reclamation projects.
Reclamation projects?
We rescue fighting dogs here.
I have some literature
if you guys want
to learn more about it.
LAPD.
We need to speak
to a Karl Rezian, please.
Uh, yeah,
he's in the back.
BOTH:
Thank you.
(barking)
(loud barking and whining)
(growling)
Karl Rezian?
Yes. Shh, shh, shh, shh.
LAPD. Can we talk
to you for a minute?
Attack, Shirley!
(barking)
You get the dog.
I'm gonna get the car.
How do I get the dog?!
(barking)
See that? It's shiny, isn't it?
Just like a human liver.
(barking)
Want that? Go get it!
Freeze!
You're under arrest
for the murder of Craig Seward.
Down on your knees. Down!
What did he do to you, Karl?
Why did you murder Craig Seward?
I didn't kill anybody.
WES:  We've got two people
who can place you where
his body was found, Karl.
Your DNA test results are
gonna be back any minute,
and if they match what we found
on Seward's body,
you're gonna go away... forever.
I didn't kill anybody.
(buzzer sounds, door opens)
That's all I'm saying.
You heard the man.
He's done talking.
Gentlemen,
Timothy Mullin, counsel
to Mr. Rezian.
I didn't call a lawyer.
No. My services are provided
for you free of charge.
WES:
Let me guess.
By Aram Parisyan?
No, that's no concern of yours.
Are we done here?
We sure as hell
are not done here.
(door opens)
DNA's back.
MULLIN: And I guess
that concludes
our business.
Let's go, Karl.
I don't think it does.
Sit down, Karl.
Look, even if you didn't
kill Craig Seward,
you dumped the body
for whoever did, didn't you?
We're gonna go
pick up your boss,
so if there's anything
you want to say to us
before we put cuffs
on him, you should say it.
MULLIN: As it happens,
I also represent
Aram Parisyan.
Yeah, what a coincidence.
He's aware
that his name has come up
during this investigation,
and he's willing to offer
his full cooperation.
Gentlemen, let me introduce
you to Aram Parisyan.
Hey, guys, how you doing?
Hi.
You get in a fight?
What, this?
No, I just had my nose
done again.
Again?
Yeah, well, you know,
we keep, uh... refining.
I actually went in
for an eye lift,
but my guy offered me a rate.
Would your guy have
some contact information?
Absolutely. Hey, uh,
if you mention I referred you,
he'll give me a discount
on my next procedure.
Okay, well,
this isn't a referral.
We're just confirming
your story.
All right.
Why would you think
I wanted plastic surgery?
(laughs) Hey, we're all racing
Father Time.
Doesn't hurt
to get a head start.
Yeah. That's
awesome.
Listen, the lab is down on
the third floor,
and the lab tech will take
your DNA swab.
Oh, that's okay.
I brought my own.
This is a piece
of my, uh, columella.
That's like the, um...
the little nub
that divides up your nose?
My guy took a whack
at it yesterday,
gave me that
as a keepsake.
Should be some good DNA in there.
Okay.
We'll stick
with the usual procedures.
Thank you.
All right,
suit yourself.
Lab's on the third floor.
All right.
Take care, guys.
Good seeing you, man.
Thanks for your
cooperation.
Really good
to see you.
Okay.
That was strange
and disgusting, but...
most murderers don't usually
provide their own DNA sample.
Well, we'll find
out soon enough.
Even if Parisyan's
not a match,
we've still got Karl Rezian
for dumping that body.
Yeah, but if we ask Robert Ewell
to testify,
Dr. Ryan's gonna know
what he did.
Security guard can put
Rezian at the scene.
Okay. Sounds good.
Hey, man, sweet dreams.
Thank you.
Shut up.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Morning.
Good sleep?
I can't take it much more.
You too, huh?
Okay, let's get started.
Wes is having dirty dreams
about you.
How does he get it to stop?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Look, he's having
dirty dreams, too, okay?
I had, like, two.
You had, like, a hundred.
Okay, first of all, I did
not have a hundred, Travis.
I'm not a degenerate, and
secondly, I don't see why
we have to embarrass Dr. Ryan
by bringing this up.
I'm not embarrassed.
I'm encouraged.
(sighs)
Oh, no.
You're not gonna stand up and
take off your dress, are you?
No. Never mind.
Um, erotic dreams are
an extremely common occurrence
in therapy.
It's called transference.
You're hardly the first people
in the room
to have experienced it.
Really?
You had the dreams, too?
Cool.
RYAN: I'd say it's happened to
about half my patients.
It's a little uncomfortable
on both sides,
but it's a sign
that the therapy's working.
Really?
It is?
Yes, it means
that your mind has metabolized
what we're doing in here.
It's seeped into your thoughts.
Hence, the dreams.
Okay, hold on.
So, you want us
to have dirty dreams about you?
Ah. I want you
to have breakthroughs.
I want you to change
your lives and how
you relate to each other.
This is just a signpost
along the way.
but it's a significant one,
because it means
that you have committed to
therapy on a subconscious level.
Great.
Uh, okay, all right.
Keep right on dreaming, then.
Right.
I, uh... I'm sorry,
but he's not in there.
What?
I'm sorry, but the guy
that drove onto the lot
that night-- he's not there.
Look again.
That's enough.
Wait, wait, wait.
Did Parisyan threaten you?
Because if he did,
we can protect you.
MULLIN:
That's enough.
We had a lineup,
there was no I.D.
End of story.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
WES:
Rezian's DNA
doesn't match
the killer.
Parisyan's DNA does not
match the killer.
Our witnesses recanting
their testimony...
One witness.
We make Robert Ewell go on
record, this thing goes public.
Dr. Ryan knows exactly
what her fiancé did...
If Ewell doesn't testify,
the only thing you have
on this Rezian character
is that he sicced a dog on you.
Now, you guys started it,
you gotta live with
the consequences.
ROBERT: I don't know what
to do here, guys.
A couple of
Aram Parisyan's... buddies
came to my office yesterday.
And they made it very clear
that I shouldn't say anything
about what I saw.
Well, we're pretty sure
the other witness
got the same treatment, 'cause
he's not talking to us either.
Yeah, can you blame him?
I mean, you can
have my DNA, fine.
But...
other than that, we're-we're
talking about my family here.
Okay. We will
protect your family.
What does that mean?
What, I...
I get to tell my fiancé
that we're going to have cops
following us around
all the time?
We've been doing everything
we can to keep you out of this,
but if you don't cooperate
with us right now,
a man who buried
another man in concrete,
at your construction site...
He walks.
Okay.
Dr. Ryan is
a good woman.
And you don't think she'd
really want that, do you?
She's a great woman.
(door opens)
And there she is.
Well, we can go.
RYAN:
Hi, darling...
ROBERT:
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Uh, Detective Mitchell
and Marks
have been investigating my case.
What?
No, I asked you
to stay out of it.
Yeah. We-we know.
Yeah. We know.
We didn't mean to,
it was this other detective,
he wasn't very good...
Yeah.
And so we took his file, and we
decided we were gonna try...
Mistake?
...and follow up on it.
It was a mistake.
Could someone please
tell me what is going on?
Yes.
We need to talk.
Let's go upstairs.
How pissed off do you think
she's gonna be?
How pissed off
would you be?
Hi...
Robert will identify the man.
He'll testify at any trial.
He'll provide you with
a DNA sample that proves
he had nothing to
do with this murder.
We spent the night together,
we had dinner, we went to bed...
We were both woken
by the phone call.
He told me he had to
check on something at work.
Thank you.
Yeah. Listen, uh, Dr. Ryan,
we were just trying to...
Is there anything else you need?
No.
Good.
Pissed.
Yeah.
TRAVIS: We have a witness that puts
you at the site of the murder.
That's conspiracy
after the fact.
WES:
You'll do 20 years, Karl.
TRAVIS: Add that to the time
you're facing
for siccing your
pit bull on us...
you should get free just in time
to start collecting
Social Security checks, Karl.
Stop trying to
intimidate my client.
Karl, a lot can
happen at a trial.
Yeah. We could just
decide to charge him
with Craig Seward's murder.
Make a circumstantial
case out of it.
I didn't kill him!
You don't have to
talk to these men.
Shut up!
I didn't even hire you.
Karl.
Talk to us.
Tell us what happened.
We'll ask the D.A.
to cut a deal.
You might only do five years.
I got an e-mail.
Told me to go to the fountain
in Riverside Park
and bring the trash over
to that construction site.
I got there, that guy's body
was stuffed under a bench.
So I cleaned
up the garbage.
Who sent the e-mail?
Karl...
Aram Parisyan.
WES: So his DNA's wasn't
found on Seward's body,
but he gave Rezian the order
to dispose of that corpse.
That's conspiracy.
Let's see if that's
enough to convince him
to give up the murderer.
Hey, Mullin... what are you
doing? Give me that!
Give it to me.
Don't let him go anywhere.
He just committed a felony.
Maxine, I gotta
leave early today...
You want me to
forward your calls?
Take messages...
Damn it!
Ah!
Stay down. Stay down!
(groans)
My nose isn't set yet!
My, uh... my bad.
MULLIN: If you expect my client
to cooperate,
let me assure you
you're dead wrong.
TRAVIS: Be quiet.
We're charging you the
second we're done here.
With what?
I advised my client of a
development, that's all.
Oh, come on.
I'm  still Aram Parisyan's attorney...
You told him to run, Mullin.
Why would he run?
You got the word of a convicted
felon that says, what?
He sent an e-mail?
He conspired to
cover up a murder.
And Rezian's gonna
give up the cell phone
where he checked the e-mail.
Anyone could have borrowed
my client's phone.
Oh! Is that the defense
you're planning on using?
Because if that's the case,
I suggest you find
new counsel, Mr. Parisyan.
Who killed Craig Seward?
You don't have to
do this, Aram.
Oh, shut up, Tim!
It's over, man.
I'm sorry.
Stop him!
(grunting)
Get him out of here.
All right, Cap!
Always wanted to
do that to a lawyer.
(laughs)
Nicely done.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's get back.
Wow. Mullin.
I know.
Should've known
by the suit.
WES: It turns out that
Aram Parisyan and his lawyer
have been friends
since they were kids.
Now, Timothy Mullin
and Craig Seward,
they went to
law school together.
Mullin got a DUI
a little while back,
so he hired his old
schoolmate to represent him.
See, the thing is...
Mullin started talking about
the work he was doing
for Aram Parisyan.
He said some things
he shouldn't have.
Seward started blackmailing him.
Mullin paid for a few months,
Seward tried to up the payments,
then Mullin snapped.
He called Aram Parisyan
to get rid of the body.
Parisyan just farmed out that
disposal out to Karl Rezian.
Now, Mullin, Parisyan, Rezian,
all these guys are in jail now.
They're not gonna bother
your family anymore.
Thank you.
Okay.
Um, listen, Dr. Ryan...
we owe you an apology.
Well, you did what
you're trained to do.
You're not wearing
your engagement ring.
Look, uh, this is
none of our business.
You know relationships.
We know criminals.
Your fiancé got involved in some
stuff, made some mistakes...
You did what you're
trained to do,
and I'm going to do the same.
So, gentlemen, we have
a conflict of interest.
I'm terminating your therapy.
What?
There's a group that
meets over in Hollywood
under Dr. Van Waals.
I'm going to refer you over to him.
Wait.
Hold on.
Don't do this.
You're a good doctor.
Yeah.
We're-we're
metabolizing therapy.
We're doing better...
We like you.
Regardless.
We are where we are.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Travis said it,
I didn't say it.
It's better that I know.
But I can't help you
if I can't trust you.
RYAN:
I wish you the best of luck.
You ready for this?
I don't really want to
break in a new therapist.
Well, then, you shouldn't have
stolen that case file, Travis.
What are you talking about?
You wanted me to steal it.
I never said to steal it.
You didn't have to say anything...
I just said,
"Let's check in on Doctor..."
MAN: I do not care to!
Let's just... go.
MAN: You're the one that
wanted this divorce.
Do you hear that?
No, it is not my problem,
Susan, it is your problem!
You want the divorce,
that's just fine!
But my lawyers are
gonna grind you into dust!
And I'm gonna take that dust and
put it in a jar on a shelf
next to a picture of my new
wife, who, in addition to being
younger and hotter than you,
is also gonna be dumber
so she's gonna go for
the freaking pre-nup!
(snaps phone shut)
Geez!
Hey.
Hi.
Welcome. You here for...?
Yeah. Yeah.
You, too.
And just in time, huh?
Well, actually, uh... no.
I'm Dr. Van Waals.
I'm your new therapist, and...
the thing is...
you weren't supposed to
hear any of that.
We've really need to get
Dr. Ryan to take us back.
Hells, yeah.
'Cause this guy is...
Okay.
VAN WAALS: Please. Come into
the safe circle.
Let's sit,
and let's find some inner peace
with a deep, cleansing breath.
(inhales, exhales)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==