Lisa!
What in the hell are you doing?
Stop it!
Honey, are you awake?
Can't you have breakfast with me
before I go to work?
Can't you stay in bed a little longer?
I don't have time.
What would we do in that case?
I don't know. Sleep.
What are you gonna do today?
Nothing.
- I might visit Mackan in his office.
- Okay.
Can you pick up a bottle of wine for
your parents tonight?
That's not necessary.
Dad has plenty.
Would you please do it, I don't want
to come empty handed again.
I feel embarrassed about it. Please?
- I'll fix it.
- Thanks.
I really need to go now.
Go, then.
Damn you're hot.
Now I really have to go.
I'm opening today.
Can't you check with the girls,
so they are free.
- What do you mean?
- This weekend.
Oh, of course.
Say hi to Mackan for me.
Don't forget the wine.
I checked up on the house
we talked about,
it seems like it's been abandoned
since forever.
- So I think you can walk straight in.
- Sounds great!
That's perfect. Now we have a place
to stay for the weekend.
But are you sure it's abandoned?
Yes, of course.
If you run into any problems you can
just forward them to me.
- Promise me you'll be careful.
- Of course we'll be careful, Eva.
If you get bored, Dad and I
might come over.
Anyone for a whisky, Albin?
No, I hate whisky.
You know that.
I can take a whisky.
A small one.
Alright, nice.
Mom, could I have another beer?
Have you made any other
plans for the summer?
We talked about going somewhere in
August, but that depends
on if I can get time off.
- I see.
- Thanks.
If you're not doing anything else, you
could always come out to the cabin.
Well, you can barbeque,
go fishing or help out dad.
It sounds nice, mom, we'll consider it.
Dad, what do we do about
the electricity?
- Elin? (A girl's name)
- Electricity. In the house.
Aha, I thought you said Elin.
That's not gonna be a problem. I can
power it up temporarily from work.
I work for all the power distribution
so that's not a problem.
How long has the house been abandoned,
do you know that?
- I don't know, five years, maybe.
- Is there still furniture?
Yes, absolutely.
I'll make a map for you.
There are some small, hard to find
roads, but it'll be alright.
Great.
Now let's make a toast.
To Elin. No, what am I saying?
- For Ida and Albin.
- Cheers!
Something like this.
What do you think?
Looks great.
- Bye.
Hi.
- God, you are sweaty.
- Sorry, I was at the gym with Marie.
- Did you talk about the weekend?
- Sorry, she can't come.
What?
Of course she's coming.
What a relief. I've been
looking forward to this.
Tove is coming too,
so we'll be four girls.
- That's perfect.
- So we can take my car.
Okay, so the guys take the
other car, perfect.
So, who's coming?
Albin and Markus of course. And...
I haven't talked to him.
But can you call and ask at least?
I think he's busy with his friends.
I don't think he wants to.
I don't want you to see him.
He's a player.
You can't say that,
you are siblings.
That's exactly why I know
what he's like.
Okay, but if I promise not to do
anything with him?
What kind of promise is that?
I don't want to, but okay,
I'll call him.
It's gonna be so much fun.
But tell him we are three
single girls that are coming.
Absolutely, I'll tell him that.
- I have a customer soon, so...
- Okay, I'm leaving. Later, kiss kiss.
- I'm so excited!
- Linnea, I have a surprise for you.
- What is it?
- You'll have to wait and see.
I'm so happy you could make it.
I don't know if I would want
to come along otherwise.
The asshole didn't want to give me
the weekend off at first.
So how did you manage?
I'm not going back anymore.
Marie, tonight you and I are
gonna go all in!
We're gonna get so wasted!
I have a good wine with me, Linnea.
You're gonna love the taste.
It's sweet and dry at the same time.
Okay. I've got liquor.
Marie, you should do wine reviews.
Sweet and dry at the same time.
- Linnea, stop, there is Simon.
- What, is he coming?
Yes, I told him you were coming.
Thanks for the heads up,
I haven't had time to fix myself up.
- Hi sis.
- Hi Simon.
- What's up?
- I'm fine, thanks.
This looks like a promising weekend.
Simon.
- Do I go with you?
- I don't think so.
But ask Albin if he can drive ahead,
we don't know where to go.
- Okay, I'll tell him. See you there.
- Bye, Simon.
- Hi, Simon.
- Hi.
- Long time no see.
- Yeah.
- Good to see you.
- You too.
- This is Markus.
- Hi.
- Hi, Markus.
- Hi, Simon.
Have you... traded up?
- No, this is Olof's car.
- What happened to the Mazda?
I still have it.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
The girls asked us to drive first.
They didn't seem to know the way.
- Okay.
- Where are we going?
- It's a house that my dad found for us.
- Cool.
It looked promising in the other car.
That sure as shit wasn't three miles.
- Where are we?
- You're so impatient.
- We just need to go straight in here.
Isn't he hot, Ida's brother?
Shall we?
Abbe, I have a feeling this
is gonna be so much fun.
Yeah, I know.
It sure was a long time since we
got together like this.
- Yeah, as long as Dad keeps his promise.
- You haven't seen the house?
No, I haven't. But it's cool,
he said it was fine.
- How are things with Ida?
- It's good. In fact, better than ever.
I'll have to keep chasing girls myself.
C'mon, what happened to my wingman?
C'mon, I'm always on your side,
you know that.
You have lots to choose from this weekend.
I almost wish I were single.
Look, someone's standing over there.
- Who is that?
- I don't know.
Hi.
Do you want something?
Hey! I'm talking to you! Fucking idiot,
who the hell does he think he is?
Cut it, Simon, maybe he just doesn't want
to talk to you. Take it easy. Let's go.
- What was that about?
- Eh, forget it.
- Shit it's rundown.
- Three doors, that is something new.
All the doors are locked.
Albin, do you have a key?
No.
- How did you think we were gonna get in?
- He didn't think at all.
- I can try and lockpick the door.
- Can you do that?
I had a certain need for
that back in school.
So you have some gypsy in you after all,
I wouldn't have thought that.
Marie, over here.
Come.
- Can't we scare the shit out of Albin?
- Okay, but how?
Look, this window is open.
I'll help you get inside, then you can
open the front door from within.
- But I don't want to go in alone.
- C'mon, you can do it.
If you'll take my bag for me.
- Markus, I can't see anything in here.
- Use your eyes.
"Use your eyes".
This is awesome.
Hello?
Who said I was the best?
Most handsome too, was that you?
- What, is it open?
- Oh, you're so talented, sweetheart.
- Let's not exaggerate here.
- Exactly, I would've kicked the door in.
That's great, Simon, then we can be
eaten by mosquitoes all night.
Shall we go in?
- So this is what it looks like.
- Does it smell a little funny in here?
What a place.
- Imagine they just left it like this.
- Yeah, really.
Oh, my God.
Shit, you scared me.
- How the hell did you come in?
- You really startled me.
My idea. We got you good.
- Is there gonne be any action here tonight?
- For sure.
- Wanna check it out upstairs?
- Alright.
- My Dad did great, right?
- Absolutely.
It's been so long since we had a
whole weekend together.
The girls really appreciate this.
And it's good for Tove
to get away from
all her problems for awhile.
- Where are we gonna sleep?
- We're not gonna need that.
We won't be sleeping.
It's strange how you can be so different.
My parents would never do anything for us.
I guess. We didn't get to
choose our parents.
Wow. So this is where we're
supposed to sleep tonight?
Pink. That's really my color, isn't it?
- What are you thinking now?
- I don't know. What do you want?
We were suppose to scare Albin,
what happened?
I don't know.
I don't feel so well.
Is it something serious?
C'mon, we're suppose to have a good time,
you can't be sick now.
I'm sure it'll pass.
I'm going inside.
Mackan, do you want your bag or not?
I'm looking forward to a cold drink.
Guys, Linnea is here.
Screw Markus.
- You might need this.
- Thanks.
It feels really fun to be able to get
together for a weekend again like this,
it's been a long time.
I mean, Marie has been talking about moving
to Japan for like, five years now.
Now you're stuck with us instead.
- All jokes aside, cheers.
- Cheers for Marie.
Tasty.
Marie, been drinking too much already?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Fuck, I feel horrible.
(Low battery level)
You scared me.
Could you move over, Marie?
C'mon, let's head down to the others.
Hello, Marie?
C'mon, answer me.
- Albin, you have to help Linnea.
- What the hell happened?
What the fuck is happening?
Oh, fuck.
Albin, come here!
Get something to tie her with.
Sit still!
Tove, can you hear me?
Oh God, she spit on me.
I found this.
- How is it going?
- Not good. Her upper lip is torn off.
- She needs to go to a hospital.
- I have to help Simon, where is Markus?
I don't know, maybe he
went outside or something.
- Hit me. Hit me!
- Shut the fuck up.
Shut up before I knock your teeth out.
Oh, shit.
I have an idea!
- Abbe?
- Where the hell have you been?
- What the hell has happened?
- Stay away.
- Why is she tied up?
- She was totally insane before, okay?
- How did she become like this?
- She came down the stairs and attacked me.
Move over.
Have you seen her eyes?
What happened to you?
Did she get rabies?
Rabies? Do you think you become
like this from rabies?!
- Has she been drugged?
- Have you even tried drugs?
- Don't fucking open the door.
- Mackan, in the kitchen, now.
Close the side door and stand behind me.
- Stay behind me now.
- Give me the towel.
Keep quiet both of you, I'll handle this.
Hey.
Hello there.
Is everything alright in there?
Yes, why wouldn't it be?
I need you to let me in.
Why?
I want to have a look at your friend.
Who the hell are you?
- Have you been spying on us?
- Wait inside.
Let's put it this way, I was nearby and
you people aren't exactly quiet.
Let me in now.
Look, I don't know who you are,
and you're standing here with a rifle.
I want you to leave now.
- That's enough, let me in.
- Okay, just take it easy.
Where is she?
Behind the door.
Hello, can you hear me?
- This girl is dead.
- Are you out of your mind?
She's sitting there, damn it.
She has been turned into something else.
It's too late, you have to get rid of her.
Let's take it easy. If you know something
about this, you need to tell us right now.
Back up! I said back up.
Stand over there, let's go.
- What are you doing?
- Listen to me now very carefully...
A couples of days ago, me, my wife and
daughter were out here in the woods.
Keep in touch when you're getting
ready so we can meet up here again.
Of course. But are you sure
this is alright with you?
Yes, I'm sure. You get the fish
and we'll get the chanterelles.
Okay.
We parted there. I went fishing and
Karin and Lisa went to pick mushrooms.
About chanterelles, you know it's those
yellow things, right?
Yes, dad, I know that.
- Alright, good luck now.
- Take care.
And then they found this fucking house.
I don't know what happened,
but it was something.
Her eyes, I can't describe it, but...
It wasn't her.
What exactly do you think you know?
Okay...
My grandfather told me a story
when I was a little kid.
About a legend that was about creatures
that lived beneath the ground.
I was told that if you trespassed their
lands, things could go very bad.
If you saw one of these creature, you
should turn and run as fast as you could.
They were so powerful if you gazed into
their eyes, they would take your soul.
- Wait up, old man, is this your theory?
- That's exactly what I mean.
- And that is what has happened in here.
- What happened to your family?
They didn't make it.
Just before Lisa...
She whispered to me...
Mom and I found a house. We went in.
We found a basement. Help me Dad...
I think your girl suffered the same fate
that my grandfather told me about...
Like my wife and Lisa suffered...
- So you're saying Marie has...
- Listen to me now.
This girl is dead. Something has taken her
body. What happens here is dangerous.
You have to call the police.
But the most important thing is...
We get rid of her.
You don't touch Marie,
we have to take her to a hospital.
A doctor can't do anything about this.
Have anyone been in contact with her
since she changed into this?
We've all been near her, why?
I don't understand what you mean.
I mean, if anyone has gotten any blood on
themselves, or has been scratched or bitten?
What has that got to do with anything?
Once you've been exposed,
it spreads easily.
We have to get rid of her.
Preferably, burn her.
Of course we're not gonna do that.
I have to call an ambulance.
Shoot her!
Stay back.
- Are you okay?
- What happened, where is Tove?
She went completely crazy and attacked me.
She jumped out the window.
This can't be fucking happening.
- Where are you going?
- Ida, come now, we're leaving.
Simon, wait.
I have to call the police.
Come on.
Simon, if we're getting out of here,
everyone needs to come along.
I don't give a shit about
the others, okay?
Do as I say for once and get going.
We need help, I don't know exactly
what's going on but...
- You don't have a choice, okay?
- Simon, release her.
Excuse me, you want something?
You heard me, it's not up to you
to decide what Ida should do.
I talked to the police and they told
me that someone has to go
- and meet them by the cars.
- Fine. I guess I'm going.
Stay here and fucking rot.
I'll go with you.
Yeah, that's gonna be fun.
You're the last person on
earth I want with me.
I'll go.
No, you're gonna stay here.
It's okay. It's better if we are two,
it's gonna be fine.
Let's go.
Sweetheart, it's gonna be okay,
I promise. Be careful now.
Yes, Daddy.
- Hello? Are you still there?
- Hello?
- Can you hear me?
- Yeah, I hear you.
- What did you decide?
- Two guys are meeting you by our cars.
Where are you going?
I'm just gonna check something out.
Do you really have to?
Just over here.
Keep close to me.
- Here, take this.
- What am I suppose to do with it?
You never know.
I'll take this.
What is this?
No, are those birds? Oh, shit.
Have they eaten each other?
Let's go.
I'm coming.
Motherfucking idiot.
Now you son of a bitch.
Hold that rifle for me.
Fucking shit, hell.
Wait up, Simon,
I can't keep up with you.
We can't stop now, come on.
I can't see anything when you're
walking ahead with the flashlight.
There are fucking stones everywhere.
Okay, come here.
Let's stick together.
This is probably the wrong
time to ask but...
What?
Wait a second.
What's the matter?
It's not very good.
I know you feel a bit shocked because
of everything that has happened.
Marie and Tove,
I barely know them but...
I feel a bit down myself.
It's gonna be alright.
We're on our way to the police now.
It didn't turn out the way we planned.
- Oh, shit, stay there.
- What is it?
Don't come any fucking closer.
I said stay there.
- Simon, what's wrong?
- I go, you stay.
Are you insane?
You can't just leave me here.
What the fuck.
I told you to stay away.
I don't feel so good.
I have to lie down.
Do you want something to drink?
- I'm screwed, right?
- Mackan, drink this.
Mackan, listen to me now. The police
are gonna be here soon.
Everything's gonna be alright.
- Mackan, it's gonna be alright.
- Why the hell are you still here?
Listen, the police are
gonna be here soon.
- Marie is gone.
- What do you mean, gone?
Markus, you need to get up now.
Damn, I'm bleeding.
- Was that Marie?
- I don't know.
What do we do?
Wait.
Ida, stay there now.
Albin, you fucking cunt,
get over here!
No!
Honey, look at me.
We got to go now, we can't wait
any longer. Where is your phone?
On the sofa, I think.
- Okay, let's go.
- Weren't we suppose to wait?
No, we need to get out of here, we
need to go through the woods.
Albin, get up.
We have to go now.
Fuck, this isn't gonna work.
Get inside again.
Ida!
Ida. Where are you?
Ida. Open the door.
- Open the door.
- Simon, are the police with you?
Where is Linnea?
I said, open it!
Open it!
Fuck.
Come on, fucker!
Come on!
Forgive me, Linnea.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Please, don't do it.
Please!
No, Linnea, Please.
He's still outside.
I think it's Markus.
It's too high up,
we're gonna break our necks.
We need to get out,
It's our only chance.
How? We're never gonna
get out of here.
Okay, honey, let's do like this.
We can't wait for the police anymore.
I'm gonna loosen the ropes now.
If Markus is outside
I'm gonna hit him immediately.
Stay right behind me and don't do
anything before I say so.
- Okay.
Okay.
We're not gonna see shit in the woods, but
we'll get through this. Are you ready?
Okay, let's do it.
Ida, down.
Go down the stairs.
Linnea?
Ida, get up again.
Get up!
Try to find another way out!
Up! Up!
Ida, fuck that, Ida!
Ida!
Albin!
We need to go. We need to go.
- I'll be right behind you.
- I can't do it.
I'll be right there. Hurry!
Simon. Simon!
Simon, come here!
Ida!
Ida. Ida!
Ida. Honey.
Can you hear me?
Say something.
Fuck!
Albin. Albin.
Honey?
Fuck! Fuck!
No, no, no!
Die!