It is November.
A full moon rises.
Almost 400,000 kilometers away,
Planet Earth falls under its spell.
Our oceans stir.
An ancient undersea ritual
is underway.
The outcome of this event
will not only affect marine life
in the surrounding waters,
but will also give us a clue
about the health
of the entire ocean system.
The creature responsible is coral.
And this is coral's story.
The story begins here,
with the incredible phenomenon
that is mass coral spawning.
It's an annual event,
cued by the sun and the moon.
It involves
over 140 different species,
and has been occurring
for thousands of years.
Although corals
have no brain and no eyes,
somehow individual species
spawn together,
sometimes down to the minute.
Like tiny love-letters,
the genetic material
is cast into the ocean currents,
connecting reefs
over hundreds of kilometers.
Like us, corals take up to
nine months to prepare for birth.
But many are hermaphrodites,
so they gestate both egg and sperm.
On spawning night,
these are grouped into bundles and
delivered through the coral's mouth.
For most, it's a gentle birth.
Over a short time-span,
the bundles break apart
and the egg and sperm must find their
counterparts from another colony.
Billions set forth, but few survive.
Many other creatures
choose the same conditions to spawn
and the reef waters are transformed
into a vast liquid womb,
clouded with eggs and sperm.
Mass spawning
overwhelms potential predators,
so the coral eggs have more chance to
be fertilized and begin a new colony.
By daybreak, vast slicks
on the surface mark their passage.
Coral is an architect
not only of the undersea world,
but above the surface too.
Dead coral breaks down into sand
that eventually builds up
to create coral cays.
These shores and shallows
provide sanctuary -
and important breeding grounds -
for a variety of other creatures.
All told, reef-building corals
have colonized every tropical ocean,
shaped and protected
thousands of kilometers of coastline
and influenced marine evolution
for millions of years.
Birds like these noddy terns
rely on coral reefs for food
and coral cays for shelter.
Birds help vegetate cays
by depositing seeds.
These seeds grow
into trees and forests
which in turn provide the birds
with nesting sites.
These sandy outposts are frequented
by many tropical seabirds,
with some pairs returning to the same
nesting sites year after year.
Primitive corals date back
over 450 million years.
Modern reef-building corals first
emerged around 250 million years ago
and their reefs
have provided homes and sustenance
for innumerable species ever since.
Over coral's long history, five
mass extinctions have come and gone.
During each,
up to 90% of all life-forms perished.
Two of these extinctions
occurred during the rise
of modern reef-building corals.
Rather than falter,
they somehow survived,
rebuilt their reefs
and transformed the oceans anew.
Today, coral reef ecosystems
are important nursery grounds
for many iconic marine animals,
such as the sea turtle.
There are seven species
of sea turtle
and all are long-lived
and slow-growing.
They take between l 0 to 30 years
to sexually mature and mate at sea.
These marine reptiles are nomadic
and swim thousands of kilometers
during their lives.
But strong instinct and
mysterious natural forces guide them,
so that when a female
needs to lay her eggs,
she returns to the very beach
where she was born to do so.
Here, she digs a nest
and coral sand becomes the womb.
Hundreds hatch, but only one or two
will make it to adulthood.
They can then live
for up to a century.
When a turtle hatched 100 years ago,
it would have seen the world's
coral reefs in all their glory.
Pre-industrial seas
were clean and clear
and corals had enjoyed good
conditions for millions of years.
Throughout the Indian
and Pacific oceans,
and into the Caribbean
and west Atlantic,
reefs were thriving.
The turtle spent its youth
exploring these reefs
and witnessed the engineering marvel
that is coral.
By harnessing the power of the sun
and perfecting recycling,
coral built energy-efficient cities
that put many of ours to shame.
Collectively,
these cities created vast empires,
some visible from outer space.
Here, the turtle found itself
in great company,
for these undersea empires were home
to vast numbers of marine species
of every imaginable shape and size
and were crowded, colorful places.
Today, reefs have one of the
highest levels of biodiversity
of any ecosystem
and are some of the most biologically
important places on Earth.
Together, turtles and corals
have witnessed many changes
to their watery world.
They are some of the only beings
to have survived
the last mass extinction event
65 million years ago.
Scientists predict
that in the coming century,
they will face ocean conditions
as catastrophic
as during that last extinction.
Wise old turtles have seen
the warning signs for a while.
70% of the world's reefs
have already been destroyed
or are seriously threatened.
And all but one
of the seven sea turtle species
are classified 'endangered'
or 'critically endangered'.
For the first time
in millions of years,
the future of both turtle and coral
is uncertain.
Many things affect
the health of coral reefs,
in particular, sea temperature,
sea level and water chemistry.
Reefs may look mighty,
but corals themselves are fragile
and can be fatally harmed by just
subtle changes in their environment.
When sea levels rise too rapidly,
corals can't grow fast enough
and reefs drown.
As atmospheric
carbon dioxide levels increase,
ocean acidification intensifies
and reefs will dissolve.
And a sustained increase of only
1-2 degrees in ocean temperature
can cause corals to bleach and die.
By the end of this century,
it's predicted that the global climate
could be 5 degrees Celsius hotter
or more.
At this rate, bleaching
will become an annual occurrence,
and this colorful landscape
will literally fade away.
A healthy coral reef
is easy to spot.
A complex structure awash
with color, variety and activity.
This is a tangled, tropical garden
to rival anything on land.
Most amazing about this garden
is that many of the 'plants'
are actually animals.
Like grasping hands,
coral mouths hungrily sift
the passing currents for food
day and night.
The creature we call 'coral'
is a primitive sac-like polyp,
part animal, part plant.
The animal part feeds on plankton.
The plant part
consists of microscopic algae -
called zooxanthellaethat
photosynthesize using sunlight.
Each polyp is connected
to its neighbor
passing along energy and nutrients.
These polyps multiply
to create colonies,
which combine to form reefs.
In this way, energy is produced,
shared and recycled
throughout the entire ecosystem.
With the energy they produce,
corals not only thrive
but also manufacture
calcium carbonate,
the special 'concrete'
that builds reefs.
This is one secret
behind corals' great empire building.
The other is budding.
Budding is a process
where coral polyps produce
genetically identical copies
of themselves
and extend their colonies
without spawning.
The calcium carbonate foundation
secreted by hard corals
can be one kilometer thick in p laces
and hundreds of thousands
of years old.
The living reef we see today
is just a thin veneer on top,
made up of many different species,
including soft corals...
...fan corals...
...and sponges,
gorgonians and crinoids.
All told, coral has evolved into
more than 1,000 hard coral species
and over 700 soft coral s,
each perfectly specialized
to fill its own niche.
Understanding how corals build reefs
highlights the seriousness
of climate change
and how it threatens
this complex ecosystem.
Our oceans have always absorbed
atmospheric CO2 like a giant sponge.
But now those levels are so high that
the water chemistry is changing -
a process referred to
as 'ocean acidification'.
Alkalinity is falling
and naturally-occurring
carbonate ions are being affected.
Many marine creatures need these ions
to produce calcium carbonate
for their shells and skeletons.
Hard corals need them to build reefs.
Ocean acidification seriously
threatens all these processes.
But in every natural catastrophe,
there are winners and losers.
Jellyfish
are distant relatives of coral,
but unlike coral,
they are more adaptable
to changes in water temperature
and chemistry.
Their numbers
are already on the rise.
And they are making our seas sting.
Coral's other ancient cousin
is the sea anemone.
Like coral,
the anemone is a simple being
that has been highly successful.
In fact, the anemone
is like a huge coral polyp.
At its center is a mouth
surrounded by a vast mantle
of stinging tentacles.
Within the mouth is a big stomach
filled with acidic enzymes.
Because the anemone does not have
a solid physical structure or skeleton,
it does not rely
on calcium carbonate,
so it's not as vulnerable as coral
to ocean acidification.
But, like coral some species
possess zooxanthellae algae
and warming seas
will also cause them to bleach.
There are over 800 species
of sea anemone.
10 are suitable homes
for anemone fish
and this is one of the reef's
most marvelous partnerships.
The anemone's tentacles
normally sting invaders.
But these fish are coated
with a protective mucus
and can dance in and out unharmed.
The fish rarely wander
more than a meter away.
Everything they need is right here -
scraps of food,
protection and community.
Not surprisingly,
the fish lay their eggs near
the protective folds of the anemone,
aerating and defending them
until they hatch.
And being stuck in one place
hasn't harmed their sex life.
In fact, it's enhanced it.
To keep everyone satisfied,
they've mastered sex change.
If a dominant female is required,
a male can change sex.
If a dominant male is needed,
a subordinate male
accelerates into sexual maturity.
As ocean conditions change, anemone
fish seem more protected than most,
safe within those stinging arms.
But even they are not immune
from danger.
All fish have internal structures
and organs
which may be weakened
by ocean acidification.
Even now, scientists are finding
that the ear bones of fish
are being affected,
which is impacting
the way they communicate.
If ocean acidification
goes unchecked,
it may affect key metabolic processes
for all marine animals.
Whenever conditions
get more challenging,
the natural process of selection
just gets more ruthless.
Those that cannot cope
will be quickly cast aside.
Every citizen must earn its keep.
These shrimp gather in locations
referred to as 'cleaning stations'.
This particular station also happens
to be the home of a moray eel.
But the shrimp aren't running away.
If anything,
they're competing to get closer.
And although the eel
finds the shrimp irritating,
he just grins and bears it.
The reason why
these entirely different species
tolerate one another
is because they have
an unspoken agreement.
The shrimp has the important job
of removing parasites
as well as dying or dead flesh.
These can be fatal to the moray,
but provide a delicious banquet
for the shrimp.
Animals are engaged in complex
relationships right across the reef.
Going solo is risky business.
And if you're going to attempt it,
you'd better be very clever.
One clever survival tactic
is camouflage.
Decorator crabs attach tiny sponges,
corals and anemones to their shells
and look more like walking flowerbeds
than animals.
Others attempt to go incognito by
placing toxic sponges on their heads,
like these aptly-named
hat-carrying crabs.
Sponges are living creatures,
but the crab doesn't care,
cutting the sponge up
into whatever size fits.
Other crabs collect forest leaves
and use them for disguise
and as hang-gliders.
Boxer crabs
are always ready for a fight,
with tiny poisonous anemones
as boxing gloves.
Hermit crabs reinforce their own body
armor by wearing second-hand shells.
Bigger shells must be found
as the crab grows
and this gives the crab lots of time
to develop its own unique look.
More sophisticated hermit crabs
collect stinging anemones
and will remove these anemones
and reattach them
whenever they change shells.
Crabs date back to Jurassic times
200 million years ago
and over 10,000 species exist.
They're hardy souls - even missing
half their legs won't slow them down.
And they're great opportunists -
some feasting inside
a sea cucumber's mouth.
Sea cucumbers have some remarkable
physical adaptations themselves.
They breathe through their rear end,
move on hydraulically-powered
tube feet,
and have a special collagen
in their body wall
that enables them
to radically change shape.
They also spawn from their forehead.
Sea cucumbers
have few natural predators.
So it's no wonder they're a popular
taxi ride for crabs and shrimp.
Because the sea cucumber
stirs up food with its front end,
there's even a free meal
as part of the ticket.
Nudibranchs
are also great to hitchhike.
These highly poisonous sea slugs
offer guaranteed safe passage
through dangerous open territory,
with the shrimps
scavenging on the run.
But for first-class travel,
nothing compares
to a jet-propelled jellyfish.
Magic carpets also glide above
the reef, in the form of flatworms.
Flatworms and nudibranchs
don't have shells,
so draw on chemical warfare
as defense.
Some eat toxic hydroids and anemones
and sequester poison in their skin,
which in turn makes them poisonous
to any potential predator.
They advertise their toxicity with
bright, bold colors and patterns,
which have conspired to make them
incredibly beautiful.
They are as wild in character
as they are in appearance.
They have gills on their backs,
sex organs on their sides
and all of them are hermaphrodites.
And some are fierce cannibals.
Trying to eat your lover during sex
is not quite acceptable,
but snacking on a cousin is fine.
Joining the sea slugs on
the ocean's floor are the sea stars.
Sea stars are often referred to
as starfish,
but they're not fish at all,
they're echinoderms.
Echinoderms date back
over 500 million years,
so predate the evolution of coral.
They have evolved
into a wide range of life forms
and what many have in common
is the spine.
Urchins are some of
the most heavily spined of all,
but for some color-coordinated crabs
and shrimp, this isn't a deterrent.
They've adapted
to live amongst the spines
and remain there all their lives.
It's a classic case of symbiosis
on a reef and worlds within worlds.
Tropical oceans are like vast blue
deserts and largely nutrient poor.
On coral reefs,
nothing goes to waste.
Various specialist filter feeders
have evolved
to sift the passing currents -
capturing, digesting and recycling
every available bit of food.
Worms are among the most numerous
and diverse of all filter feeders.
20,000 marine species exist
and, unlike the earth worms,
they're an exotic bunch.
Befitting their name,
Christmas-tree worms unfurl
festive, feathery mouth parts,
which they use like tiny nets.
Their bodies, meanwhile, are buried
in the coral and rarely seen.
Equally shy are ribbon eels.
They spend most of their time
concealed in deep burrows,
with just their heads peeking out.
They're relatives of moray eels
and their gaping mouths
make them look aggressive.
But they're simply breathing,
with their exaggerated nostrils
sniffing for food.
Adopting the same lifestyle
are garden eels.
These delicate sea serpents rise
from the sand in vast communities,
performing their hypnotic
Indian snake dance.
Ever watchful for predators,
they nervously pluck plankton
from passing currents,
their tails anchoring them down.
Because of corals/ longevity
on our planet
they're considered
our living fossils.
Another living fossil
still with us today is the nautilus.
It's an ancient mollusk, whose
line eventually dropped its shell...
...and gave rise
to the age of the cephalopods.
Cephalopods
are synonymous with the reef
and one of the most intriguing
is the mimic octopus.
As its name implies,
the octopus mimics
the physical likeness and movements
of more than 15 different species,
including sea snakes, lionfish,
flounder and ghost crabs.
It's one of nature's
great contortionists.
If it doesn't want to be seen,
it certainly won't be.
Many species of octopus
live in the vicinity of reefs
and a true reef specialist is this -
the day octopus.
These octopus are great hunters
and fish hurry to defend their eggs.
And being so tasty themselves,
octopus have had to develop
excellent martial arts skills.
They have the most complex brain
of any invertebrate
and can process information
from all eight arms at once.
They have short
as well as long-term memory
and possess a special way
to communicate with their skin.
They're also highly interactive
and tactile.
Courtship rituals can last for hours,
with couples intertwining all 16 arms
in a sticky embrace.
Once they mate,
their bodies are programmed to die.
For some species, this means
a lifespan of just 6 months.
For others, up to 5 years.
Cousin of the octopus is the squid,
seen here delicately laying eggs
in forest fronds.
We know squid more commonly
as calamari,
but despite being a favored delicacy
around the world,
many species
are increasing in number.
Like other cephalopods,
they're making the most of oceans
depleted of natural predators
and seem more resilient than others
to changing water conditions.
Another charismatic member
of the family is the cuttlefish.
These creatures
have magical attributes.
On the outside,
large eyes as expressive as our own.
On the inside,
three hearts that pump blue blood.
During their breeding season,
they gather in small groups,
zooming amongst one another
like miniature spaceships.
Masters of jet propulsion,
they can move backwards, forwards
or sideways with equal ease.
Every year they return
to favorite nesting sites,
like this colony
of venomous fire coral.
Males use dramatic body displays
and postures
to compete for mating rights.
So although competition is intense,
it's rarely physical.
Clutching her brood of eggs
in her mouth,
a female surrenders her young
to the care of coral.
The flamboyant cuttlefish
is one of the tiniest cephalopods,
yet lives up to its name.
Its cuttlebone is too small to float,
so it walks more than swims.
And it has a highly poisonous flesh,
advertised by its pulsing skin.
It's also a deadly predator.
Two specialized tentacles are
contained within a muscular sleeve,
which is launched like a spear.
With this kind of hunting prowess,
it's no wonder
the cephalopods have been
such a success story on the reef
and will no doubt
rule the seabed for eons to come.
Reefs are not only important
to their permanent residents,
but also to many oceanic visitors.
Strong currents and rich upwellings
of food often occur around reefs
and attract nomads such as rays.
In fact, the total number of marine
creatures dependent on coral reefs
is immeasurable.
Perhaps as many as
seven million species coexist here.
Over 4,000 species of tropical fish
are associated with coral reefs,
of which 75% depend on the reef
for their survival.
They may look
like just colorful confetti,
but each fish is its own individual.
Fish can smell, hear, see and touch.
They feel pain
and have complex relationships.
The vast majority of reef fish
have defined home ranges.
The reef sustains them, houses them
and conceals them from predators.
Like tiny kites on invisible strings,
the fish hover above
their beloved reefs,
venturing only far enough
to snatch a meal,
but otherwise inseparable.
The connection between fish and coral
is one of nature's
most enduring love stories.
Humans too benefit from
a healthy relationship with coral
and the seas at large.
Reefs create barriers to the sea
and protect shorelines.
Various life-saving medicines
are extracted from reefs.
Ocean-derived chemicals
are used to treat many illnesses,
including cancer.
Microscopic marine algae
processes our atmospheric CO2
and produces 70%
of the oxygen we breathe.
So, like these fish,
we need healthy oceans to survive
and reefs to secure our homes.
In both our terrestrial world
and the undersea,
there have been constant cycles
of creation and destruction.
The rule of nature is chaos.
Although a reef looks harmonious,
it's as chaotic
as any other ecosystem.
And one of the ways
to survive chaos,
whether you're above
or below the surface,
is to cooperate.
This cooperation
is called symbiosis,
a mutually beneficial relationship
between two
entirely different species.
These little blue and black striped
wrasse would be perfect fish food
if they hadn't made themselves
so useful.
They're cleaner wrasse
and earn their keep by cleaning.
So vital is this service
that none of their grateful hosts
would ever dare to eat them.
Both parties benefit
and a form of balance is achieved.
There is constant tension on the reef
as different species
work out this balance
and try to maximize
their moment in history.
For some of the bigger fish,
that moment
used to stretch into decades.
Some even lived
for a century or more.
But old age is a rarity now
and iconic reef species
are vanishing even as we watch.
Angelfish live
for l 0 to 15 years in the wild
and are some of the reef's
most recognizable species.
They are highly prized by collectors
and, tragically, many live out
their long lives in aquaria.
A fish in a tank
is like a bird in a cage -
we're able to observe them
but we get little idea of their wildness.
It's only here, on the reef,
that we can truly appreciate just
how complex a fish's life can be.
Some angelfish are promiscuous,
some bond for life,
others have male-driven harems.
And many fish, including these
delicate leafed scorpionfish,
engage in long courtship rituals.
New species of fish
are discovered every week,
and with each discovery
comes a wealth of new information.
Some spawn daily,
others do not begin breeding
until they are 20 or 30 years old.
Many start life as a male
but die a female.
Most are highly social
and have intelligence
beyond our comprehension.
Like wildebeest and zebra
on the African plains,
tangs and parrotfish
often graze together.
Both fish are herbivores
and dine on algae
and even live coral.
Other species converge
on the reef crest.
This area is exposed to wave action
and lots of sunlight
and is rich in nutrients.
Fish like this rock-mover wrasse
literally move rocks in the search
of worms and mollusks.
Dining this way is hard work,
and they're not always willing
to share their patch.
Others excavate the substrate
and swallow large mouthfuls of sand.
Their bodies are specially designed
to filter the sand for algae,
dispelling waste through their gills.
Access to the reef crest is limited.
It's only at certain tides
and during calm seas
that it's possible to feed here.
When all the conditions are right,
fish arrive from miles around to take
advantage of this rare opportunity.
Some are in couples,
others dine alone,
and completely different species
feed side by side.
It's biodiversity at its best.
Eccentric earth-movers,
like triggerfish,
also join the dinner party.
They use their powerful beaks
to cast aside whole chunks of coral,
as they search for clams,
shrimp and crabs.
They're much too busy to worry
about their table manners.
Like a human city,
a reef boasts
an eclectic jumble of characters
conducting themselves
in a variety of ways.
There are loners and drifters.
There are clandestine meetings
and underground movements.
There are the watchful and the wary.
And different forms
of self-expression.
As in all of our cities,
strange alliances occur...
...and odd fashion is tolerated.
Every beauty and beast
has its place.
Just like the terrestrial world,
a reef has a 24-hour cycle.
As the afternoon light
begins to fade,
fish, like these anthias,
spawn with abandon,
knowing that night
will soon follow
and conceal their eggs.
Meanwhile, tiny fish
shudder their bodies,
indicating their readiness to mate.
And countless other daytime fish
are inspired by the waning light
to court or breed.
Here, a pair of flutemouths
engage in a seductive sword dance.
It's their form of foreplay,
and they've been at it for hours.
Over the millennia,
the battle between predator and prey
has fueled an evolutionary arms race
under the sea.
Mother Nature is always
updating her designs
and making old ones redundant.
Animals have had to constantly refine
their offensive
and defensive capabilities.
The result
can be pure science fiction.
Angler and scorpion fish
are as bizarre as they come.
They're expert mimics of sponges,
but have one of the fastest strikes
on Earth.
But they're certainly
not out to win a beauty prize.
When it comes to some of these
creations, love is certainly blind.
This myriad life has enthralled us
since the beginning of human history.
We did originally evolve
from the sea.
And ever since early humans
first emerged,
we've been drawn back to its shores.
Seafood has been a favored diet.
Shells have been our money
and jewelry.
Coral limestone paves our roads.
Sand cements our houses.
Our myths and legends,
books and films
are all full of characters
derived from the sea.
And as light fades,
these characters begin to change
and the story of coral moves
into a very different narrative.
Big predatory fish cruise the reef's
edge, searching for a final kill.
Daytime fish hurry into hiding.
This is a dangerous time
of transition.
All across the reef,
there is a changing of the guard.
The night shift has begun.
Little is known about our oceans.
The surface of Mars is better mapped.
Most living coral reefs
descend to only 50 meters or so,
due to the reliance on sunlight.
But the seafloor
falls to 11 kilometers in places.
This is what we call the abyss.
Night-time on the reef
gives us a sense
of what this abyss might be like.
The inky black is very much alive
and full of aliens.
In special places
where reefs drop to great depth,
deep sea plankton rise to the surface
to hunt shallow water phytoplankton.
They travel hundreds of meters.
They number in their billions
and they repeat the journey
every night.
It's one of the biggest migrations
in the animal kingdom.
The chase of plankton-hunter
and plankton-prey
triggers a larger chain reaction
right across the night-time reef.
Baitfish snatch mouthfuls,
while basking stars
emerge from their lairs
and extend web-like arms.
The water flashes with color
as the plankton frantically
communicate with one another.
Coral is not an idle bystander.
The reef has become a wall of mouths.
The true animal nature
of coral is revealed.
Equipped with poisonous harpoons
and acid,
each polyp becomes a deadly trap
from which escape is impossible.
Meanwhile, catfish eat on the run.
Parrotfish sleep
with eyes wide open
or conceal themselves
in mucus cocoons.
Without torches,
humans are blind at night.
Underwater,
we'd barely know up from down.
But the undersea hunters
are not at all disadvantaged.
Instead of sight, they use vibration,
electrical impulses
and chemical traces
to find what they're after.
Stone walls are, in fact,
living stonefish waiting in ambush...
...while the sharp teeth
of stargazers lurk beneath the muck.
It's easy to swim towards danger
without realizing it.
This anemone has become
a serial killer.
A lucky squid escapes, releasing ink
to cover its tracks.
A pipefish looks on,
as fish scatter and more fall victim.
Down on the seabed,
scavengers collect the scraps...
...while lionfish use their long spines
to herd unsuspecting prey.
There is activity in all directions,
as night hunters of every description
eat their fill.
The anglerfish is back
and now completely in its element.
It may not move with grace,
but that doesn't affect
its chances for a kill.
All it needs to do is wait for a meal
to come to its mouth.
When it comes to nocturnal hunting,
moray eels are known
for their viciousness.
But other killers
are not so easy to spot.
Mantis shrimp are sophisticated
and savage.
They're armed with supreme eyesight
and actively hunt live prey
while other crustaceans,
like lobsters,
scour the sea floor for leftovers.
With a busy time ahead,
day fish try to sleep
despite all the activity.
Some drifting
like ghosts in the dark.
The anemone fish are also trying to
sleep, but aren't finding it easy.
Their flat-mates, the dotted crabs,
are enjoying a midnight snack.
Some of the most active
night prowlers are shells.
Many of us only know them from
shell shops or dead on the beach.
But shells alive
are much more precious -
gypsy caravans, varnished by the
oceans, constantly on the move.
Darkness also suits
courting mandarin fish.
They have an unusually high
sex drive
and can spawn every night
if the urge takes them.
Although our underwater lights
give us a glimpse,
we still know very little about
what happens on a reef at night.
And our unwarranted fears
have made it harder to learn.
Our attitude to the sea
has been full of contradiction.
On the one hand we've revered it,
on the other
we've seen it as an enemy -
dark and unfathomable,
full of dragons and monsters.
These monsters of the deep
have long been proven figments
of our collective imagination.
But some believe they still exist
in the form of sharks.
How wrong they are.
These magnificent creatures
predate dinosaurs.
Like coral, they've survived
several mass extinctions
and have played an equally vital role
in shaping ocean evolution.
Sharks have been roaming our seas
for over 400 million years.
Fossil records show that thousands
of species have come and gone,
of which 370 are with us today.
They can be found worldwide,
with many dependent on coral reef
ecosystems for protection and food.
As top predators,
sharks have influenced adaptation
and evolution
all the way down the food chain.
But contrary to popular myth,
sharks are not just instinctive
eating machines.
Many species exhibit
powerful problem-solving skills
and their brain-to-body-mass ratio
is similar to many mammals
and other higher order vertebrates.
So they are as intelligent,
curious and social
as some of our more favored animals.
They not only possess
the 5 senses we do -
sight, hearing,
touch, smell and taste -
but can also perceive
electrical currents
and magnetic fields.
If we're in the water with them,
they can detect our presence
from miles away.
They can monitor
the beating of our heart...
...and read our mood.
When it comes to humans,
they are normally cautious creatures.
Whenever possible, they avoid us.
With good reason.
Every year,
over 100 million sharks are killed,
the majority just for their fins.
Their fins are a traditional
ingredient in Asian soup
and their value rivals caviar.
The sharks are often finned alive
and thrown back into the water
to drown.
One third of all open-ocean shark
species are now facing extinction,
primarily due to over-fishing.
So if there is a killing machine
in our seas, it's not them,
it's us.
No shark is safe,
not even the biggest of them all,
the whale shark.
Up to 15 meters long and 12 tons in
weight, they're an impressive sight.
But they're strictly filter feeders
and dine mostly on plankton.
Unbelievably, they are also victims
of illegal fishing.
Whale sharks are not actually whales
but sharks.
True whales that visit the reefs
include these, the minke.
Incredibly, these graceful animals
are still being harpooned.
What trust they show us, regardless.
Before we began to plunder the seas,
this is what they were like.
Linking the abyss with the surface,
layer upon layer
of shimmering silver.
A big school of fish
is a defining image of a healthy sea.
It's a show of strength and
incredible physiological adaptation.
Running head to tail in most fish
is a row of scales
known as the lateral line.
Connected to nerves in the brain,
this line consists
of specialized cells
that are sensitive
to water displacement and movement.
Meanwhile, fishes' eyes are located
on the sides of their heads
to make it easy to see where they are
in relation to one another.
So, vision helps maintain angle
and distance between fish,
while the lateral line dictates speed
and direction of the entire school.
In this way,
many fish can move as one
and choreograph
their own aquatic ballet.
Many fish school as juveniles
and around half of all fish species
form aggregations
at some point in their lifecycle.
Even fish that prefer their solitude
join a school from time to time.
Barracuda hunt on their own at night
but hang out in packs during the day
for protection and company.
With their pointed heads
and streamlined bodies -
up to 2 meters long
they fly in unison through
the blue like polished arrows.
Schooling makes it hard for
a predator to focus on one target
and is a great defense mechanism.
It's also a force to be reckoned with
when it comes to feeding.
Few plankton in the area will escape
this sweep of open mouths,
as these rare filter-feeding mackerel
make their coordinated attack.
Over the eons, the art of schooling
has helped fish in many ways.
But now, ironically,
it contributes to their downfall.
Just one net can collect
a ton of fish at once.
And over 100 million tons of fish
are hauled from the oceans each year.
For the few big schools left,
it must feel quite eerie moving
through so much empty liquid blue.
These days, one of the only
safe places for schooling fish
is a marine sanctuary.
Whenever sanctuaries
have been established and policed,
fish stocks have slowly increased,
helping to restore biodiversity.
A successful sanctuary
becomes a precious time capsule...
...a reminder of how rich
the seas once were.
And could be again.
Unlike a zoo,
a marine sanctuary has no walls.
So it has the capacity to not only
replenish the immediate area,
but the oceans around it.
Because we have individual names
for our oceans
and have territorial borders,
we forget that
there's only one system.
There is only one sea.
Water, covering 70% of our planet's
surface, connects us all.
What occurs even in our polar regions
will eventually affect coral.
And, conversely, each new marine
sanctuary is another powerful step
towards saving our seas.
And when you consider
that the global ocean makes up 99%
of the living biosphere of the planet,
every step counts.
Because reefs
are such important breeding grounds
for so many marine creatures,
this is where a new future might lie.
Renewal here is a daily affair
and brings with it
magical transformation.
Here, a coral cod blushes a different
color when wooed by its mate.
A thriving reef
is an aquatic rainbow.
And like the skin of the coral cod,
these colors have meaning
and function.
Silver scales reflect light
and allow fish to blend
into their watery backgrounds.
Bold, strong colors allow fish
to recognize their own species
in a crowd.
Color also indicates whether a fish
is a juvenile or adult,
and some fish change color
quite radically as they mature.
Once fish are paired up,
they can then use body posturing
and color displays
to communicate their intentions.
A male parrotfish erects his dorsal fin
to intimidate other males
and impress a nearby female who
happens to look completely different.
And all across the reef, fish are
on the lookout for a chance to mate
and pass on their precious genes.
Most sea creatures have short
intense lives compared to ours.
For some fish, a few years
constitutes an entire lifetime.
So every good day on a reef
is truly great.
A good decade is even greater,
the chance
for countless marine creatures
to live their lives to the fullest
and give rise to new generations.
In the quest to survive
in these tropical seas,
animals have had to be
highly inventive
and sometimes nature's own rules
are broken.
Consider the seahorse.
These mystical creatures
come in all sizes.
Some bigger than your palm,
others as small as your fingernail.
The daintiest of them all
is the pygmy seahorse,
whose life is completely bound
to gorgonian coral.
The extended seahorse family
consists of 320 species,
and includes pipefishes,
pipehorses and sea dragons.
In most species of pipefish
and seahorse,
it's the male
that broods the young.
It's not just this unusual parenting
that sets them apart.
They have equine heads,
prehensile tails...
...and bony body plates
instead of scales.
Despite their dragon appearance,
many fish like to eat them.
So not being noticed
has become their speciality.
Ghost pipefish are expert mimics
of other animals and plants,
including crinoids and coral.
Their predators
find it hard to see them
and so does their prey.
They spend most of their lives
upside down,
focused intently
on the sandy bottom,
searching for the tiny crustaceans
that are their principal food.
So specific is their camouftage
that pipefish rarely wander far
from a particular habitat
and perfect their mimicry
down to the finest detail.
Other species
conceal their true identity
by moving like eddies and currents.
While some pretend
to be sand-encrusted sticks
or fallen leaves...
...or pieces of algae.
If you know how to look, the masters
of disguise are everywhere.
In this underwater Garden of Eden,
even the snake
turns out to be a fish.
Down on the seabed,
deception is commonplace.
Individual reefs are often connected
by areas of sand and rubble,
and this is where the so-called
'bottom dwellers' dwell.
The most numerous of these
are the gobies.
There are over 2,000 species of goby,
making them
one of the largest fish families.
Few of them
grow bigger than your finger,
which makes them a favored food
for many large predatory fish.
So they're always on the lookout
and never far from the seabed.
They spend most of their days
feeding,
filtering sand through their gills
to extract tiny food particles.
Sand is everything to the goby.
Sand puts food in their belly
and also a roof above their heads.
Many gobies build burrows.
Its tiring excavation work,
and partners sometimes don't agree
on whose turn it is.
If the domestic argument
can't be worked out,
then this species,
camouflaged as big eyes,
can always go for a stroll
to smooth things over.
Some clever gobies have enlisted
the services of a slave.
In a most extraordinary partnership,
gobies and blind shrimp
live together, bonded by mutual need.
The shrimps excavate a burrow
in which the gobies can hide,
and they eat the goby's scraps.
The gobies act as sentinels, warning
the shrimps of approaching danger.
The fish and crustacea have
such a close working relationship
that they're always connected,
by tail or fin or feeler.
For fish close to the bottom
of the food chain,
a safe home base is essential.
Space is limited
and good real estate hard to come by.
Trespassing isn't tolerated.
Territorial disputes
are normally quick to work out.
But not always.
There's definitely no point
picking a fight
with this mighty armored beast.
It's the crown-of-thorns starfish,
corals' mortal enemy.
By disgorging their stomachs
and drenching polyps with acid,
they eat living coral
and suck the life out of a reef.
The starfish play an important role,
clearing space
and fostering biodiversity.
And few have stood in their way.
The starfish have always been
a natural part of the cycle.
But now the cycle is unnatural.
Agricultural pollution
has increased nutrients in the water,
which in turn causes algal blooms.
Starfish juveniles
are feasting on this algae
and many more
are surviving into adulthood.
Plagues of crown-of-thorns starfish
are now regularly experienced
on reefs worldwide.
But not all infestations
are bad news.
A perfect example
is the unlikely alliance
between the eared sponge
and the pink sea cucumber.
This sponge is highly toxic to most.
But the sea cucumber has adapted
to live here in huge numbers,
rising off the edges to spawn.
This is an inhospitable habitat
where creatures are thriving.
Perhaps it offers hope
for life in our changing seas.
It's certainly proof
that anything is possible.
The oceanic world is ever changing.
Nothing stays the same here
for more than a moment.
Over the ages,
corals have come and gone.
Today, they are disappearing again.
But what sets this cycle apart
from any other in geological history
is the presence of us.
For the first time
in corals' existence,
humans are having a direct impact
on the ocean's chemistry
and corals' destiny.
Many scientists believe
we are heading towards
our next mass extinction
and that humans are the cause.
Reef-building corals
are now seriously endangered.
And as reefs disappear,
hundreds of thousands of dependent
creatures disappear with them.
Furthermore, the demise
of coral reefs is a clear indicator
that our ocean is dying,
and our ocean is our planet's
life-support system.
The only way to save our ocean
is to radically curb
our CO2 emissions
within the next one or two decades.
We have all the tools to do it.
And if we succeed,
we will not only save our reefs,
we will ultimately save ourselves.
The future of coral,
and how this story ends,
is up to us.