Everybody Front and Center!
On the Double!
Front and Center,
battle formation.
The last one there
is in deep shit!
Move it!
How can you sleep at a time
like this? Breakfast is ready.
Come on, Front and Center!
Let's go now!
Sergeant!
Captain!
Why the sudden meeting?
Didn't you call us here?
What's the reason for this?
I was sleeping in my room!
Front and Center!
Up and at 'em boys.
Front and Center, Formation!
Do you pussy's understand
Chinese? I said move!
What the fuck?
Faster!
Those at the back,
quit straggling behind.
Keep loafing and you will
crawl to mess.
Damn! Private!
I said run fast!
Got ya!
Fuck, this hurts.
A lack of water around here and
here you are, playing with it.
Captain is Concerned that
it might get heat stroke.
Heat Stroke?
I don't care
if he has heat stroke or not.
I'm finished running, sir!
How many laps have you run?
How would I know?
You don't know how many laps you've run?
Sir, I forgot.
You forgot? Would you forget to eat also?
Seems to me like you slept
all night. Keep running.
Yes Sir!
Idiot. Fat ass.
One day he will screw
the company.
Faster!
I had a dream last night.
I dreamt that a girl
I knew in grade school died.
And?
Is it possible she really died?
Have you gone nuts?
Thinking of this nonsense everyday.
I haven't seen her for a long time.
Now she shows up in my dreams,
Dead
Is she trying to tell me something?
Yes, quit jerking off so often.
Faster!
Call someone, Hurry!
Something's wrong!
Get him out of here. Hurry!
One, Two, Three.
What a heavy pig
Lin Kuen-He,
Lin Kuen-He!
There's a squadron ahead,
Full speed ahead
Masculinity! Dignity!
Iouder! Firm!
Resolute! Silent!
Strong! Louder, louder, louder! Precise!
Salute! Sergeant!
Orange.
Yellow. Heh, heh.
Tell you what,
I use this to pick up girls
and it has never failed.
Besides being handsome,
it is crucial to have good technique
Humor
A sense of humor, you understand?
Know why you are a loser everytime?
Why?
Because you are as dumb as
an ass
Who wants to be
with a dumb ass?
Let me have it, please?
Sure.
We are pals, right?
You can have it for $60
What? These flowers cost $60!?
What? You think it's expensive?
You are a moron.
The cheapest whore around will cost you $60.
You are not just buying flowers
It's a technique, man.
Come on
$ 60 for your happiness.
What do you think
Too expensive?
Happiness is just
around the corner.
But...
Come on! Forget about it.
We're getting discharged
next week -
then you won't be able to
buy them even if you want.
That's it.
Here is your happiness
Xiao-Gui
Apple is calling for you.
Bugger.
Xiao-Gui
Take your time.
Ah-Zhou,
let's go! Let's go!
Shit, something's burning!
Aim it here, would ya?
Throw it HERE!
Ah-Zhou, I've brought you milk.
Catch!
Thanks, Apple
No problem.
Hey, Xiao-Gui! Stick your head out
I want to see you
Give me a break, would you?
Come on, I haven't seen you
for days.
It hasn't been that long.
Yeah, it has. Come on, let me see you!
Over here.
Happy now?
Yes.
Meet me tonight, okay?
No. It's tiresome to go out
at night.
Come on, come over.
I will cook you
something special
Okay?
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
Can you make curry?
Curry. Anything else?
How about some vegetables
Okay, vegetables. Anything else?
Can you two discuss this later?
Sweet and sour pork then?
Talk about it later!
All right, all right.
Go home first and we'll
talk about it tonight.
All right,
I'm leaving now.
Bye-bye
Bye - bye.
You a weak man.
Ah-Zhou, Good bye. Bye.
Stop that, you can't abandon me
I love you so much.
Hello, mom? Ummm,
will you go find my
elementary school yearbook?
It's in the lower left drawer of my desk.
Hello? Check it for me.
There is someone named
Chen Shing-shing in my class.
What's her phone number?
Just give me the number. Yes.
Hello? Hello?
My phone card is out of money,
can I borrow yours?
Okay?
Thank you.
No. Don't move.
Stop it!
Attention!
This private in your company
seems to have some mental problems.
I think so, too. What else could it be?
I think we will have to send
him to a psychiatrist.
Also, check to see if we can
get him early-discharge
If it goes on like this
I will go crazy
before he does
You okay?
I guess I shouldn't have
borrowed that phone card.
And drive him crazy over a phone card!
Are you out of your mind?
He is in upper class
and you dare to hit him?
Get up
Fat ass.
Stop faking
Don't hit me
Still faking
what are you crying about?
My girlfriend wants to
break up with me.
When did you get a girlfriend?
I have one.
Let me see,
let me see.
He says this is his girlfriend.
What does she do?
She's a model. Right now she is on a shoot,
involving in a love scandal now
I told her not to get into
this business.
Is she really your girlfriend?
Yes.
Are you out of your mind, too?
He is just in love
with a page from a magazine
Take back your girlfriend.
Give me a tissue.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Password?
It's me.
Sorry sir.
Captain!
Shape up! Otherwise, I make
sure you never get discharged
Sorry about today, sir.
I'll make it up to you next time.
I'll loan you my phone card from now on.
I'll buy my own
Shine the light here. Here!
The wind is clearing the road,
the cloud is leading the way.
I'm throwing away love,
climbing over that high mountain
and crossing the sea,
destroying enemies, hey, hey...
Destroy the enemies of the
country, hey, hey...
Please encourage me, wait for me,
wait for my victorious return.
Hey big guy, how much do you want to spend?
Chewing beetlenut is bad for the teeth.
Well then, cigarettes?
What's your favorite brand?
No, my mother says
I can't smoke since I am
You are under 18?
How about going to karaoke?
Come on.
No,
I am working now.
You look so beautiful today.
Come on
I can't.
Charge
Xiao-Gui, what are you doing?
What?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
We are closing now
Why? We are friends
Tell him we are closing
Don't be like that!
You're not going to tell him,
are you?
Ah-Zhou, let's go.
Okay, okay, Xiao-Gui.
I'm sorry.
I will buy you drinks next time,
Okay?
Forget it.
Do come again.
Why did you do that?
Why do you dress like a slut?
Don't you know that
there are lots of perverts around
You used to enjoy watching me like this
I don't enjoy it now,
go get changed.
Why did you do that?
Didn't I just ask you
how would you feel
if your mother dressed like a slut
and I came by to get some beetlenut?
Is this okay?
Sure. Look at yourself, you look cute.
You must dress this way from now on.
Is that okay?
Sure.
There are so many perverts right now, right?
How dangerous.
Hello, may I speak to Chen Shing-Shing?
26357741
May I... Oh, wrong number
I am sorry
Be quiet!
Anyone who ordered milk, come and get it!
Wang Ing-Zhou,
you didn't order milk, did you?
I'll give you mine.
From now on I will give you
my mother orders for me everyday.
Really?
Really.
Is it tasty?
Yes.
What do you want?
$5 of beetlenut.
She's busy.
Don't bother.
Lin Kuen-He,
Lin Kuen-He
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Emergency assembly, get up!
I think Apple is cute.
Cute? She's annoying, okay.
No, I think she is
You don't understand.
Who is there?
Fuck. What are you two pricks doing here?
Shit.
They want us on search patrol
this late at night
Why don't they just ask us to catch ghosts?
Why are you shining the light on me?
It's too dark, I can't see
Is it funny? Let's move.
Up front Private!
Hurry up!
Baby, the soy milk is burnt.
Go check whether the dumplings are ready.
Did you find the Private?
Come on, if we have found him
we would not be hiding here
for a break before we go on another search
I don't care
Stop, I am trying
to get some sleep.
Come on
How do I make soy milk?
Xiao-Gui, the captain said you
two could take a day of leave.
Go report to him now
don't lie to me.
True, why would I lie to you?
Get back quickly
Is it true?
Of course. Hurry up!
Take your time cooking.
All right, day off.
Put it back. Let's go!
I wanna take a leave as well.
Trust me, you don't want
Why?
It will bring bad luck.
I haven't taken leave
Captain, what will you do with the mouse
once we leave?
I will take care of it myself.
But Captain,
he has a gun!
This is the home address of
Lin Kuen-He.
Bring him back
before
the MP's find him.
I need to save my face
Captain, that guy is a bit weird.
Yeah. Yesterday he was...
Find him. What now?
How about me getting lost
and you come find me.
Why are you laughing?
You get discharged next week,
so what else do you have to worry about?
I still have to stay here
for ten more years
and no matter how hard I try
I will still be a captain!
You boys
should go out and have fun
instead of wasting your days here.
Now what?
What do you mean what now?
We're getting out of here soon
and we should know how to goof around.
He told us to play,
so we go play.
We'll just go hang around in Taipei first
and then head for his house, right?
You don't really think we're
going to catch him, do you?
We are out of here soon,
who cares?
Know any fun palces in Hualian?
Hualian is fun. You can surf,
I will take you.
Then I need to bring
Swimming trunks?
Everyone wears shorts now.
What if we do see him?
How could that happen?
If you were AWOL, would
you take your gun home?
Fuck! Shit!
My ass got attacked in the toilet!
Really? And then?
What then?
What happened next?
What do you mean what happened next?
Take off your pants.
Why should I do that?
Friends should share happiness
as well as misery
So, you wanna touch my ass?
Take them off
No!?
Here, I'll help you.
No.
Let me give you a hand
No
Oh, what a white shining ass!
Young man, what are you doing
taking your pants off in broad daylight?
Showing off your
Show me your tickets,
quit playing around.
Okay, stop it!
Purple? Purple!
Miss, should I put this here?
I see everything this way.
Right here. Green, red
Not bad.
Last one, pink
It's simple.
You learn quickly.
A yellow one here.
I'm out of here.
You going?
Yes. I wanna go home
You aren't being a good friend.
What are you going home for?
Stay here and keep me company
I'm going home to sleep.
Why are you going to sleep?
I am about to hook up
with a girl
and she is going to bring her friends.
I will introduce any one of them to you,
all right?
No. I wanna go home
No? No what?
I am going home.
What for?
Okay!
Remember, tomorrow,
12:00 at Taipei station.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye
What do you want?
Tell you what,
although I'm a Marine,
I can only do it once.
No, I can't.
What?
Loan me $1500, okay?
I'll get it back to you
You look so cute
like this
I mean it. I spent all my tuition
My mother is going to kill me.
Loan me $1500, please.
Do we know each other well?
You'd better be generous,
we just had a great time,
and now you're being stingy.
Just loan me the money and
and we'll go out for fun, okay?
Okay?
Come on.
Money always hurts relationships,
right?
Everybody got hair,
only in different locations.
Fuck.
You don't plan to pay for
the service?
What's the pen code of your ATM card?
My boss is asking you, so tell him.
What's the pen code?
Say it!
What's the number?
Are you losing your mind?
1519!
Should have told us earlier.
Boss, 1519.
Is anybody here?
Sir,
Do you have an appointment?
Dr. Chen is off work now.
You need to make
an appointment for tomorrow.
I'm here for his daughter.
Is she the one in the picture.
Yes.
Is she here?
She's not in either.
Where is she?
I've heard Doctor Chen say
she works in a hospital.
Works in a hospital?
So she is a nurse?
How is she?
I don't know. She hasn't been here
since I've worked here.
Sorry, I am off work now.
I'm sorry.
We are almost done
Okay! Okay!
Hang in there
It's a deep cavity
Why don't we come here
No, your teeth are filled with cavities,
how can we wait?
Can we come tomorrow then?
Mom, I don't want to have my tooth pulled
Let's go home.
It will only take a minute.
Open your mouth
What a cavity! I will pull it out.
Wang Ing-Zhou, have you come here
to have your tooth pulled?
Dad, is he getting
his tooth pulled?
Yes. The cavity is too big to
fill. He must get it removed.
Look, your classmate is here.
Be brave, don't cry.
Mama's going to
make a phone call.
Are you afraid of having
your tooth pulled?
No.
I'll tell you a way not to feel any pain.
First,
take a deep breath
and then yell AAAHHH.
That's it, now you try.
Uh-huh. That's it.
Okay, open your mouth.
Take a deep breath.
Okay! Almost done
You okay?
When did you come back?
Last night.
Oh. Thought you want the phone number
of Chen Shing-Shing.
Why didn't you call back
to get it?
My phone card was out of money.
Oh, I went to Dr. Chen's yesterday.
Did you see her?
No. I saw her a couple of years ago,
but I haven't seen her since then.
Dr. Chen said she works in the hospital.
Why are you wondering
about her?
Nothing.
Nothing? Can I help?
Help me what?
Seriously, I will help you
talk to Dr. Chen.
Talk about what?
Look,
I'm taking a dump!
Okay, I will tell you.
You go out first.
Let me finish brushing my teeth.
I told you
to come see a doctor.
I can't help you
over the phone.
Come see a doctor!
Excuse me,
is Chen Shing-Shing here?
Who are you?
I'm her classmate.
On the third floor.
Is she busy now?
She has nothing
to be busy with.
Excuse me,
coming through,
Where did he take you to
last night
Nowhere
Nowhere?
Then why did you take off early
Home for dinner
Oh
Excuse me,
is Ms. Chen Shing-Shing here?
She's over there.
Thank you.
Miss, time to take
your medicine.
No.
Stop playing around.
What are you doing?
No!
Hurry, let's go take the medicine!
It is strange the way you put your book.
Don't take my book away!
Now come take the medicine.
No!
Come on!
Chen Shing-Shing!
Shing-Shing, you have a visitor
Get up and take the medicine.
This is her medicine,
please help give it to her
she isn't behaving well
I have other things to do.
Thank you.
Is she Chen Shing-Shing?
Yes.
Sit.
Sit
Drink.
Drink
Finished studying?
Well then, you ask me.
Ask me
Why does wine go sour
when left open?
That's because there is alcohol in wine...
What is the question?
Not supposed to give me
the answer
Don't you know how to
ask questions?
You read it wrong.
You need 450 points to
get into medical school.
How can you take the test
if you act like this?
I'm worried about you. Don't
tell me you've studied.
You're not making progress.
Don't you know that it is
hard to get into college?
Not as easy as you thought
It's more difficult.
Everybody is waiting
to see you fail.
If you don't get into college,
your father will give you pressure.
Your mother will give you pressure.
Everyone gives you pressure
Everyone is waiting
Not acceptable to go
from a top high school to a bad college
Water.
You should take medicine.
The medicine puts me to sleep.
I have to take the entrance
exam. I must stay up late.
It won't put you to sleep.
This will strengthen your immune system.
That will improve your memory
and help you with your exam.
Quit lying to me!
You take the medicine first.
I'll test you and see
if your memory is getting better.
See. You are all the same. You are all liars.
Do you know what?
My mom also gives this
to me every morning.
Then you take it first.
You take one, and I'll take one.
See, nothing happened.
Tell you what,
you are the one who treats
me the best in the world.
Others are trying
to get something from me.
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
Be careful on the road
How did you get out?
Last time you told me
you would come visit me.
I waited for a long time.
You never came.
Do you study at all?
I am worried about you.
You will not make it
to college!
I do study.
Well then, you go back and study, okay?
Next time I'll test you.
You wanna test me?
Keep your promise
Do come.
Okay. You have to go back.
Bye Bye. Be careful on the road
What's the matter?
You all lied to me.
You promised to take me to take the test.
I've been urging you to study,
and now you want to go to
the test alone.
You are all the same.
Who is she?
Chen Shing-Shing.
Are you going to take the test
as well?
Huh?
Dumpling for good luck
Take it!
Who is she?
Tell me
Look!
She studied hard and went
to a top high school.
See what she has become, a nut
Thank god I didn't study hard
Where are you taking her?
I don't know.
She just followed me.
Let me check your tickets.
You two again?
Take out your tickets.
Nutcase!
Two nutcases together.
Freaks!
You are disgusting.
It's so beautiful!
Where the hell are we?
Where are we going?
The test site. It's getting late, let's go!
There are MPs over there.
Shh. Be quiet.
Is Lin Kuen-He coming back?
It's impossible.
Can anyone escape with a gun
and then dare to return?
You want the bad guys
to know where we are
They're gonna catch us. Hide!
They are all gone.
What should we do?
Are they gone?
What do you mean
what should we do?
Have they gone yet?
Let's go, let's go.
Go where?
Move it!
Xiao-Gui!
You want to come down
to the beach?
No.
My mom says
the beach is dangerous.
Tell you something.
My stomach hurts.
Your stomach hurts?
Seems like my period has come.
What has come?
My period.
Period?
Where can we find pads
in this fucking place?
Which college major are you interested in?
Which college major are you
Interested in?
Hello,
Hello?
Gentlemen,
take what you need yourself.
Don't you have women here?
Women? I am looking for some myself.
Kill! Kill!
No, Come on!
It is totally wrong
You asked me to teach you,
and you must pay attention,
okay? Try it again!
Kill!
That's not right!
Thank God you aren't qualified
for military service
if you were
you would have died
in the Marine training
Is it always so strict in the Marine Corps?
Of Course.
Let me show you how to kill, okay?
It's important to show
your force
You can threaten enemies
with the gleam of your eyes
can kill a man,
you understand?
Kill!
Get it?
Once more!
Kill! Kill!
Much better,
I can feel your force
Kill!
Correct!
I am Finished!
Not bad.
You can come out now!
I often see the military parades;
they are all marching
in step - Pretty cool.
Teach me how to do that?
Give me a break.
I'm in the Marine Corps.
No Marine would march in step like that.
We are trained to be special forces!
Really? Special forces?
Thanks boss.
Not at all.
Go play over there,
okay?
be good
How many days are you going to stay here?
We'll stay for a while.
Oh yeah?
We should be here.
Then I will come and find you.
Great.
Bye.
Thanks.
No problem.
Bye.
He is weird, wants to learn
all this nonsense.
Who knows what he's thinking.
I'm hungry, what do we have?
There is no damn restaurant here,
it's faster to eat worms.
Where are we going?
This way?
Let's go.
Let's go!
Shoes, My shoes!
Xiao-Gui,
wait for me!
Dinner is ready!
Yeah! Dinnertime!
Food's ready, let's eat.
No! I'm not eating.
I cooked a lot of food -
You just said you were hungry
I'm having stomach problems. I can't eat
Ah-Zhou kept saying that
he was hungry,
give it to him.
Eat it while it's hot.
Eat!
Is it tasty?
Very good.
You spit it on me!
Give it to Xiao-Gui.
Tasty?
Had enough?
Delicious
I'm full.
And I got food all over me
You spit it on me!
What a waste of food you guys.
There's only a little left.
Don't eat!
Had enough?
Yes, I'm full.
Yummy?
Outstanding. Really good.
I added pepper, can you tell?
Yes, it is tasty!
Since you are all full,
I'm going home. Bye.
Shing-Shing, wait a second.
Huh? I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
Xiao-Gui, there's something in my eye.
Oh. Shing-Shing,
what's wrong?
Don't cry,
what's the matter?
I have to be home by 10:00.
10:00? But it's late.
We can't get a bus.
We'll take the bus
tomorrow morning,
Okay?
In early morning?
No!
We'll have dessert after dinner, okay?
You must make a fine dessert as well.
Xiao-Gui loves to eat dessert,
right?
Yes.
Great! We'll have tiramisu.
Sounds good.
I'll have it next time. Bye.
Shing-Shing, wait a minute.
Wait!
There's something sharp
on the ground.
Wait up! Shing-Shing!
Don't go!
Shing-Shing, wait until the sun comes up,
okay?
No!
Neither of us are wearing shoes.
We'll go back to get them, okay?
No! It's already a quarter to ten!
I must catch the 10:00 bus.
There are no late night buses
I don't care,
I have to go home tonight,
or my mother will yell at me.
The buses have all gone to sleep!
You are so childish!
Buses don't go to sleep!
Drivers need to sleep!
Then wake them up!
One-two, One-two...
Say it louder!
Masculine! Dignified! Firm! Resolute! Silent!
Strong! Speed!
Calm! Patient! Alert! Brave!
March!
One-two, One-two.
Get in step!
1-2-3-4, 1-2-3-4, 1-2-3-4.
Halt!
One, two.
Kuen-He, Where are you taking us?
I'm sorry, Kuen-He,
we shouldn't have found you.
Let us go,
we'll pretend we haven't seen you, okay?
Move faster!
Turn left!
Get in there!
It is dark!
Get in, be quiet!
Get inside!
Squat down!
Hold still!
Don't even
think of running away.
So many fireworks!
What are you doing?
Don't touch it.
Move over, move over there.
I'm warning you, don't even
think about escaping,
I've got other things
to attend to.
What is Lin Kuen-He doing?
Making bombs I guess.
To bomb who?
I don't know.
What are you looking at?
What?
Lin Kuen-He,
Calm down!
I can't do anything right,
I haven't done anything right
since I was a child,
not even fireworks.
No wonder my girlfriend
breaks up with me.
Fatso, are you crying?
Poor boy,
Don't cry.
Fatso, don't cry!
Ah-Zhou, Ah-Zhou, Ah Zhou.
What?
We're out of here.
Where is Kuen-He?
He hasn't noticed us.
What are you talking about?
Shhh! Shing-Shing, we are
going to have a game.
Let's play hide and seek, okay?
Hide and seek?
Shhh. Pipe down!
Don't make a sound!
Don't talk at all.
Untie me!
Now who's the seeker?
Fatso! Fatso will be it.
Can I be the seeker later?
Sure, of course.
Help, help!
Fatso fell into the water.
I can't swim!
Scram!
Fuckin' fat-ass!
Help, help!
Hold it! Go! Fatso go!
Help!
Grap it.
Fatso wins the game
What the heck?
The water is shallow
and you are pretending
to drown.
What are you doing?
Sir, I just wanted to
catch some fish
to grill it for you.
Smells good!
Tell you what,
whenever I Bar-B-Q
with my friends,
they loved my grilled fish
because they tasted the best.
Can I have this one later on?
Sure.
Sir, do you want it spicy?
Okay. Just a little though.
Is it ready? I am starving
Yeah, it's ready.
I'm hungry
Be careful
Let's eat fish!
Be careful!
Sir
Thank you for saving me, sir.
Sorry about yesterday.
I never meant to tie you up.
Well then, I will get back to work.
Take your time and enjoy it.
It's okay if you leave first,
don't wait for me,
I still have some fireworks
to make.
What are those fireworks for?
Kuen-He, why are you
making those?
My girlfriend, You-Lin, wants
to break up with me.
I wrote a letter telling her
that I would
have a special fireworks show
on the beach tonight.
I made it myself
hoping she wouldn't leave me.
Now he is fantasizing about
the model from the magazine.
The wind is clearing the road,
the cloud is leading the way.
I'm throwing away love,
climbing over that high mountain
and crossing the sea,
destroying enemies,
Destroy the enemies of the country,
I don't see any fish.
All the fish are gone.
Sir, you're still here?
My clothes are still wet.
Are you done?
Yes. Sir?
Sir, can I ask you to write some blessings
for me and my girlfriend
on the fireworks later?
Sure.
Thank you, sir.
Look at those fireworks he made.
It would be a miracle
if they actually work.
So strange, where have
Fatso caught them all!
They're all in your stomach!
How could there be any fish left?
No fish? But I want to fish!
I want to fish!
Yeah! I've got the fish. I've got them.
Aah blowfish!
And an octopus.
And there is a crab!
A Mermaid!
A Dolphin!
And look, also a shrimp!
A shrimp!
And a seahorse!
Xiao-Gui!
Xiao-Gui
Thanks.
Next time we'll go fishing again.
I forgot to catch ajellyfish
and a seahorse today.
And the...
Blowfish?
Sir, I'm going to put on a firework
display on the beach.
Do your fireworks really work?
Of course they do.
It must be a special firework display.
Do you wanna come along
fireworks? I'm in. I'm in.
Great.
We'll find you after the Bar-B-Q,
okay?
Sure.
Do your best, Fatso!
Sir, I'm leaving.
Bye-bye. Be careful
Yeah, fireworks.
You're not flipping the meat!
This should be great.
Did you enjoy yourself?
Yes, I did.
Me too.
The Bar-B-Q got burnt.
Is he still there?
Lin Kuen-He!
What's up?
Put down your gun? Hands up!
Look, what's that?
The wind is clearing the road,
the cloud is leading the way.
How does the next part go?
I'm throwing away love.
What the hell?
Fatso put on the fireworks without us.
He didn't even wait.
Hurry up, or else we won't make it!
Those fireworks would actually go off?
They're too loud.
Run slower, slower!
Be careful,
Slow down.
Who's that guy? Is it Fatso?
No.
What are they doing there?
Nothing.
Where are they going?
Nowhere.
Where's Fatso?
Did he leave with his girlfriend?
I didn't see any fireworks at all.
Haven't you been wearing
those clothes long enough?
Are you taking them back
to match yourjeans?
I'll take them back as a souvenir
You two.
Captain.
Congratulations. You finally
finished the service.
Your Discharge Orders
Thank you Captain.
Do your best
and come visit if you have time. By the way,
the mice are going to miss you.
Take care.
Thank you Captain. Good-bye.
Good-bye captain.
Xiao-Gui, we have been discharged already,
there is no need to climb over the wall
I am a man of habits
Are you going to see Apple?
No, of course not
Please don't be shooting
your mouth like this
If she finds out that
I have been discharged,
She may insist on going
back to Taipei with me,
then I have to say goodbye to the happiness
You don't need to say goodbye to her?
No need.
You are really annoying
We're out of there!
Be careful of the cars!
Watch out!
Hurry!
Are you bored?
Yeah.
If you come back to keep me
company, that would be nice.
Of course! No problem!
Didn't you say you would do
a magic trick for me?
Yes, watch.
Wow, that's wonderful.
Hold on, there's more.
Wow! You're really great.
Thank you.
Would you like a drink?
Is it cold enough?
Yes, it tastes great.
You're all sweaty
Will you teach me
how to do the trick?
Hello.
One dollar please
Thank you
She feels much better these days.
Her father took her home last night,
didn't you know that?
Huh? I didn't know.
Do you hear sound of the sea?
You're out of your mind!
THE END
Subtitles by: Reklame11