Just knowing you're with us!
Won't you?
I'll wash my beans as best I can.
It's no good. We can't fight like this.
We can't win.
I'll go.
To save Sunekosuri.
Now you're looking good!
I'll be with you, beating my chest!
You, too!
Sorry.
Don't get carried away.
What's wrong?
He's taken flight!
Where to?
To the city of rage!
Tokyo?
Sis!
Who is 'Kato Yasunori'?
He was human.
The rage...
...of the tribes...
yours destroyed made him a demon.
What tribes?
I don't understand.
You...
...poor thing...
You humans live in ignorance, don't you.
Those who discard their past have no future.
Well?
The teacher hasn't seen him,
I left word at Kikue's.
I hope he's all right!
Can't find him
He's not down by the port!
And that's not all.
There's monsters all over the place!
The town's in an uproar!
Monsters?!
These aren't rotten yet. I can still eat them.
Governor!
Hey, it's only Gamera.
We interrupt this program with a news bulletin.
Big news! Osaka Castle has been...
This is too slow!
We'll never catch him!
I know!
What is this?!
Argh! The dish on my head hurts!
(Don't try this at home, kids!)
This won't work!
This isn't funny!
Who is next?
Thank you.
I'm One-Leg the Smith...
Swordsmith to the Sprites.
What?
Hurry up, go back to your home...
Ignore it! Hurry up!
There's a time to drink!
Nothing will leave after the world is engulfed!
Drink a little more
But you amazed me. A real surprise.
I didn't think you'd go that far.
The President was impressed!
Moved to tears!
Chief I need more from you than tears!
At least we know the project won't be canceled,
for now.
It's that 'for now' I don't like.
What's up with that? I don't get it.
What do you mean?
What? What's that mean?
You don't know that
What's that mean?
Can you tell me what's that mean?
You can't say that
Why not?
Yokai, schmokai!
Soon they'll understand. There'll be a boom...
What was that?
Something sure went 'boom' there!
What's that?!
Look at the size of that thing! What's that?
My food...
It'll suck up all Tokyo's rage and resentment!
What power!
Chief!
Let's start with you.
No! Please don't!
You're ugly!
I'll keep my promise!
Forgive me!
You won't get away!
I'll make you really ugly.
It's huge!
Look!
Um... did you see Sunekosuri?
Mr. One-Leg did you see Sunekosuri?
Where is Sunekosuri?
He is not here.
Oh, no!
He's fine.
He's making everyone feel better.
Damn!
The fire's making my eyes water!
What's this?
New clothes.
You have to look the part!
Have you heard?
There's something big happening in Tokyo!
Aye.
Something bigger than Tokyo Dome ate City Hall...
...and all the lights went out.
Shall we go have a look?
Old Edo... it's been years!
Have you heard?
They're raising the roof up in Tokyo!
The Tokyo Dome ate the City Hall!
And all the power!
The place is dark, dark, dark!
The place is dark!
Great! Great!
Did you hear? A Festival of Darkness in Tokyo!
We have to go!
Yes, I heard!
That Governor sure has some great ideas!
Party! There is a party in Tokyo!
A big festival!
Have you heard? Everybody's going!
The biggest festival there ever was in all Japan!
Right! Let's go!
A festival!
The biggest in Asia!
What are you talking about? Tell me
This sounds interesting...
Isn't this a bit much?
How do you feel?
(Kirin Rider)
Tie this up
Now you won't drop it again.
Tadashi?!
There's too many of them!
Great!
Princess!
Oh, no!
You monsters! You broke my dish!
319 short!
Not enough!
There's too many!
Dangerous!
This won't do!
Look!
What?
What? They've started already!
It's a circle, like the Lantern Festival!
You all came!
What a great festival!
Huh? A festival?
A fight! A fight!
A festival fight!
My 'Tofu'!
It hurts me?!
It hurts me!
A fine festival!
Kirin Rider! Now's your chance!
Go inside!
What just stepped on me?!
Tadashi!
What the...?!
Whose is this?
Ah, that's good!
What?
I see you!
Wow!
A great yokai war!
Tadashi!
Look at its leg!
Sunekosuri?
Is that you?
Sunekosuri
No, Sunekosuri!
Don't!
Sunekosuri! Stop!
Stop!
I'm sorry.
I can't forgive you!
He won't...
...get away with this!
Kato...
...goes down!
Oh no you don't.
Do you know...
...after all the time
I've spent on Lord Kato...
...I'm not letting you get in my way!
Agi...
Lord Kato!
Put Tomio down!
But why don't they come here?
Tadashi! Where are you?
There!
Here... 314!
Only five left!
Kato!
You were...
that effigy...
Stop this!
Please!
Stop it!
How has it been,
wandering this world as a yokai?
I hate it!
Hate what?
People!
How much?
More than you can say?
hen take revenge.
No!
Why not?
That only proves...
you're human.
Revenge is only proof that...
...you are human?
I won't defile myself!
That's why I save people, and love them.
That's why I can't forgive you!
Then...
...be at peace.
There!
One more to go!
There it is!
Found it!
I've got them all!
Tadashi!
You...
Do you think you'll defeat me
with a thing like that?
Fool!
Agi...
...let's go.
Why?!
You're in the way.
How?
The love you have for me.
That love is a hindrance.
Do you hate me?
Does your heart pain you?
Then my work...
...is complete.
I see her!
I've found her!
Hi!
(Azuki beans, I love 'em... )
A bean...
Azuki beans...
...are good for you.
What?!
(Azuki beans grow from love and peace... )
(Azuki beans, I love 'em... )
(I love Azuki beans!)
What the hell?!
This is great!
Here it comes!
Sensei... this night is over.
Rejoice! It would seem we have won the war.
Won the war?
Don't be a fool!
There is a limit even to foolishness.
Wars must not happen.
They only make you hungry.
Wars sure make you hungry!
It wasn't a dream!
What?
I forgot to call home.
Your mom's probably worried.
I've never done this.
Stayed out all night without calling.
Well...
you're on vacation.
That girl...
Do you know her name?
Yeah. Kawahime.
'Kawahime'
That's a nice name.
Did she...
Did she say anything...
...about me?
She's always...
...wanted to see you.
She was glad...
...she finally did.
Yeah?
She was?
Ah, that's good!
Real good!
For the first time in my life...
...I told a white lie.
A 'red lie' is one you tell for your own sake.
A 'white lie' is one you tell for someone else's.
That seems to be the gateway to adulthood.
Tadashi!
Yeah?
Take out the garbage. I'll leave it here.
I won't need dinner tonight.
It's Mr. Yamada's farewell party.
All right.
I'm off, then.