Celebrating 60 Years of the Kadokawa Group
Is anyone here?
Dad...
Sis...
...don't go.
I had a nightmare.
Tokyo, where I was born, was in ruins.
Are you going to sleep all day?
You'll be late for school!
Tadashi, get up!
It had been six months since the divorce.
From the window of the room Grandpa built for me...
...the sea was calm.
That summer, I fell in love for the first time.
And...
...I told a little white lie.
What's that?!
Horror... horror...
There's a horrible war...
...coming!
The time has come... now is the time of revenge.
O ye things humanity has used and discarded...
O spirits persecuted...
O rage shut away...
...arise.
It's time to arise!
Arise.
Join with us.
Arise, O vengeful wraith...
...Yomotsumono!
THE GREAT YOKAI WAR
Executive Producer: KADOKAWA Tsuguhiko
'Kwai' Production Team: MIZUKI Shigeru
ARAMATA Hiroshi
KYOGOKU Natsuhiko
MIYABE Miyuki
Executive in Charge of Production: KUROI Kazuo
Planning: SATO Naoki
Producer: INOUE Fumio
Directed by MIIKE Takashi
Hey, Tadashi!
What are you scared of?
Uh... nothing.
Is the little city kid...
...scared of a spooky village festival?
Watch out the kirin doesn't bite you!
Why?
The one it bites is this year's 'Kirin Rider'.
'Kirin Rider'?
Don't you even know that?!
Guardian of Peace, Friend of Justice.
The wrestler Antonio Inoki got bit once.
It won't choose me.
The 'Kirin Rider'! Go for it, lad!
I'm home.
Grandpa, I'm home!
Grandpa!
Captain! Permission to board!
Akira?
Well done!
It's 'Tadashi'!
'Kirin Rider'?
Yeah.
The festival kirin chose me.
I'm the boy who preserves peace.
Sounds great. But what do you do that with?
All I won...
...was beans and rice, and a towel.
Still, that's great!
Grandpa must be happy.
I haven't told him.
Anyway, today I'm 'Akira'.
Oh... is he OK?
Yeah, he's fine.
Every third day I go back to being 'Tadashi'.
Every third day, huh?
I bet he's forgotten me.
Bless this food.
Good boy!
Tadashi?
I'm used to it. It's been six months.
Hey, it's almost summer vacation.
Dad says we might sneak down and see you.
He said that last spring.
Oh.
Yeah, he did.
I'll call again.
OK.
Tadashi...
Hang in there.
Yeah. See you.
I'm home.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Were they teasing you again?
No.
OK, then.
Pickles.
Thanks.
What's this?
Oh, that...
Oh, Dad!
Not that!
What?
That towel...
Azuki beans are good for you.
'Azuki beans are good for you.' by Grandpa
Quiet, please! Quiet!
Don't forget your summer homework.
And write those book reports.
A child who doesn't read makes a worthless adult.
And now, vacation!
See you later!
Rider!
When are you going for
the legendary sword?
What sword?
Didn't they even tell you that?
They know a feeb like you...
...can't handle it.
The Kirin Rider...
has to go to the cave on Great Goblin Mountain...
...to get the Great Goblin Sword.
No way...
...crybaby Tadashi can do that!
Cut it out.
What are you guys up to?!
Watch it!
Your Grandpa's here.
Again?
You be quiet!
Grandpa...
What?
Akira was Mom's elder brother?
Right.
But he died years and years ago.
My son and heir.
Always getting in fights, never good for anything.
Do I look like him, Grandpa?
you do.
You do, somehow.
Grandpa...
...do you know 'Great Goblin Mountain'?
Well, of course!
That be it there, over yonder.
Long, long ago, they say...
...there was an evil goblin
there who'd snatch children away.
And then he was felled...
...by the Kirin Rider!
'I'll never work evil again,'
the Great Goblin said.
He changed his ways,
and swore allegiance to the Kirin Rider.
So then the Kirin Rider...
...left the Great Goblin a sword to keep...
...and bade him be Guardian Spirit to this land.
Since then they say the one chosen Kirin Rider...
...must climb that mountain...
...and get the sword
that Great Goblin has in his keeping.
Will you go?
You were chosen Kirin Rider, weren't you?
How did you know?
Hmm, how did I know?
What?
I didn't finish those beans!
They know a feeb like you...
They know a feeb like you can't handle it.
No way...
No way crybaby Tadashi can do that!
'Great Goblin's Cave...
'... left.'
No way!
Thank you!
Driver!
A cat?!
Do you understand me?
OK!
Here. Drink this.
NO?
You've got to have something
or you won't get better.
Kitty.
No?
Then what are you?
I can't find you in here.
What?
'Shin'?
Why are you rubbing my shin?
'Shin',
'Rub'... the sprite that rubs against your shins!
'Sunekosuri'!
Agi!
Let me out! I'm warning you!
Do you hear me?!
Agi!
This isn't funny!
What do you want with us?!
You're one of us!
I'm not one of you any more.
I will unite with Lord Kato...
...and be reborn.
You'll what?!
I can't wait, Agi.
Ow...! Let me go!
Stop it, I tell you!
Stop playing games!
Agi, what are you doing?!
Stop it!
No!
No! Don't!
Release your rage...
...and bury humankind in darkness.
Yoichi!
You haven't brushed your teeth!
This won't do.
That boy...
The Kirin Rider
Where should we go?
Sunekosuri
...why can only I see you?
Why not anyone else?
Are you a yokai?
Mizuki Shigeru
One of Japan's best-known comic artists...
...Mizuki Shigeru was born in
1922 here in Sakaiminato.
The yokai spirits in his work
are based on Japanese folklore...
I knew it!
You're...
...a yokai!
But this is where it all started!
And I've come all this way!
Give me a few days.
Tell the Editor that.
I'll come back later.
Aren't you...
...the Kirin Rider?
Amazing!
I'm doing research on the kirin dance.
I still have to go to Aoya.
You must like yokai.
Like them?
Yeah.
Why?
Don't laugh.
OK.
When I was a kid, just once...
...I saw a real one.
Was that the only time?
Uh, yeah.
Just the once.
Now I probably can't.
Why not?
Maybe...
...I grew up.
You don't see them after you grow up?
Maybe not.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm coming...
Hello, Chief?
Sorry about this.
What?
The project's on hold?! things happen!
You know what publishing's like.
The company's changed plans.
Would I write about goblins...
...if I was scared of the company?!
I've got to go back to Tokyo.
Bye!
'I'll be at the Great Goblin's Cave. Grandpa.'
Why?
Help!
Something's got me by the feet!
Grandpa!
Grandpa?
Oh, no!
Sunekosuri!
Where are you?
Tadashi...
What are you doing here?
Sis?
But... why are you here?
'Sis', you called me?
Sis!
Does your sister...
...Iook like this?
Help me!
I'm sorry...
I'd like to help you...
but...
I'm a bit...
How?!
How do you do that?!
I'm sorry.
Keep away!
Help!
No!
Tadashi! Help me!
Tadashi! I can't breathe!
Tadashi!
I can't breathe!
Tadashi! Help me!
No! I can't!
I'm dying!
Grandpa!
You passed.
You did great.
A river-sprite! A 'kappa'!
Sunekosuri!
Hey! That's discrimination!
The kappa talked!
Don't point!
I'm glad you're safe.
Go away!
Who are they?!
ey, stupid! Don't go judging on appearances!
That cute little Sunekosuri...
...and this pretty River
Princess are yokai just like us!
As far as I'm concerned, you're pretty ugly, too!
I can make cute noises. Cuddle me, too!
Cuddle me, too!
Kawataro!
Stop it.
But that kid...
But you did fine.
You're the Kirin Rider, for sure.
Sorry!
We were just testing you...
...to see if you had what it take
to draw the sword.
The sword?!
Remember me?
It is 'Shrine Festival'...
Yes, leading the Kirin.
But this isn't a mask now.
Grandpa!
I've got to save Grandpa!
Tadashi! Help me!
We didn't think you'd come if I didn't do that.
Anyway, shall we go visit the Great Goblin?
No!
Oh? Can you get home alone?
Not all the yokai...
...are nice guys like us, you know.
Hell may lie ahead, but worse lies behind!
I'm Kawahime, the River Princess.
Come on.
Let's go!
Nothing but small fry left here.
Help me!
The Great Goblin...
Every kid dreams about a summer adventure!
I'll never make it!
You know, kid, what usually happens now is...
...everyone goes 'you can do it! '
...as you struggle across.
Then the rotten board breaks. 'Aaarrghhh! '...
...and you're saved in the nick of time!
So don't go causing us the trouble.
Dangerous, huh?
Be careful.
Hey, kid!
Now, what happens here...
A huge great rock
comes rolling down from above...
See?
And you run like this!
Kawataro!
He's squashed!
Tadashi?
A sandal?
You have done well.
Who draws this sword becomes...
...the true Kirin Rider...
...and guardian of peace in the land.
Draw it.
It's painful!
I can't. I'm too scared!
What's that?!
Found you!
Of all the nerve!
Wow!
I want that power.
Your Greatness!
Sunekosuri!
Tadashi!
Princess! No!
Sunekosuri!
Suffer.
Hate us. Curse us.
That gives us strength.
Agi...
Kato Yasunori!
Who's he?
Come back.
We begin.
Now you and I will finally be one?
Sunekosuri!
You're awake at last?
You are...
Hey!
Lamp-Oil!
Your head's too big!
Make it smaller!
OK!
Lamp-Oil
Hello, everybody!
Hello!
Not much of a Kirin Rider...
I know!
One-Leg the Smith!
He might know what to do!
Eh, General?
He's a fine swordsmith.
I see... we reforge the sword.
Yes, One-Leg the Smith...
Where is he?
Mirror!
Show us One-Leg the Smith!
What's that?
Mirror, show us where he is!
Sunekosuri!
What's that?!
It's her!
What's going on?!
That horrible flame!
No mistake...
...that's Yomotsumono!
'Yomotsumono'?
Yes.
The accumulated wrath
of resentful things...
...humanity has used
and thrown away...
...the raging spirit Yomotsumono!
What?
He is the resentment
humanity has earned...
...from those things you use no more...
...and throw away
You...
...threw away your worn-out shoes.
They gave themselves for your feet...
...because they were 'dirty' or 'too small'...
...and you threw them out.
People just throw things away!
That creates Yomotsumono.
Kato Yasunori!
O effigy...
...so cruelly used...
and cruelly abandoned.
Be reborn in the demon realm,
and take vengeance...
...with me.
Fool!
Kato!
He's brought Yomotsumono
back to life!
He wants only one thing.
What?
Revenge.
He wants to bury humanity in darkness!
So he's turning yokai into monsters!
He won't get away with it!
Who does this Kato?
Don't be afraid!
That's enough!
Meeting adjourned.
Hey, wait a minute!
Help us!
Wait...
You called me?
For what?!
We all join together
to beat Kato and Yomotsumono!
How?
I'm an umbrella.
Huh, Wall?
I'm only a wall...
I know that!
But even a wall...
...can be of some use!
Well, maybe next time.
I know you've got a job to do
and I sympathize, but...
Well, everyone, let's go.
Bye.
Hey, all of you!
Wait a minute!
My foot's asleep!
Wasn't that something!
I'm very happy!
Hey! You said you'd help!
I've already stuck my neck out once!
Snow Woman!
I'd help if it was winter,
but this really isn't my season.
At least you're one who won't get away!
You're always real brave...
...with Kitaro in those comics!
Bunch of wimps!
Azuki-Washer!
Will you stay?!
Huh?
It's just that my foot's...
Thank you!
You're the conscience of us all!
I just...
I know. You just wash beans.
But that's fine!