Mr. Tang Shu-be, the Deputy Secretary
for Mainland Affairs Association
becomes the first communist
to visit Taiwan
He'll be arriving at Chung Ching
International Airport this 15:52
People supporting the Independence
for Taiwan movement
and those who support unity of
the two shores are staging a riot
Which resulted in a massive fight
Against corrupted China
Taiwanese cheer up...
I am thankful to the Taiwan Police Force
What I see at the airport
is not a courteous way
to receive a guest
Get ready
Quick
Cheer up! Cheer up
Cheer up...
Chung-shu
Tell me...
why the party should nominate you
Because I love Taiwan
I am loyal to the party
I love the party
I am loyal to the chairman
I am loyal to you
I love you
Thank you so much!
Chiu-sen, why should we nominate you?
One reason, if you nominate me, I'll win
If you nominate him, he will lose
So, the seat will be taken
by the other party
You're right
The boss shares the same
point of view with you
In fact, we are inclined to nominate you
Chung-shu, how much have you spent
on the election so far?
About 15 million
Chiu-sen, send him 20 million
within three days
And then send a sum of money to the boss
I'll tell you the exact amount
Thank you, Chairman
Go back and settle your gang
Don't lose your cool
and get into trouble
Chung-shu, it's settled
wait for the next election
Don't you have any hard feeling
I won't yield
A nationwide raid against triad code named
1st Liquidation was conducted in 1989
Chau Chiu-sen was put behind
bars for five years
Now, he is an entrepreneur with
a net worth of over NT$3 billion
Let's focus on
his electronic games business
He has 38 electronic game shops
which are actually underground casinos
With a daily turnover of
fifty million NT dollars
He is bigger than Mcdonald's
Approximately half of his revenue goes
into bribery for government officials
This big boss
Being the head of the Sung-lin Gang
Now wants to enter politics
He has enrolled as a candidate for
the coming Legislative Council election
There is a government practice
Once a person becomes a legislative
councilor, he is above the law
Even his seedy past will be buried
It doesn't make sense
So? Let's do something about it
Let's stop him
As for the corrupted departments...
Let's wait for the right time to act
Because it involves too many officials
Be patient
Yes sir, I know the importance of timing
I am proud to have you as my student
So many expensive cars are parked here!
Thank you
Welcome...
Dear customers
Grab a seat quickly...
The sooner you put a bet on
the sooner you can win
Damn you bastard!
All you care about is gambling
Congratulations...
You've won the jackpot!
You've won an electric rice cooker
This is filled with
gambling electronic games
Call the police
Sorry
The cars parked outside are too expensive
ride for this crowd
Fong, the police said they've just
finished their routine inspection
They said that this shop is legally run
They rejected our case
Call again, tell them someone is
trafficking drugs here
"Staff only"
Only members are allowed to enter
Welcome
The couple who have just entered
are using membership card number JKO843
But this card was reported lost
a few days ago
This game is specially designed for you
It brings extraordinary excitement...
There will be six participants
appearing on screen
Their horoscope signs, blood type
and physical condition will be shown
Push the right button to place a bet
The maximum bet is 50 points
minimum bet is 1 point
The dividend paid is shown on the screen
Good luck
Police raid
Change the boards at once
Change the board
It's alright, go on...
Routine inspection only
Miss
May I buy you a drink?
They're in trouble
Ask him to hang on for ten more minutes
Fong said to give him 10 more minutes
Good luck
Nice to meet you
Some coca cola?
You're so kind
My pleasure
We received a report that
you are selling amphetamine
Must be sore losers
Tso, we are making
so much money here already
Why do we want to sell drugs?
We can provide them for free
We never sold any drugs
Captain
two small sized electric cookers
It's too small!
Bring two big ones
Go exchange them for money
Ah Koon, you go do it
I'm in uniform
maybe it's not a good idea
Two big electric cookers
are worth $200,000
Wait, I'll get the right sum
Two hundred thousand
You count it
He stole my cooker
Alright, stop it, just tell them
Run!
May Li, move
Go down this stairs and then turn left
Turn right and walk for 30 meters
Turn left, walk 23 meters
Where are we?
I can't open it
You can't open it?
Are we at the right place?
Open the door, if you see water
then it's the right exit
Over there! Move over there
Go!
It hurts!
Be gentle!
Don't be naughty
Let go of me!
Please be gentle...
It hurts!
Sir, you should get a massage
more regularly
Your health is poor
Really?
When I press the pressure points
and he feels great pain
That means those parts of his body
are in bad shape
So how come he is
not screaming like I am?
His health must be much better than mine
No, it's only because
he has a strong mind
He can tolerate great pain
Tell us about
the strong parts of his body
Tell us
Why talk about
the strong parts of his body?
His weakest organ is his kidney
When I pressed the point
which reflects your kidneys
It must hurt so much
you want to piss in your pants
I can hear the ladies laughing
That reconfirms that you've a weak kidney
which is already affecting your sex life
I am sure I have the right diagnosis
You're so generous!
Do you know what this is?
A nutcracker
Apart from cracking nuts
it's a very versatile tool
Yeah, I also use this when I eat crabs
San-pao, take him to the toilet
Take off his trousers
Crack his nuts...
So he understands how
a depressed sex life feels like
Take him away
Chinese people said
blind people are usually smart
He must be the exception
That's right
Come on...
This case will determine the legitimacy
of the electronic game business
Whether it can legally exist in Taiwan
Welcome, welcome!
Playing electronic game isn't gambling
We support Mr. Chau
Playing electronic game isn't gambling...
Mr. Chau, what is your view?
Here comes Mr. Chau
Mr. Chau, we support you
Thank you...
You are invited to our restaurant
for a dinner at 6pm this evening
As a gesture of our appreciation
Quiet
Please be seated
The court's in session
From the official report
provided by the Education Dept
It's said that, the electronic games
which are popular in this society
has not categorically been
defined as gambling
It means that we have no
legal ground for indictment
I find the defendant
Chau Chiu-sen not guilty
All electronic games & computer IC boards
must be returned to Mr. Chau at once
Rumor has it that you have a very good
relationship with the Education Department
Chiu-sen is a nice guy
he has friends everywhere
Right?
You are the chairman of
the Union of Electronic Game Centers
So why do you operate
underground casinos?
Since the definition between gambling and
electronic games isn't clearly defined yet
Being the chairman
I have to be proactive
So I would like to hold a public hearing
To invite representatives
from all walks of life
to help draw up
a standard code of practice
Then I'll make sure our members
will follow the set rules
Hopefully it will clear up
any misunderstandings
You are the accused
but you are sounding like the judge!
Excuse me, goodbye
Excuse us...
Chiu-sen has to rush off to officiate
an inauguration for a highway
Please excuse us and save the questions
for some other time
Thank you
Ling Fei, are you alright?
I am fine
"Righteousness is usually late
but it'll come sooner or later!"
Stop playing around
Dinner is ready
Good evening, this is your DJ
This afternoon, I received a call
A young man wants to
dedicate a song to his dad
He wishes his dad to be happy forever
The song is...
Mei Lan-fong's Drunken Concubine
How's business today?
Terrible!
You know, your dad is always
picky about whom to pick up
Especially single girls
If they are not suitable
to be my daughter-in-law
I won't give them a ride
Have you seen the picture
I gave you last week?
The girl is pretty and well educated
A customer you met on the street?
A customer I chose on the street!
Fei, I have to stop here
A lady wants a ride
Taxi...
Excuse me, will you take me to Bei-tau?
Sorry, I am in a hurry, I am sorry
About the book report
You haven't written a word yet
You just go shopping everyday
I don't know how to write it
I am not going to the meeting
This Heritage Society is organized by
the wife of Chairman Hau
The members are all
wives of senior officials
I put in a lot of effort
to make you a member
How can you refuse to go?
Give me a reason why
Damn it
I am not well educated, they despise me
I don't think
they are well educated either
It's an excuse for them
to do some networking
I am satisfied just to be your wife
I don't need to be the wife of
a legislative council member
Do you remember the days
of the First Liquidation?
Don't you think it's enough to be kept
behind bars for five years?
During the Second Liquidation
we were lucky to be in Hong Kong
Who knows when the government will
launch a third liquidation?
Now, I am rich enough to bid for a seat
in the legislative council
It provides the best insurance
Otherwise, how can we be sure
to have a stable life in the future?
But you have to spend 20 to 30 million
dollars to be elected!
You fool, don't you understand
what investment means?
Once I have power
I can get many times
return on my investment
Alright, be a good girl
I'll help you write the report
And you memorize it
and go to the meeting tomorrow
You've ruined my dress
Go buy another one
Hello
This is a live report by Ling Fei
in the Benefaction Villa
A charity auction for ash urns
is being held right here
Excuse me. Thank you
Please give way...
Sir
Chiu-sen, I'm so glad to see you
Please rise
The Benefaction Villa
Supreme Sung Miu-tin
May we have Madam Chiu
Chairlady of the Chai-sai Association
Also Mrs. Hau
Deputy Chairman of the Council
to host the auction for us
The objective of this auction
is to gather all the kind hearted people
for those uncared
we can now offer them free urns
and a good buried place
Those who has done good...
will find internal peace
At the same time, Master Sung will offer
the donors his special spiritual blessing
to help them to avoid evils and bad luck
And to strengthen their luck and wisdom
The starting price for each urn
is $300,000
I hope all of you will
do your best to contribute
Madam is a great lady
I am really touched by her speech
To show my support
I'll buy ten urns
The starting price for each urn is
$300,000, is that right?
So how much is ten urns?
3 million!
You know how much Madam Chau paid?
$60 million!
How generous!
That may be the political donation by Chau
in order to get the party's nomination
Is that right?
That's right It's possible
How is the money channeled
from that charity association?
Who knows?
You're right
Look at this
On last Monday and Saturday
Chau and the Deputy Commissioner
of the Public Works Department...
played golf twice
Mr. Lam is the boss of
Tak-cheung Construction Company
He wants to bid for the construction
contract for Bin-hai Road
But he received anonymous threats
He suspects that it was Chau
so he came to report the case
Now, all the government construction
contracts go to Chau
He is a triad
He knows nothing about construction
Kidnapping, killing
setting fire... they are experts
They can easily burn a building down
But they have no idea
on how to build one
The triads are connected
with the officials
They share most of the gov't construction
budget with the Public Works Dept
And allocate only a small sum
for the actual construction
The quality of the work is
thus grossly compromised
Even before an earthquake
the building will collapse
Our government is collaborating
with illegal gangs
Our construction site is being forcefully
occupied, my staffs are beaten
It's worse than what's shown
in Hollywood movies
They sent this to my son's school
Open
Paper pagoda tombs
Two big ones and a small one
do you get it?
How dare I report to the police?
They are all bribed
If I go to the police, I am just leaving
myself wide open for further danger
I come to you just to try my luck
God knows you are getting nowhere
And you want me to be your undercover?
Don't you feel ashamed even asking me?
We serve the community in different ways
I construct building and you beat crimes
Are you kidding me?
Alright, you are a nice guy
I know you from the TV report
You are straight
But you'll have it do it on your own
I can't help you at all
What's the matter?
Shut up!
See what they have done to my son!
I swear, I would take revenge for you
Thank you
Well...
Nice haircut? I did it
Be careful, someone might find out
Competition - Tea Ceremony
Mr. Lam
Nice to meet you
Me too
Take a seat
Thank you
Alright, let's start the meeting
The late comers
have given up their rights
Who will make the tea for us?
Come on, speak out
don't just look at me
I am just the organizer
I don't have to be the chairman
Mr. Chau, I am sorry, I was caught
in a traffic jam, I am sorry
San-pao
Move the empty chair away
Since everyone is kind enough
to give me face
I'll serve the tea
Please turn off your pagers
and mobile phones
Sorry, sorry...
Mr. Chau, I am late
It's because of a traffic jam
Traffic jam? What car are you driving?
I have a...
Mazda
We all drive Mercedes or Rolls Royce
And you drive a Mazda
that's why you are late
You are not even qualified
to join this meeting
Find a seat
Yes, thank you
Can you find any?
No
You are 11 minutes late
that shows you don't respect this meeting
You are despising us
So how can you expect us
to treat you as a buddy?
Wait for my call at home
I'll call you later
About the Bei-hoi Road construction
A total of 18 companies are planning to
bid for the contract
According to my estimates
9 companies are not big enough
to handle such a big project
So I talked to them before this meeting
And they gave me face too
They decided to withdraw
Which leaves us, the nine companies
And one has just forfeited
So, there are eight of us left
We are all resourceful and strong
But I would like to call for unity
If we bid separately
Will the successful bidder
end up being a winner?
I am sure the final price will be so low
it's not worth it
I hope we would make money together
To share the profit from the project
After all, it's the government's money
Our government is very rich
I'd like to make a suggestion
Actually
I would like you to do me a favor
I'll be frank
I want this project
Since my business is growing rapidly
my cash flow is tight
And here is my offer
Firstly, the government's budget
for the construction is 1 billion
Say I'll make 20% profit
that's 200 million
I'll allocate 40 million
The seven of you can share it
That is, each of you will get
just over 5 million
Secondly, the government will offer 3 more
contracts in the second half of the year
I promise I won't be bidding
I'll be satisfied with
my nominal share of the profit
as calculated similarly to this project
I'm finished
Yes, or no?
I object
I always tell my friends that
Mr. Chau is someone I really admire
He gets the contract and
he doesn't need to lift a finger
You'll take half of the 1 billion
And then subcontract out the project
With several levels of subcontracting
The quality of the building material
will be compromised
Then you work with the officials
of the Public Works Department
To build in an over-budget allowance
of 300 to 400 millions
You will end up making at least
700 millions from the construction
And you are offering us
such a pathetic sum of money
You are out of your mind
What he says makes sense
I told my buddies not to come
But they insisted on coming
They are just small timers
and don't know the better
But, Mr. Chau
I've talked to Mr. Lau
beforehand about this contract
We've decided to join up in the bidding
We are determined to win
But, after listening to
what you just said
We find it hard to accept
Cute!
I am impressed
You are not Chinese
You're like Americans
You are such good negotiators
you are just like the Americans
Alright, this is my last offer
First, each of you will get 7 million
Second, Kiu-wu and Mr. Lau
will be my authorized subcontractor
I'm done, yes or no?
I object
I agree
No, I agree
I agree We agree too
Get out
Thank you for giving me face
please go back
Mr. Lam and I will sort out our problem
Let's go...
Why don't you stay a bit longer?
Do you have your own driver?
You have intentionally tried to
make trouble in the meeting today
Who is backing you?
Damn you
Shit! Mr. Lam has got a gun
Chau Chiu-sen, I am an upright person!
I am not afraid of any triads
To hell with you!
You should know what I mean
Help!
Shit
Nicotine, turn on the taps
You're tough
Thank you
You're lucky to be alive
Last year, more than 160 people
were hurt when three projects
Using inferior building material
resulted in collapses
Look!
Citizens are furious
about the triads rigging
such biddings in collaboration
with government officials
Director of the construction company
Chau Chiu-sen has disappeared
The Public Works Dept
announced today that
the Bin-hei project
will be suspended for 3 months
All investigation will be conducted
on the alleged collaboration
between government officials
and bidding contractors
Leading the investigation
is Fong Kuo-fei
the investigator who has headed
the government's
anti-electronic games gambling campaign
Fong and his team of investigators...
Are the true guardians of Taiwan
Doing their best to
maintain its peace and order
I am Ling Fei, reporting live
I watched your report
you've done a great job
Congratulations
Thank you, I am just reporting the facts
But my boss always criticizes me
of being too forthcoming
You've come to buy pet's food?
Yeah, for my daughter
Doggie or kitty?
Neither, I'll show you
Look, this is Evita
Pretty!
Who do you mean?
Both
This is for you
Thank you
They are my kids
Li, Dun, and Fei
Welcome, Miss
do you have any reservation?
Yes, Mr. Fong's table for two please
This way please
Over there
Thank you
He is a nuisance! A chain smoker!
It doesn't matter
She doesn't always dress like this
We don't mind
Please sit down
They are my partners
They insist on coming
I can't say no, I am sorry
You are a considerate guy
What's the matter, you don't measure up?
But you've bigger ones
Stop teasing me
Mr. Fong, excuse me
Someone ordered wine for you
Who?
Mr. Chau
A gift from Mr. Chau
This is a Petrus
This wine is worth over $60,000 NT dollars
Please do us a favor
Please accept the wine
Otherwise, we will be blamed
Alright
Please open it Thank you
Please pick up my handbag
Thank you
Mr. Fong, let the wine breathe for a while
Give it 20 minutes
I think my friend
would like to taste it now
Sure
The wine has gone bad
That's highly unlikely
There shouldn't be a problem
I think the taste is weird
You try it
Sure
Mr. Fong, I am sorry...
Don't worry
Send the wine back to Mr. Chau
Tell him that
both the wine and its master are rotten
I am sorry
What did you drink?
Come on, water please
I toast you
How can I be so stupid!
Why didn't I take ketchup instead?
I am sure the final price will be so low
it's not worth it
I hope we would make money together
To share the profit from the project
After all, it's the government's money
Our government is very rich
I'd like to make a suggestion
Recently
there are all sorts of rumor...
Spreading all over town
A lot of people are taking this chance
To attack the Public Works Department
for collaborating with triads
You are responsible, do you know that?
The boss is mad
What do you expect
your punishment to be?
Don't tell me
he will withdraw my nomination
You are right
We decided to nominate
Ting Chun-shu instead
At least he is obedient
Any chance to rectify the situation?
What do you think?
If it's money, I can pay more
It's not that simple
Better forget this year's election
Wait for the next one
So the 60 million I paid'll be treated as
an advanced payment for the next election
Damn you! Cut the bull shit!
I've done enough covering up for you
In the last few days
I've kept running around
I didn't get enough sleep, and I drank
so much. And it's all because of you
Why should I even bother?
If it weren't for me
this tape would have leaked out
For sure you won't be sitting here
watching this so comfortably
You would have been arrested
by the investigators
You must be crazy
Is there something wrong
with your brain?
Your ass is transplanted to your brain
isn't it?
Damn it! Isn't saving your ass
worth $60 million?
I have never demanded a cent more
Damn it
Bastard!
You should think before you talk
Thank you, Chairman, thank you for your
benevolence and generosity
It's all my fault
I will go back
and reflect on my mistakes
Chairman, take care
and have a good rest
I am leaving now
I've been cheated
They took my 60 million
And then turn the investigators onto me
Actually, they have never really
considered nominating me
Damn!
I'll have to fight this
Great, now that you are here
Master
What the hell did you feed her?
I didn't feed her anything
So, what's happened
Maybe, she'd stolen the drugs
from somewhere else
She is your disciple
You are responsible
Don't worry
Leave this to me
Is her family here?
Don't worry
Her family is far away from Taipei
She has no friends or family in Taipei
Anybody knows you are here?
No, impossible
I've created a double as a cover
Ask Leung to help you
to get rid of the body
Yes
Can you fix it within an hour?
Sure
You promised
Yes
If not, I'll cut you up into two
It's fixed
I just spent 53 minutes
I am proud of you
Thanks for the good work
Thank you
And I wish you a happy holiday
I've approved your leave of absence
Why?
Cheung, please come here
Didn't I teach you?
Just obey your orders
And never ask why
Come in
Go to Captain Fong's office
Collect everything about Chau Chiu-sen
Sealed them and put them
into the confidential file
Yes Sir
This is signed by the Commissioner
You should at least give me a reason
You embarrassed me
How dare you check the account of
the Cai-sai Association behind me?
Is this the reason?
Yes
You acted without
the consent of your superior
According to the regulations
I can sack you right away
Any other reason?
You better reflect
on what you've done wrong
And learn from your mistakes
Thank you
I shouldn't have been your student
You don't deserve to be a teacher
Do you always come here
when you're unhappy?
Yes
I think this is the best treatment
Don't give up, I'll support you
Thank you
Good morning
The case against the bid rigging
is most encouraging
Yes, but we could have done more
But why has it stopped?
Who told you that?
As I know, it's still proceeding
Is it due to a shortage of staff?
I won't deny that
We have always been over-worked
We are seriously understaffed
How do you rate Captain Fong Kuo-fei?
He is the finest
But, particularly in light of
the staff shortage situation
Why is he suddenly suspended?
I haven't received a report on this case
So I can't answer your question
Commissioner, when can you
give me a satisfactory answer?
This is internal personnel affair
I don't need to discuss it in public
good bye
Commissioner
Ling Fei
Commissioner Off record please
Is Fai your friend?
Yes...
Just an ordinary friend
I didn't ask whether he is your ordinary
friend or boyfriend
He is a special friend
This is a letter from him
What are you laughing at?
Long live China
Long live our party chief
I have to thank the party
for the opportunity and the trust
A special thanks to the party chairman
I, Ting Chun-shu would give my best...
No matter how difficult it gets...
Ladies and gentlemen, journalists
Chiu-sen has an important announcement
I, Chau Chiu-sen now declare
From this second
I withdraw from the party
An independent fighting for
a national peace and prosperity
I will enter
the Legislative Council Election
As an independent candidate
I would appreciate all your support
My campaign would be fair
honorable and transparent
And I will be a very formidable
opponent for Mr. Ting
Behave yourself, mind your image
Thank you
National Prosperity and Peace
Welcome...
Congratulations!
Thank you for
your taxi company's support
My pleasure
It's our pleasure, thank you
Mr. Chau, congratulations on the
founding of your election headquarters
Not only will I support you personally
Everyone of our taxi company
will put up your election flags
Dear fellows, Chau Chiu-sen is one of us
He is not only our friend
But a man of honor and integrity
We should support him
What would you say?
Bravo!
Chau Chiu-sen...
Miss, take my cab, Miss
Miss, take my cab!
Damn you!
How dare you grab my customer?
I arrived first
So what?
Thank you...
A driver from Pai-yun is having a fight
with a driver from Chuen-kuok
San-pao
Call Mr. Kwan
Heung
Check where the wife of the Commissioner
of the Police Dept. Will be going tonight
Mr. Kwan, what happened?
No big deal
it's just a small misunderstanding
God knows how it becomes
such a massive battle
Boss, if we can't solve it
as soon as possible
The traffic of Sai Mun-ting
will be totally jammed
This is a good opportunity
You have to support me
Anything you want, just tell me
I want you to choose ten spots
with heavy traffic
Ask all your drivers to start fights
with the other company's drivers
at the same time
I want traffic in Taipei
to come to a complete stop
San-pao
Boss
Mobilize the Ten Generals
Each of you lead three small teams to
3 spots to back up Kwan
You lead a team to Fu Huo Bridge
Yes
Remember, Fu Huo Bridge
is the main battle ground
And the rest are covers
I get you
Now, it's five pm, it's rush hour
I want a complete mess in Taipei
within half an hour
The messier the better
Mrs. Tung will go to a ball
held by the Taipei University
Graduates Association
at the Hyatt Hotel at 6 pm
That's great
Have you been invited?
No, neither have you
Get an invitation
By hooks or by crooks
find a way to get in
But I wouldn't have a seat assignment
Keep switching tables
and chatting to different people
Or, dance with some of the
university graduates
You are beautiful and a good dancer
It will be their dreams
to dance with you
It's too late
I have no time to get changed
Alright!
Alert the press to
wait for further instructions
My bedroom will be
the War-room for this operation
To anyone else
I am drunk and have fallen asleep
Except by you, I cannot be reached
Go
A fight resulted from two taxi drivers
solicitating the same customer
Now the two taxi companies
are gathering their gangs
After heated argument
they began fighting
Now the heart of Taipei
is completely paralyzed
The police is now on site
to try to solve the dispute
If you are intending to pass through
Sai Mun-ting, please reroute
Son, I've seen my daughter-in-law...
Reporting on TV
Work is important
but she can't work with an empty stomach
I'm going to send her some food
Dad, don't go there, it's dangerous
Dangerous? Not compared to
what I've been through before
When I fought the Japanese
you were not even born yet
Cut it out, will you?
Damn it!
Yes
Don't worry, I'll take care of it
Damn you!
I want a fight
but the Commissioner wants negotiation
The other gang just doesn't want to talk
Damn!
Drivers of the 2 taxi companies
are fighting fiercely...
under the bridge
And we can see
more taxies from Chuen-kuok Company
are still moving in
The situation will definitely get worse
Right here, we see only 20 cops
But no one from any government dept
is on the scene
What! Do it!
Yes
Kwan, go
No shooting...
Kuo-fei...
It's dangerous. Leave!
Have you seen my dad?
What did you say?
You must leave here at once
Leave me alone
Run, my son!
Push! Push!
Son
I'm fine
When did you change
your hair style and dress?
I went to the ball
You're really something
Commissioner
Mr. Chau, I'm so sorry to bother you!
We know you are not well
we have no choice but have to bother you
Please take a seat
If we haven't seen
Madam Chau in the ball
I'll have no way of locating you
My anti-riot troop
has been dispatched to the scene
But, before any action is taken
If they could reach an agreement
That will avoid
a lot of unnecessary casualties
So, I wish you would
help settle this riot
I have been asleep for an hour
how come the world has become a mess?
Let's go
Mr. Chau
don't you need to change first?
We need to save lives
time is of the essence here
Let's go
Give Kwan a call
No pictures...
Chau Chiu-sen
candidate for the Legislative Council
Election, has effectively
put down a riot between the taxi drivers
Chau Chiu-sen
is willing to give assistance...
to the injured and deceased
police and drivers
I feel very bad about such a riot
I can't imagine that such small fight
would end up to be a tragedy like this
A small quarrel
could ignite a riot in Taiwan
Watching the guys lying on the floor
soaked with blood
If you were their relatives
how would you feel?
While we are threatened by
external military power
We are still fighting
among ourselves domestically
So much worries
both externally and internally
is breaking our hearts
What we don't understand is
Why peace only
comes after severe injury?
Please take it back
I am leaving
OK
Don't look
This is what I found
while I was being suspended
What do you think?
I think Chau Chiu-sen, Ting Chung-shu
And those on the video tapes
are all criminals
They should all be put behind bars
I hope the Commissioner
would back me up in this mission
You do know there are
still big bosses behind them?
I know
So, why do something you have
so little chance of succeeding?
I love this land
I can't let these scumbags mess it up
Many years ago
they ruined Mainland China
Our people retreated to Taiwan
If they ruin Taiwan now
Where can we go?
We have our backs against the sea
You are as tough as I was
Very good
We are waiting for someone
to light up Taiwan
You are the torch we need
Kuo-fei, go ahead and do it
I will support you
Thank you
What took you so long?
The air conditioner is out of order
I'll go fix it right away
Boss, something's coming up
Take a look
Isn't that Ting Chung-shu?
Chairman Hau's wife is here
to collect his takes again
No smoking
What's up?
Do you want to stuff this in?
This crook is doing one of his fake
Miracle Split shot again
His disciples are really buying his act
Each of these photos
are selling for $5,000
During the last few days
I have been very restless
I can feel some evil spirit
disturbing me
What?
What kind of bull shit is that?
Vice-Chairman Hau
To make it simple
I feel that someone has been tailing me
during the last few days
I don't know you that well
How come you have my phone number?
Lease don't call me again
Get rid of him
Use the press against Chau Chiu-sen
Let's go
Got you
Go
What are you doing?
Please help...
We are trapped
Someone tried to shoot at me
but a woman was shot instead
Call the ambulance
Be careful!
Now I am in front of the noodle stall
Nicotine
Mei Li, take Nicotine away
Come on, please hang on
Watch out and be careful
Get down
Everyone, get down!
After them!
Go!
Legislative Councilor candidate
Chau Chiu-sen is rumored to be...
Associated with the shooting of inspectors
Fong & Ngai at the Shi-lin night market
Chau was alleged to be running
video arcaded casinos and
is also behind the rigging of bidding
for gov't construction contract
Fong and his team members...
Including Wah and Mei Li are all missing
What are you laughing at?
You are really popular these days
I keep seeing your face in all the media
You have a bigger exposure
than our president
Tell me, what's so funny?
If you can't give me a satisfactory
explanation, I'll beat you up
All right! I am thinking what if you
become our president one day
It's not funny at all
Really?
Yesterday, I imagined how you would
look when you grow old...
See!
Just like our president!
You are holy...
Shit!
Stop crying!
Help!
Chau Chiu-sen
Murder must withdraw
It's rumored that
a guy named Chau is involved in
bid rigging for a gov't project
Investigators were able to get proof
Chau is also rumored
to be involved with the murder
of an investigator I Chin-kuo
in Shi-lin Night Market
Now, the focus is on Chau
It's suspected that
it is a revenge by Chau
My friends...
Murder must not become
a Legislative Councilor
The murderer should withdraw
from the election
Damn you!
Shit...
Beat him!
Stop your bull shit!
If you have guts
Come with me in front of
the temple to make an oath
I swear
my husband never did such a thing
If he did
I, Tsui Miu-heung
will be found lying dead in the street
so everyone can step on me
But you have to make an oath too
If you maliciously spread
such harmful rumors
You'll die a horrible death with no
children bearing your family name any more
This is not rumor started by me
This is written in newspapers
This is public knowledge
Everyone knows it
Besides, I have never said
your husband is a murderer
I never do my watching with my ears
But I did see you working in a nightclub
as a hostess 10 years ago
You readily provided sexual service
to any man who asked
No, you liar!
No, I assure you it's a right fact
Damn you! Ting Chung-shu
Are you a real man?
You can insult me
But you cannot insult my wife
Let me handle this
Chiu-sen, you are a gentleman
let me say something
Quiet!
Quiet please, listen to me
let me say something
Quiet
Ladies and gentlemen
Yes, I worked in a nightclub
I have an unfortunate past
I never denied it
There are things I regret having done
Chiu-sen knows everything
But, he hasn't despised me
Yes, he was a triad kingpin
But bygone is bygone
I hope everyone would give him a chance
So that he can do something
for our country
Think, if he can help reform me
Surely he can help
reform this country as well
Chairman, how are you?
I saw your car from above
That's why I come to say hello
Chairman
Are you going to
Ting Chun-shu's funeral?
No, I am going to
attend my friend's wedding
When did you join the air force?
The traffic jam is getting worse
If I don't buy a helicopter
I can't control my time
Chairman, there are so many
social problems to be solved
I wish to become a councilor
as fast as possible
So I can work with you
to service our people
Do you want a ride?
That's great, I am in a hurry
This way please
Have you seen the TV live broadcast?
Chau won the election by a big margin
Chau has been elected councilor
The big surprise is
as a first time candidate
Mr. Chau... got 125,000 votes
a very high figure
With all the controversy
surrounding him lately
He is receiving a lot of press coverage
building awareness for him
What a beautiful way
to begin his political life
Good morning
Time is running short
Soon, I will be forced to resign
Do what you have to do
The Master splits again
Now, you are watching
proof of your crime
You know you are guilty
My name is Sung Miu-dee
brother of Sung Miu-tin
Miu Tin has forced me
to be his split image cover
I was short and thin
He didn't let me do any exercise
And he stuffed me with food
He gave me plastic surgery
He removed half of my hair
Broke my knee caps to make me taller
He ordered me to
wear high-heel shoes everyday
Apart from your profitable
religious racket
You still sell drugs with Ting
behind your boss's back
Urn number 19 is the place
you hide the drugs, right?
You use religious healing as an excuse
To rape a lot of woman disciples
Mrs. Hau?
That's right
I'll be damned...
How come you have this picture?
He screwed Mrs. Hau?
Computer-graphic
I only suspected it
But judging from his face
I know I am correct
Get ready
Alright, time's up
Let him talk
I know I am guilty
Please give me a chance
How are you, boss?
Hi! Master
Master
This is for Madam Chau
Master Hung
This way please
May I propose a toast to the four
new Legislative Councilors
Welcome
Cheers
In the Legislative Council
there are 164 seats
Thirteen of us are from the triads
Now, what I have to say is this
We must be united
We must not have a Judah
betraying each other
I heard that the government
is preparing a 3rd liquidation
The code name is Chi-ping
That's why you are invited
We need a solution
May I know where the toilet is?
Last month you earned 87 million
Which is 17 million
more than the previous month
You are to be complimented
That's because Madam Chau
and Mr. Chau decided to
join our Board of Directors
It brought great
Fung-shui to our villa
Really?
Mr. Chau rises so rapidly
It's just like
he is sitting in a helicopter
That's because he bought a helicopter
We treat the government as our buddy
We are most obliging to their needs
Anything they want
we provide money, manpower
But, once he thinks you are useless
or gets in their way
He will get rid of you
First Liquidation and Second Liquidation
an iron fisted campaign
No judiciary process
instant arrest and jail sentence
Quite a few of us here, including me
were imprisoned
Tough life, huh?
As our master Tao Yu-sang said
The government treats you as a night pot
When it's no longer useful
they think you stink
They will just throw you under the bed
During the first
and the second liquidation
None of our buddies
were legislative councilors
Now, among the 164 seats
We occupy 10%
And over half of the rest
are closely associated with us
They include local representatives
Mayors, etc
Many are gangsters
We have over 2 million
gangsters in Taiwan
May I ask a question
Can you tell me whether the 13
legislative councilors here...
Are politicians or triads?
They've become one
When wise guys become politicians
After the process of white wash
From black to white
What exactly have we become?
I said, we are neither
We are a hybrid
So, why don't we organize all
our buddies all over the country
Dissolve all the gangs
And form a new party
I guarantee that
We will become the biggest party
within three years
We can easily be the ruling party
We can have our meetings
in the President House
We don't need to act stealthily
We can hold our heads up
Let's go to Lu-tao by helicopter
And turn the place into a golf course
Let's go play golf
Yeah, play golf in Lu-tao
Good speech!
Last month, we're supposed to
make a deposit into a bank account
held by Mrs. Hau's distant relative
a Mr. Leung
The sum was 3.2 million dollars
The man claimed
he only received 1 million
The signed receipt should be with you
I hope you can check it for me
So I can inform Mrs. Hau immediately
Alright, please wait
Thank you
Ling Fei, I would like to employ
the influence of the press
Master Sung is tying his shoe laces at
location 18, on the 2nd floor
Something's wrong
Arrest them
The master is missing
Run
Call our people from Tao-yuen
Sin-yuk, Nam-han and Tai-yuen
Instruct them to stop those guys
I'll be there in three minutes
This way...
Run!
It's too late, the press has arrived
What?
Excuse me
How do you find me here?
The boss knows everything
Do you have a solution?
What do you think?
I can go very high with my offer
How high?
Sky high
Are you willing to leave Taiwan?
Yes, but I wish to
come back at some point
The Boss has a similar idea
Actually
you don't even need to leave Taiwan
Just live in Benefaction Villa
Never to come out again
Damn it
Are you in a hurry?
Would you like me to give you a lift?
Brother...
Can we talk about it?
What do you think?
Now that we are in the air
Can your offer go sky high?
"Resignation"
Any news on Chau Chiu-sen?
This is Ling Fei reporting live
We are following Legislative Councilor
Chau on his escape route
Chau is being escorted by
over 30 vehicles
The entourage is traveling on
Jie Tung Highway heading south
Watch out, there are journalists ahead
San-pao, what is that strange noise?
Go for him
Get him
San Pao!
Heung
Chau Chiu-sen
Go!
The biggest scandal since Taiwan entered
the age of democracy has just erupted
Legislative Councilor Chau
has been found guilty
Capital punishment has been imposed
Master Sung Miu-tin
who turned witness for the plaintiff
Also the Minister Sun
were both convicted...
And are given jail terms
on Lu-tao Prison
This case has sparked off
an avalanche of scandals
A lot of senior government officials
has fled the country
The chief inspector Fong Kuo-fei
and Minister of the Legal Department
have both resigned under
immense pressure from society at large