Andrew!
I missed you so much!
Hey, everyone's looking.
Let them look.
OK, let's go.
- Welcome back, Andy.
- Thanks.
To your good health, Professor.
I had you transferred from Hong Kong,
because I need your help on a case.
It might involve a high ranking
officer in the police department.
I need someone with a new face
to go undercover.
- You'll be reporting to Jerry.
- OK.
Papa, stop talking business
and start eating,
or all the food will go to waste.
All right, we'll discuss this
tomorrow. Come on now, dig in.
Yes, sir.
- Cheers.
He's only been home a few hours
and already you're trying
to get him drunk.
Sally cares about you.
I should be the one
proposing the toast.
I used to just hang around here
until Jerry sent me to reform school.
Then the Professor helped me and sent
me to study at the police academy.
If it wasn't for you two,
I wouldn't be here today.
To both of you. Thank you, sir.
- Shall I walk you to your car?
- No, thanks. It's just there.
- Good night, Professor.
- Good night, Jerry.
I'll take Andy back to his hotel.
You get to bed.
Good night, Professor. I'll see you
tomorrow. I'd better get going.
You'd better get back
and get some rest. Come on.
All right.
Who's visiting the Professor
so late?
Hold it!
"Fingerprint of Suspect"
"Fingerprint Number:"
"Match Number:"
"Carl Chan,
executed January 10th, 1987."
Strange, how could our murderer
have been executed three months ago?
How could this be, Jerry?
It was a well-planned hit.
Using a supposed dead man
to commit a murder.
Either someone's been messing
with the computer,
or there's something up at the jail.
Don't dwell on it, Andy.
I'm OK. You go home if you want.
I want to be alone for a while.
OK, then.
I'll head off, then. Bye. See you.
Give me some stuff, Ronnie.
- Got the money?
- It's all gone.
That's bullshit!
Sell your body, then.
- I can't stand it!
- Get lost!
Boss, someone's looking at you.
What are you looking at?
Do you think it's worth it?
We've checked it out.
The computer is secure.
The prison is our only clue.
I've got to do it.
You might get killed.
I'll take the risk.
And what about Sally?
Don't tell her anything
until I've finished this case.
I won't. But assault
and battery is serious.
You'll be in for two years.
For your safety in prison,
no one can know who you are,
apart from you and me.
Operation - Hunter.
Take these.
I'll inform you of the rules here.
On your clothing is a number - forget
it and it's ten days in the hole.
Fighting is on Saturday afternoons.
Any unsupervised fighting -
ten days in the hole.
First bell rings at 7:55,
second bell rings at 8:00.
Never go against the officers.
Never try to escape.
No raping other inmates.
No breaking of fixtures.
Six months hard labor
for these offences.
If you smoke in bed,
it's ten days in the hole.
Every Saturday,
you'll receive one clean sheet.
Change the bottom one.
If you get it wrong -
ten days in the hole.
You'll memorize these rules. If you
forget any - ten days in the hole.
All right, this is your cell.
All right, guys. That's enough.
Now back off, all of you.
Sorry, that's my bed.
Yours is the lower one.
The last guy in that bunk
was in here for forgery.
He couldn't take it,
so he killed himself.
Hey, is this your first time in?
Don't be like that.
A guy needs a friend in this place.
Charlie.
I'm Andy.
Bed check! Hand over that cigarette!
- A whole cigarette - rich man!
- You scared me!
Who's gonna win?
- What are the odds?
- 20-1 he won't last 30 seconds.
What's going on, Charlie?
The new guy is fighting the prison
champ and the new guy is you!
And if I don't?
Everyone will be out for your blood.
Am I right, Charlie?
Yeah, that's right.
This way. Excuse me, thank you.
Hey, kid. We're all betting on you.
If you stay in for 30 seconds
we'll be rich.
Get back in there!
Get him!
There's five seconds to go!
He's still in!
Get him! Get him!
I'll get him!
It's over.
Come on.
- 20453?
- Here!
- 15783?
- Yo!
- 11795?
- Yeah!
- A letter from your son?
- His mother remarried.
She sent Joey to a boarding school.
His birthday's in two days.
But she's on her honeymoon
with her new husband.
Boarding school's not so bad -
it makes a kid more independent.
I've some fresh meat in the kitchen.
Shall I cook it for you?
It would go well with your wine.
Would you like some?
- Hurry up.
- Yes, sir.
Bill, open the gate.
Thanks.
Hey, cap,
are you going to be a cop forever?
Why do you ask?
Well, if you ever open a restaurant,
I'll be your cook.
What a laugh!
Who's laughing? Don't blame me
when all you have to eat is dog meat.
Hey! What's there to know?
Plenty! I'll show you.
Fry the onion.
Add the meat.
Hold this.
Hey!
You got a light?
Thanks a lot.
It's almost New Year again.
I hope I'm not working this holiday.
My wife will run off
with another man.
What's up with you?
On my salary,
I can't even afford new shoes.
Get out, come on.
I've got to check the car.
What is it, officer?
Doesn't your mother feed you?
She's thinner than I am.
What's going on?
This is all your fault.
It's mine! It's mine!
Get the ball, Joey!
- Joey.
- Papa!
Headquarters,
we've located the stolen car.
We're outside the Lawrence
boarding school. Requesting back-up.
Headquarters -
we've located the prisoner,
requesting immediate back-up.
Listen to your teachers.
I'll visit again soon.
Do you promise?
OK.
Papa loves you always.
Now go back to school.
Your teachers will miss you.
But I don't want to.
Listen to Papa.
Run inside and don't look back.
Why not?
If you do I'll turn into stone. Now
on you go or you won't see me again.
Promise you'll come visit
on New Years'?
I'll count to three and you go in.
One, two, three!
Don't move! Hands up!
Heaven's up there. I'm here.
Then come the dogs.
You're worse than a dog.
Don't go against me again.
Apologize! Go on!
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
My boss's business card.
I believe you've heard of him.
He'll give you half a million
to lose the championship tomorrow.
Be a good boy.
He could beat me...
if he's good enough.
Be a good kid and I'll guarantee you
plenty of dough.
- How was it?
- A great success.
Your shoes.
You know better
than to wear these with me.
Not bad. I've got the touch today.
Think about it.
Kiki!
I'm sorry. I ran all the way.
Don't be mad at me.
I'm so sorry, really.
- I'm sorry.
- I forgive you.
Let's grab a bite to eat.
So you think you're a big shot?
- What do you want?
- No, Kiki.
Let go of her!
Let's go.
Kiki!
Someone help!
Her kidney is badly damaged.
You'll need $200,000
to cover her bills.
If we don't operate now,
we may not be able to save her.
Where can I get it at this hour?
Doctor, can you do
the operation first?
I'm sorry. Hospital policy.
I can't help you.
Do what you can to raise the money.
I'm out!
What's your bet?
It's all I've got.
I call.
I see you. Full house. I win.
- See you.
- Hold it! Play a couple more.
I've got to go.
Bastard! You're a cheat!
You're a cheat!
Hey, my brother says you're a cheat.
Don't let him get away!
I need this money.
Don't make me do it.
You win.
Boss, telephone.
- Get back!
- Please cooperate. Stay back!
- Back!
- He's my brother.
- It's a police matter.
- Let me through!
- Who did it?
- He's in the car.
Boss! Boss!
- What are you doing?
- You! Get out here! I said out!
I'm going to kill you! Get out here!
Come back here! Come back here! OK.
- He killed Teddy.
- Quiet!
No matter where he goes, he's dead.
Come on!
On your clothing is a number. If you
forget it, it's ten days in the hole.
Fighting is on Saturday afternoons.
Any unsupervised fighting,
ten days in the hole.
First bell rings at 7:55,
second bell rings at 8:00.
Never go against the officers!
Never try to escape!
No raping of other inmates...
Charlie, what are the odds
for tonight?
No bet. Not tonight.
Why not?
That guy killed Boss Li's brother
Those other guys are in Li's gang.
They're in the Ghost Shadow Gang.
Word is they're going to kill
that guy Steve tonight.
Those two!
Let go of me! Let me at him!
Calm down, Steve!
- Let go!
- It's all right.
Let me go.
Let me go!
- Take him to the sickroom.
- Yes, sir.
Superintendent,
those guys were trying to kill Steve.
No way, sir. Those guys were
fighting, we tried to separate them.
Better tell the truth.
It is the truth.
He's got the knife on him.
- You're lying.
- No, he's not, Superintendent.
I can prove he's telling the truth.
Here's the knife they used.
Listen up, no screwing up
in my place.
- Take them in.
- Get going!
Write me a report.
You can come out now.
Lucas.
Don't screw up again. Going against
me is like going against God.
We respect our God.
We don't respect you.
There's no comparison.
You're back!
My brothers, never surrender!
Come in.
You asked for me, boss?
Sit down.
I hear you've been asking
about Carl Chan.
- Are you an informer?
- No.
I was looking at your hands.
You've got a well developed
trigger finger.
No one's heard of you.
So the way I see it, you're a snitch.
I'm not!
Talk! What is it with you?
In the service, I was selected
for the Olympic shooting competition.
- That's why I have strong hands.
- And Carl Chan?
We served together in the army.
He owes me some money.
You're lying.
Lucas! I won't yell out.
I won't get the guards after you.
Please, believe me.
Enough!
If you're really here to settle a
debt, Carl Chan's dead so forget it.
His slate is clean.
You watch what you're doing.
Your life is in my hands.
- Andy! Over here.
- Right.
Oh, sorry.
- Use your spoon.
- Yeah.
What's wrong with your hand?
I cut it in the shop.
Oh, yeah?
No more food till I get the truth.
Come get it
when you're ready to talk.
Thanks, Lucas, but I'm being watched.
- So you're great friends?
- No appetite.
- Bring the rice pot.
- Yes, sir.
Move!
Now let's have some fun.
You'd better eat it all,
or it's another ten days in the hole.
Lucas, save some for me.
You've all come here to work,
not to sunbathe!
I won't tolerate any goofing around.
If you're not able to complete the
road, there'll be no dinner tonight.
Officer Chang, what if we finish
early? Can we break then?
Finish early! And I'm a pig!
There's no way you'll finish early.
Now get to work!
Hey, friend, take it easy.
It's a long road.
You heard what he said. If we finish
early, he'll turn into a pig.
Hey, listen up.
If we finish early, somebody
will turn into a pig! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Come on, guys. Let's move it!
Hurry it up!
Some water, sir?
- Are they crazy?
- I don't know.
OK, let's go!
Come on, brothers! We're almost done.
Are they on drugs?
They're two hours ahead of schedule.
Anyone here see an angry pig?
Get in there, hurry up.
Hey, did you see your son?
Yeah.
He's growing up so fast,
I hardly recognized him.
I promised I'd visit him
at New Years'.
Next time don't get caught.
Every time they bring you back
and they give you another year.
At this rate, you'll never get out.
One day I'll escape for good. My son
and I will sail away on a boat.
Where will you go?
The Philippines.
Living costs are low there.
A few dollars will get you a virgin.
Keep her for a month and you get a
discount, and she does the housework.
What do you want her for?
The usual stuff, you know, cooking
and cleaning... that kind of thing.
No wonder you want to escape. Let me
know if you get another chance.
A live-in maid!
Now that's good for your health.
Boss, sir. Glasses on.
She's not wearing any bra.
Boss, sir! Cleaning glasses.
Dear Lord, whatever I've done wrong,
please don't strike me blind now.
Oh, shit! I can't see anything
with these glasses.
Boss, sir! Taking off glasses.
Why don't any of you help me?
Hey, John! Go help her.
Yes, sir!
- Hi, miss.
- Thank you.
Don't mention it. It's no bother!
- Are you all right?
- I'm OK.
You can break my bones,
but don't strike me blind.
Don't stand there. I need you
to push the car from over there.
Lean against the window and rock it.
All right, place your bets, gentlemen
on one, two or three.
Hurry up, the race is about to start.
Come on, place your bets,
then stand back.
Come on, everyone,
place your bets here.
Come on...
Hey, John, how'd that girl look
up close? Was she fine?
She was better than fine,
she was inspiring.
I didn't need a jack
to change her tire.
Really?
Of course not.
All right, all bets in. Ready...
Go!
You bet on number two
and you lost it all.
Johnny, can I have just two?
Two? Here!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight...
Li's man is out!
In here I'm the boss.
I know all about you and Boss Li.
But what happens on the outside
stays on the outside. Understand?
When you're in here,
it doesn't matter who you are.
We're all together in this.
I don't want any feuds in here.
Lucas, Boss Li's brother's dead.
It's blood for blood.
I'll bleed for him.
Andy, have you seen my mouse?
Maybe he's asleep
in the mattress again.
I'll help you look after we eat.
- Thanks.
- Hey, that's not enough.
Why?
Why? Why? Why did you do it?
Why did you do it to him?
He cooked my mouse!
In the hole with him.
Here, I got it!
Better keep away from him.
Here, take this. I'm not hungry.
Boss? I got to do the business.
Great timing!
Make sure you go downwind.
- Let me know where you are.
- Yes, sir.
Shoot.
I'm here! I'm here!
I'm still here! I'm still shitting!
Don't tell me that, just shake
the grass. We're eating here!
OK, I'm moving the grass now, boss.
Don't let him get away! After him!
Maybe we can find ourselves
a boat at dawn.
I heard your son broke his leg
playing football. Is he all right?
He's a kid.
He'll be fine in a few days.
It's almost New Year. Time flies.
Yeah, time flies.
Why?
I'm sorry. I had to see my son.
I promised I'd see him at New Years'.
They said I could if we turned
ourselves in. Nothing will happen.
Lucas! Lucas!
Why? Why? You said we'd just get
a few days in the hole!
I don't negotiate with convicts.
- Take him away.
- Yes, sir.
I'll report you!
I don't think
you'll be seeing your son.
And if anyone hears you sold Lucas
out, you'll die a terrible death.
- Get him out of here!
- Come on!
Wake up! Everybody up! Wake up!
Come on!
This is what happens
when you break the rules.
Even though John went along
with Lucas' escape plan,
when we caught up with him,
he surrendered and said he was sorry.
He went for the sake
of his son's broken leg.
We forgive him. We are not
as unreasonable as you think.
We'll be watching him closely and if
he behaves, we'll forget about this.
A potato a day won't make you fat,
but will keep you healthy to fight
another day - Charlie.
Boss, Eddie's out of jail.
He's in the back room.
I'll go talk to him.
Sit down. How's everything?
Steve's not dead, he's injured so
they're keeping him in the sickroom.
We couldn't get him.
What are my men doing?
It seems as if Lucas got involved.
Brother, Eddie just got out of jail.
Make him comfortable.
Alfred, get Eddie set up
in the casino.
- Enjoy yourself.
- Thanks.
Well?
- What is it?
- That bastard Steve.
He's still alive and walking around.
God dammit!
Teddy died for nothing.
That bastard!
Boss, let me do it!
Some water, sir?
Here, boss, have some more noodles.
You eat. I'll do this.
Snake! Snake!
Go!
Freddy's dead.
- Get him out, hurry!
- Yes, sir.
Prisoner John Liu escaped three times
during his incarceration.
Additional punishment
proved no deterrent.
Furthermore, he caused the death
of corrections officer, Freddy Tang.
The judgment of this court
is that he be executed forthwith.
ID cards everyone. Come on.
Get in line.
Lieutenant, what's up?
Inspector, what's all this about?
Routine check.
Oh, yeah? Why now?
You only gave my daughter $5,000
as a wedding gift.
If I check here often,
you lose business.
You lose business, you lose money.
This is a nice place. It'd be a real
shame to have to close it down.
Really sad.
OK, how much do you want?
Five hundred dollars and two zeros.
All right, I'll pay you.
Come with me.
Hey, brother, what's up?
- Make him out a cheque for $50,000.
- Right.
We're all good friends here.
You can't come between us.
Now, listen. Choose a day
and I'll take you out to dinner.
I, ah...
I think I'll come back tomorrow.
What did you do that for?
I thought we were friends.
No need to fight. A zero here
or there, what does it matter?
I'm sorry we made you suffer.
I just need to get into the jail.
Thank you.
The cheque.
$50,000- less a zero or two. You're
going to do this favor for me.
- All right?
- All right.
Lock him up.
- Let's go.
- Move out.
Wait a second.
- Brother, look after the place.
- Be careful.
It's over.
Open up.
These are the rules.
On your clothing is a number, forget
it and it's ten days in the hole.
Fighting is on Saturday afternoon.
Any unsupervised fighting -
ten days in the hole.
First bell rings at 7:55,
second bell rings at 8:00.
Never go against the officers.
never try to escape.
No raping of other inmates.
No breaking of fixtures.
Six months hard labor
for these offences.
Ten days in the hole
for smoking in bed.
Every Saturday,
you'll receive one clean sheet.
Send your bottom sheet
to the laundry.
Make a mistake -
ten days in the hole.
Memorize these rules. If you forget
them, ten days in the hole.
This is your cell.
Any questions, ask me.
He's still alive
because of your cowardice.
- You don't understand.
- Yes, I do.
My bet's on you.
Eat and get strong for the fight.
Mr. Li, your brother's death was
an accident. I want to apologize.
My little brother is dead.
Nothing you say can change that.
I had intended killing
your girlfriend to get in here.
But she couldn't wait around.
She's already dead.
You're lying.
They wouldn't tell you
cos it's not good for morale.
It was up to me to let you know.
I want you to feel the agony.
I'll kill you when I'm ready.
Who are you betting on?
Kill him!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Go on, you can do it. Kill again.
Don't do it, Steve!
Don't do it!
Kill him!
Stand back.
Don't! If you do, I'll report you.
- Take him away!
- Yes, sir.
"Happy New Year"
Sit down.
Try your luck.
I'll get some money.
Take mine.
- Thanks. I'll get my own.
- OK, but hurry.
Charlie! Let me go!
Let me go! Let me go!
You bastard!
Why? Why? Why?
Why? Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
It was him...
- Get this murderer out of here.
- Yes, sir.
No! No! You're just trying to shut
me up! You told me to kill Andy.
Charlie was a mistake.
You're trying to frame me!
Inmate Andy Wong was cited for bad
conduct during his prison term.
He has been found guilty of murder
in the first degree.
It is the high court's decision
that Andy Wong shall be executed
by firing squad.
This is your funeral.
That's where you're buried.
Here's your death certificate.
We've kept you alive to work for us.
You're now a member
of the Executive Committee.
We've been watching you
for a long time.
You're a survivor with a strong sense
of justice, though misguided.
Society is becoming complex. There
are too many criminals on the street.
And too many loopholes.
They always seem to find a way
to escape punishment.
The Executive Committee
is in existence
solely to deal with these criminals.
Blood begets blood,
filth begets filth.
Your Government has given you
the honor of joining this team.
When your assignment is through,
we'll give you a passport
and a new identity.
You can go anywhere you want -
start all over again.
In fact, you don't have a choice.
You're already dead.
This is your only chance.
This mission is your life.
This assignment is an assassination.
The target is Colonel Sama.
The biggest drug dealer
in Southeast Asia.
He's being brought in to stand trial.
But we know he's paid off
all the judges.
Before he boards his plane,
we must execute him.
Each of you has been issued two guns.
When you have accomplished
your mission,
you'll find a jeep waiting for you
directly behind you, 800 meters away.
Leave immediately.
Someone will meet you at the gate
and give you your passports
and airline tickets.
Let's go!
Come on, get in!
There's a bomb in the car. Jump!
Hey! Hold it! If I...
I promised my son I'd see him again.
Move it! You piece of shit!
Come on!
Hurry! Get in!
Tell him to slow down.
- Tell them to hurry up!
- Hurry! Quickly!
Faster!
Hey, Chief, looking for your gun?
Executive Committee member
number 24 reporting.
Well done, good job.
I'll get you your new passport.
You're free.
Using dead convicts to work for you.
Then killing them
when they're through.
A very clever plan.
You didn't realize
I'd come back alive.
I knew you would. I'll give you some
money, you can go wherever you want.
No one will be the wiser.
What do you say?
That's a real good plan.
There's just one thing...
Why did you do it?
That drug dealer was my partner.
I'd be dead if he testified.
What about Professor Leung?
Why did you kill him?
He was investigating me
and he was getting too close.
Here they are.
It's a lot of money. And tomorrow
I can send you a lot more.
It's all yours, Andy.
You make me sick.
So many good men killed.
Aw, Andy, don't be stupid.
You couldn't earn this much money
in a lifetime.
Thousands die every day, what
difference does a few more make?
What difference?
Can you pay for all of them?
The price is too high!
Bastard! I serve God, not you.
I'm going to kill you!
Andy! Don't.
DVD Subtitles
by European Captioning Institute