Toho Co. LTD. JAPAN MCMLVI
SAMURAI Ill
DUEL AT GANRYU ISLAND
Producer
Kazuo Takimura
Based on Hideji Hojo's adaptation
of the novel "Musashi"
by Eiji Yoshikawa
Screenplay
Tokuhei Wakao and Hiroshi Inagaki
Cinematography
Kazuo Yamada
Art Direction
Hiroshi Ueda and Kisaku lto
Lighting
Tsuruzo Nishikawa
Music
lkuma Dan
Sound
Masanobu Miyazaki
Cast
Musashi Miyamoto - Toshiro Mifune
Kojiro Sasaki - Koji Tsuruta
Otsu - Kaoru Yachigusa
Akemi - Mariko Okada
Omitsu - Michiko Saga
Court Official - Takashi Shimura
Director
Hiroshi Inagaki
Young Kojiro Sasaki is determined
to win a match...
with Musashi Miyamoto, his lifelong
rival in love and swordsmanship,
to become Japan's No. 1 fencer
"Clothes Rod" my poor sword
Your owner, such a fencer,
is still unrecognized
Despite his great skill
His dream remains
unattained!
Blind fools!
Poor swallow
Not just anyone can do that
"Swallow turn" swing.
I'll kill Musashi with it
Why must you fight him?
My long cherished dream
He has nothing against you.
Why must you kill him?
Tell me!
You're a devil!
Why get excited about him?
Please.
Forget him
I won't mention him from now on.
So please. -Conceited girl!
I'm not after him because of you
He's good. He's my only match
in this country today
My dream is to fight him.
He must dream it too
Akemi, stop!
-I won't
You scare me.
You horrify me
Looking for Musashi?
Go - then.
If you see him...
tell him not to trifle with
his life till we fight
Mu-sa-shi!
Ancient city of Nara
Martial Arts Tournament by the
Hozoin Temple Priests
Who's next?
Come on!
You?
-No, pass
If no one sallies forth,
I'll leave
I'll call myself
today's winner!
Any objections?
Speak up!
You may come in a group
No one?
No contender?
Oh, well
Let's go
Hang it!
-Wait, kid!
I like your spirit.
You insulted me audaciously
You challenged
Fight with you?
-You can't?
Then why did you say that?
He's only a child.
Forgive him
Who are you?
-His companion
You urged him?
-No, my own idea
Then you'll fight with me
You may attack me together,
if you wish
Please.
-I won't forgive him
I apologize in his place.
-No!
I was insulted publicly
I won't swallow it
Fool
Prize fool Agon!
Agon, stop it.
-No!
Stop!
You're no match for him at all
He's peerless. Hasn't lost in
60 odd matches
Stop it!
-Musashi?
This is no fight
The winner of the tourney is
Priest Agon here!
I remembered your old self
in Priest Agon
I marvel at your perfection
Power alone won't make an
accomplished samurai
He must be strong. At the
same time he must be just
I want to be able to fight
without regrets
My past encounters were
full of them
Errantry has its points
Your suffering will polish you
I feel so pleased tonight
Have you ever fallen in love?
I know a person who's longing
for you
Want to meet this person?
So you've somebody in your heart
Don't worry.
I mean a man
A man longing...?
-Yes, for a man
Besides, he hasn't seen you
even once, mind you!
Who is he?
-Lord Yagyu
What? Lord Shogun's teacher?
Why don't you go to Edo and
see Yagyu?
You brought a letter from
Lord Karasumaru? I see
So your name's Otsu
Are you connected with
Musashi Miyamoto?
Yes, Your Grace.
I'm looking for him
Too late
He was here until this morning.
-Was he?
But he left for Edo
Stop.
Don't chase him
I must see him.
-I see, you care for him
The city of Edo had become
Japan's most crowded city
It was the Shogun's political and
military headquarters
His captains maintained villas here...
to serve him
and to recruit their forces.
Many ambitious samurai sought
employment...
coming to this large city
with high hopes.
I am Okaya.
-One moment
Why cover your spearhead?
Don't worry about hurting me,
please
Take it off
See his assurance, my Lord
Now that I use it uncovered,
use a sword yourself
No. This will do
-I won't fight like this
It's all right.
-Use your sword
I am only an unemployed samurai
Use of my sword will offend
His Lordship
Full of confidence, sir.
-Okaya, let him have his way
He overdid it
I was embarrassed
Was the audience successful?
Well... I fear not
Why? A man of your ability!
-It's true
My opponent was not very strong.
I should have been gentle
Did you win?
-I did
True, he will live.
As a cripple
Nobody will hire one who
cripples his vassal
I overdid it.
-I like it. You always mean business
I think I did nothing wrong.
But people disagree
Why are you doing that?
Still like me after I tore
your present?
I did the same thing today
I'll stay unemployed
I like it. I like
your straightforward character
Omitsu
Elope with me
I love you.
-Please!
Don't you want freedom?
Don't you love me?
lf you do, follow me
I am leaving Edo
Where are you going?
These young men of today!
lmpertinence!
Conceited!
-Please
You don't know how worried he is
about today's match
Did he tell you that?
-No, Father
Only...
I can sense it
Very painful, Okaya?
-It is
I was lucky...
it was not...
a sword
I am very sorry, believe me.
-I was just no match for you
I may be sorry but
it was my fault
Did you get the job?
Take good care of yourself
I thought he was arrogant
But he's fine.
I never knew it
Kojiro visited Okaya?
-Okaya told me so, sir
What do you suggest? -If he
really meant to console Okaya...
he must be somebody.
I am for employing him
Who is better, your Musashi or him?
I hear Musashi is a matchless
swordsman. -I must see Musashi
Try and find him for me.
-And Kojiro?
I'll think it over
Hey, kid! Your master's been
carving images for days
Quit fencing? Is he a fencer?
-None of your business!
Keeper, is this an inn?
Master. When will you see
the Shogun's teacher?
I won't. -Really? Where's
the letter that monk gave you?
Threw it away.
-You shouldn't have!
Lord Yagyu might've recommended
you to the Shogun
You disgust me.
-Why?
If you succeed in life,
so will I
Jotaro, is that why
you've followed me?
But why stay here then?
Waiting for her?
-Who?
Otsu.
-Fool!
I know you want to see her.
I'm positive
Sure. Look.
This is her face
Please. Mercy
Why?
-No
Don't
You mustn't
Yes, I want to see her.
But she'll refuse to see me
Why?
I did something shameful to her
It's four to one.
-And he's winning
What skill!
Where is he?
He left a note
"The four are students of
Obana Strategic School
He who is responsible for it is
Kojiro Sasaki of Isarago."
I appreciate...
your kind deed
However, Miyamoto,
the bodies you brought...
have nothing to do
with my school
But I hear that they drew
when he slandered you
Please. None of my students
are as weak as that
You call me a meddler, then?
Miyamoto, I teach the Shogun.
Mine is an honorable family
My 100 students are
accomplished men
I see. Forgive my rudeness for
bringing the corpses
Let me pass
Professor Obana told me they
could not be his men
Don't be offended.
Please give them up to us
I will not.
The dead men won't like it
Fortunately I know several sutras.
I'll bury them
I learned a lesson today
"Here lie four unknown samurai"
So it is you
I thought it was one of them
Thank you for your help
last year
You fought marvelously.
I saw it
I learned of your ability today
for the first time
Those four. One stroke each!
-Try it?
Kid. Go away awhile
Be calm no matter what you see
I've always wanted to meet you
Stop.
-Scared?
No.
Postpone it
Elsewhere.
If we fight here...
they may say I fought for Obana
Which is not true
Let us fix it properly
and fight freely
You are right.
Tomorrow evening...
I'll be at the East Gate.
Right? -Very good
You have been evading me.
Scared of me? -No
However, I won't elope with you
You think I am joking?
You meant it
You are a darling.
I meant it
But I've changed my mind.
-Why?
Tomorrow night you'll know
I'll do or die!
You won't be seeing me, anyway
If I win I'll seek a much
larger fortune
If I lose...
I'll be dead
In either case, you'll always
remember me as your lover
His Lordship
What was it?
-Well, he was delighted
He wants to hire Kojiro
as his teacher
Kojiro did something big.
Where is he?
I'll bring him here
Did you come back?
-I bring good news!
My Master heard about you
and Obana's students
Please. They were just weaklings.
It did me no credit
However, their master is
Lord Shogun's teacher
Vengeance will be sought.
-I'll fight
Listen to me.
You are too full of youthful vigor
My Master said "Such animosity
must be stopped"
He suddenly decided to employ
you as a retainer
Well? lf you become Lord
Hosokawa's teacher...
they dare not attack you.
-I decline
I dislike seeking protection.
-Don't be silly
If they challenge,
fight as Lord Hosokawa's teacher
It's not like you.
Another thing
Chief Retainer Sado is recommending
Musashi
Musashi?
-He is being sought quietly
We must decide this
before they find him
Taking an initiative is always
advantageous
Listen.
I duel with Musashi tomorrow
What! With him?
-So your worry is over
His dream is too vast
What noise!
Hey, quiet you!
Thanks
They became quiet.
You are persuasive. -Sure!
Excuse me
Samurai! Stop eating
Confess you're scared.
Don't pretend you're calm at heart
Stop!
Who are you?
-Don't know me?
Those who don't know me here,
must be deaf
Speak loudly, as I am
hard of hearing
Who?
-Shut up!
I'm Kumagoro the horse-dealer,
a tough guy
And when I say tough I mean tough.
-Horse-dealer, eh?
I deal with samurai.
I handle live horses, mind you
So what?
-You sent this kid to me...
to tell me to be quiet,
didn't you?
I have a big voice.
You don't own this inn, do you?
So, what?
-Apologize
Write a letter of apology
addressed to us all
Or I'll take you out into
the yard and punish you
Amusing.
Very interesting
Fresh! You heard me.
Now answer me!
Answer me at once, or else...!
Which would be better?
Too many.
Wash these sticks
He's terrific!
Training for revenge?
I'm his pupil now.
Musashi Miyamoto! No wonder!
Are you out of your head?
-Of course not!
Horse-dealer.
Did you say Musashi?
Does he live here?
Now I fully understand you
I will not force my ideas on you
However, will you be good enough
to see my Master?
But, I am to fight a duel tonight.
-A duel?
It will be the memorable match
of my life. -Who's your man?
Kojiro Sasaki.
-Sasaki?
You mean it?
I hear he may be employed
by my Master
What? Is Kojiro...
Miyamoto, if you win...
...please certainly accept my offer
Must you fight?
Hey, kid!
Where is Musashi?
"l have decided to leave
on a journey
Let me please postpone the
promised match for a year
When we meet again, I will be
quite ready...
to vie with you.
Yours truly"
Why do you cry?
-I don't like it
That Kojiro as Hosokawa's teacher!
I dreamt of worldly success once
I thought it was natural
to settle down
But now I want to train
myself further
Jotaro, I'm hungry.
Let's eat, shall we?
Kuma.
I'm your senior, am I not?
Call me Master Jotaro
I say... Master Jotaro.
-What is it?
A man should be kind to his juniors
Let's eat, shall we?
Shall we?
Drop the reins.
Or we'll shoot
Surrender your swords
Step back
How did you reach here safely?
-We met brigands
Nothing happened?
-We won a horse
They appear often?
-More than often, sir. They ruin us
They steal our crops,
they steal our women
We're at their tender mercy
Many have left this village
for safety
Imagine. They won a horse!
Isn't it something?
Have you an axe to cut down trees?
Master.
Why fell trees?
Build a hut.
-What for, Master?
We'll live here.
And plough
What about fencing practice?
-We'll continue as we plough
Brace up!
Hurry up will you, girls?
They'll be angry
Hurry! They seem like rich people.
We'll get rich!
Rich - nothing!
The keeper'll become rich
We'll become thinner.
-The greedy pimp!
Hurry up!
You're free, Hanagiri?
-Let me breathe
We're short of one girl for
five customers. Hanagiri!
Keeper.
Do all your girls wear bells?
No, sir, she's the only one.
Tinkles around like a kitten
Hanagiri, you say?
Bring her. At once
You have a quick ear.
-Reminded of someone?
You win!
We'll stick to drinks then
So it's you
You laugh at me.
Don't you?
I'm not that heartless.
-I know you. Worse than that
I didn't even touch you.
-It was your vanity
Had I not loved him,
you'd have...
Probably.
Come here and pour us drinks
She cares for Musashi
Unrequited love.
See her now!
Stop!
I may be soiled
but my heart is pure
Is it?
I'll tell you where he is now
He ploughs at Hoten Field
in Shimosa
Care to go?
-No joking, sir
If she goes, I'll suffer a big loss.
-Keeper
Enough?
Just a farmer
A woman?
-What?
What a find!
Stop!
I saw her first. Didn't l?
A girl.
-Brigands again!
Why - Otsu!
Why - Jotaro!
More loot
Master!
-What, we eat now?
Big news! Otsu came!
-Otsu?
Lord Yagyu of Edo told her, she
says. How did he know about us?
Bring me something to wear
She's washing her face now
to make herself presentable
Will you hurry?
I missed you
I thought you were mad at me.
-But why?
I was to blame
It was sudden.
So...
You forgive me?
I won't leave you again!
That's the hut we built
We three live in it
And we have tilled those
patches of land
It was barren. But it is yielding
crops lately thanks to our labor
In the old days
I hated farm work
And was daydreaming always
Wanting to become famous
and successful
Vainly and at random
Now I'm tilling again.
Isn't it strange?
I'm beginning to learn
the value of life
The soil has taught me that
Jotaro
Cook something for Otsu.
I'll ask old Gen to house her
Are you very happy
to see him again?
He's still angry about me.
-What happened?
Listen, Jotaro.
-Master Jotaro
Yes, sir.
I don't understand him at all
Me, neither.
He's carving again
He told me he'd done
something bad to her
Can't be true! lf so,
why would she come here? -Yes
Who goes there?
I hate to leave this village.
I'll stick to it...
even if I may be killed
on that account
Please, sir, teach us how to fight
We must fight the brigands
away from here!
Please, Master!
It's no use teaching you
how to fight
If you must learn to run
Away from them, sir?
-And laugh last
You're going there by yourself?
-Yes. I have come alone so far
It's dangerous from here
The way to the next village
is infested with bandits
I've known bandits
since I was a baby
My father was a brigand, too
Isn't my lunch ready yet?
-It is
Better disguise yourself as a man
They'll stop any girl
Men have made a plaything of me.
I don't mind anything now
If I can see him,
I'll die content
One moment. Men come here regularly
to buy oil and salt
Wait till then and go with them.
-A good idea
That may be them
Give us drinks!
It's bad since those samurai came
I hear they're teaching them
fencing. -Who are they?
We've got to destroy them, anyway
This is too small.
Bring bigger bowls!
Keeper, that your daughter?
Hey, girlie!
Come here!
Why - you're Akemi!
You're Toji!
-Yes, I am
Know her?
-She's Oko's daughter.
What happened to my mother?
Where is she?
-I killed her
You were there when
she was killed!
You surrendered to save your skin!
-Shut up!
I avenged my brother's death.
-Avenged?
Your mother had killed him.
I'm Kohei
But you two had killed my father!
-You'll be with him
That's the village
Tell them the brigands were all
arrested by the officials
Understand?
And set Musashi's hut on fire
tomorrow evening
We'll attack then.
Right?
I can't. Never! No!
-Don't be a fool!
Musashi is his enemy.
Also mine
He spared you.
You must do it
If you won't...
I'll have to kill you
Don't. You're still sick
But I can't stay idle here.
-Stop!
Tell me.
Tell me what to do now
Must I leave?
-Well, no
Tell me then.
Why do you evade me?
You dislike me?
Hate me?
Have I been erased from your heart?
Please!
You're heartless! Stony-hearted!
I hate such a man! -But...
I can't live!
I wish I were dead!
-Don't be stupid
I am stupid!
Watch what a stupid girl does!
What are you doing?
So. She's here
This is because of her.
That dame!
I'm sorry. -Old Gen
can accommodate another person
Otsu won't like it.
Neither will Akemi
I think I'll go ask Aunt Oseki
I'll do that for you.
-Me, too
At last we're alone
Why don't you like it?
You have changed, Akemi
But I like your tone.
I'm so glad
Darling! I have loved you since
we lived in the hills
I really cared for you.
-You don't mean that
But I mean it. I tried to tell you
when you were trapped last time
I didn't understand you
Darling... elope with me
Won't you?
-Stop it
Oko, your mother, asked me to do
that once
Her blood is in your veins
No. I'm different.
I'm not like her at all
I never loved men
till I met you
I've never loved anybody
but you, darling
That's why I came here
I'm sorry
It's not your fault
You have Otsu.
I shouldn't be unreasonable
I will leave in the morning
Be happy with her.
Good luck
Darling.
It's hard!
But I give you up!
I promise
So hold me tightly before I go!
Choke me to death!
In your arms!
As your last favor!
Men!
I heard on my way here...
that all the brigands
were arrested. -Really?
The whole town's talking.
-If they're arrested, we are safe
Akemi said that?
-Serves 'em right. -Now we're saved
Akemi, are you sure about
the brigands?
Akemi! Is it true?
You wouldn't believe me
I'll stay here awhile.
I like it here
Master, did you hear it?
Very good news, eh?
Did you hear? -Yes, I did.
-Let's stop work and celebrate!
She'll signal to us with a fire.
Set houses afire!
You kill the villagers
Don't take on Musashi.
I'll handle him
Come with me.
We'll talk alone
Where's Otsu?
She's at my home.
-She'll play the flute
I'll fetch her
Otsu.
You know how a girl feels
I'm in love with him.
-Akemi
You are a terrible girl
Why must you come between us two?
Take it up
If you want him...
fight!
How horrible!
-Take it up
Help! Somebody!
Fire! Fire!
Brigands! Brigands!
Calm down! Quiet!
Take women and kids to Old Gen's.
Musashi! Come out!
Fight with me!
Musashi, I'm here to avenge
my brother's death!
Brace up, Kuma!
Jotaro... you're... truly my senior
Akemi!
Well done!
What are you doing?
Akemi! Brace up!
Otsu. I'm dying now
I've been so wicked.
-Oh, no!
You saved my life!
Don't die! Akemi!
Darling!
At last...
you hold me...
in your arms.
-Brace up, Akemi!
It's all over with me
I can't even...
see you
Be happy together, you two
Musashi!
Where is Master Musashi?
"l have been officially employed
as Lord Hosokawa's teacher...
and will leave for Kokura,
his Castle Town
I am desirous to have the match
at Kokura, April next."
My Master's so unreasonable
to leave you like this
After all,
he prefers fencing to me
Kokura Town, Lord Hosokawa's
country seat
"Our Lord's Retainer Kojiro Sasaki
will fight by command...
with Musashi Miyamoto of
Mimasaku Province."
Musashi.
In five days, eh?
Fight fair and square,
like a real samurai
He is a peerless match, sir.
I will not spoil your honorable name
In four days
He's busy.
But I am his childhood friend
An intimate friend
I was with him at the fencing school
He'll remember my name without fail
They ignored me while I was jobless
But today even strangers
want to see me
Such is life.
-But it's something for rejoicing
Your prowess will be acknowledged,
definitely
After the match,
another big event
My daughter is impatient
Please, Otsu!
Let me find my Master
Please.
Why have I come all this way?
In this match
he might meet the worst
If so, I'll gather his remains
So I must see him.
I must speak to him!
From Musashi, sir?
"l will arrive in my own boat
in time
I hope this is satisfactory"
I see.
He didn't come here out of respect
He'll go directly to the isle
But where is he?
Brace up, Otsu
What happened?
-She's sick
Omitsu
You look pensive
Think I'll lose?
-Oh, no
You may not expect it
but you're afraid
I'll win.
To defeat him has been my ambition
I'll defeat him with my own ability
Prayers of those who wish me victory
and talismans...
are useless to me
Therefore don't pray for me, dear
Sympathy harms my
mental tranquility
I want to fight alone
Return to the castle
Now I feel relieved
Hey, Sasuke. Is it ready?
-Sure
It's an honor for a boatman
to row for Master Musashi
The boat's been purified
Thank you for the kind gift
I wear now
I feel so refreshed.
-Good luck, sir
One moment. I want you to see
someone before you leave. -Me?
Don't bother to get up
Otsu!
I can't see him like this
Master!
Don't come in!
I'm coming!
Otsu.
-At last we meet again
You look weak. Very ill?
-I'm cured now
My illness is so whimsical, you know
Let's take a walk, shall we, Otsu?
This is the first time
you ever asked me
Let's. Of course
Until today
I've walked my own way...
and made you suffer a lot
Forgive me. But I'm not
as heartless as I may seem
I know.
-You do?
That's why I've loved you
Darling!
What a lucky day it is today!
I can fight with clear conscience now
Why do you cry?
I hate it
I wish you weren't a samurai!
Darling, abandon your sword.
Don't fight!
Let them call you a coward!
I crave for happiness, just us two!
That's impossible now, Otsu
Please! I won't let you go!
Oh no!
Don't be unreasonable
I'm a woman
I wish you had been an ordinary man
Otsu, don't demoralize me, please
A samurai's wife sends off
her man with a smile
Especially when it might be
for good
Is that the Island?
-No, sir, that's not it
Our island lies beyond that.
A smaller one
Is this where a sea-battle was
fought in olden times?
What is that for, sir?
For the duel
Fight with a wooden one?
-I like the size
Listen.
If I lose and fall...
take my dead body back...
to Otsu
-Dear God!
Don't talk rot!
-Take this as my memento
Musashi's boat is sighted!
Musashi is coming!
-Musashi has come!
Don't be nervous
You'll see the mysterious
power of my sword
Watch me
Musashi!
Mr. Miyamoto.
That was splendid
He was the best fencer
I will ever encounter
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad!
I was praying
so I wouldn't bring you back dead
I'm so glad about it all.
I'm so happy!
THE END