TOHO CO. LTD., JAPAN MCMLVI
SAMURAI III
DUEL AT GANRYU ISLAND
Produced by
KAZUO TAKIMURA
FROM HIDEJI HOJO'S ADAPTATION OF
THE NOVEL MUSASHI by EIJI YOSHIKAWA
Screenplay by TOKUHEI WAKAO
and HIROSHI INAGAKI
Cinematography
KAZUO YAMADA
Art Direction
HIROSHI UEDA and KISAKU ITO
Sound
MASANOBU MIYAZAKI
Lighting
TSURUZO NISHIKAWA
Music
IKUMA DAN
Cast
Musashi Miyamoto - TOSHIRO MIFUNE
Kojiro Sasaki - KOJI TSURUTA
Otsu - KAORU YACHIGUSA
Omitsu - MICHIKO SAGA
Akemi - MARIKO OKADA
Court Official - TAKASHI SHIMURA
Directed by
HIROSHI INAGAKI
"Drying Pole" my poor sword.
Your owner, a master swordsman,
is still unrecognized.
How long must he remain a ronin?
Will Kojiro Sasaki's dream
remain unattained?
Blind fools!
Poor swallow.
Not just anyone can do that.
The "swallow turn" swing.
I'll kill Musashi with it.
Why must you fight him?
It's my long cherished dream.
He's got nothing against you.
Why must you kill him?
Tell me!
You're a devil!
Why get excited about him?
Please. Forget him.
I won't mention him from now on.
So please.
Conceited girl!
I'm not after him because of you.
He's good.
He's my only match
in this country today.
My dream is to fight him.
He must dream of it too.
Akemi, stop!
I won't.
You scare me.
You horrify me.
You'll go looking for Musashi?
Go, then.
If you see him,
remind him that he is to duel
with Kojiro Sasaki.
He must not lose his life before then.
Musashi!
NARA
MARTIAL ARTS TOURNAMENT
BY THE HOZOIN TEMPLE PRIESTS
Who's next?
Come on!
You?
No, I pass.
- How about you?
- Maybe some other time.
If no one sallies forth,
I'll leave.
I'll call myself today's winner!
Any objections?
Speak up!
You may come in a group.
No one?
No contenders? Oh, well.
Let's go.
Damn monks!
What? Wait, kid!
I like your spirit.
You insulted me audaciously.
You challenged me. Let's go!
Fight with you?
You can't?
Then why did you say that?
He's only a child.
Forgive him.
- Who are you?
- His companion.
- You urged him?
- No, it was my own idea.
Then you'll fight with me.
You may attack me together,
if you wish.
- Please.
- I won't forgive him.
I apologize in his place.
No!
I was insulted publicly.
I won't swallow it.
Fool.
You're a prize fool, Agon.
Agon, stop it.
No!
Stop!
You're no match for him at all.
He's peerless.
Hasn't lost in 60 odd matches.
Stop it!
Musashi Miyamoto?
This is no fight.
The winner of the tournament
is Priest Agon here!
Priest Agon reminded me
of your old self.
- Yes.
- I marvel at your improvement.
Strength alone won't make
an accomplished swordsman.
He must be strong.
At the same time, he must be just.
I want to be able to fight
without regrets.
My past encounters
were full of them.
"One can only smile contentedly
after 10 years of pilgrimage."
Musashi, you still have much to learn.
I feel so pleased tonight.
Have you ever fallen in love?
I know a person
who's madly in love with you.
Do you want to meet this person?
Well...
So there's already
someone in your heart.
Don't worry.
The person I'm talking about is a man.
- A man who longs for a man?
- Yes, a man.
He wants to meet you
and he hasn't even seen you once.
Who is he?
Lord Yagyu.
What? The Lord Shogun's teacher?
Yes. Why don't you go to Edo
and see Yagyu?
You brought a letter
from Lord Karasumaru? I see.
So your name's Otsu.
Are you connected
with Musashi Miyamoto?
Yes, Your Grace.
I'm looking for him.
You're too late.
He was here until this morning.
- He was here?
- Yes, but he's left for Edo.
Stop.
Don't chase him.
I must see him.
I see, you care for him.
EDO
I am Okaya.
One moment.
Why cover the spearhead?
Don't worry about
hurting me, please.
But -
Take it off.
Note his assurance, my Lord.
Now that I have uncovered it,
use a sword yourself.
No, this will do.
- I won't fight like this.
- It's all right.
No, use your sword!
No.
I am only a masterless ronin.
If I use my sword,
it will offend His Lordship.
Full of confidence, sir.
Okaya, let him have his way.
He overdid it.
It's an embarrassment.
Was the audience successful?
Well -
I'm afraid not.
- Why? A man of your ability!
It's true.
My opponent was not very strong.
I should have been gentle.
- Did you win?
- I did.
True, he will live.
But as a cripple.
Nobody will hire a swordsman
who cripples his vassal.
I overdid it.
I like it.
You always mean business.
I feel I've done nothing wrong,
but people disagree.
What are you doing?
Still like me
after I tore your present?
I did the same thing today.
I will remain a ronin.
I like it.
I like your straightforward character.
Omitsu.
Elope with me.
I love you.
Please, no!
Don't you want freedom?
Don't you love me?
If you do, follow me.
I am leaving Edo.
Where are you going?
These young men of today!
Impertinent. Conceited.
Please.
You don't know how upset
he's been about today's match.
- Did he tell you that?
- No, Father.
Only I can sense it.
Okaya, is it very painful?
It is.
I was lucky
it wasn't a sword.
I'm very sorry, believe me.
I was just no match for you.
I'm only ashamed of myself,
but I won't blame you.
Did you get the job?
Take good care of yourself.
And I thought he was arrogant.
But he's fine.
I never knew it.
- Kojiro visited Okaya?
- Okaya told me so himself, sir.
What do you suggest?
If he really meant to console Okaya,
he must be quite a person.
I'm for employing him.
Who is better,
your Musashi or him?
Musashi is said to be
a peerless swordsman.
I must see Musashi.
Try to find him for me.
And Kojiro?
I'll think it over.
Watch it, idiot!
Hey, kid!
Your master's been
carving images for days.
Did he quit? Is he really a swordsman?
- None of your business!
Keeper, is this really an inn?
Master.
When will you see
the Shogun's teacher?
- I won't.
- Really?
Where's the letter
the monk gave you?
I threw it away.
You shouldn't have.
Lord Yagyu might've
recommended you to the Shogun.
You disgust me.
Why?
If you succeed in life, so will I.
Jotaro, is that why
you've followed me?
But why stay here then?
Waiting for her?
- Who?
- Otsu.
Fool!
I know you want to see her.
I'm positive.
- You are?
- Sure.
Look. This is her face.
Why? Please.
Why not?
No. Don't.
You mustn't.
Yes, I want to see her.
But she'll refuse to see me.
Why?
I did something shameful to her.
Fight! Fight!
It's four to one.
And he's winning!
I'm not finished yet!
What skill!
Where is he?
Samurai, he posted a declaration.
These four men are students
of the Obana Strategic School.
The one responsible for killing them
is Kojiro Sasaki of Isaragozaka.
I appreciate
your kind deed.
However, Miyamoto,
the bodies you brought
have nothing to do with my school.
But it's said that they drew
when he slandered you.
Please.
No student of mine
could be so weak.
You call me a meddler, then?
Miyamoto, this school
is an honorable school
that has served the Shogun.
My 100 students
are accomplished men.
I see.
Forgive my rudeness
for bringing the corpses.
Please, wait a minute.
Let me pass.
Master Obana told me
they could not be his men.
Do not be offended.
Please give them up to us.
I will not.
The dead men won't like it.
Fortunately, I know several sutras.
I'll bury them myself.
I learned a lesson today.
HERE LIE FOUR UNKNOWN SAMURAI
So it is you.
I thought it was one of them.
Thank you for your help last year.
You fought marvelously
at Ichijoji Temple.
I witnessed it.
I learned of your ability today
for the first time.
Those four.
One stroke each.
Duel me.
Kid. Go away for a while.
Be calm no matter what you see.
I've always wanted to meet you.
- Ready?
- Stop.
- Are you afraid?
- No, but today's not the day.
What?
Elsewhere.
If we fight here,
they may say I fought
for the Obana School,
which is not true.
Let us set a proper time
and fight freely.
You're right.
Tomorrow evening,
I'll be at the East Gate. Understood?
Very good.
You've been evading me.
Are you scared of me?
No.
However, I won't elope with you.
You think I'm joking?
You meant it.
You're a darling.
I meant it.
But I've changed my mind.
- Why?
- Tomorrow night you'll know.
I'll succeed or die.
You won't be seeing me either way.
If I win, I'll seek larger fortunes.
If I lose, I'll be dead.
In either case,
you'll always remember me
as your lover.
His Lordship.
- What was it?
- Well, he was delighted.
He wants to hire Kojiro
as his teacher.
That's wonderful.
Kojiro did something bold.
Where is he?
I'll bring him here.
- You've returned?
- I bring good news!
Come in.
My Master heard about you
and Obana's students.
Please.
They were just weaklings.
It brought me no credit.
However, their master
is the Lord Shogun's teacher.
Vengeance will be sought.
- I'll fight.
- Listen to me.
You are too full of youthful vigor.
"Such personal feuds must be stopped,"
my master said.
He suddenly decided to employ you.
Well? If you become
Lord Hosokawa's teacher,
they dare not attack you.
- I decline.
- What?
I dislike seeking protection.
Don't be silly.
If the Obana School challenges you,
you can fight
as Lord Hosokawa's teacher.
It's not like you to decline.
Another thing.
Chief Retainer Sado
is recommending Musashi.
Musashi?
He's being sought quietly.
We must decide this
before they find him.
Taking the initiative
is always advantageous.
Listen.
I duel with Musashi tomorrow.
What! With him?
So your worries are over.
This man's dreams are too grand.
Place your bets!
Game!
What noise!
Hey, be quiet!
Thanks.
They got quiet.
You're persuasive.
- Sure!
Excuse me.
Hey, ronin.
Stop eating.
Admit you're scared.
Don't pretend you're calm at heart.
Stop!
Who are you?
Don't know me?
Those who don't know me here,
must be deaf.
Speak loudly,
as I'm hard of hearing.
Who are you?
- Shut up!
I'm Kumagoro the horse-dealer,
a real tough guy.
And when I say tough,
I mean tough.
Horse-dealer, eh?
I deal with samurai.
I handle live horses, mind you.
So what?
You sent this kid to me
to tell me to be quiet, didn't you?
I have a big voice.
You don't own this inn, do you?
- So what?
- Apologize.
Write a letter of apology
addressed to us all.
Or I'll take you out in the yard
and wash your face with horse piss.
- Amusing.
- What?
Very interesting indeed.
Don't talk back to me!
Now answer me at once!
Depending on how you answer,
you could get this!
Let's see, what shall I do?
There are too many.
Wash these sticks.
He's terrific!
Training for revenge?
I'm his pupil now.
Musashi Miyamoto! No wonder!
- Are you out of your head?
- Of course not!
Horse-dealer.
Did you say Musashi?
Does he live here?
Now I fully understand you.
I will not force my ideas on you.
However, will you be good enough
to see my Master?
But I am to fight a duel tonight.
A duel?
It will be the most memorable fight
of my life.
Who's your man?
- Kojiro Sasaki.
- Sasaki?
- Is that true?
- Yes.
In fact, Sasaki has been referred
to my colleague Iwaoka
and is to meet my master
either today or tomorrow.
What? Kojiro?
Miyamoto, if you win,
do not fail to accept my offer.
Must you fight?
Hey, kid.
Where is Musashi?
I have decided
to leave on a journey.
Let me please postpone
the promised match for a year.
When we meet again,
I will be quite ready to vie with you.
Musashi Miyamoto.
Why do you cry?
I don't like it.
That Kojiro
as Hosokawa's teacher!
I dreamt of worldly success once.
I thought it was natural
to settle down.
But now I want
to train myself further.
Jotaro.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat, shall we?
- Kuma.
- What?
I was here before you, wasn't I?
Yes, that's right.
Call me Master Jotaro.
I say, Master Jotaro.
What is it?
A man should be kind
to those who follow him.
It's time for lunch, isn't it?
Get down!
- Drop the reins.
- Or we'll shoot.
Surrender your swords.
Step back.
How did you make it here safely?
- We met bandits.
- Nothing happened?
We won a horse.
Do they appear often?
More than often, sir.
They're ruining us.
They steal our crops,
they steal our women.
We're completely at their mercy.
Many have left the village
for safety.
Imagine.
They won a horse!
Isn't that something?
Do you have an ax
to cut down trees?
Master.
Why are we felling trees?
To build a hut.
What for, Master?
- We'll live here.
- Here?
And plow.
What about training
for sword fighting?
As we plow, we will learn
the way of the sword.
Let's get to it.
Welcome!
Hurry up, will you, girls?
They'll be angry. Hurry!
They seem like rich people.
We'll get rich!
Hurry, hurry.
Oh, really?
The keeper will get rich.
And we'll get thinner.
The greedy pimp!
Hurry up!
Hanagiri, are you free?
Let me have a moment.
We're short one girl
for five customers. Hanagiri!
Keeper.
Do all your girls wear bells?
No, sir, she's the only one.
Jingles around like a kitten.
Hanagiri, you say?
Bring her at once.
You have a sharp ear.
Reminded of someone?
You win.
We'll stick to drinks then.
She's here. Come in.
Hanagiri.
So it is you.
You're mocking me, aren't you?
I'm not that heartless.
I know you.
You're worse than that.
I didn't even touch you.
Because of your vanity.
Had I not loved him,
you would have.
Probably.
Come here and serve us drinks.
This girl cares deeply for Musashi.
Unrequited love.
See her now.
Stop!
I may be soiled,
but my heart is pure.
Is it?
I'll tell you where he is now.
He plows at Hoten Field
in Shimosa.
Care to go?
Please don't kid around, sir.
If she leaves, I'll suffer a big loss.
Keeper.
Is this enough?
Just a farmer.
- A woman?
- What?
Stop!
What a find!
I saw her first, didn't I?
Somebody, help!
A girl.
Damn, it's those bandits again.
Let's go!
Help!
Why, Otsu!
Why, Jotaro!
More loot.
Master!
- What, is it time to eat?
- Big news! Otsu came!
Otsu?
Lord Yagyu of Edo told her,
she says.
They already know that you live here.
Bring me something to wear.
She's washing her face now
to make herself presentable.
Will you hurry?
I missed you.
I thought you were mad at me.
But why?
I was to blame.
It was sudden, so -
You forgive me?
I won't leave you again.
That's the hut we built.
We three live in it.
And we've tilled those patches of land.
It was barren.
But it's yielding crops lately
thanks to our labor.
In the old days,
I used to hate farm work.
I was always daydreaming,
longing for victory and renown.
I could think of nothing else.
Now I'm tilling the fields again.
Isn't it strange?
I'm beginning to learn
the value of life.
The soil has taught me that.
Jotaro.
Cook something for Otsu.
I'll ask Old Gen to house her.
Otsu, aren't you happy
to see him again?
He's still upset with me.
What happened?
- Listen, Jotaro.
- Master Jotaro.
Yes, sir.
I don't understand him at all.
Me neither.
He's started carving again.
He told me he'd done
something bad to her.
It can't be true.
If that were so,
why would she come here?
You're right.
Who goes there?
I hate to leave the village.
I'll stick by it,
even if I may be killed
on account of it.
Please, sir,
teach us how to fight.
We must drive the bandits
away from here!
Please, Master!
It's no use teaching you
how to fight.
You must learn to run.
Run away from them, sir?
Lose today, win tomorrow.
You're going there by yourself?
Yes. I made it here alone.
But It's dangerous from here on.
The way to the next village
is infested with bandits.
I've been around bandits
since I was a child.
My father was a bandit, too.
Isn't my lunch ready yet?
It is.
It's best you disguise yourself as a man.
They'll stop any girl.
Men have already
made a plaything of me.
I don't mind anything now.
If I can see him,
I'll die content.
One moment.
Men come here regularly
to buy oil and salt.
Wait till then
and go with them.
A good idea.
That may be them.
Give us drinks!
It's been bad since
those ronin got here.
I hear they're teaching them
how to wield a sword.
Who are they?
We've got to
destroy them, anyway.
This is too small.
Bring bigger bowls!
Keeper.
That your daughter?
No.
Hey, girlie! Come here!
What are you doing?
Why, it's Akemi.
Toji.
Yes, it's me.
Know her?
She's Oko's daughter.
I see.
What happened to my mother?
Where is she?
I killed her.
Toji, you were there
when she was killed!
You joined up with them
to save your own skin!
Shut up!
I was avenging my brother's death.
- Your brother?
Your mother and a man
killed my brother, Temma Tsujikaze.
I'm Kohei Tsujikaze
- What are you talking about?
It was the two of you
who killed my father!
I'll do the same to you.
There. That's the village.
Tell them the bandits
were all arrested by the officials.
Understand?
And tomorrow evening,
you set fire to Musashi's hut.
That's when we'll attack. Got it?
That's horrible.
I can't do it.
Don't be a fool!
Musashi is Kohei's enemy.
He's mine as well.
Kohei spared your life.
You must do it.
If you don't,
I'll have to kill you.
Don't. You're still sick.
But I can't stay idle here.
Stop!
Tell me.
Tell me what to do now.
Must I leave?
Well, no.
Tell me then.
Why do you evade me?
Do you dislike me?
Do you hate me?
Have I been erased
from your heart?
Please!
You're hard-hearted, unfeeling.
I hate it!
But -
I can't go on living!
I wish I were dead!
Don't be foolish.
I am foolish!
Watch what a foolish girl does!
Stop!
What are you doing?
So, she's here.
This is because of her.
That dame!
I'm sorry.
Old Gen can accommodate
another person.
Otsu won't like it.
Neither will Akemi.
I think I'll go ask Aunt Oseki.
- I'll do that for you.
- Me, too.
At last we're alone.
Why don't you like it?
You've changed, Akemi.
You do remember me.
I'm so glad.
Takezo, I've loved you
since we lived in the hills.
I really cared for you.
You don't mean that.
But I do mean it.
That's what I tried to tell you
when you were trapped at Ichijoji.
I didn't understand then.
Takezo, let's go away together.
Won't you?
- Stop it.
Oko, your mother,
asked me to do that once.
Her blood runs in your veins.
No, I'm not like her.
Not at all.
I never loved a man
till I met you.
I've never loved anyone but you.
That's why I came here.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
You have Otsu.
I shouldn't be unreasonable.
I will leave in the morning.
Be happy with her.
Take care.
Takezo.
It's so hard.
But I'll give you up.
I promise.
Just hold me tightly before I go.
Crush me to death in your arms.
That's all I ask, then I'll give up.
Men!
I heard on my way here that
all the bandits were arrested.
- Really?
- Yes.
The whole town's talking.
If they've been arrested,
we're safe.
Now we can finally relax.
Akemi said that?
- Serves 'em right.
- Now we're saved.
Akemi, are you sure
about the bandits?
Akemi!
Is it true?
You wouldn't believe me.
I'll stay here for a while.
I like it here.
Master, did you hear it?
Very good news, eh?
Old Gen, did you hear?
Yes, I did.
Let's stop work and celebrate!
When the sun rises, let's work
When the sun sets, let's relax
Heave-ho, hey, hey
Let's dig a well and drink the water
Plow a field and eat the crops
Heave-ho, hey, hey
Not even birds would visit our village
But we live here and it's our heaven
Heave-ho, hey, hey
For a thousand years and forever
May our rice fields give us food
She'll signal to us with a fire.
You set the houses on fire!
You kill the villagers.
Don't take on Musashi.
I'll handle him.
You and I need to talk, and alone.
Let's have a drink.
Where's Otsu?
- She's at my house.
- She can play the flute.
Good idea.
I'll fetch her.
Otsu.
You're a woman, too.
You should know
what a woman feels.
I'm in love with him.
Akemi.
You're terrible.
Why must you come
between the two of us?
Otsu.
Take it up.
If you want him, fight!
How horrible!
Take it up.
Here I come!
Help! Somebody!
Fire!
Go!
Bring water!
Bandits! Bandits!
Calm down! Quiet!
Take the women and children
to Old Gen's.
Musashi Miyamoto!
Come out!
Fight me!
Musashi! I'm here to avenge
my brother's death!
Run!
Bastards!
Kuma!
Bastard!
Damn kid!
Hold on, Kuma.
Jotaro, you're...
truly my master.
Akemi!
Well done!
What are you doing?
Akemi! Hold on!
Otsu.
I'm dying now.
I've been so wicked.
Oh, no!
You saved my life.
Don't die, Akemi.
Akemi.
Takezo.
At last
you hold me in your arms.
Hold on, Akemi.
It's all over for me.
I can't even see you.
Be happy together,
you two.
Musashi!
Where is Master Musashi?
I have been officially engaged
as Lord Hosokawa's teacher
and will leave for Kokura,
his Castle Town.
I am desirous to have our match
at Kokura, April next.
My Master's so unreasonable
to leave you like this.
After all, his heart has chosen
the way of the sword.
KOKURA TOWN
"By permission of Our Lord,
Retainer Kojiro Sasaki will duel
with Musashi Miyamoto
of Mimasaku Province."
Musashi.
In five days, eh?
Fight fair and square,
like a true samurai.
He is a peerless match, sir.
I will not spoil
your honorable name.
In four days.
I can hardly wait.
He's busy.
But I'm his childhood friend.
An intimate friend.
I was with him
at the school of Master Ito.
I'm Ichinomiya from Yamazaki Dojo.
He'll know who I am.
Please, calm down!
They ignored me
while I was a ronin.
But today even strangers
want to meet me.
Such is life.
But that's something to rejoice over.
Your prowess will be
acknowledged, definitely.
And after the match,
another big event.
Another big event?
My daughter is impatient.
Don't go, Otsu!
Let me find my Master.
Please.
Why have I come all this way?
In this match
he might meet the worst fate.
If so, I'll gather his remains.
So I must see him.
I must speak to him!
All right.
Out of the way!
From Musashi, sir?
"I will arrive in my own boat
at the appointed hour.
I hope this is satisfactory."
I see.
He stayed away from here
out of respect.
He'll go directly to the island.
But at what inn is he staying?
Hold on, Otsu.
What's wrong?
Help!
- What happened?
- She's sick.
Sick? Come this way.
Omitsu.
You look pensive.
Concerned I'll be defeated?
- Oh, no.
You may not expect it to happen,
but you're still worried.
I'll defeat Musashi.
That has long been my ambition.
I'll defeat him
through my own ability.
The prayers of those
who wish me victory and talismans
are useless to me.
Therefore, do not pray for me.
Affection and attachments
disturb my inner tranquillity.
I want to fight alone.
Return to the castle.
Now I feel relieved.
- Hey, Sasuke. Is it ready?
- Sure.
It's an honor for a boatman
to row for Master Musashi.
The boat's been purified.
Good.
He's ready to depart.
Thank you for the kind gift
I wear now.
I feel so refreshed.
Good luck, sir.
One moment.
I want you to see someone
before you leave.
Me?
Don't bother to get up.
Otsu!
I can't see him like this.
Master!
Don't come in!
I'm coming!
Otsu.
At last we meet again.
You look weak. Are you very ill?
I'm cured now.
My illness is so whimsical,
you know.
Otsu, let's take a walk,
shall we?
This is the first time
you ever asked me.
Of course I'll go with you.
Until today
I've walked my own way
and made you suffer a lot.
Forgive me.
But I'm not as heartless
as I may seem.
- I know.
- You do?
That's why I've loved you.
Otsu!
What an auspicious day.
I can fight
with a clear conscience now.
Why do you cry?
I hate samurai.
I wish you were still the Takezo
who I used to know.
Musashi, abandon your sword.
Don't fight!
Let them call you a coward!
I long for happiness,
just us two together.
Otsu.
That's impossible now.
Please!
I won't let you go.
I won't.
Don't be unreasonable.
I'm a woman.
I wish you had been
an ordinary man.
Otsu, don't demoralize me, please.
A samurai's wife sends off
her man with a smile.
Especially when it might be
for the last time.
Of course.
Is that Funa Island?
No, sir, that's Hiko Island.
Funa Island lies beyond that.
It's a smaller one.
Isn't this where a sea battle
was fought in olden times?
Yes.
What's that for, sir?
For the duel.
You'll fight with a wooden one?
I like the size.
Listen.
If I lose and fall,
take my dead body back
to Otsu.
Dear God. Don't say that.
Take this as a memento of me.
Musashi's boat is sighted!
- Musashi is coming!
- Musashi has come!
Don't be nervous.
You'll see the mysterious
power of my sword.
Watch me.
Musashi!
Mr. Miyamoto.
That was splendid.
He was the best swordsman
I will ever encounter.
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad!
I was praying I wouldn't bring
Master Musashi back dead.
I'm so glad about it all.
I'm so happy!
THE END