It all started out so nice.
A bunch of kids going
to a cabin in the mountains.
Drinking, laughing,
having fun.
And then a horde of
Nazi zom bies shows up.
I know.
Sounds like a cliche,
but that's what happened.
You see, we found something...
something we shouldn't have.
Old Nazi gold.
And then...
all hell broke loose.
They took us out...
one...
...by one.
One of them bit me,
but I knew how to fix that.
And my girlfriend,
Hanna.
She...
She didn't make it.
I found the gold...
gave it back...
and I was free to go.
I was safe.
Turns out...
I was wrong.
Take your fucking coin!
Crawl back to the hell
you came from! Huh?
Shit, Shit, Shit, Shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit...
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Fuck.
I told them not to touch that shrine.
Radio.
Always something good on the radio.
The Arctic Tern is a sea bird
of the Tern family Sternidae.
The species is strongly migratory,
seeing two summers each year,
as it migrates from
its northern breeding grounds
seeing two summers each year,
as it migrates from
its northern breeding grounds
along a winding route
to the oceans
around Antarctica and back,
a round trip of about 70,000...
The Tern flies as well as glides...
Troops...
Sieg Heil!
- Doctor?
- Yes.
Oh, good.
Let's see what we got here.
Martin, can you hear me?
Martin, are you there?
Welcome back.
Martin, you crashed your car.
Badly.
You're lucky to be alive.
More than you can say about your friends.
Did you see them?
The things?
The creatures?
Did the police take them?
Or the Army?
Erlend?
Roy?
Hanna?
We found your friends. All of them.
Dead.
Hanna, is that your girlfriend?
We found her too,
with an ax jammed into her throat.
With your fingerprints all over it.
Any idea how that happened?
The things...
They came up... came from up...
from the snow.
Nazis. I had an ax, and I...
So little Nazi creatures
came up from the earth?
Are you certain he didn't
suffer any brain damage?
Okay, call his family,
tell them he's awake,
and get the DA, tell him to send a car
and four extra guys, out of here.
They will kill again if we don't stop...
Martin, Martin, Martin, Martin.
Calm down. I've seen what you've done.
I was there.
The only place you're going is jail.
Nobody knows exactly
what happened up there.
Only you do.
Besides, it's not only bad news.
When we found you, you were hurt.
Your right arm was ripped off by the elbow.
- Yeah, I...
- It was cold when we found you.
The snow kept you cool, which was good.
You understand?
And so, we found your arm in the car.
Yeah, it was a bit bruised and pale,
but the operation was a success.
We managed to put your arm right back on.
Huh?
What have you done?
Please calm down, my friend.
Martin, please...
This is Satan's arm!
Martin, calm down, please.
Hey, hey!
I'm so... It is not me!
It's not... I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! Stop it!
Emma?
I think you have to remove
your teeth tonight,
'cause I'm in the mood for some head.
From the one that got away.
The ground.
Warm.
The men...
have rotted.
We need more people.
Ah, Jesus!
You scared me, Nils.
I'm telling you, I'm not
in the mood for this.
I had a long day today.
Two funerals and two weddings.
And one of the girls getting married
today she was so fucking hot.
What I wouldn't give
to be 15 years younger,
and, yeah, not a priest, of course.
Nils?
Sieg...
Heil.
Sieg Heil, Sieg Heil,
Sieg Heil,
Sieg Heil, Sieg Heil...
They're down from the mountain.
They're gonna kill us all.
Fuck!
Hey!
They're down from the mountain!
Get me the fuck out of here!
Get me out!
They're coming!
They're gonna kill us all!
Psst! Hey! Hey, you.
Psst! Yeah, you.
Hello.
I saw your arm. Looks really cool.
Took some pictures, too.
Looks sick, but still cool.
I'm not supposed to be in here, but...
I snuck in here like a ninja.
- Ninja?
- Yeah.
Oh, I'm Bobby.
I'm here on vacation with my mom.
She ate some bad fish
yesterday, so, yeah...
Hmm. Cool. Seriously cool.
It looks burned and old,
like a zombie arm.
Zombies are cool.
Zombies?
Sorry, gotta take this.
They're wondering if I
can get some more info.
More than just a picture of the arm.
Who? What?
The Zombie Squad.
They're wondering if I
can get some more info.
They're experts on zombies.
They live in America.
They've trained for this for years,
just waiting for a
zombie outbreak to happen.
So they can come here?
Just tell them to come here
right now to get the zombies!
If they're experts,
they can kill the zombies for us.
- I know. You've seen the zombies?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause they're real, right?
- Can you help me get loose?
I'm not sure if I should. I mean, you're...
- I have chocolate.
- You do?
- Yeah.
- Nice.
Yeah, I have chocolate.
'Cause I could get it for you,
but, you know...
- Yeah.
- So...
- Double-triple fudge.
- Oh, my God!
Yeah.
Let me get this right here...
Come, come, come! You can do it.
Come on. Yeah.
Help me with the other.
- Can I have my chocolate now?
- There's no chocolate, kid.
- No chocolate?
- Shut the fuck up!
What?
I gotta get out.
What are you...
Hey!
It's not what it looks like.
Stop!
Hello?
This is Daniel Heffernan,
leader of the Zombie Squad.
Can I please speak to Bobby?
Bobby, uh...
Bobby, uh.
I don't speak the language of Thor.
- Is Bobby there?
- Bobby was killed by zombies.
My God!
Is this the Zombie Squad?
That is a 10-4, Martin.
We will be heading your way shortly.
Before we go, we need as much
information as you can give us.
Anything you have.
Well...
We came up to the cabin
and there was a bunch of...
Nazi zombies there, and...
You know, they killed us all, and...
Except me. Yeah, and...
I sawed my arm off, but it's...
Yeah, the arm is... And...
I think they wanted treasure,
or a coin, and...
Were any of you bitten?
We were all bitten.
But we didn't become
one of them, we just...
We just died, so...
Listen Martin. And listen good.
These are not your classic,
textbook zombies
just hungering to feast
on the flesh of man.
No, these are most likely
cursed zombies,
awakened to reclaim something
that was stolen from them,
or to complete a task given to them.
They called him Herzog. They...
They called him Herzog.
Martin of the North,
we will be on our way shortly.
And we will take care of this infection.
We are professionals. But until then,
find out what they seek, their purpose.
Bye.
Zombie Squad.
Zombie Squad is coming. They'll be...
They're professionals.
Okay, girls.
Looks like we're going to Norway.
Norway?
We can't go to Norway.
That's on the other side of the world!
Yeah, and how do we know it's for real?
Daniel, that's a long way to go
to find out if it's a hoax.
You guys saw the picture.
This is a bona fide infected arm.
You know this. This is...
All the signs are there, guys.
The decayed skin, the rotten hair,
the dark blood.
This is real, guys. It's real.
This could be dangerous!
No shit. It's fucking zombies!
Of course it'll be dangerous!
But this is what we've been waiting for.
This is our chance to prove
to everyone that we were right.
We've been telling everyone for years
that it's just a matter of time
before the first outbreak happens.
And what have we seen in return?
Laughter.
Ridicule.
Wedgies.
Well...
Guess who was right?
Guess who's laughing now?
- I guess we're laughing now.
- You're damn right, we are!
What did we start the Zombie Squad
for if it wasn't for this?
- He's right.
- Damn right, I'm right.
Besides, if we don't do this,
if we don't go there and help these people,
who the hell will?
Yeah.
- So what do we do?
- Yes!
Okay. We need as much information
as we can get on this Herzog character,
on Martin, the north of Norway, everything.
Oh, wait, hold on!
Guys, we can't let our
landlords know about this.
- You mean our parents?
- Yes, our parents, but...
- We just can't tell them what's happening.
- Got it.
All right. Official members
of the Zombie Squad USA...
Oh, my God!
It's time to go hunting.
That was farther than usual!
I poured you a coffee.
- Hell, this is cold!
- Because you're 40 minutes late.
I'm still on wintertime.
The winter time, summer time system...
is stupid.
What do you got?
Not much. Petra's son
been at it again, shoplifting.
Just do what they do in Iran.
Cut his hands off.
That will teach him.
And Jack's dog is on the loose again.
He pooped in Mr. Olsen's yard.
- Shoot him.
- Shoot Mr. Olsen?
Not Mr. Olsen. The dog!
Otherwise, we have
the lecture at the school
about the dangers of smoking marijuana.
Oh. Boring!
Oh, there was one other thing.
From Oxfjord.
Oxfjord? No, no, no, no, no.
That's not our jurisdiction.
Martin Hykkerud,
escaped from the hospital...
Whoa, wait.
Martin Hykkerud?
Is that the same Martin Hykkerud that
killed his friends up in the mountains?
He escaped from the hospital yesterday,
killed a kid and a policeman by, um...
throwing a Mercedes star into his face.
- He cut off a Mercedes star?
- Yeah.
- What does Oslo say?
- About the Mercedes star?
Not the Merced... The Hykkerud case!
They said to stay alert,
get in extra people,
and keep it tight
until they send a team up.
Ah, "extra people." Hmm.
Do we have the money? No, we don't.
I don't even have money
to buy new batteries to the car.
Okay. Okay.
- Uh...
- What?
Didn't we agree to be more
casual around here?
Okay, go.
My God!
I was expecting something
like the Hoth-systems,
but this is more like Endor.
Monica, can you reference anything
other than Star Wars?
What, like Star Trek?
Maybe if I can't sleep.
Yeah, at least it's based on
scientific theories
- and a dog isn't running a starship.
- Guys, guys! I have a lock on Martin.
- Oh.
- Where is he?
Ice Bay.
- Ooh. Okay, let's go! Come on!
- Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
First, there's something we need to do.
Oh, yeah, I really have to pee.
- No, guys!
- I'm hungry.
- Arm up.
- Oh.
- You really fuckin' ruined that.
- Yeah.
It would be a lot easier
if you could buy weapons here.
I know. What the fuck's
the matter with this country?
Can I help you?
No, I'm sorry.
Just, uh... Just...
Back away, please.
I like you. Like you.
This is a war museum, right?
Yeah.
Do you have information on the Germans?
Help! Help me!
Listen to me! Listen!
Please don't hurt me, I have two kittens.
Help me! Help!
Shut... Shut up!
Do you have any information on "Einsatz"?
Yeah. Second floor.
Show me.
Where are you?
Fuck.
- What are you looking for?
- Herzog.
Best buddies with Hitler.
Isn't that cute?
You're not supposed to touch the display.
Herzog was made commander
of Einsatz in 1942
and sent to the far north of Norway
in order to protect the warships that
the German Navy was hiding in the fjords.
He was on duty in Oxfjord
doing a routine inspection
on the ship Scharnolsht, when...
Scharnholst.
...when Tirpitz,
the German fleet's biggest warship,
was attacked...
by English bombers in Talvik,
after getting vital information
on the ship's location
from Norwegian spies.
Hitler, humiliated by
the attack on Tirpitz,
ordered Herzog to wipe out
all of the 800 men and people
who lived in Talvik at the time.
So, he was on his way...
to Talvik...
that night when and his men
were butchered down in Oxfjord?
On a mission given
to them by Hitler, himself.
Yeah.
A mission that was never accomplished.
He's going to destroy Talvik.
He came from Oxfjord.
Here.
Going to Talvik.
Talvik is here.
Where are we?
Where are we?!
We're here.
Ice Bay.
That means...
That's just in-between.
They're recruiting.
They're recruiting new zombies.
They can do that too, now?
- They're coming here.
- I don't want to die.
I don't want to die here in a museum!
With you!
You're gonna die.
But not today.
Jesus.
Let's see what this thing can do.
What thing?
What you do...? How did you do that?
You just... killing all of them...
You didn't even break a sweat? Jesus.
It's the arm.
Somehow, I'm controlling it.
It reacts to what I'm thinking.
What arm? What are you talking about?
It's Satan's arm.
It's a long story.
He's building an army.
It's growing in numbers.
There'll be too many.
Even with the arm, I can't...
All this death.
- You...
- He...
- You did that!
- He was...
You did what the bastard did earlier.
I...
It's the arm.
He's not attacking.
Did you see that?
Did you see that? I hit it!
I hit it! Oh, my God, I did it,
I fucking did it!
I hit it right in the eye!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Take a picture, please.
Take of picture of me.
First Zombie Squad kill.
One, two...
Cheese.
Did you get it?
Oh. We spoke on the phone.
I'm Daniel, this is Blake and Monica.
- Hi.
- We are the Zombie Squad.
- Goddammit.
- They're real.
These are real dead people.
And that's a real zombie. You killed him.
I can't believe it.
Can we just focus for one second, guys?
I'm so sorry. We are more
professional than this.
- You're the Zombie Squad?
- Yup.
- Yeah.
- You're the Zombie Squad.
Yeah, we are the Zombie Squad.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I was...
just expecting something different.
So was this guy when he
woke up this morning!
Because I hit him in the face with an ax.
Yeah. How did you find me?
We tracked your iPhone, of course.
We're fuckin' nerds.
This is what we do. Technical shit.
Let's cut the chitchat.
What did you find out?
What do the creatures want?
Revenge.
This is insane!
You?
You have the gift?
The force is strong with this one.
Okay...
Martin, this is how we defeat them.
This is how we take them down.
What do you mean?
I mean...
We create an army of our own.
I tried to get as much information
as I could on the trip over.
Especially about Herzog.
To defeat your enemy,
you must know your enemy.
This is Lieutenant Stavarin
of the Soviet Army.
He and his battalion were captured
during the battle of Kursk,
And brought here to
the north of Norway as POWS.
In '44, they were all
sent to Kven Mountain
to build a road through
the mountain pass,
but it was after they built
the road that shit got ugly.
All of the prisoners were shot.
Shot to death!
No survivors.
And the man in charge?
Herzog.
Those bodies are still buried there.
Buried in the frozen soil.
Preserved. Waiting.
Waiting for what?
For the same thing that drives Herzog.
Revenge!
And guess who's gonna give it to them?
The man who can raise the dead?
Kafucking...
You guys go after Herzog,
try and slow him down.
Give us as much time as possible, okay?
What if this doesn't work?
It has to. All we have
to do is get to Kven mountain,
find Stavarin, wake him back from the dead,
then bring him back to Talvik
so he can help us fight Herzog and his men.
Easy.
Besides...
We got help.
Here we go.
He is our last hope.
Look! A tank!
Visitors, now?
That's early.
Hello?
Look. His army is growing bigger.
Glenn, are there any more towns or
villages before he reaches Talvik?
Maybe a few houses, but that's it.
Good. So what he has now
he'll use for his attack.
Yeah, pretty much, that is, until he starts
killing the people of Talvik,
making them join him as well.
How many people live in Talvik?
- About 3,000.
- What? Holy shit!
All the more reason for us to
slow him down as much as we can.
Look. Do you know how to use
one of those things?
Of course. I'm from
Northern Norway, aren't I?
I don't know what that means.
Okay, guys, pack light.
We're moving out. Now!
What in the name of God
has happened here?
What does the forensic team say?
That's not the forensic team.
That's just Tom and Ole.
They put on white suits today.
They thought it looked more professional.
Nice.
The real forensic team
is gonna be here this evening.
Do we have any witnesses?
Not unless you can get the seagulls
to talk. Doesn't look good.
Seagulls, yeah, well.
That's an amazing invention, isn't it?
You know, the guy, the person who
can come up with a thingy
that could translate seagull
language into human language.
The guy who come up with that thing,
he would make a fortune, you know.
Okay, let's get these bodies up to Talvik,
before the Seagulls eat them,
and let us take lots of photos,
or else the creepers will have my balls.
Hey, boss, here's a picture
from the surveillance camera.
Isn't that...?
Would you eat my little man-pussy?
Okay!
All right, all right, all right. Let's move.
Let's move! Come on, hurry up.
Listen up, we gotta hurry. Move out!
- There they are.
- And they have a tank, I see.
Yeah, they stole it from the museum.
Ah, fuck!
What is that?
A large-ass tank and 40 or 50 zombies.
No, no, no, no.
- That. What is that?
- Oh.
These are replicas of the binoculars
that Han and Chewie used
on the planet Hoth.
Did you guys know... Fun fact...
- All of the Hoth scenes were...
- Shh!
...filmed here in Norway.
This place called Finse.
Girls, can we please maybe focus on,
you know, the Nazi zombies instead?
What do we do?
Well, Daniel told us to slow them down,
so that's what we're gonna do.
Look.
We need to get out there,
get their attention
and lure them into the swamps, right?
And then, when they get stuck,
we can use the fertilizer bombs we made
and blow them into bits and pieces.
That sounds basically impossible.
And how are you planning on
luring them out there?
We need... we need bait. Live bait.
Yes, we need someone
to attract their attention.
Someone who is light on their feet,
who knows these swamps, and can move
through them without getting stuck.
What?
No.
No. That's a swamp.
I'm not getting out there!
Who says I won't get stuck?
And one more thing,
Those things are fucking zombies
who want to rip my face off!
Hey, Talvik is your hometown, am I right?
Yeah.
You must have people you love there.
Yeah. Especially one ma...
...woman that I love.
With long hair and big breasts.
Do it for...
"her".
You just bring them here,
and we'll do the rest.
Capisce?
Hey, man.
Martin?
Yeah?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
First we wake up
a battalion of Nazi zombies,
And now I'm supposed to...
wake up a bunch of dead Russian guys.
Martin, look, your arm, your power,
is the only thing that can
take down Herzog at this point.
Remember that. If we don't succeed,
his power will keep growing
until he's unstoppable.
That, my friend, is a big bowl of shit
that we don't want to live in.
Oh!
Oh, my God. That's... That's...
That is vile-smelling.
How did it fill up the car
so fast? That smell...
No, it's all right.
He's just carsick, or something.
That smells foul!
No, no, no, no!
Fuck! That's disgusting!
That smells!
I didn't know there was supposed to be
an "ugly face" convention in town.
Well, come get me, then.
Come get me.
Come get me, if you dare!
Go!
Halt!
- It's working. They're following him!
- But not Herzog, and most of his men. Shit.
No, no, no. It's okay.
We've got their attention.
If we take these guys out,
he'll come for us himself.
Come on, Glenn!
- Run faster!
- Faster!
Yes!
- Come on, Glenn!
- Go, go, go, go!
- Yes. yes!
- Yes.
- Run, Glenn!
- Faster!
Run, run!
Please, God...
- Yes!
Oh, my God, Blake!
- USA! USA!
- USA!
- Yeah!
Shot!
- Hey.
- Hey!
That tank is moving.
That can't be good.
- Run!
Talvik. Now.
Hey.
- Where are we?
- We're getting close.
But we're also stuck.
Can I push it?
I don't think that would help.
Is it far? We could walk.
We don't have that kind of time.
If only we could find something
to put under the car.
You know, something that
would give us traction.
Then I could get us out of here.
Oh, there she is.
It was a bloody nightmare trying to
find space for all the bodies.
I mean, the fridge is completely full,
so we just had to put all the rest
of them on the garage floor
and throw a shitload of ice cubes on top.
That sounds like a perfect solution.
Thanks.
Ah, you know,
mostly Germans, French people.
Don't think they pictured this
when they ordered a trip to Norway.
No, getting their heads and arms hacked off
and their intestines ripped out?
- Doubt it.
- Well, unless they're into that kinky shit.
Should you be doing that?
Where's the, you know...
the special force?
It was really windy down in Alta,
so the plane couldn't land,
but they should be here tomorrow afternoon.
That's perfect.
What?
Yeah. This is our chance.
We're gonna show people
what we're really made of, here.
What are you talking about?
We are gonna find
Martin Hykkerud ourselves.
We're gonna bring him in.
We're gonna be heroes,
not those fancy, dressed-up,
stuck-up, sushi-eating
dickweeds from the south.
Beef the boys...
Brief the boys.
Send a picture out to every cop
and citizen in Talvik.
If he so much as stops to make a piss,
I want to know both color
and scent of that urine.
Color and scent.
Get the shotguns ready.
We're gonna shoot something else
than seagulls for a change.
Do you really think this is going to work?
I mean, say we actually manage to wake
these Russians back to life...
What's stopping them from killing us?
I don't know what's gonna happen.
But judging based on him...
He treats you like you're his master.
So, hopefully they do the same.
Hopefully.
Hope... Look, what...
I don't know, man.
This is some unprecedented, unheard of,
mysterious, voodoo-zombie shit, man.
I've never seen this before.
I've seen a thousand zombie movies,
and this is not in any of them.
You've created a whole
new genre here, man.
Look, I mean, if we're gonna go up against
a battalion of Nazi zombies,
we could do a whole lot worse
than teaming up
with a battalion of Russian zombies.
He has to die, you know.
Herzog.
For what he did.
We have to kill him.
I have to kill him.
For Hanna.
This is it.
Yeah.
This is definitely it.
Herzog killed Stavarin
and 50 of his men here.
So they've gotta be buried...
in this frozen ground.
How do we do this?
You do it just like you did with him.
I put my hand on his head.
Okay. Right?
Yeah?
We can't dig up everyone.
It'll take weeks.
You have to wake them up
one way or another.
Master...
Fuck yeah!
First, he was seen here.
In Oxfjord.
Next, here. By the museum at Ice Bay.
Then it looks like he's turning south.
Gunga, we have a situation.
So what they said on the phone
there was a bunch of guys
dressed up as German soldiers going crazy?
If by crazy, he means slaughtering
a bunch of people, then, yeah.
What the hell is going on? We haven't had,
a decent murder here since 1974.
And now this?
Okay, guys, listen up!
Shoot first, ask questions later!
Hey!
You're too late.
There's nobody here.
We sent them away.
Since there's nobody here,
maybe you should forget
about your assignment and
return to your little snow cave.
Somebody's grown. Gotten bigger!
I hope you don't mind but I,
invited some friends to tag along.
Don't you just hate it
when somebody that was supposed
to be dead comes back to kill you?
Let's kill 'em.
Troops!
Attack!
Let's kill 'em all!
What the hell is going on?
Is there a carnival in town?
Is that a tank?
Get out of the car!
Ah! Get out!
Daniel!
The tank.
- Shouldn't we help them?
- Help who?
The guys with rotten skin
in Russian uniforms?
Or the guys with rotten skin
in German uniforms?
Okay.
Good boy.
- What the fuck is going on?
- It looks like a computer game.
Gunga, look! Look, it's him!
It's Martin Hykkerud!
- Should we go get him?
- No, no, no! Wait, wait, wait!
This is technical police work.
Zombie Squad. It's about time!
- It's a long story.
- There was a tank.
A guy took my jacket.
Looks like you found
Stavarin and his men, I see.
Yeah, but there's still more than us.
I guess it's time we even out
the odds a bit, huh?
- Guys!
- What?
We're losing!
Look!
Shit!
No, no, no...
No!
Wait!
We have to kill him!
They're all bound to him
like the Russians are to you.
If he dies, the others will too.
Let's finish this.
Sub-human.
Guys, come on. No seat belts?
You're just askin' for it.
Fucking hell, how many more
of these are there?
Is this it?
- Monica, is this how it's gonna end?
- No. No.
- Are we gonna die now?
- No.
Fuck it.
Fuck it, I'm just...
just gonna say it.
What?
I...
Glenn Kenneth Toivonen, am...
No!
Blake! Glenn?
Monica?
Why didn't you just stay on the mountain?
You got what you wanted.
You got your gold...
your treasure.
But it wasn't enough, was it?
You got greedy.
You wanted more.
Monica. Watch out!
- Monica!
- Blake!
Blake! No!
That's why you lost the war.
Did you know?
You lost the war.
You got greedy.
Guess what?
You lose again.
No!
My God!
He did it!
- He killed Herzog.
- It worked!
I knew it!
Herzog is dead.
He's dead!
Yes!
Holy cow, that was close.
You did it! You killed Herzog!
Uh-huh.
I can't believe that that actually worked.
Of course it did.
You doubted the Zombie Squad?
Glenn Kenneth, is he...?
He didn't make it.
It's been a true honor
killing zombies with you guys.
You too, Martin.
What is it?
Okay.
- You can say it.
- Go for it.
May the force be with you.
Really? That one? Of all.
You chose that one?
There's like a million to choose from.
Why would you choose that one?
Where are they?
They were just here.
I don't know.
Bjarne!
Are you in a coma?
Go and find them!
I was supposed to solve this murder case,
not end up with a hundred new bodies.
Yeah, I don't know where
we're gonna put them all.
Both the garage and the freezer
are completely packed.
I don't know. I do...
I dont... I don't know!
The seagulls again.
They haven't eaten
this well since the war.
You know. We should've had
that machine, you know.
That seagull translator machine.
We could've cracked this case like an egg.
Like an egg.
"Turn around"
"Every now and then
I get a little bit lonely"
"And you're never coming round"
"Turn around"
"Every now and then
I get a little bit tired"
"Of listening to the sound of my tears"
"Turn around"
"Every now and then
I get a little bit nervous"
"That the best of all the years have gone by"
"Turn around"
"Every now and then I get
a little bit terrified"
"And then I see
the look in your eyes"
"Turn around, bright eyes"
"Every now and then I fall apart"
"And I need you now tonight
And I need you more than ever"
"And if you only hold me tight
We'll be holding on forever"
"And we'll only be making it right"
"'Cause we'll never be wrong"
"Together we can take it
to the end of the line"
"Your love is like a shadow
on me all of the time"
"All of the time"
"I don't know what to do
and I'm always in the dark"
"We're living in a powder keg
and giving off sparks"
"I really need you tonight"
"Forever's gonna start tonight"
"Once upon a time I was falling in love"
"But now I'm only falling apart"
"There's nothing I can do
A total eclipse of the heart"
"Turn around, bright eyes"
"Every now and then I fall apart"
"And I need you now tonight"
"And I need you more than ever"
"And if you only hold me tight"
"We'll be holding on forever"
"And we'll only be making it right"
"'Cause we'll never be wrong"
"Together we can take it
to the end of the line"
"Your love is like a shadow
on me all of the time"
"All of the time"
"I don't know what to do"
"I'm always in the dark"
"Living in a powder keg
and giving off sparks"
"I really need you tonight"
"Forever's gonna start tonight"
"Once upon a time I was falling in love"
"But now I'm only falling apart"
"Nothing I can say"
"A total eclipse of the heart"
"Turn around, bright eyes"