I have the feeling that
I should be angry with this child,
with this childish young thing,
or I shouldn't forgive her
for not realizing the horrors,
the monster, before it was too late,
for not realizing
what she was getting into.
How could I have agreed to it
so impulsively?
I was not an enthusiastic Nazi.
When I came to Berlin,
I could have said "No,
I won't take part. I don't want to be
sent to the Führer's headquarters. "
But I didn't say no.
Curiosity got the better of me.
And I simply never thought
that fate would take me somewhere
I'd never really wanted to be.
And yet, it's very hard
to forgive myself for doing it.
The ladies are here.
Military District II has confirmed.
- You may pass.
FÜHRER'S HEADQUARTERS "WOLFSSCHANZE"
RASTENBURG, EAST PRUSSIA, NOV. 1942
Please take a seat, ladies.
I must ask you to wait a few minutes.
The Führer is feeding his dog.
He will be with you shortly.
Tell me... How do we...
How does one greet the Führer?
The Führer will speak to you first,
and you just say, "Heil, my Führer. "
What about the Nazi salute?
That won't be necessary. The Führer
isn't recruiting you as soldiers,
he's looking for a secretary.
Behave normally.
Just be natural. I'll ask him
if he has time for you now.
My Führer,
the ladies from Berlin are here.
I'd like to thank you for coming
in the middle of the night, ladies.
But in war, we aren't always
masters of our own time.
May I ask your name?
- Margarethe Lorenz. Heil, my Führer.
Where are you from?
- Fulda. Heil, my Führer. - And you?
Ursula Puttkammer.
Heil, my Führer. - Leave that out,
child. Tell me where you're from.
Frankfurt on the Main, my Führ...
I'm Hannah Potrovsky,
born and raised in Berlin.
To be precise, I come from Pankow.
Hedwig Brandt
from Crailsheim, Swabia.
And you?
Traudl Humps. I come from Munich.
A Munich girl.
So, Fräulein Humps...
shall we start?
Blondi won't hurt you.
She has a very sharp mind.
In fact, she's more clever
than most people are.
Just make yourself comfortable.
Don't be nervous. I make
so many mistakes when I dictate...
You'll never make as many as I do.
You're quite young.
How old are you?
22, my Führer.
My national comrades...
German men and women...
members of the Party...
It is, I believe, a rare thing
that a man can stand before his old
supporters after 20 years in office,
and that during those 20 years
he did not have to modify
his policies whatsoever.
I suggest...
that we try it again.
I made it! He gave me a job!
Berlin, 20 April, 1945
Adolf Hitler's 56th birthday
21/2 years later
Duck!
Keep moving! Get off the street!
That's artillery.
Are you crazy?
How could they be firing artillery?
Frau Junge, you're right!
Those aren't bombs, it's artillery!
It's the Russians.
- What a fine birthday present!
What's going on, Burgdorf?
Where's that gunfire coming from?
Happy birthday, my Führer.
Central Berlin is being shelled,
from the Brandenburg Gate
to the Reichstag,
up to Friedrichstrasse Station.
- Where from?
No reports yet. Koller's on the line.
- Give him to me.
Koller, do you realize
Berlin is under artillery fire?
No.
- Don't tell me
you can't hearthe gunfire!
No, I'm at Werder Game Park.
- Berlin's in uproar!
The Russians have taken
a rail bridge on the Oder.
They've got no railway batteries
near the Oder.
That's not long-range gunfire.
The flak command post
in the Zoo-bunker
claims the guns have a caliber
of just 10 to 12 cm.
The Russian battery
is now in Marzahn.
That's only 12 kilometers
from the city center!
Are the Russians that close?
The entire air force command
should be hanged!
Outrageous!
The Russians are just 12 kilometers
from the city center,
and nobody told me! I had to ask!
My Führer, perhaps
it's long-range gunfire.
You mentioned a railway battery...
Nonsense!
Himmler is such a pompous clown!
- Big shots!
Big shots everywhere! It makes me
sick just looking at them!
The Führer is putting "Clausewitz"
into operation today.
Berlin as a front-line city...
He won't be able to hold the city.
If the Führer stays, he'll take
the whole Reich down with him.
We have to talk him out of it.
Speak to Hewel...
He's the only diplomat
who can still influence him.
Believe me, it's no use.
Then talk to your sister-in-law.
Why not? You're married
to Eva Braun's sister,
so you're "related" to the Führer.
We have to try everything.
Berlin is practically
surrounded by the Russians.
You're young.
You'll be a father soon.
Do you want to die in Berlin?
- Certainly not.
Gentlemen, the Führer!
Everything out, and quick!
We're leaving in two hours.
What's going on?
- We're packing!
Leaving... Haven't you heard?
"Clausewitz" is in effect.
All government departments and
Wehrmacht offices are leaving Berlin.
Who's going to feed
the civilians and soldiers?
Don't ask me, Professor.
This is insane!
Ah, Professor!
I won't allow my staff
to be evacuated! - Is that so?
The food supply to Berlin
will collapse!
A good soldier always finds
something to eat! - Sure!
And when fighting begins, who
will he take food from? Civilians!
I cannot permit it!
- The Führer's orders!
As the department head,
I answer to the SS and to Himmler!
But as a doctor I belong to the
Wehrmacht, and we are still here!
Please bear that in mind!
The professor can stay in Berlin!
Give him an authorized permit!
Move out!
Everything for Germany. Heil, my Führer!
My Führer, I... Heil, my Führer!
They can hardly wait to get away.
I hate those two-faced sods who say
"Sieg Heil", but behind their
backs say, "Kiss my a... aunt. "
My Führer...
I beg you to leave Berlin.
It's not too late.
Too late?
Come here, Hewel.
Hewel, you also feel we should
get in touch with the Allies...
and use politics.
Yes, indeed. We should use politics.
Politics? No more politics!
I'm sick of politics!
When I'm dead, you'll have
enough politics to deal with!
- My Führer...
It's okay, my dear Himmler.
My loyal Heinrich.
It's okay... Go now.
Between us, I'd say he's had it.
- Yeah?
What do you expect from a teetotal,
non-smoking vegetarian?
Be serious.
I'll have to
to take it into my own hands.
Berlin will fall
in the next few days.
Once the Führer is dead,
who will the Allies negotiate with?
What makes you so sure
they'll negotiate?
They need the Nazi state and my SS
to keep order after the war.
Give me an hour with Eisenhower, and
he'll agree. We're already in touch.
Be careful, that's treason.
- Fegelein, I have other worries.
Should I give Eisenhower
the Nazi salute or shake his hand?
Well, well...
The later it gets,
the nicer the guests.
Gentlemen, are you leaving already?
I wanted to talk to you.
The Führer's orders to destroy all
public... - I really must go.
Drop in to visit me
at Hohenlychen sometime.
My staff and I are heading north
to support the battle for Berlin.
So, Speer...
the bombing raids on our cities
have a positive side too.
It's much easier to remove the debris
than to tear everything down.
Once we win the war, reconstruction
will be completed very quickly.
How many thousands of hours have we
spent on these magnificent models?
You're a true genius, Speer.
Yes, you are.
Only you and I realize
that a Third Reich isn't possible
if it only consists of
department stores and factories,
skyscrapers and hotels.
This Third Reich
will be a treasure house
of art and culture
that will survive the millennia...
We see before us
the ancient cities, the acropolis,
we see medieval cities
with their cathedrals, and we know
that people need something
like this, a center.
Yes, Speer...
That was my vision...
And it still is.
My Führer...
If you want to realize these plans,
you should leave Berlin.
Say something, Eva.
- He's the Führer.
He knows what's right.
Please leave Berlin.
The Russians have nearly cut us off.
I can't do that, child.
I'd feel like a lama
spinning an empty prayer-wheel.
I must force an outcome in Berlin,
or face my downfall.
Speer...
What do you say?
You must be on stage
when the curtain falls.
Reload!
Leave me alone!
How old are you? 12? And you? 14?
And you? Do you want to play war?
Go home, play another game!
- Who are you?
What do you want?
- My son... alive.
You should be proud of him.
He destroyed two tanks. Today.
The Führer is giving him a medal.
You're young.
On which front did you fight?
I haven't had the honor yet.
You're lucky you haven't seen
a battle yet. Send the children home.
We will fight to the very last man.
What are you defending?
This is nothing but a trap.
The Russians will attack from
both sides, so there's no escape.
We'll shoot back at them!
With what?
- We're using flak as artillery.
The Russians are coming,
several armies with tanks
and heavy artillery.
Do you really believe
you can hold off their assault
for even five minutes?
We made our pledge to the Führer.
Don't you understand?
We've lost the war! It's over!
Coward!
Get outta here! Now!
When the Russians come and
you're still here, you'll all die!
I may be repeating myself,
but the 9th Army must retreat.
Otherwise, it will be wiped out.
The 9th Army will not retreat!
Tell Busse to fight where he stands.
In that case, the 9th Army is lost.
We will drive back the Soviet units
in the north and east
with a relentless
and almighty assault.
With which units?
Steiner's division will attack from
the north and unite with the 9th.
The 9th Army is unable to move north.
The enemy outnumbers us 10 to 1.
Have Wenck support them
with the 12th Army.
But the 12th Army
is marching west, to the Elbe.
Then tell them to turn around!
That would expose the Western front.
- Are you questioning my orders?
I believe I've made myself
perfectly clear!
The western Allies will realize that
only we can hold off the Bolsheviks.
We're the last bulwark
against the Asian hordes.
If we hold Berlin for a few more days
we'll make a deal with the Americans.
Ah, Mohnke...
you're here.
- My Führer.
I put "Clausewitz" into effect today.
Berlin is now a front-line city.
You're in charge of defending
the government district.
If there's a battle in Berlin,
we'll fight to the last man.
But there are over
3 million civilians.
They have to be evacuated.
I appreciate your concern, Mohnke.
But we have to be cold-blooded.
We can't worry about
these so-called civilians now!
With all due respect, what will
become of the women and children,
the thousands of wounded,
and the elderly?
In a war like this
there are no civilians.
The Führer has lost
all sense of reality.
He moves divisions
that only exist on his map.
Steiner's scattered unit
can hardly defend itself,
and now he wants Steiner to attack.
It's insane! - Tell him yourself.
He wouldn't listen. You know that.
- Something has to be done.
Are you crazy? He'd kick us out like
Rundstedt and Guderian. - So what?
We're soldiers! We pledged
our allegiance to the Führer!
Should that prevent us from thinking?
Look who's talking! An opportunist!
A ruthless careerist!
Pardon?
Where were you?
- None of your damned business!
My Führer, Berlin Hitler Youth's
most successful tank hunters.
I'm proud of you all.
My Führer, this boy alone
destroyed two tanks with a bazooka.
His name is Peter Kranz.
So your name is Peter.
I wish my generals had your courage.
Fine, fine.
History will take note of you.
And when Germania rises up
from these ruins,
you'll be the heroes.
Heil to you!
I don't know about you,
but this gives me the creeps.
I prefer bombing raids.
What will happen to us?
Yesterday, he told me it was alright
if I left.
Everyone's deserting him.
We can't just get up and leave.
I can't either.
I've no idea where I should go.
My parents and friends back home
warned me. They told me
not to get involved with the Nazis.
Should I go back and say,
"I'm home. I made a mistake.
When things got bad
I realized my mistake. "
Life will go on, somehow.
What do you think, Colonel?
We should go.
Where to?
I don't know.
Some place where we're needed.
Come upstairs, everyone!
We're going to have a party!
Come on!
Come on, kids!
I want us to have some fun today.
No matter where the enemy goes
he has to find nothing but wasteland.
That's the death sentence
for the German people.
No electricity, no gas,
no clean water,
no coal, no transportation.
By destroying all our railways,
canals, docks, ships and locomotives,
we would hurl Germany
back to the Middle Ages.
You'd be robbing our people
of every chance to survive.
If the war is lost, it's immaterial
if the people perish too.
It is not necessary
to consider the German people's
primitive survival needs.
On the contrary, it is better
to destroy those things ourselves.
They have proved themselves
too weak and it is a law of nature
that they will be exterminated.
They are your people.
You are the Führer.
The only ones who
will survive the battle
are the inferior ones.
Our best people have fallen already.
Here you go.
Oh, come on, you're supposed to dance.
With pleasure.
Excuse me.
- Yes, of course.
What's the matter?
Convince him that
we have to leave Berlin, Eva!
Or come with me.
You're going to die.
Put on the music!
I want to dance!
Dance!
Anything in particular?
- Swing.
Traudl...
It's all so unreal...
...like a dream
where you want to wake up,
but you can't.
It keeps going on and on...
Gerda, I feel sick...
Come on! Come on!
I haven't moved my command...
I haven't moved my command post!
...to the west...?
I'm 1000 meters from the enemy!
- General!
Hello? Hello!
The report, General?
I'm to be shot.
- What? What for?
They claim that I moved
my command post
to the west, away from the enemy.
- Not a bad idea.
Come with me.
Schenck.
- Mohnke.
I'm at the chancellery bunker
defending the government district.
I need your help. - That's difficult,
everyone's been evacuated.
Everyone's gone
except me and my adjutant.
You're a doctor?
- Yes. Internist.
Find a vehicle and bring us
all the morphine, penicillin
and first-aid supplies you can find!
I'll see what I can do.
- Thank you, and hurry.
I have to see the Führer.
What for?
I'm to be shot.
Wait here.
Your guns, please.
Not here.
Guard post 2.
Roger.
General...
Not you.
Heil Hitler.
- Heil Hitler.
What's going on?
Why am I to be shot?
You know the Führer has forbidden
any westward retreat.
Officers who disobey are to be
arrested and shot on the spot.
What do you mean? My units
have been in fierce battle for days!
My command post is just one kilometer
from the front line.
Go on.
You see this, don't you?
Don't use that tone with me!
Now do what you have to do!
I think you should explain it
to the Führer yourself. Come along.
I can't let you through. - I'm here
on orders from Commander Mohnke.
We need first-aid material
from the military hospital.
It's empty. They all left.
And the wounded?
- How should I know?
I'll have a look.
- Colonel! - Stay here!
Careful you don't get killed.
There are Russians everywhere.
See that?
It's the end of the Reich.
That's Russki territory!
May I?
He's so damn stubborn.
Why didn't he let me do it?
I should be with my troops.
Are you sure the Führer needs me?
Drink up! The Führer's orders!
You really impressed the Führer.
- You don't think Steiner'll attack?
I doubt that Steiner's units
are able to attack,
but why am I telling you this?
You know better than I do.
If Steiner doesn't attack,
Berlin will be lost.
Congratulations, your report
really impressed the Führer.
He has appointed you
commander of Berlin's defense.
I'd rather have been shot
than have this honor...
Tank alarm!
Stay calm.
They're too far away to do anything.
Out of the way please, ladies.
Is that German artillery out there?
- I'm afraid not.
But Steiner's attack
should be underway by now!
You have to leave.
There isn't much time.
But the Führer believes
Steiner's attack
will make good of the situation.
I heard him say
that Steiner's assault
will turn things around.
All the Führer's advisors
know that's absurd!
I'd not be surprised if he thinks
so too. - Why would he deceive us?
What does he have to lose?
I don't believe a word of it!
The enemy has broken through
along a wide front.
They've taken Zossen to the south
and are advancing to Stahnsdorf.
They're on the northern outskirts
between Frohnau and Pankow.
They've reached Lichtenberg,
Mahlsdorf and Karlshorst to the east.
Steiner's assault will
bring it under control.
My Führer...
Steiner...
Steiner couldn't mobilize
enough men.
He wasn't able
to carry out his assault.
These men will stay here:
Keitel, Jodl, Krebs and Burgdorf.
That was an order!
Steiner's assault was an order!
Who do you think you are
to dare disobey an order that I give?
So this is what it has come to!
The military has been lying to me.
Everybody has been lying to me.
Even the SS!
Our generals are just a bunch
of contemptible, disloyal cowards.
I can't permit you
to insult the soldiers...
They are cowards,
traitors and failures!
My Führer, this is outrageous!
Our generals are the scum
of the German people!
Not a shred of honor!
They call themselves generals!
Years at military academy
just to learn how to hold
a knife and fork!
For years, the military
has hindered my plans!
They've put every kind of obstacle
in my way!
What I should have done
is liquidate all the high-ranking
officers, as Stalin did!
I never attended an academy,
and yet I have conquered Europe
all by myself!
Traitors!
I've been betrayed and deceived
from the very beginning!
What a monstrous betrayal
of the German people.
But all those traitors will pay.
They'll pay with their own blood.
They shall drown in their own blood!
Gerda, please calm yourself.
My orders have fallen on deaf ears.
Under these circumstances,
I am no longer able to lead...
It's over.
The war is lost.
But, gentlemen, if you believe
I am going to leave Berlin,
you are seriously mistaken.
I'd rather blow my brains out.
Do whatever you like.
The Führer didn't really mean
he'd shoot himself...
Frau Junge
and Frau Christian...
Get changed. A plane is leaving
in an hour. It will take you south.
Everything is lost...
Hopelessly lost.
You know I'll stay with you.
I won't let you send me away.
I'm staying too!
What now?
It's time to end this spectacle.
What? You want to give up?
That's unthinkable.
The Führer said we won't surrender.
We won't repeat November 1918.
Never!
You heard him. He'll no longer lead us.
He said, "Do whatever you want. "
- The Führer is the Führer!
He'll pull himself together.
Great.
And what happens then?
We can never surrender.
The Führer would never approve.
We swore to obey his will.
- Nothing but empty phrases!
We have to do something
before it's too late.
You want to save your own skin.
- Stop it!
Damn it!
We'll never get out alive.
It's all over. - Just wait.
But the Führer is uncertain.
What if he kills himself?
Günsche said there's a tunnel
under the Russian lines to the Yanks.
Why did you say you'd stay with him?
I don't know... honestly.
They've stopped. Come on.
Let's go for a walk.
Traudl...
Look...
Hey girls, I need a cigarette.
Let's go back down again.
Where did they come from?
- New Volkssturm recruits!
Assigned this afternoon!
Tell them to get out
of the line of fire!
These recruits
are under Dr. Goebbels' command!
I want them outta there,
right away!
I'll answer for it.
I'm not sure it's the right way.
Oh, splendid.
Stop! Lights out!
Stop. Don't move.
Don't move.
- Lucky! Germans.
Help! They want to kill us!
What's going on here?
- They're MPs.
I don't believe it!
Stop it! Let those men go!
What's going on here?
- It's none of your business!
We found these deserters
in their homes.
They'll be shot, like every traitor.
They're old men, civilians.
You can't do that!
No?
Who's going to stop me? You?
That's enough.
Move out!
Here's a doctor.
Can you operate?
Not really.
Tell Ilse that the children
can't take too many toys.
One toy per child.
And no unnecessary nightclothes.
- Minister Goebbels...
My wife and children are coming.
Please take care of them.
Thank you.
Brigadeführer, what can I do for you?
The Russians are mowing down
your Volkssturm recruits.
They lack experience
and suitable weapons.
That is compensated for by their
fervent belief in the final victory.
If you can't arm these men,
they can't fight.
They are dying in vain.
I feel no sympathy.
I repeat, I feel no sympathy!
The German people chose their fate.
That may surprise some people.
Don't fool yourself.
We didn't force the German people.
They gave us the mandate. And now
their little throats are being cut.
Yes?
Eva, you have to leave the Führer.
Hermann!
- Don't be stupid.
It's a matter of life and death.
How can you say such a thing?
Where are you?
I've decided not to die in Berlin.
Hermann, does my sister know
where you are?
I have to call you back.
Hi there, kids.
Your room's on the right.
Wait for me.
Hello, Frau Goebbels.
- Nice to see you, Frau Junge.
Come on now, get in line!
Come here, Helga. Get in line.
We'll put on our best clothes,
and then you can say hello
to Uncle Hitler.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Remember your song?
Yes.
No land is more beautiful...
...far and wide
than the land we call our own...
If you want to be certain,
shoot the gun into your mouth...
Your skull will explode.
You don't notice a thing.
You die immediately.
I want to look nice when I'm dead.
I'll take poison.
If I'm going to die heroically
I don't want to feel any pain.
That's a sure-fire way.
It paralyzes the nerves
and the respiratory system.
You die within seconds.
Could I have one, too?
Me, too.
Thank goodness
Himmler left me well supplied.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry I can't give you
a better present.
Berlin, 23 April,
1945.
My dearest sister, I'm so sorry
I have to write you this.
But there's nothing we can do.
At any minute, it could all be over.
You should know
that Hermann isn't here.
But I truly believe
you'll see him again.
I'm sure he'll continue
the fight in Bavaria
for a certain time. The Führer
has lost all belief
in a favorable outcome.
My beloved son, I don't know
if this letter will reach you.
Perhaps there is some human soul
who will pass on
my final words to you.
I've stayed with Papa
against his will. Last Sunday,
the Führer wanted to help me leave.
You know your mother well.
We have the same blood.
I had no second thoughts.
Our magnificent idea has died...
along with every beautiful,
admirable, noble, good thing
I've ever known.
The world after the Führer's death
and after National Socialism
is no longer worth living in.
That's why the children are here.
They are too good for what will come.
A merciful God will understand me
for giving them redemption.
I'll wear the golden bracelet with
the green stone until the very end.
Then it may be taken from me,
and you shall wear it
just as I have always worn it.
I'm afraid I sent my diamond watch
to the jeweler's.
I wrote the address at the bottom.
If you're lucky, you can get it back.
I want you to have it.
You'll also get the diamond bracelet
and the topaz pendant which
the Führer gave me for my birthday.
The bill I'm including for
Heise & Co. Hasn't been paid yet.
You might receive some other bills,
too, but not for more
than 1,500 Reichsmarks.
Please burn all private and business
letters to the Führer at once.
I'm also sending you
food and cigarettes.
Please give Lindners and Kathl
some of the coffee.
The cigarettes are for Mandi.
The tobacco is for Papa.
The chocolate is for Mom.
That's all I can tell you.
It's enough for now.
I wish you the best of luck,
my dearest sister.
And remember,
I'm sure you'll see Hermann again.
Best regards
and kisses. I remain...
your sister...
Inge!
Listen Keitel,
I want you to leave tonight.
Make your way to Dönitz.
Help him organize everything.
We have to get things moving again.
I don't understand.
It's a disaster.
We have no more oilfields.
It's impossible to carry out
far-ranging operations.
Once I've managed this situation,
we must recover the oilfields.
Any more questions?
No, my Führer.
Fine. Have a nice trip.
"My Führer, Following your decision
to stay in Berlin,
do I have your approval
as Vice Chancellor
to immediately take charge
of the entire Reich...
with the necessary power
and authority?
If I receive no answer
by 10 p. m., I will assume
that you have been incapacitated.
I will serve the well-being
of our people and fatherland. "
He's betraying Germany...
and you!
Göring's concern isn't unjustified.
If our communication system
breaks down,
which could happen any time,
we'd be cut off from the world.
We could no longer pass on orders.
I see it differently.
Göring wants to seize power.
I never trusted that mob he gathered
at Obersalzberg. It stinks of a coup.
That failure! That bloodsucker!
A parvenu! A lazybones!
How dare he declare me
unable to act!
Tomorrow he might declare me dead!
- Hello, Frau Junge.
How did you reach Berlin?
It wasn't easy.
I have to see the Führer.
I'd wait if I were you.
The air force...
What did he do with it?
That's reason enough
to execute him!
That morphine addict
helped to corrupt this country.
And now this!
He has betrayed me.
Me!
I want Göring to be deprived of power
and removed from office.
If I don't survive this war...
that man is to be executed at once.
What about us?
Is there any hope?
Leave before it's too late.
The Führer wants to stay here.
We can't leave him alone.
For that which awaits the Führer,
he won't need anyone.
Least of all you.
But Herr Goebbels and his wife
are staying. The children too.
But the children...
I'd always thought that...
I thought there was some way out...
Come in.
Albert... hello.
Fever?
Albert, my heart can't take it.
Why don't you take the children
and get out of here?
But where to?
I once told you, I can send a barge
to Schwanenwerder.
It can be fixed up as a hideout
until it's all over...
which won't be long.
I've thought it through carefully.
I won't let the children grow up in
a world with no National Socialism.
Think it over again, Magda.
The children deserve a future.
If the idea of National Socialism
dies, there is no future.
I can't believe you really want this.
Go...
Come in.
I knew you'd come. You're not one
of those who'd abandon the Führer.
I... I've just come
to say goodbye to the Führer.
I have to return to Hamburg tonight.
- Of course.
Take a seat.
Look, I brought some of the furniture
you designed for me.
I just couldn't part with it.
Come on, help yourself. I bet
you haven't eaten all day.
You happen to be right.
Thanks.
It's so important that you came.
It shows him you're on his side.
Did he have his doubts?
He's been wondering
if you were possibly against him.
But I kept telling him you'd come.
And now you're here.
It pleased him that you
advised him to stay in Berlin.
I think it's the right choice, too.
You know what?
It may be crazy, but...
I'm really happy to be able to stay.
And I'm not afraid.
Yes?
So... you've come.
My Führer...
It's okay... Let's sit down.
I had such big plans
for the Germans and for the world.
No one understood me,
not even my oldest comrades.
What huge opportunities we had.
The world was within reach...
Too late.
What I am proud of is that
I openly confronted the Jews...
and I cleansed the German lands
of Jewish poison.
It isn't hard for me to go.
Just that one moment...
...and then eternal peace.
Spare the German people, my Führer.
If my own people fail this test,
I will shed not one tear for them.
They deserve nothing else.
It's their own destiny.
They themselves are to blame.
For months...
I must tell you this, my Führer...
For months I have not carried out
your orders of destruction.
Documents exist which prove
that I not only ignored,
but even acted
contrary to your orders.
I had to tell you.
My personal loyalty to you
never wavered throughout.
So, you're leaving...
Fine. Goodbye.
I wish you all the best.
So gentlemen, eat your fill.
Peter!
Everything's okay, my boy.
Fever.
Yes, but he's alive.
Courage and loyalty still exist.
Lord von Greim and Frau Reitsch,
I am pleased that...
you both arrived uninjured,
more or less.
Be seated.
We were under heavy fire
but were able to land in Gatow.
The roads were impassable,
so...
we got a plane, a Fieseler Storch,
and flew over the Russian lines,
landing on the East-West axis,
a few hundred meters from here.
Just before landing,
we got hit by Russian artillery.
General von Greim, I appoint you
Commander in Chief of the Air Force
and General Field Marshal.
A great responsibility
rests on your shoulders. You must
shake up the entire air force.
Many mistakes have been made.
Be ruthless.
Life never forgives weakness.
This so-called humanity...
is just priests' drivel.
Compassion is a primal sin.
Compassion for the weak...
is a betrayal of nature.
The strongest
can only be victorious
by eradicating the weak.
I have always obeyed
this law of nature
by never permitting myself
to feel compassion.
I have ruthlessly suppressed
domestic opposition and
brutally crushed the resistance
of alien races.
It's the only way to deal with it.
Apes, for example,
trample every outsider to death.
What goes for apes
goes even more for human beings.
In Lübeck, Himmler has made an offer
to surrender to the western powers
through Count Bernadotte...
...according to a report
by English radio.
Himmler...
Of all people, Himmler!
The truest of the true!
This is the worst betrayal of all!
Göring, of course. He was corrupt...
Speer, an idealistic,
unpredictable artist!
All the others! Yes! Yes! Yes!
But not Himmler.
Has he gone crazy?
He claimed authority
by saying that I was sick,
perhaps already dead.
Please leave me alone with
Lord von Greim and Frau Reitsch.
And bring me Fegelein.
My Führer, we don't know where he is.
But he's Himmler's adjutant,
he must be here!
We haven't seen him for days.
I want his report at once!
Please stay, Doctor.
You and Greim are to leave at once.
Fly to Dönitz. Tell him
to do everything necessary
to ensure Himmler receives
just punishment.
My Führer, Lord von Greim and I
have decided to die with you here.
Thank you for this sign of loyalty.
But Himmler must die.
He committed treason!
It was the right decision
not to inform him of my plans.
My Führer?
Do you think I'd stand by and watch
those Jewish pigs do me in?
This is all part
of a gigantic ploy.
I allowed the enemy
to invade the Reich. They believe
they've won, but you'll see, Greim.
It'll be a rude awakening for them.
Dönitz is mobilizing troops in
the north, Kesselring in the south.
We will crush the enemy
in a massive pincer movement.
And I have 3 armies near Prague
which will attack from behind.
I had no idea that we still have
so many troops available.
I have made arrangements
that within a short time
you will have thousands
of jet fighter aircraft,
so you can make the air force
as powerful as it once was!
I kneel down to your genius and
before the altar of our fatherland.
Heil, my Führer.
You have requested to leave Berlin?
As you know,
all the medical units and staff
under Himmler's authority
have left Berlin.
Himmler is a traitor. He will receive
the punishment he deserves.
As an SS physician,
I have no more duties here.
Your application to leave Berlin
is completely unacceptable.
My... family...
If the Russians find me here...
I have to leave!
You did nothing wrong.
Future generations
will be thankful
for the medical research you did.
I'll take responsibility for it all.
Let's discuss this another time.
We can't find
Gruppenführer Fegelein.
He is not in the bunker.
- What do you mean, "can't find him"?
Then look for him!
I want to see Fegelein at once!
If he's gone AWOL,
it's desertion! Treason!
Bring me Fegelein!
Fegelein! Fegelein!
Dad, why are you wearing
your Sunday uniform?
Ernst... is something wrong?
No... Thank you.
Gitte is hungry, too.
Well, Ilse,
now you have to eat something, too.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What's going on?
You're under arrest.
What?
- For desertion.
Get dressed. You must come with us.
Kiss my ass!
Let go, you bastard!
You got no right!
Please don't let them kill Hermann.
He wanted to flee,
it's beyond doubt.
So what?
It's all over anyway.
Think of my poor sister.
She's pregnant!
He collaborated with Himmler.
He's a traitor.
There is no compassion for traitors.
There is no mercy for traitors.
He'll be court-martialled and shot.
What good is that now?
It is my will!
You're the Führer.
Go ahead.
The Russians are breaking through
everywhere.
There are no reserves left,
and air support has stopped.
There's no way
to bring in more ammunition.
The Russians have reached
Weidendammer Bridge,
Lustgarten to the east,
Potsdamer Platz to the south
and Tiergarten to the west,
300-400 meters from the Chancellery.
How long can you hold out?
One or two days at most.
The government district too?
Yes, my Führer.
My Führer,
as a soldier I suggest
we try to break through
the encirclement.
During the fight for Berlin
we've already lost
15-20,000 of the younger officers.
But that's what young men are for.
Your suggestion is absurd! Insane!
Think of the thousands
of wounded. We can't help them now.
My Führer...
the orders are ready.
I give you my word...
The Führer can't just disappear
from history
like some inglorious fugitive!
- Even if we got out
successfully, I'd only be escaping
one trap to fall into another.
I'd have to sleep in the open air
or in a farmhouse
or something similar
and wait for the end to come.
Wenck is approaching
with the 12th army.
He can unite
with Busse's 9th Army
and inflict a crushing blow
on the Russians to save us all.
Wenck is a man of excellence.
Telegraph Keitel.
Report to me
immediately: First, where are
Wenck's front lines? Second,
when are they attacking? Third,
where is the 9th Army?
Fourth, where will the 9th Army
break through?
You'll see, gentlemen.
I'll be proved right.
Wenck will come.
I want to know if it's possible
for Wenck to attack or not.
It's unlikely that Wenck's small
force can attack the Red Army...
How dare you say it's unlikely?
Wenck has nothing
to confront the Red Army!
Why don't you tell the Führer?
Have you all gone crazy?
- The Führer knows it himself!
But he will never surrender!
And we won't either!
I went through that before!
And once is enough!
Come on. I have to get out of here.
Stopp!
Heil Hitler!
Sorry, I fell asleep.
So you rested up a bit, dear?
Take it in shorthand.
My political testament.
Since 1914,
when I invested my modest strength
in the First World War,
which was forced upon the Reich,
over 30 years have passed.
In those 3 decades, all my thoughts,
actions and my life
were dictated by my love for
and loyalty to the German people.
Sorry, but the heavy gunfire...
You sit there.
Centuries will pass,
but from the ruins of our cities
and cultural monuments
our hatred will be renewed
for those who are responsible,
the people to whom we owe all this:
The international Jewry
and its supporters.
What's wrong, Herr Minister?
Imagine!
The Führer wants me to leave Berlin.
He ordered me to leave.
I've never disobeyed
one of the Führer's orders. Never!
But I will not obey this order.
I will stand by the Führer.
I'm sorry, Frau Junge, but...
I have to dictate
my personal testament to you.
I'm typing the Führer's testament.
Fine.
I understand. I'll get back to you.
My Führer, I...
The Race Laws require me
to ask you this: My Führer,
are you of pure Aryan descent?
Yes.
- May I see your ID?
You're talking to the Führer.
- Yes, sir.
And are you, Frau Braun,
of pure Aryan descent?
Yes. - Then the matter is...
There are no obstacles...
I ask you:
Do you, my Führer Adolf Hitler,
take Eva Braun to be your
lawful wedded wife? - I do.
Do you, Eva Braun, take
the Führer Adolf Hitler to be your
lawful wedded husband? - I do.
I hereby declare you
man and wife.
I need two men!
You'll be okay.
The Führer wants to see you at once.
- At this hour?
How long can you hold out?
Perhaps 20 hours. No longer.
The Russians are just
a few hundred meters away.
For the moment we've stopped them.
Know what, Mohnke?
The Western democracies are decadent.
They will be defeated by
those disciplined people of the East.
All the best. Thank you.
It wasn't only for Germany.
Keitel's report.
First, Wenck is stuck
south of Lake Schwielow.
Second, the 12th Army cannot
continue its assault on Berlin.
Third, the bulk of the 9th Army
is encircled.
My Führer, we need instructions
in case we run out of ammunition.
I will never surrender. Never.
I forbid you to surrender. That goes
for every other commander as well.
Listen, Günsche. Frau Braun...
my wife and I will commit suicide.
But I don't want the Russians
to exhibit my body in some museum.
Don't let me fall
into their hands, dead or alive!
I want my body to be burned,
so it can never be found.
Günsche...
Promise you will make
all necessary arrangements
for the disposal
of my mortal remains.
My Führer...
This is a terrible order,
but I will carry it out.
Kempka. - Erich,
I need 200 liters of gasoline.
Are you crazy?
Where do I get that much gasoline?
From the parked vehicles.
No one needs them now.
Why do you need so much gas?
I can't tell you on the phone.
Come with me, please.
The Führer wants to see us.
Should I tell him you can't come?
It's my pneumothorax.
I won't last much longer anyway.
Excuse me, Madam.
This way, Professor.
Please wait here.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry to interrupt
your important work.
My Führer, preserve our belief
in the final victory!
Lead us, and we will follow you!
Come on.
Come in and join us!
Here, have a drink.
Drinking's all we have left.
- Have a seat.
That's better.
Yes sir, our situation is hopeless.
It's what you call shitty!
Be seated.
We are honored, Fräulein...
Frau...
You may call me Frau Hitler.
Don't worry, it's all right.
Pity we can't go outside anymore.
Only if you want a hero's death.
Fritz, pull yourself together!
Yes, sir! Pull myself together!
Duck!
That was a close call.
Heil Hitler!
Obersturmbannführer, what's up?
- I must report to the Führer.
Not now. Have a seat.
Sit down, drink up.
May I introduce you to Frau Hitler?
So young and so many medals!
You must be proud of yourself.
I must go.
I'm not used to drinking anymore.
You can use our toilet. Go ahead.
If your hand shakes, the bullet
might only destroy the optic nerve.
That's why it's advisable
to take poison too.
Pull the trigger
the moment you bite the capsule.
Will I have enough time to do it?
The poison takes effect
after 1 or 2 seconds.
Tornow, you too.
Come on, Blondi.
Frau Junge, I've known him...
my husband... for over 15 years.
But when I think about it,
I don't know anything about him.
Although he likes to talk.
I was looking forward to Berlin.
But he's changed so much.
He only talks about dogs
and vegetarian meals.
I really hate Blondi.
Sometimes I kick her secretly, then
Adolf wonders about her behavior.
It seems he doesn't want
anyone to see inside him.
I mean deep inside.
In private, he can be
such a caring person.
But then he says...
such brutal things.
When he's the Führer?
Come on, let's have a smoke.
I'm sorry.
You've so many worries,
and I sit here whining.
Frau Junge, let me give you
this coat as a going-away present.
I love well-dressed women. I want
you to have it and to enjoy it.
What a surprise. Thank you.
I have no idea
where and when I could wear it.
Please... try to get out of here.
Promise me.
Thank you, that was very good,
Fräulein Manziarly.
The time has come.
It's over now.
The Führer wants to say farewell.
You're the bravest mother
in the whole Reich.
My Führer, you've made me
the happiest woman in Germany.
Give my regards to Bavaria.
Why are you here? - We want to see
Aunt Eva and Uncle Hitler.
Have you had anything to eat?
- Just breakfast.
I'll get you something to eat
and be right back, okay?
Okay.
Comrades, have you heard
the latest news from outside?
Berlin's a city of warehouses.
Where's my house? Where's my house?
Herr Günsche,
I have to see the Führer.
Please! - The Führer does not want
to be disturbed by anyone.
Please, Günsche. Just one moment.
Please!
My Führer, Frau Goebbels is here.
What now?
My Führer, I beg you
to leave Berlin!
My Führer, please...
Don't leave us!
What will become of us?
Tomorrow millions of people
will curse me,
but fate has taken its course.
Get up... Come on.
Come on...
Aunt Traudl,
I really like those loud booms!
Why?
- Nothing can happen to us here,
can it?
You're right.
Bull's eye!
Herr Reichsleiter,
it has happened.
The Führer is dead.
There's Papa.
Are you crazy?
That gasoline has caused...
- Be quiet, Erich.
Step back!
Come on!
No! Don't!
Let go of Grandma!
Order... Order...
Order must be restored!
Run, Grandpa, run!
Go after those two!
Here, this way!
We know our way through the ruins!
Trust us! Hurry!
I WAS ON THE SIDE
OF THE RED BEASTS
I SUPPORTED THE BOLSHEVIKS.
I hope the Russians got our message.
We'll know in a minute.
- Or maybe not.
What news do you bring us, General?
Hitler and his wife committed suicide
in the Führer's bunker.
The new government has empowered me
to begin peace negotiations.
Between our two countries which have
suffered the highest casualties.
General, would you want peace
in my position?
My government will not accept
an unconditional surrender.
Under the circumstances,
there's no other alternative.
We'll never surrender! Outrageous!
I conquered Berlin against the Reds
years ago! And I will defend it
against the Reds to my dying breath!
I won't use my final hours
as Reich Chancellor to sign a
statement of surrender!
We must protect civilians!
- The Führer's order is final!
Have you gone mad?
We have to negotiate.
I repeat, gentlemen,
I will never agree to surrender!
- Telegraph Marshal Schukov.
Marshal Schukov? - What's going on?
- This is crazy!
We must surrender to the Russians!
- I'll shoot you!
The Führer forbade
any kind of surrender!
How long does it last?
- About 4 hours.
Alright, children.
Dr. Stumpfegger
has brought the medicine
I told you about. - It's bitter,
but it's good for you.
Everyone gets a sip.
Who's first?
Heide, you're always so brave.
One more sip.
It wasn't that bad.
Good... Helmut?
Good.
It will keep you from getting sick
in this damp bunker.
But it isn't damp here.
Good, good.
Helga...
I don't want any.
Do you want to get sick?
- Please, Mama. I don't want to.
Don't cry.
It won't help if you cry.
You have to drink it.
Helga!
Come on! Open your mouth!
Papa!
Now!
Drink. Drink!
Sleep tight, children.
One day the lies will vanish,
and light will brighten the darkness.
Would you read it to me, please?
"One day the lies will vanish,
and light
will brighten the darkness. "
Let's do it again.
One day the lies will vanish,
and above them...
truth will triumph once again.
It will be the moment
when we stand above everything,
pure and...
unblemished.
We don't stand a chance.
- I don't care. I want out.
How do we cross the Russian lines?
I won't stay a minute longer.
We're gonna die!
- Stop it! It won't be so bad.
The Russians will get us if we stay.
Good luck.
- Okay, let's go.
On 30 April 1945,
the Führer committed suicide.
Thus he abandoned all those
who had pledged allegiance to him.
German soldiers, you obeyed
the Führer's orders and were prepared
to continue the battle for Berlin,
although
you were running out of ammunition
and further resistance was futile.
I order an immediate ceasefire.
Every further hour of battle
will only prolong
the civilians' terrible suffering
and the suffering of our wounded.
In agreement with the
Soviet Army Supreme Command,
I order you
to cease fighting at once!
Weidling, former Commanding Officer
of the Berlin Defense Force.
A glass of water, please.
I need you no longer.
The dice is cast.
It's time, Doctor.
- You see how busy we are.
I insist that you accompany us.
So that's it.
Go on. You've done a great deal.
Thank you.
Schädle, come with me.
Sorry, I'm not going anywhere.
Let's go!
Sturmmann Krüger gets the Iron Cross,
2nd class, for defending Wolf Bridge.
Sturmmann Wagner
took out 2 machine gun posts
and defended Puttkammer Strasse.
He gets the Iron Cross,
2nd class.
Sturmmann Rauch gets the Iron Cross,
2nd class,
for helping messengers
get through enemy lines.
The others!
Oh God!
Duck, Müller!
Get outta here! Hurry!
Help!
Who goes there?
A German.
Herr Hewel?
Hewel,
thank God you're alive.
Where are the others?
I don't know, Frau Junge.
Somewhere... perhaps.
I'm sure most of the people
in my group are dead.
I never should have left the bunker.
I should have shot myself.
But I couldn't.
Eat something.
There's time enough to die.
Attention!
Stay with the women.
Come here.
The Russians have surrounded us.
What will we do?
You can try to get through.
I'm not taking another step.
Think it over.
The Russians are only after us.
As women, you have a chance.
Give it a try.
Good luck.
When you go past the Russians,
don't look anybody in the eye.
Don't forget.
Good luck.
The Russians!
Let's go.
Go ahead... I can't go on.
Please.
I have to try.
Don't be angry with me.
I'll manage.
Doctor!
My comrades want to surrender
to the Russians. May I join you?
The Führer is dead.
You want to fight the war alone?
I feel committed to my oath.
Then talk to the Brigadeführer.
The Russians are clearing the area.
- Yes? - No resistance.
No shots have been fired.
- They'll be here in an hour.
What should we do? - Our honor
won't allow us to surrender!
What does that mean?
When the Russians come,
we fire until we're out of bullets.
Then we blow our brains out.
Rubbish! Is this murderous,
suicidal killing for the sake
of prestige the only way out?
We're SS officers.
We can't outlive the Führer's death!
Who else feels that way?
Want to sit with me a moment?
- I'd love to.
Why do you want to go on living?
And why do you want to die?
See this?
The Führer himself gave it to me.
A final decoration?
Perhaps. Hitler gave it to me
at his farewell.
He made me swear a vow.
That I would kill myself
the moment the Russians captured me.
Hitler made you promise
to kill yourself?
But why?
He probably didn't want me to be
forced to speak negatively of him.
But as a diplomat, you are protected
by international law.
Who will benefit
if you keep your promise?
They're here!
Don't shoot, comrades!
We have surrendered.
The war is over.
It's over.
Germany officially surrendered
on May 7, 1945.
It was agreed that all hostilities end
at midnight, May 8.
By then,
the war had cost over 50 million lives.
6 million Jews had been murdered
in German concentration camps.
GERDA CHRISTIAN was able to escape
and avoided imprisonment.
She died in Düsseldorf on April 14, 1997.
PROF. DR. ERNST-GÜNTHER SCHENK was
released from Soviet captivity in 1953.
He died in Aachen on December 21, 1998.
GENERAL WILHELM MOHNKE was released
from Soviet captivity in 1955.
He died in Damp, near Eckernförde,
on August 6, 2001.
GENERAL HELMUTH WEIDLING
died in Soviet captivity in 1955.
PROFESSOR WERNER HAASE
was arrested by the Red Army
in the military hospital bunker.
He died in Soviet captivity in 1945.
OTTO GÜNSCHE was captured by the Soviets
and was released from Bautzen prison
in East Germany in May 1956.
He died in Lohmar, near Bonn, in 2003.
HANNA REITSCH
survived the war and went on
to set many world flying records.
She died on August 28, 1979.
LORD ROBERT VON GREIM
committed suicide in Salzburg
on May 24, 1945.
HEINZ LINGE and JOHANNES HENTSCHEL
were captured by the Soviets.
Linge was released in 1955.
He died in Bremen in 1980.
Hentschel was released in 1949.
He died in Achern on April 27, 1982.
CONSTANZE MANZIARLY
vanished without a trace in Berlin,
during her escape.
ALBERT SPEER
was arrested in Flensburg in 1945.
He was sentenced 20 years at the Nuremberg
Trial and was released in 1966.
He died in London in 1981.
GENERALS KEITEL and JODL
were sentenced to death
at the Nuremberg Trial and executed.
HERMANN GÖRING
was sentenced to death
but committed suicide in prison
before the execution was carried out.
HEINRICH HIMMLER
tried to escape under a false identity
with other fleeing refugees. After being
exposed and captured, he committed suicide.
MARTIN BORMANN and DR. LUDWIG STUMPFEGGER
committed suicide
close to Lehrtertrain station
on the morning of May 2, 1945.
ROCHUS MISCH
was released from Soviet captivity
in 1955. He now lives in Berlin.
TRAUDL JUNGE was classified by
the Western Allies as a "young follower".
She continued to work as a secretary
for various companies and lived in Munich
until her death in 2002.
Of course, the terrible things
I heard from the Nuremberg Trials
about the 6 million Jews
and the people of other races
who were killed were facts
that shocked me deeply.
But I wasn't able to see
the connection with my own past.
I was satisfied
that I wasn't personally to blame
and that I hadn't known
about those things.
I wasn't aware of the extent.
But one day I went past
the memorial plaque
which had been put up for
Sophie Scholl in Franz Josef Strasse,
and I saw that she was born
the same year as me,
and she was executed the same year
I started working for Hitler.
And at that moment
I actually sensed
that it was no excuse to be young,
and that it would have been possible
to find things out.