1
00:00:22,330 --> 00:00:25,940
DOWNFALL

2
00:00:25,980 --> 00:00:31,710
I feel as if I should be angry
with that child, that...

3
00:00:32,230 --> 00:00:36,400
naive young girl.
Or that I must not forgive her...

4
00:00:36,920 --> 00:00:40,560
for not recognising the
nature of that monster.

5
00:00:41,610 --> 00:00:44,520
For not being aware of what
she was getting into.

6
00:00:45,040 --> 00:00:48,690
And especially that I went
along without thinking.

7
00:00:49,210 --> 00:00:55,460
Because I wasn't a fanatical Nazi.
I could have said, in Berlin:

8
00:00:55,460 --> 00:01:00,140
'No, I'm not doing it. I don't want
to go to the Führer's headquarters.'

9
00:01:01,180 --> 00:01:04,310
But I didn't do that.
I was too curious.

10
00:01:04,830 --> 00:01:07,950
I also didn't realise...

11
00:01:09,000 --> 00:01:14,200
that destiny would take me somewhere
I didn't want to be.

12
00:01:15,240 --> 00:01:20,970
But, nevertheless, I find it hard
to forgive myself.

13
00:01:27,040 --> 00:01:28,080
The ladies are here.

14
00:01:30,160 --> 00:01:33,810
It's confirmed.
-They can pass.

15
00:02:02,840 --> 00:02:05,970
'Wolfsschanze'
headquarters of the Führer

16
00:02:07,010 --> 00:02:08,570
November 1942
Rastenburg, East-Prussia

17
00:02:12,210 --> 00:02:14,300
Sit down, ladies.

18
00:02:15,860 --> 00:02:21,070
One moment. The Führer is feeding
his dog. He'll see you in a short while.

19
00:02:23,150 --> 00:02:27,840
Can you tell us... How are we supposed
to address the Führer?

20
00:02:28,880 --> 00:02:33,040
The Führer first speaks to you
and then you reply: Heil, mein Führer.

21
00:02:33,040 --> 00:02:35,130
And the Nazi salute?

22
00:02:35,130 --> 00:02:37,730
That won't be necessary...

23
00:02:37,730 --> 00:02:42,940
since the Führer isn't looking for
a soldier, but for a secretary.

24
00:02:43,460 --> 00:02:46,060
Act as normal and calm
as you can.

25
00:02:47,100 --> 00:02:49,180
I'll see if
he has time for you.

26
00:02:53,350 --> 00:02:56,470
Mein Führer,
the ladies from Berlin are here.

27
00:03:15,230 --> 00:03:20,950
Thank you for coming
in the middle of the night.

28
00:03:21,480 --> 00:03:26,160
Sometimes, during a war,
one is not in control of time.

29
00:03:28,170 --> 00:03:31,810
Can I ask your name?
-Margarethe Lorenz.

30
00:03:32,330 --> 00:03:34,930
Where are you from?
-From Fulda.

31
00:03:35,460 --> 00:03:39,100
And what is your name?
-Ursula Puttkammer. Heil, mein Führer.

32
00:03:39,620 --> 00:03:42,750
No need for that.
Where are you from?

33
00:03:43,270 --> 00:03:45,350
Frankfurt am Main, mein Füh...

34
00:03:47,430 --> 00:03:49,520
Hannah Potrovsky,
born and raised in Berlin.

35
00:03:50,560 --> 00:03:52,640
In Pankow, to be precise.

36
00:03:53,680 --> 00:03:56,280
Hedwig Brandt
from Crailsheim, Schwaben.

37
00:03:57,850 --> 00:04:01,490
And you are?
-Traudl Humps. I'm from Munich.

38
00:04:04,620 --> 00:04:06,180
A lady from Munich.

39
00:04:13,470 --> 00:04:17,110
Shall we start then,
Fräulein Humps?

40
00:04:28,050 --> 00:04:31,690
My Blondi won't hurt you.
She's very intelligent.

41
00:04:32,220 --> 00:04:35,860
She's much smarter
than most people.

42
00:04:40,550 --> 00:04:43,670
First, sit down, please.

43
00:04:44,190 --> 00:04:48,360
Don't be nervous. I make
many mistakes during dictation.

44
00:04:48,360 --> 00:04:52,000
You won't make nearly as many.

45
00:05:01,380 --> 00:05:02,940
You're very young.

46
00:05:02,940 --> 00:05:08,160
How old are you?
-22, mein Führer.

47
00:05:12,850 --> 00:05:17,020
My German fellow-countrymen
and women...

48
00:05:18,070 --> 00:05:19,110
...fellow party members.

49
00:05:19,110 --> 00:05:23,810
It is, I think, rather special...

50
00:05:24,330 --> 00:05:30,590
that, after 20 years of service, a man still
stands in front of his supporters...

51
00:05:33,720 --> 00:05:40,500
...and that in all those 20 years,
his program never needed to be modified.

52
00:05:55,630 --> 00:05:59,280
I suggest we try it again.

53
00:06:11,570 --> 00:06:13,650
I did it.
He hired me.

54
00:06:30,350 --> 00:06:32,950
Berlin - 20 April 1945
Hitler's 56th birthday

55
00:06:33,480 --> 00:06:35,040
two and a half years later

56
00:06:35,560 --> 00:06:36,610
Take cover.

57
00:06:41,250 --> 00:06:44,900
Hurry. Continue.
Get that off the street.

58
00:06:47,280 --> 00:06:48,320
Take cover.

59
00:07:01,450 --> 00:07:02,500
That's artillery fire.

60
00:07:03,020 --> 00:07:07,190
Don't be silly.
Where would it be coming from?

61
00:07:07,710 --> 00:07:10,320
You're right. These are no planes,
this is artillery.

62
00:07:11,370 --> 00:07:16,060
It's the Russians.
What a birthday present.

63
00:07:20,230 --> 00:07:22,320
Where is that cannon fire coming from?

64
00:07:22,840 --> 00:07:25,450
Happy Birthday,
mein Führer.

65
00:07:25,970 --> 00:07:28,060
The city centre of Berlin
is under fire.

66
00:07:29,290 --> 00:07:32,940
Grenades have hit near the Brandenburger
Tor and the Reichstag.

67
00:07:33,280 --> 00:07:35,880
Where did they come from?
-We don't know yet.

68
00:07:36,410 --> 00:07:39,540
I have Koller on the line.
-Give me Koller.

69
00:07:40,060 --> 00:07:44,230
Koller, do you know Berlin
is under artillery fire?

70
00:07:45,280 --> 00:07:47,880
No.
-Can't you hear the shooting?

71
00:07:48,400 --> 00:07:51,530
No, I'm in Wildpark-Werder.
-Berlin is chaotic.

72
00:07:52,060 --> 00:07:54,660
Apparently, the Russians captured
a railway bridge over the Oder.

73
00:07:55,710 --> 00:07:58,840
The enemy has no railway
artillery near the Oder.

74
00:07:59,360 --> 00:08:01,450
It's not long-range artillery.

75
00:08:01,450 --> 00:08:06,660
The anti-aircraft defence near the
Zoo-Bunker reports they're 10 to 12...

76
00:08:06,670 --> 00:08:11,360
...cm calibres. The Russians have
positions near Marzahn.

77
00:08:11,360 --> 00:08:16,050
That's only 12 kilometres from the centre.
Are the Russians that close?

78
00:08:16,580 --> 00:08:20,230
They should hang the entire
Luftwaffe leadership.

79
00:08:21,770 --> 00:08:24,370
This is unheard-of.

80
00:08:24,920 --> 00:08:27,530
The Russians are at 12 kilometres
from the city centre.

81
00:08:28,580 --> 00:08:31,180
Nobody told me anything.
I had to ask.

82
00:08:32,230 --> 00:08:34,830
Maybe it's long-range artillery,
after all.

83
00:08:35,360 --> 00:08:38,490
That railway bridge over the Oder...
-Nonsense.

84
00:08:44,750 --> 00:08:47,350
That Himmler,
such a pompous buffoon.

85
00:08:47,880 --> 00:08:53,610
Party bosses, everywhere.
They make me so sick.

86
00:08:56,220 --> 00:08:58,310
The Führer starts
'Clausewitz' today.

87
00:08:59,350 --> 00:09:02,990
Berlin as a front city.
He won't be able to keep the city.

88
00:09:03,510 --> 00:09:06,640
If the Führer stays here,
the Reich will go down with him.

89
00:09:07,160 --> 00:09:10,800
We have to talk him out of it.
Talk to Hewel.

90
00:09:10,800 --> 00:09:14,440
He's the only diplomat
with any influence on him.

91
00:09:14,970 --> 00:09:18,090
Hewel tried everything.
It's useless.

92
00:09:18,610 --> 00:09:21,210
Talk to your sister-in-law, then.

93
00:09:21,730 --> 00:09:26,940
Why not? You're married
to the sister of Eva Braun.

94
00:09:27,460 --> 00:09:31,100
We must try everything.
Berlin is almost surrounded.

95
00:09:31,100 --> 00:09:34,230
You're still young.
You'll be a father soon.

96
00:09:34,750 --> 00:09:37,350
Do you want to die here?
-Absolutely not.

97
00:09:42,560 --> 00:09:44,640
Gentlemen, the Führer.

98
00:09:55,490 --> 00:09:59,140
Everything out. Quickly.
We're leaving in two hours.

99
00:10:07,300 --> 00:10:10,430
What's going on?
-We're leaving.

100
00:10:12,510 --> 00:10:14,070
'Clausewitz' has started.

101
00:10:14,510 --> 00:10:18,160
All the ministries and departments
are leaving Berlin.

102
00:10:18,760 --> 00:10:21,880
And who's going to look after
the people and the soldiers?

103
00:10:22,920 --> 00:10:26,560
Don't ask me, professor.
-This is insane.

104
00:10:44,300 --> 00:10:46,380
Professor.

105
00:10:47,430 --> 00:10:49,510
I won't allow the
evacuation of my office.

106
00:10:50,030 --> 00:10:54,190
Is that so?
-Food supply would collapse.

107
00:10:54,710 --> 00:10:57,320
A good soldier can
always find food.

108
00:10:57,840 --> 00:11:02,520
And when there's fighting all over the city,
where does he get it? The population.

109
00:11:03,410 --> 00:11:06,530
It's irresponsible.
-It's an order from the Führer.

110
00:11:08,100 --> 00:11:11,220
As department head, I
report to the SS and to Himmler.

111
00:11:11,740 --> 00:11:15,900
But as a doctor, I'm part of the Wehrmacht
and they're not leaving yet.

112
00:11:16,420 --> 00:11:19,030
Keep that in mind.

113
00:11:23,710 --> 00:11:27,360
The professor stays in Berlin.
Get him the proper papers.

114
00:11:30,930 --> 00:11:32,490
We're leaving.

115
00:11:46,050 --> 00:11:48,650
Everything for Germany.
Heil, mein Führer.

116
00:11:50,220 --> 00:11:52,820
Führer, I...
Heil, mein Führer.

117
00:11:54,260 --> 00:11:56,860
They're in such a hurry
to get away from here.

118
00:11:57,380 --> 00:11:59,470
The brown nosing is the worst.

119
00:11:59,990 --> 00:12:03,630
They say 'Sieg Heil'. but they think
'Lick my... you know what.'

120
00:12:07,720 --> 00:12:12,400
Mein Führer, I beg you: Leave Berlin.
It is not too late yet.

121
00:12:13,440 --> 00:12:15,000
Too late?

122
00:12:16,570 --> 00:12:18,650
Hewel, come here for a moment.

123
00:12:19,280 --> 00:12:23,970
I'm sure you agree we should contact
the Allies...

124
00:12:24,490 --> 00:12:29,690
...and start conducting politics.
-Certainly. We need politics.

125
00:12:29,690 --> 00:12:33,860
Politics?
I don't do politics anymore.

126
00:12:33,860 --> 00:12:36,460
I'm fed up with it.

127
00:12:38,540 --> 00:12:42,710
When I'm dead, you'll have plenty
of time for politics.

128
00:12:43,230 --> 00:12:49,100
It's good, dear Himmler.
My loyal Heinrich.

129
00:12:49,100 --> 00:12:54,040
It's good.
Just go.

130
00:13:14,390 --> 00:13:15,950
He has no strength left.

131
00:13:16,990 --> 00:13:20,630
What did you expect from a
vegetarian teetotaller?

132
00:13:21,160 --> 00:13:24,800
Seriously, though, Fegelein.
I'm taking control now.

133
00:13:25,840 --> 00:13:27,920
Berlin will fall in a couple of days.

134
00:13:28,440 --> 00:13:33,130
When the Führer's dead, who will
the Allies negotiate with?

135
00:13:33,130 --> 00:13:36,250
Why do you think they'll
negotiate with you?

136
00:13:36,770 --> 00:13:39,900
The Nazi state and my SS are needed
to maintain order.

137
00:13:40,940 --> 00:13:43,020
One hour with Eisenhower
and he'll feel the same way.

138
00:13:44,060 --> 00:13:48,220
The first contact has been made.
-Careful, that's high treason.

139
00:13:48,750 --> 00:13:51,350
Fegelein, I have other concerns.

140
00:13:51,350 --> 00:13:56,550
Should I give Eisenhower the Nazi salute
or shake his hand?

141
00:14:03,160 --> 00:14:04,720
Look at that.

142
00:14:07,850 --> 00:14:09,420
The best guests
always arrive late.

143
00:14:09,940 --> 00:14:15,150
Leaving already, gentlemen?
I wanted to talk to you.

144
00:14:15,680 --> 00:14:20,370
The scorched-earth order...
-I really have to go now.

145
00:14:20,370 --> 00:14:23,500
Come and see me one day
in Hohenlychen.

146
00:14:26,110 --> 00:14:31,320
I'm going north to help with the
battle of Berlin there.

147
00:14:41,240 --> 00:14:45,940
You know, Speer... There's an
advantage to those bombings.

148
00:14:46,460 --> 00:14:51,670
It's easier to clean up debris
than to demolish everything ourselves.

149
00:14:53,240 --> 00:14:56,890
When the war will be over,
reconstruction will be quick.

150
00:14:58,460 --> 00:15:04,190
We spent thousands of hours
together with these replicas.

151
00:15:05,760 --> 00:15:08,890
You're a true genius, Speer.

152
00:15:10,450 --> 00:15:16,190
Yes, absolutely. Only you and I know that
the Third Reich would be inconceivable...

153
00:15:16,710 --> 00:15:21,410
...with only warehouses and factories.
Skyscrapers and hotels.

154
00:15:22,450 --> 00:15:26,620
This Third Reich will be a treasury
full of art and culture...

155
00:15:27,150 --> 00:15:30,280
...that will survive thousands of years.

156
00:15:30,280 --> 00:15:34,760
We see, before us, the ancient cities,
the Acropolis...

157
00:15:35,280 --> 00:15:37,890
We see the medieval cities...
the cathedrals...

158
00:15:37,890 --> 00:15:42,590
...and we know that the people
need that.

159
00:15:45,720 --> 00:15:48,320
Indeed, Speer.

160
00:15:50,930 --> 00:15:53,020
That was my vision...

161
00:15:54,590 --> 00:15:57,190
...and it still is.

162
00:15:59,800 --> 00:16:05,020
Mein Führer, if you want to realize
these plans, you must leave Berlin.

163
00:16:10,760 --> 00:16:13,360
Eva, you say something.

164
00:16:13,890 --> 00:16:17,020
He's the Führer.
He knows what's best.

165
00:16:17,540 --> 00:16:22,230
You must leave Berlin.
The Russians almost have us isolated.

166
00:16:22,750 --> 00:16:24,840
I can't do that, my child.

167
00:16:25,360 --> 00:16:30,580
I would be like a lama priest
with an empty prayer wheel.

168
00:16:30,580 --> 00:16:36,600
I have to solve the problem,
here in Berlin, or perish.

169
00:16:38,170 --> 00:16:39,210
Speer...

170
00:16:41,820 --> 00:16:43,390
...what do you think?

171
00:16:44,950 --> 00:16:48,080
You have to be on the stage
when the curtain falls.

172
00:17:06,430 --> 00:17:07,480
Reload.

173
00:17:18,060 --> 00:17:20,150
Go away. Leave me alone.

174
00:17:20,670 --> 00:17:24,320
How old are you? Twelve?
And you? Fourteen?

175
00:17:24,840 --> 00:17:27,970
Why are you here?
To play at war? Go home.

176
00:17:28,490 --> 00:17:32,140
Who are you? What do you want?
I want my son. Alive.

177
00:17:32,660 --> 00:17:35,790
You should be proud.
He destroyed two tanks.

178
00:17:36,320 --> 00:17:39,440
The Führer will decorate him
for it, today.

179
00:17:39,970 --> 00:17:43,100
You're still young.
At which front did you fight?

180
00:17:44,140 --> 00:17:45,700
I haven't had
the honour yet.

181
00:17:46,230 --> 00:17:50,920
Count yourself lucky.
Send the children home.

182
00:17:51,970 --> 00:17:54,050
We'll defend this position
to the last man.

183
00:17:54,570 --> 00:17:57,700
Which position?
This is not a position, it's a trap.

184
00:17:58,750 --> 00:18:01,880
The Russians will come from two sides
and you won't be able to get out.

185
00:18:02,400 --> 00:18:04,480
We'll shoot back.
-What with?

186
00:18:05,530 --> 00:18:07,090
With the anti-aircraft guns.

187
00:18:07,620 --> 00:18:11,270
The Russians will arrive with several
armies, tanks and heavy artillery.

188
00:18:11,790 --> 00:18:15,960
Do you really think you'll
last even five minutes?

189
00:18:16,480 --> 00:18:19,090
We promised the Führer.

190
00:18:19,610 --> 00:18:22,740
Don't you understand?
The war is lost.

191
00:18:23,270 --> 00:18:24,310
Coward.

192
00:18:29,010 --> 00:18:31,090
Go away. Right now.

193
00:18:32,660 --> 00:18:36,830
If you're still here when the Russians
arrive, you'll all be dead.

194
00:18:40,480 --> 00:18:46,220
The 9th army had to retreat
or they would have been decimated...

195
00:18:46,750 --> 00:18:51,960
We won't retreat the 9th army.
Busse must fight where he stands.

196
00:18:52,480 --> 00:18:55,090
Führer, then the 9th army is lost.

197
00:18:55,620 --> 00:19:00,830
We'll push back the Soviet armies
in the north and east...

198
00:19:00,830 --> 00:19:05,530
...with a ruthless, mighty attack.

199
00:19:06,570 --> 00:19:07,610
Using which units?

200
00:19:08,660 --> 00:19:13,350
Steiner will attack from the north
and join the 9th army.

201
00:19:15,440 --> 00:19:18,050
The 9th army is unable to move.

202
00:19:18,570 --> 00:19:20,660
The enemy outnumbers us ten times.

203
00:19:21,700 --> 00:19:24,310
Wenck's 12th army must
support them.

204
00:19:24,830 --> 00:19:30,050
The 12th army is approaching the Elbe.
-Then it must turn around.

205
00:19:30,570 --> 00:19:34,740
Then the western front would be open.
-Do you doubt my orders?

206
00:19:35,270 --> 00:19:38,920
I think I've been
clear enough.

207
00:19:40,480 --> 00:19:47,790
The Allies will see that only we
can stop the Bolsheviks.

208
00:19:48,310 --> 00:19:53,010
We have to keep Berlin and
make a deal with the Americans.

209
00:20:12,310 --> 00:20:15,440
Mohnke, you're here.
-Mein Führer.

210
00:20:17,010 --> 00:20:21,700
Today, 'Clausewitz' started.
Berlin will be a front city.

211
00:20:22,220 --> 00:20:26,920
You will be the commander of the
defensive circle around the citadel.

212
00:20:27,440 --> 00:20:31,620
We'll fight until the last man, in Berlin.

213
00:20:32,140 --> 00:20:36,310
There are still three million civilians here.
They have to be evacuated.

214
00:20:37,880 --> 00:20:44,140
I understand your concern, Mohnke.
But we have to be cold as ice.

215
00:20:44,660 --> 00:20:48,310
We can't spend any energy
on so-called civilians.

216
00:20:49,880 --> 00:20:54,050
With all due respect, what will
happen to the women and children...

217
00:20:54,570 --> 00:20:57,180
...and the thousands of wounded
and elderly?

218
00:20:57,700 --> 00:21:01,350
In a war such as this one,
there are no civilians.

219
00:21:02,400 --> 00:21:04,490
The Führer has lost all
sense of reality.

220
00:21:05,010 --> 00:21:08,140
He's moving divisions around
that no longer exist.

221
00:21:08,660 --> 00:21:13,880
Gruppe Steiner has been scattered,
yet Steiner must attack. Madness.

222
00:21:14,400 --> 00:21:18,050
But why don't you tell him that?
-He doesn't listen to reason.

223
00:21:18,570 --> 00:21:22,750
Something has to happen.
-Are you crazy? He'll throw us out.

224
00:21:25,360 --> 00:21:29,010
We're soldiers.
We took an oath.

225
00:21:29,010 --> 00:21:31,610
Does that mean we can't use
our own brains anymore?

226
00:21:32,140 --> 00:21:35,270
And that's coming from you?
A ruthless careerist?

227
00:21:36,310 --> 00:21:37,360
I beg your pardon?

228
00:22:02,570 --> 00:22:04,660
Where were you?
-None of your business.

229
00:22:13,600 --> 00:22:17,770
The most successful tank hunters of the
Berlin Hitler-Jugend stand before you.

230
00:22:27,120 --> 00:22:28,170
I'm proud of you.

231
00:22:31,820 --> 00:22:35,990
This boy took out two tanks
using anti-tank shells.

232
00:22:36,520 --> 00:22:41,210
His name is Peter Kranz.
-So you're Peter.

233
00:22:43,300 --> 00:22:46,950
I wish my generals were
as brave as you.

234
00:22:56,860 --> 00:22:57,900
Very good.

235
00:23:04,450 --> 00:23:06,530
You've made history.

236
00:23:07,050 --> 00:23:11,750
And when Germania will rise
from these ruins...

237
00:23:12,270 --> 00:23:14,360
...you will be the heroes.

238
00:23:15,920 --> 00:23:18,010
Heil, to you.

239
00:23:47,750 --> 00:23:51,920
I don't know about you,
but I prefer air raids.

240
00:23:52,960 --> 00:23:57,660
What will happen to us?
-I could go if I wanted to.

241
00:23:58,180 --> 00:24:02,880
But everybody is deserting him.
We can't all go, can we?

242
00:24:03,400 --> 00:24:04,960
I can't go either.

243
00:24:10,690 --> 00:24:13,290
I wouldn't know
where to go.

244
00:24:13,810 --> 00:24:18,490
My parents and all
my friends warned me.

245
00:24:19,020 --> 00:24:21,620
Don't get involved with the Nazis.

246
00:24:22,140 --> 00:24:25,260
What should I say:
'Hello, I made a mistake'?

247
00:24:25,260 --> 00:24:27,860
'When things went wrong,
I admitted my mistake.'

248
00:24:29,950 --> 00:24:32,550
Life will go on.

249
00:24:40,990 --> 00:24:44,120
What do you think, Herr Oberst?
-We have to go.

250
00:24:47,240 --> 00:24:50,370
Go where?
-I don't know.

251
00:24:50,890 --> 00:24:52,970
Wherever they need us.

252
00:25:04,420 --> 00:25:07,540
Let's go upstairs.
We'll party.

253
00:25:08,070 --> 00:25:09,110
Come on.

254
00:25:12,740 --> 00:25:13,780
Come, children.

255
00:25:21,080 --> 00:25:23,680
We should have fun today.

256
00:25:29,580 --> 00:25:34,780
Wherever the enemy goes,
all they find is destruction.

257
00:25:35,820 --> 00:25:38,430
That's the death sentence
for the German people.

258
00:25:39,990 --> 00:25:43,630
No power, no gas, no drinking
water, no coal, no traffic.

259
00:25:44,670 --> 00:25:51,440
If you destroy everything, our country
will go back to the Middle Ages.

260
00:25:51,960 --> 00:25:55,090
This order denies the people
any chance of survival.

261
00:25:56,130 --> 00:26:00,290
If the war is lost, what does it matter
that the people are lost too?

262
00:26:00,810 --> 00:26:06,540
The primary necessities of life of the
German people aren't relevant, right now.

263
00:26:07,060 --> 00:26:10,180
On the contrary.
We'd best destroy them ourselves.

264
00:26:10,700 --> 00:26:13,310
Our people turned out weak...

265
00:26:13,830 --> 00:26:17,470
...and according to the laws of nature,
they should die out.

266
00:26:17,990 --> 00:26:21,110
They're your people.
You're their Führer.

267
00:26:21,640 --> 00:26:24,240
What remains after this battle...

268
00:26:24,760 --> 00:26:29,440
...is only the inferior.
The superior will have fallen.

269
00:26:36,450 --> 00:26:40,090
Come along. You have to dance.

270
00:26:40,610 --> 00:26:43,740
Care to dance, Fräulein Braun?
-I'd love to.

271
00:27:09,400 --> 00:27:11,480
May I?
-Go ahead.

272
00:27:12,520 --> 00:27:13,560
What's wrong?

273
00:27:18,770 --> 00:27:21,890
We have to leave Berlin, Eva.
You must convince him.

274
00:27:26,060 --> 00:27:27,620
Or else, come with me.

275
00:27:37,070 --> 00:27:38,110
You'll die.

276
00:27:59,320 --> 00:28:02,450
Can somebody play some music?
I want to dance.

277
00:28:02,970 --> 00:28:04,010
Dance.

278
00:28:08,240 --> 00:28:10,320
Do you have a request?
-As long as it swings.

279
00:28:38,730 --> 00:28:40,290
Traudl.

280
00:28:46,170 --> 00:28:48,770
It's all so unreal.

281
00:28:49,290 --> 00:28:55,010
It's like a dream you
can't get out of.

282
00:28:55,530 --> 00:28:57,100
It keeps on going.

283
00:29:01,260 --> 00:29:03,880
Gerda, I don't feel well.

284
00:29:40,500 --> 00:29:42,070
Traudl, come.

285
00:30:02,240 --> 00:30:03,810
I did not move...

286
00:30:05,900 --> 00:30:08,520
I did not move
my command post.

287
00:30:09,930 --> 00:30:12,030
To the west? How so?

288
00:30:13,070 --> 00:30:15,690
I'm at 1000 meters from the enemy.
-General.

289
00:30:36,350 --> 00:30:38,450
And, general?

290
00:30:38,450 --> 00:30:41,590
I'll be executed.
-What? Why?

291
00:30:42,640 --> 00:30:46,820
They think I moved my
command post to the west.

292
00:30:47,870 --> 00:30:50,480
Be sensible, general.
-Come along.

293
00:31:08,220 --> 00:31:09,780
Schenck.
-Mohnke.

294
00:31:10,270 --> 00:31:14,950
I'm under the chancellery.
I'm commander of the citadel now.

295
00:31:15,480 --> 00:31:19,640
I need help.
-That will be difficult. Everything's gone.

296
00:31:20,160 --> 00:31:22,250
My assistant and I are
the only ones here.

297
00:31:23,160 --> 00:31:25,240
You're a doctor, aren't you?
-Yes, an internist.

298
00:31:25,760 --> 00:31:29,930
Commandeer a car and
bring all the medication...

299
00:31:30,450 --> 00:31:33,050
...you can find, to me.

300
00:31:33,570 --> 00:31:36,700
I'll do my best.
-Thanks. Hurry.

301
00:32:26,890 --> 00:32:28,980
I need to talk to the Führer.

302
00:32:30,020 --> 00:32:33,660
What about?
-I'm going to be executed.

303
00:32:37,310 --> 00:32:38,350
Wait here.

304
00:32:39,910 --> 00:32:40,950
Your weapon, please.

305
00:32:48,110 --> 00:32:49,290
Not here.

306
00:32:52,860 --> 00:32:56,510
Guard post 2.
Understood.

307
00:32:58,590 --> 00:33:00,150
General...

308
00:33:02,760 --> 00:33:04,320
Not you.

309
00:33:27,250 --> 00:33:30,370
What's going on here?
Why am I going to be executed?

310
00:33:30,900 --> 00:33:35,060
You know that any evasive manoeuvre
towards the west is forbidden.

311
00:33:35,580 --> 00:33:40,270
Officers who don't obey,
must be executed.

312
00:33:40,270 --> 00:33:43,910
What do you mean?
My troops have been fighting for days.

313
00:33:44,960 --> 00:33:49,120
My command post
is a kilometre away from the front line.

314
00:33:49,640 --> 00:33:51,210
Continue.

315
00:33:51,210 --> 00:33:55,890
Do you see this? I don't want you
to use that tone with me.

316
00:33:57,460 --> 00:34:00,580
And now, do whatever
you feel you must.

317
00:34:01,100 --> 00:34:05,270
It's best if you tell this to the
Führer yourself. Come along.

318
00:34:20,610 --> 00:34:24,780
You can't pass, Oberst.
-Orders from brigade-führer Mohnke:

319
00:34:24,780 --> 00:34:27,900
I have to get into the hospital.
We need medication.

320
00:34:28,420 --> 00:34:31,030
There's nobody left.
They all took off.

321
00:34:31,550 --> 00:34:34,150
And the wounded?
-How should I know?

322
00:34:34,670 --> 00:34:36,760
I'm going to have a look.
You stay here.

323
00:34:36,950 --> 00:34:41,120
Be very careful.
There are lots of Russians here.

324
00:34:41,950 --> 00:34:46,630
See that? That's where the
Reich ends. Behind it, is Russkie land.

325
00:34:58,470 --> 00:35:00,030
May I?

326
00:35:00,030 --> 00:35:10,950
He's damned stubborn.
Why doesn't he let me do that?

327
00:36:12,180 --> 00:36:15,820
I should have been back by now.
Are you sure the Führer still needs me?

328
00:36:16,350 --> 00:36:19,470
Drink.
-Führer's orders.

329
00:36:19,990 --> 00:36:23,090
You made a big impression
on the Führer.

330
00:36:23,620 --> 00:36:25,700
But you don't think Steiner
will attack, do you?

331
00:36:26,220 --> 00:36:28,820
I doubt whether Steiner
is able to do anything...

332
00:36:29,340 --> 00:36:31,950
...but you probably know that
better than I do.

333
00:36:32,990 --> 00:36:36,110
If Steiner doesn't attack,
Berlin is lost.

334
00:36:45,790 --> 00:36:47,870
The Führer was impressed
with your report.

335
00:36:48,390 --> 00:36:52,560
He puts you in command of
the defence of Berlin.

336
00:36:53,600 --> 00:36:58,280
I'd have preferred it
if he executed me.

337
00:37:19,210 --> 00:37:21,290
Let them get closer.

338
00:37:22,700 --> 00:37:24,270
Tank alert.

339
00:37:24,270 --> 00:37:29,150
Take it easy. Wait, kid.
They're still too far.

340
00:38:19,430 --> 00:38:22,550
Is it German artillery that I hear?
-I'm afraid not.

341
00:38:23,070 --> 00:38:25,160
But hasn't Steiner's
attack started?

342
00:38:28,800 --> 00:38:31,410
You have to go as fast as you can.
Time is running out.

343
00:38:31,930 --> 00:38:34,010
But the Führer has
the situation under control.

344
00:38:35,050 --> 00:38:36,610
Steiner will make
all the difference.

345
00:38:37,660 --> 00:38:40,780
He says it will change
military history.

346
00:38:41,300 --> 00:38:44,950
Everybody, but the Führer, knows
that's a fantasy.

347
00:38:45,470 --> 00:38:50,680
I even wonder if he believes it himself.
-Why would he be playing games?

348
00:38:51,200 --> 00:38:52,760
What does he have to lose?

349
00:38:54,320 --> 00:38:55,360
I don't believe a word of it.

350
00:38:56,410 --> 00:38:59,010
The enemy made a breakthrough.

351
00:38:59,530 --> 00:39:03,180
They took Zossen and are advancing
towards Stahnsdorf.

352
00:39:03,710 --> 00:39:07,350
They're at the northern city border,
between Frohnau and Pankow.

353
00:39:07,880 --> 00:39:13,090
In the east, they reached
Lichtenberg, Mahlsdorf and Karlshorst.

354
00:39:13,610 --> 00:39:16,740
If Steiner attacks,
everything will be alright.

355
00:39:20,390 --> 00:39:21,960
Mein Führer...

356
00:39:23,520 --> 00:39:25,090
Steiner...

357
00:39:26,650 --> 00:39:29,260
Steiner didn't have enough force.

358
00:39:29,780 --> 00:39:32,390
The attack didn't take place.

359
00:39:48,700 --> 00:39:54,430
The following stay here:
Keitel, Jodl, Krebs and Burgdorf.

360
00:40:09,070 --> 00:40:14,280
That was an order.
Steiner's attack was an order.

361
00:40:14,800 --> 00:40:18,970
How dare you
ignore my orders?

362
00:40:21,060 --> 00:40:23,670
Is this what it came to?

363
00:40:25,230 --> 00:40:30,450
The military, everybody lied
to me. Even the SS.

364
00:40:30,970 --> 00:40:36,180
The generals are no more than
a bunch of disloyal cowards.

365
00:40:36,710 --> 00:40:38,790
I don't allow that...

366
00:40:39,310 --> 00:40:44,010
Cowards, traitors and incompetents.
-Führer, this is outrageous.

367
00:40:44,530 --> 00:40:48,180
The generals are the scum
of the German people.

368
00:40:48,700 --> 00:40:51,310
No sense of honour.

369
00:40:51,830 --> 00:40:56,000
You call yourself general because
you spent years at the academy...

370
00:40:57,050 --> 00:40:59,650
...where you only learnt
to use knife and fork.

371
00:41:00,170 --> 00:41:04,350
For years, the military
obstructed me.

372
00:41:04,870 --> 00:41:09,040
All you ever did is
thwart me.

373
00:41:09,810 --> 00:41:12,930
I should have had...

374
00:41:13,460 --> 00:41:18,150
...all the high officers executed.
Like Stalin did.

375
00:41:22,880 --> 00:41:25,490
I never went to the academy.

376
00:41:25,490 --> 00:41:32,270
But I conquered all
of Europe on my own.

377
00:41:37,070 --> 00:41:38,630
Traitors.

378
00:41:39,150 --> 00:41:43,840
I've been betrayed and deceived
from the start.

379
00:41:44,370 --> 00:41:49,060
Such enormous betrayal
of the German people.

380
00:41:50,100 --> 00:41:55,320
But all these traitors will pay.
With their own blood.

381
00:41:56,290 --> 00:41:58,370
They will drown
in their own blood.

382
00:42:00,980 --> 00:42:02,540
Calm, Gerda.

383
00:42:10,100 --> 00:42:13,750
All my orders have
been ignored.

384
00:42:15,320 --> 00:42:19,490
How can I be a leader
under these circumstances?

385
00:42:21,270 --> 00:42:23,350
It's over.

386
00:42:27,290 --> 00:42:30,420
The war is lost.

387
00:42:36,440 --> 00:42:40,090
But if you think this means
I'll leave Berlin...

388
00:42:40,620 --> 00:42:44,790
...you're wrong. I'd rather
shoot a bullet through my head.

389
00:42:49,630 --> 00:42:51,720
Do what you want.

390
00:43:12,570 --> 00:43:16,220
The Führer wasn't serious about
killing himself, was he?

391
00:43:16,740 --> 00:43:19,340
Frau Junge, Frau Christian.

392
00:43:23,000 --> 00:43:27,690
Get changed. In one hour,
a plane will take you south.

393
00:43:29,190 --> 00:43:31,270
Everything is lost.

394
00:43:31,790 --> 00:43:33,880
Completely lost.

395
00:43:37,530 --> 00:43:41,180
You know I'll stay with you.
You can't send me away.

396
00:43:53,500 --> 00:43:55,590
I'm staying too, mein Führer.

397
00:44:20,150 --> 00:44:21,190
Now what?

398
00:44:22,230 --> 00:44:23,800
Time to end this charade.

399
00:44:24,840 --> 00:44:29,010
Do you want us to stop fighting?
That's inconceivable.

400
00:44:29,530 --> 00:44:34,740
The Führer doesn't want us to capitulate.
No more November 1918. Ever.

401
00:44:35,260 --> 00:44:38,900
But he doesn't want to be in charge
anymore. He said: 'Do what you want'.

402
00:44:39,420 --> 00:44:42,550
Nobody can replace him.
He's the Führer.

403
00:44:43,070 --> 00:44:45,150
The Führer's confused.
He'll recover.

404
00:44:46,190 --> 00:44:48,800
Great.
And then what?

405
00:44:51,410 --> 00:44:54,540
No capitulation. That was
never his intention.

406
00:44:55,580 --> 00:44:58,190
We owe it to him.
-Hollow phrases.

407
00:44:58,710 --> 00:45:00,800
We have to act now.
Or it will be too late.

408
00:45:01,850 --> 00:45:04,450
You're only looking after yourself.
-Mind your words.

409
00:45:13,680 --> 00:45:15,240
Damn.

410
00:45:19,940 --> 00:45:24,110
We'll never get out of here alive.
It's all over.

411
00:45:24,640 --> 00:45:25,680
We've got to wait.

412
00:45:26,200 --> 00:45:29,850
Even the Führer doesn't believe in it
anymore. What will happen to us?

413
00:45:30,370 --> 00:45:34,550
Günsche says there's a tunnel
that goes under the Russian lines.

414
00:45:35,590 --> 00:45:38,200
Why did you say
you wanted to stay with him?

415
00:45:38,720 --> 00:45:42,370
I don't know.
Honestly.

416
00:45:44,980 --> 00:45:47,590
It stopped.
Let's go for a walk.

417
00:46:29,410 --> 00:46:30,980
Traudl.

418
00:46:31,500 --> 00:46:33,060
Look here.

419
00:46:55,490 --> 00:46:58,100
I'm lighting another one.

420
00:47:16,040 --> 00:47:18,650
Let's go down again.

421
00:47:48,690 --> 00:47:52,860
Where do they come from?
-Volkssturm. Drafted this afternoon.

422
00:47:53,390 --> 00:47:55,990
They have to get
out of the field of fire.

423
00:47:59,650 --> 00:48:03,820
The Volkssturm is under the
direct command of Dr. Goebbels.

424
00:48:06,990 --> 00:48:10,640
I want them to go away from there.
This is insane.

425
00:48:11,690 --> 00:48:13,250
I'll take the responsibility.

426
00:48:24,420 --> 00:48:28,070
I think this is wrong.
-Great.

427
00:48:29,640 --> 00:48:31,200
Stop. Lights out.

428
00:48:31,720 --> 00:48:34,330
Stop. Stay where you are.

429
00:48:34,850 --> 00:48:37,980
Stay where you are.
-Alright, Germans.

430
00:48:42,020 --> 00:48:46,190
Help. They want to kill us.
-What is all this?

431
00:48:46,190 --> 00:48:50,370
A Greifkommando.
-You're kidding.

432
00:49:00,270 --> 00:49:03,400
Stop it.
Let those men go.

433
00:49:03,930 --> 00:49:07,060
What's this?
You have no authority here.

434
00:49:07,580 --> 00:49:12,270
These men are on the run.
Traitors will be killed.

435
00:49:12,800 --> 00:49:16,450
They're old men. Civilians.
You can't do this.

436
00:49:21,300 --> 00:49:23,910
Who's going to stop me?
You maybe?

437
00:49:26,000 --> 00:49:28,080
Stop it. That's enough.

438
00:49:42,020 --> 00:49:43,590
Dismissed.

439
00:51:27,400 --> 00:51:29,480
This man's a doctor.

440
00:51:36,770 --> 00:51:39,380
Can you operate?
-Not really.

441
00:51:42,470 --> 00:51:46,640
Don't let the children
take too many toys.

442
00:51:47,160 --> 00:51:50,290
And not too much nightwear.
That's no longer needed.

443
00:51:50,820 --> 00:51:53,950
Herr Minister...
-Frau Junge, my family will arrive soon.

444
00:51:54,470 --> 00:51:58,630
Can you look after them for a moment?
Thank you.

445
00:51:59,150 --> 00:52:00,720
Brigade-führer, what can I do for you?

446
00:52:01,240 --> 00:52:04,360
Your Volkssturm is an easy prey
for the Russians.

447
00:52:04,880 --> 00:52:07,480
They have neither combat experience
nor good weapons.

448
00:52:08,000 --> 00:52:13,210
Their unconditional belief
in the final victory makes up for that.

449
00:52:13,210 --> 00:52:17,890
Herr Minister, without weapons
these men can't fight.

450
00:52:18,420 --> 00:52:19,980
Their deaths will be pointless.

451
00:52:20,500 --> 00:52:23,100
I don't pity them.

452
00:52:24,660 --> 00:52:27,260
I repeat:
I don't pity them.

453
00:52:27,790 --> 00:52:30,390
The people called this
upon themselves.

454
00:52:31,430 --> 00:52:35,070
This may come as a surprise to you.
Don't fool yourself.

455
00:52:35,600 --> 00:52:39,240
We didn't force the people.
They gave us a mandate.

456
00:52:39,240 --> 00:52:42,880
And now they're paying for it.

457
00:52:59,910 --> 00:53:02,520
Eva, you have to leave the Führer.

458
00:53:03,040 --> 00:53:05,120
Don't be stupid.
This is about life and death.

459
00:53:05,640 --> 00:53:07,720
How can you say that?
Where are you?

460
00:53:08,760 --> 00:53:11,370
I decided
not to die in Berlin.

461
00:53:11,890 --> 00:53:16,570
Does my sister know where you are?
-Think about it. I'll call you back.

462
00:53:18,660 --> 00:53:21,260
Children, your room is to the right.

463
00:53:23,340 --> 00:53:24,900
Wait for me.

464
00:53:26,460 --> 00:53:30,110
Hello, Frau Goebbels.
-Good to see you, Frau Junge.

465
00:53:42,500 --> 00:53:44,580
Line up, children.

466
00:53:45,100 --> 00:53:47,180
Helga, come. Line up.

467
00:53:48,230 --> 00:53:52,910
Let's make ourselves look good and
then we go say hello to uncle Hitler.

468
00:53:57,080 --> 00:53:59,160
Do you remember the song?

469
00:54:38,740 --> 00:54:42,910
The best thing to do is to
shoot yourself in the mouth.

470
00:54:47,070 --> 00:54:50,200
You won't feel a thing.
You'll be dead right away.

471
00:54:51,240 --> 00:54:53,840
I want to be a beautiful corpse.
I'll take poison.

472
00:54:54,360 --> 00:54:57,480
If I have to die,
at least without any pain.

473
00:54:58,000 --> 00:54:59,570
That's definitely painless.

474
00:55:00,090 --> 00:55:04,770
It paralyses the nervous system
and the respiratory system.

475
00:55:05,290 --> 00:55:06,850
A matter of seconds.

476
00:55:08,940 --> 00:55:12,060
Can I have one too?
-Me too.

477
00:55:17,260 --> 00:55:21,950
Himmler provided me well.

478
00:55:39,770 --> 00:55:41,850
Thank you.

479
00:55:42,890 --> 00:55:47,580
I would have liked to give you
a nicer present.

480
00:55:55,460 --> 00:55:59,630
Berlin, 23 April 1945.

481
00:56:03,270 --> 00:56:08,480
Dear sister. I'm sorry
to write you this.

482
00:56:09,000 --> 00:56:13,680
But this is how it is. It could
be over any moment.

483
00:56:14,200 --> 00:56:17,330
First of all: Hermann isn't with us.

484
00:56:17,850 --> 00:56:21,490
But I'm sure
you'll see him again.

485
00:56:22,010 --> 00:56:27,220
He'll get through this
and he'll fight from Bavaria.

486
00:56:27,740 --> 00:56:31,380
The Führer lost all hope
of a good outcome.

487
00:56:32,940 --> 00:56:36,590
Dear son. I don't know
if you'll receive this letter.

488
00:56:37,630 --> 00:56:42,310
Maybe someone will allow me
to send you a last greeting.

489
00:56:42,840 --> 00:56:46,480
I stayed with daddy
against his will.

490
00:56:47,000 --> 00:56:50,120
Last Sunday, the Führer
wanted to help me escape.

491
00:56:50,640 --> 00:56:53,250
But you know your mother.
We have the same blood.

492
00:56:53,770 --> 00:56:57,410
I won't even think about it.
Our ideology's going down the drain...

493
00:56:57,930 --> 00:57:03,140
...and with it, everything that made life
beautiful and worthwhile.

494
00:57:03,660 --> 00:57:07,820
After the Führer and National Socialism,
there's nothing left to live for.

495
00:57:08,860 --> 00:57:11,470
That's why I brought
the children too.

496
00:57:11,990 --> 00:57:14,070
They're too good for the life
that awaits them.

497
00:57:14,590 --> 00:57:19,270
God will have mercy on me
if I bring them redemption myself.

498
00:57:27,090 --> 00:57:31,250
I'll wear my bracelet with the green
stone until the very end.

499
00:57:31,770 --> 00:57:36,980
After that, I want
you to always wear it.

500
00:57:38,540 --> 00:57:42,190
Unfortunately, my diamond watch
is with the watchmaker.

501
00:57:42,720 --> 00:57:46,890
I included the address below.
I hope you're lucky enough to get it.

502
00:57:47,940 --> 00:57:49,500
I want you to get it.

503
00:57:51,070 --> 00:57:54,720
You'll also get the bracelet
with the topaz pendant.

504
00:57:55,240 --> 00:57:57,850
A birthday present
from the Führer.

505
00:57:59,420 --> 00:58:03,070
I owe some money
to the Heise company.

506
00:58:04,120 --> 00:58:09,010
There may be more debts, but
no more than 1500 Reichsmarks.

507
00:58:10,570 --> 00:58:16,840
All correspondence with
the Führer must be burnt.

508
00:58:18,920 --> 00:58:25,190
I'm sending you some food and tobacco.
The coffee is also for Lindner and Kathl.

509
00:58:25,710 --> 00:58:31,450
The cigarettes are for Mandi, the tobacco
for daddy, the chocolate for mummy.

510
00:58:32,190 --> 00:58:36,890
I can't think of anything else.
That's it for today.

511
00:58:37,900 --> 00:58:41,550
Dear sister, I wish
you lots of happiness.

512
00:58:41,990 --> 00:58:45,640
And remember,
you will see Hermann again.

513
00:58:46,160 --> 00:58:49,820
The warmest regards
and a kiss from...

514
00:58:50,340 --> 00:58:51,900
...your sister.

515
00:59:43,630 --> 00:59:45,710
Inge.

516
01:00:35,330 --> 01:00:40,550
Listen, Keitel.
I want you to leave this evening.

517
01:00:41,070 --> 01:00:44,730
Go to Dönitz and help him
with the organisation.

518
01:00:45,250 --> 01:00:48,380
Things have to be
started up again.

519
01:00:49,950 --> 01:00:52,030
I don't understand you.

520
01:00:52,550 --> 01:00:56,210
We have no more oil fields.
That's catastrophic.

521
01:00:56,710 --> 01:01:02,450
It makes any serious operation
impossible.

522
01:01:02,470 --> 01:01:09,260
When everything has been solved
here, we must get the oil fields back.

523
01:01:13,950 --> 01:01:17,080
Any questions?
-No, mein Führer.

524
01:01:17,610 --> 01:01:20,210
Good.
Have a good trip.

525
01:02:46,850 --> 01:02:49,990
Mein Führer, since you have decided
to stay here in Berlin...

526
01:02:53,470 --> 01:02:57,130
...do you agree that I take charge...

527
01:02:57,650 --> 01:03:00,780
...with complete freedom of action?

528
01:03:01,300 --> 01:03:03,390
If I receive no reply
by 2200 hours...

529
01:03:03,910 --> 01:03:06,940
...I'll assume you have
been incapacitated.

530
01:03:07,470 --> 01:03:11,120
I will then act on behalf
of the country and the motherland.

531
01:03:12,160 --> 01:03:14,770
That's high treason.
And betrayal of you.

532
01:03:15,300 --> 01:03:17,900
Göring's concerns are not
entirely unjustified.

533
01:03:18,430 --> 01:03:21,560
If our communication
system fails...

534
01:03:22,080 --> 01:03:25,210
...we'll be cut off
from the outside world.

535
01:03:25,730 --> 01:03:27,820
We won't be able
to issue orders anymore.

536
01:03:28,340 --> 01:03:30,950
I think Göring wants to
seize the power.

537
01:03:32,000 --> 01:03:34,610
I never trusted his clique
on the Obersalzberg.

538
01:03:35,650 --> 01:03:37,220
This looks like a coup.

539
01:03:37,740 --> 01:03:41,390
The loser, the sponger.

540
01:03:41,910 --> 01:03:44,520
A parvenu, a lazy bastard.

541
01:03:45,670 --> 01:03:50,360
How dare he say
I'm incapacitated?

542
01:03:51,410 --> 01:03:54,540
Hello.
-How did you get into Berlin?

543
01:03:55,060 --> 01:03:57,670
It wasn't easy,
but I must speak to the Führer.

544
01:03:58,710 --> 01:04:00,800
If I were you,
I'd wait a bit.

545
01:04:01,320 --> 01:04:04,450
The Luftwaffe.
What did he turn that into?

546
01:04:04,980 --> 01:04:08,110
For that alone,
he should be executed.

547
01:04:08,630 --> 01:04:14,360
This morphine addict
corrupted the country.

548
01:04:15,400 --> 01:04:16,960
And now this.

549
01:04:18,000 --> 01:04:20,600
He's betraying me.

550
01:04:22,160 --> 01:04:25,290
Me of all people.

551
01:04:25,290 --> 01:04:35,700
I want Göring stripped
of his power, right away.

552
01:04:36,740 --> 01:04:39,340
And, in case I don't
survive the war...

553
01:04:39,860 --> 01:04:42,990
...he must be
executed immediately.

554
01:04:45,590 --> 01:04:49,750
What's going to happen to us?
Is there any hope left?

555
01:04:52,360 --> 01:04:55,480
Frau Junge, leave from
here before it's too late.

556
01:04:56,000 --> 01:05:00,160
The Führer wants to stay.
We can't leave him behind, can we?

557
01:05:00,170 --> 01:05:05,890
He doesn't need anybody for what
awaits him. And least of all you.

558
01:05:06,930 --> 01:05:11,100
But Herr Goebbels and his wife
stay here. And the children.

559
01:05:20,470 --> 01:05:22,550
But the children...

560
01:05:26,190 --> 01:05:28,280
I have always believed...

561
01:05:29,840 --> 01:05:32,960
...that there was a way out.

562
01:05:39,730 --> 01:05:41,810
Come in.

563
01:05:43,890 --> 01:05:45,980
Albert. Hello.

564
01:05:57,430 --> 01:05:59,510
You have a fever.

565
01:06:00,030 --> 01:06:03,150
Albert, I can't stand
it anymore.

566
01:06:05,240 --> 01:06:07,840
Why don't you leave with
the children, Magda?

567
01:06:08,360 --> 01:06:10,960
Leave?
And go where?

568
01:06:11,480 --> 01:06:16,170
I can arrange for you to be
taken to Schwanenwerder by barge.

569
01:06:16,690 --> 01:06:20,330
You can hide
until everything's over.

570
01:06:20,850 --> 01:06:22,940
It won't be long now anyway.

571
01:06:23,460 --> 01:06:25,540
I thought about it.

572
01:06:27,100 --> 01:06:32,310
My children cannot grow up
in a world without National Socialism.

573
01:06:35,430 --> 01:06:40,110
Think about it. The children
have a right to a future.

574
01:06:44,280 --> 01:06:48,970
If National Socialism dies,
there will be no future.

575
01:07:05,390 --> 01:07:07,990
I can't believe
you really want that.

576
01:07:10,070 --> 01:07:12,670
Go now.

577
01:07:43,530 --> 01:07:45,610
Come in.

578
01:07:49,780 --> 01:07:51,860
I knew you'd come.

579
01:07:52,380 --> 01:07:55,500
You wouldn't desert
the Führer.

580
01:07:59,530 --> 01:08:05,260
I've come to say goodbye to the Führer.
I'm going back to Hamburg tonight.

581
01:08:05,780 --> 01:08:08,380
Of course, you must go.
Sit down.

582
01:08:10,990 --> 01:08:14,110
I took some furniture
you designed.

583
01:08:14,110 --> 01:08:16,660
I couldn't leave it behind.

584
01:08:17,180 --> 01:08:21,340
Please, you must
not have eaten all day.

585
01:08:22,390 --> 01:08:23,950
That's true.

586
01:08:28,630 --> 01:08:33,840
It's very important that you came.
It shows him you're on his side.

587
01:08:34,360 --> 01:08:36,440
Did he ever doubt that?

588
01:08:38,000 --> 01:08:41,650
Lately, he often thought
you were against him too.

589
01:08:42,170 --> 01:08:45,810
I always said you'd come
and here you are.

590
01:08:50,500 --> 01:08:54,140
I think he liked it that you
advised him to stay in Berlin.

591
01:08:54,660 --> 01:08:56,740
I also think it's best.

592
01:08:59,870 --> 01:09:01,950
And, you know...

593
01:09:02,990 --> 01:09:05,070
...it may sound strange...

594
01:09:07,160 --> 01:09:12,360
...but I'm really happy here.
And I'm not afraid.

595
01:09:39,110 --> 01:09:43,800
You came.
-Mein Führer, I...

596
01:09:43,800 --> 01:09:45,880
It's good.

597
01:09:47,440 --> 01:09:49,010
Let's sit down.

598
01:10:06,970 --> 01:10:12,190
I had great plans
for the Germans and the world.

599
01:10:13,750 --> 01:10:18,970
Nobody understood me.
Not even my old brothers in arms.

600
01:10:23,150 --> 01:10:29,410
The opportunities we had.
The whole world was ours to grab.

601
01:10:32,410 --> 01:10:33,980
Too late.

602
01:10:40,240 --> 01:10:45,460
I can only be proud for openly
fighting the Jews...

603
01:10:47,030 --> 01:10:51,200
...and for cleansing the Lebensraum
from the Jewish poison.

604
01:10:55,900 --> 01:11:00,080
I don't find it hard to continue.
One brief moment...

605
01:11:00,080 --> 01:11:10,520
...and then eternal peace.

606
01:11:14,690 --> 01:11:17,820
But please spare the people,
mein Führer.

607
01:11:17,830 --> 01:11:23,570
If my people cannot endure
this ordeal...

608
01:11:23,570 --> 01:11:26,700
...I won't shed a tear.

609
01:11:27,220 --> 01:11:29,310
They get what they deserve.

610
01:11:29,830 --> 01:11:35,570
They called this fate
upon themselves.

611
01:11:40,800 --> 01:11:42,880
For months...

612
01:11:44,450 --> 01:11:46,540
...I have to tell you this...

613
01:11:48,100 --> 01:11:51,760
...for months I have sabotaged
your orders for destruction.

614
01:11:53,850 --> 01:12:00,630
I not only ignored your orders,
but even acted against them.

615
01:12:05,850 --> 01:12:07,410
I had to tell you.

616
01:12:16,720 --> 01:12:20,900
This never compromised
my personal loyalty to you.

617
01:12:34,170 --> 01:12:36,780
So you're leaving.

618
01:12:38,030 --> 01:12:39,600
Good.

619
01:12:40,120 --> 01:12:41,680
Goodbye.

620
01:12:53,310 --> 01:12:55,390
I wish you all the best.

621
01:13:17,430 --> 01:13:21,080
Eat well, gentlemen.

622
01:14:16,900 --> 01:14:18,470
Peter.

623
01:14:27,540 --> 01:14:30,150
It's alright, son.

624
01:14:47,000 --> 01:14:48,560
He has a fever.

625
01:14:50,720 --> 01:14:51,760
Yes, but he's alive.

626
01:15:16,670 --> 01:15:20,840
Loyalty and courage
still exist in this world.

627
01:15:21,360 --> 01:15:24,490
Ritter von Greim
and Fräulein Reitsch, how good...

628
01:15:27,630 --> 01:15:31,800
...that the both of you arrived
more or less unharmed.

629
01:15:32,850 --> 01:15:33,890
Sit down.

630
01:15:35,460 --> 01:15:38,590
We came under heavy fire, but
still arrived in Gatow.

631
01:15:39,110 --> 01:15:41,720
From there,
we couldn't continue.

632
01:15:42,770 --> 01:15:46,940
We flew in a Fieseler Storch,
over the Russian lines...

633
01:15:47,990 --> 01:15:50,600
...and landed on the
East-West axis, close to here.

634
01:15:51,130 --> 01:15:53,740
Before landing, the Soviets
had a go at us.

635
01:15:55,420 --> 01:16:00,130
General Von Greim, I appoint you
supreme commander of the Luftwaffe.

636
01:16:01,170 --> 01:16:03,790
I hereby promote you
to General-Feldmarschall.

637
01:16:04,900 --> 01:16:07,520
A big responsibility
rests on your shoulders.

638
01:16:08,040 --> 01:16:11,180
You have to rebuild the
Luftwaffe from scratch.

639
01:16:11,710 --> 01:16:14,320
Many mistakes have been made.
Be ruthless.

640
01:16:15,890 --> 01:16:19,030
Life doesn't forgive weakness.

641
01:16:21,130 --> 01:16:26,890
This so-called humanity
is religious drivel.

642
01:16:28,460 --> 01:16:33,690
Compassion is an eternal sin.
To feel compassion for the weak...

643
01:16:34,220 --> 01:16:35,790
...is a betrayal of nature.

644
01:16:36,830 --> 01:16:42,070
The strong can only triumph
if the weak are exterminated.

645
01:16:42,590 --> 01:16:46,380
Being loyal to this law,
I've never had compassion.

646
01:16:50,400 --> 01:16:54,590
I've always been ruthless
when faced with internal...

647
01:16:55,120 --> 01:16:59,300
...opposition from other races.
And that's the only way.

648
01:17:01,400 --> 01:17:03,490
Apes, for instance...

649
01:17:04,490 --> 01:17:09,200
...kill all the odd ones.

650
01:17:09,730 --> 01:17:15,480
And what applies to apes,
must definitely apply to humans.

651
01:17:21,780 --> 01:17:23,880
Himmler made an offer to surrender...

652
01:17:23,880 --> 01:17:29,640
...to the allied powers.

653
01:17:30,160 --> 01:17:31,730
Via Count Bernadotte.

654
01:17:33,820 --> 01:17:36,440
A message from the English radio.

655
01:17:41,150 --> 01:17:46,390
Himmler.
Himmler of all people.

656
01:17:47,440 --> 01:17:54,770
The most loyal of my loyals.
That's the worst betrayal.

657
01:17:58,430 --> 01:17:59,620
Göring, he was corrupt.
Always has been.

658
01:18:02,600 --> 01:18:08,840
Speer, an absent-minded artist.
All the others: yes.

659
01:18:09,360 --> 01:18:15,610
But Himmler?
Has he gone insane?

660
01:18:16,130 --> 01:18:20,290
He must have told
them I'm sick.

661
01:18:20,820 --> 01:18:22,900
Maybe even dead.

662
01:18:29,140 --> 01:18:33,830
Leave me alone with Ritter Von Greim
and Fräulein Reitsch.

663
01:18:35,390 --> 01:18:40,080
And get Fegelein.
-We don't know where he is.

664
01:18:40,600 --> 01:18:44,240
What? He's Himmler's assistant.
He must be available.

665
01:18:44,240 --> 01:18:48,930
We haven't seen him for days.
-I want a report immediately.

666
01:18:52,050 --> 01:18:53,610
Please stay here, Doctor.

667
01:18:58,820 --> 01:19:02,980
You and Greim must go as quickly
as possible. Fly to Dönitz.

668
01:19:02,980 --> 01:19:09,230
Tell him to do anything
it takes to punish Himmler.

669
01:19:09,750 --> 01:19:13,910
We've decided to
die with you.

670
01:19:16,520 --> 01:19:19,120
Thank you for this proof of loyalty.

671
01:19:20,680 --> 01:19:24,320
But Himmler must die.
He committed treason.

672
01:19:24,330 --> 01:19:29,010
He's no longer privvy
to my plans.

673
01:19:29,530 --> 01:19:30,570
Mein Führer?

674
01:19:31,090 --> 01:19:34,740
Do you think I'll sit and wait until
those Jewish swine slaughter me?

675
01:19:35,260 --> 01:19:39,420
This is part of a huge decoy operation.
I've allowed the enemy...

676
01:19:39,420 --> 01:19:44,630
...to invade the Reich and they
think they've won.

677
01:19:45,150 --> 01:19:48,790
But mark my words: they have
another thing coming.

678
01:19:48,790 --> 01:19:52,960
Dönitz is mobilising in the north.
Kesselring in the south.

679
01:19:53,480 --> 01:19:57,640
We'll surround the enemy
and crush them.

680
01:19:58,160 --> 01:20:03,370
From Prague, three armies will attack
the Russians, simultaneously, from the back.

681
01:20:03,890 --> 01:20:09,090
I didn't know we still had
so many reserve troops.

682
01:20:10,140 --> 01:20:13,780
I made sure you'll soon have
a 1000 of the most modern...

683
01:20:13,780 --> 01:20:17,940
...jets at your disposal.

684
01:20:18,470 --> 01:20:22,630
With those, you can make the
Luftwaffe ready for battle again.

685
01:20:23,150 --> 01:20:27,840
I kneel to your genius, at the
altar of the motherland.

686
01:20:42,720 --> 01:20:44,280
Heil, mein Führer.

687
01:20:47,410 --> 01:20:50,530
You also request to leave Berlin?

688
01:20:52,090 --> 01:20:56,260
Mein Führer, as you know,
all medical departments...

689
01:20:56,780 --> 01:20:59,900
...that fall under the SS and Himmler,
have left Berlin.

690
01:21:00,940 --> 01:21:05,110
Himmler is a traitor.
He won't escape punishment.

691
01:21:05,630 --> 01:21:10,470
Mein Führer, as Reichsarzt SS,
I have no more work here.

692
01:21:11,510 --> 01:21:15,150
Your request to leave Berlin
is unacceptable.

693
01:21:16,710 --> 01:21:18,800
My family...

694
01:21:20,360 --> 01:21:23,480
If the Russians...
I must leave.

695
01:21:24,000 --> 01:21:25,560
You did nothing wrong.

696
01:21:26,600 --> 01:21:31,810
Future generations will thank you
for you medical research.

697
01:21:32,330 --> 01:21:34,410
I take all the responsibility.

698
01:21:40,660 --> 01:21:43,260
We'll talk about it later.

699
01:21:57,600 --> 01:22:01,770
GruppenFührer Fegelein cannot
be found. He's not in the bunker.

700
01:22:02,290 --> 01:22:04,890
What, you can't find Fegelein?

701
01:22:05,930 --> 01:22:10,100
Keep searching.
I need to talk to him. Immediately.

702
01:22:11,140 --> 01:22:15,300
If he left just like that,
that's desertion. Treason.

703
01:22:15,820 --> 01:22:17,380
Bring me Fegelein.

704
01:22:17,900 --> 01:22:20,510
Fegelein. Fegelein.

705
01:22:32,000 --> 01:22:35,120
Daddy, why are you wearing
your Sunday uniform?

706
01:22:38,250 --> 01:22:42,930
Ernst, is something wrong?
-No.

707
01:22:43,450 --> 01:22:45,010
Thank you.

708
01:22:45,540 --> 01:22:47,100
Brigitte is hungry too.

709
01:22:49,180 --> 01:22:52,820
Ilse, you should
eat something as well.

710
01:22:54,910 --> 01:22:56,990
Thank you.
-There you go.

711
01:23:01,670 --> 01:23:03,230
Thank you.

712
01:23:57,250 --> 01:24:00,890
What is it?
-GruppenFührer, you're under arrest.

713
01:24:01,940 --> 01:24:03,500
What?
-You're suspected of desertion.

714
01:24:04,020 --> 01:24:06,100
Get dressed.
You'll come with us.

715
01:24:11,310 --> 01:24:12,870
Search the room.

716
01:24:13,390 --> 01:24:16,510
Let go of me.
You can't give me orders.

717
01:24:18,590 --> 01:24:21,720
You can't have Hermann
executed, can you?

718
01:24:22,240 --> 01:24:25,360
There's no doubt.
He wanted to flee.

719
01:24:25,360 --> 01:24:29,000
What does it matter?
Everything's over.

720
01:24:30,050 --> 01:24:32,650
Think of my poor sister.
She's pregnant by Hermann.

721
01:24:32,650 --> 01:24:36,290
He collaborated with Himmler.
He's a traitor.

722
01:24:39,420 --> 01:24:44,620
There's no mercy for traitors.
No compassion for them.

723
01:24:46,710 --> 01:24:49,830
He'll be court-martialled
and executed.

724
01:24:50,870 --> 01:24:52,950
What's the point of that?

725
01:24:55,030 --> 01:24:56,600
It is my wish.

726
01:25:10,490 --> 01:25:11,530
You're the Führer.

727
01:25:15,370 --> 01:25:16,410
Speak.

728
01:25:16,930 --> 01:25:19,530
The Russians are advancing
more and more.

729
01:25:20,060 --> 01:25:23,180
There are no more reserves.
Supplies from the air are impossible.

730
01:25:23,700 --> 01:25:26,300
There is no ammunition coming
in anymore.

731
01:25:30,470 --> 01:25:33,070
In the north, the Russians are standing
in front of the Weidendammer bridge.

732
01:25:33,590 --> 01:25:36,710
In the east: Lustgarten.
South: Potsdammer Platz.

733
01:25:37,230 --> 01:25:40,880
West: Tiergarten, about 400 metres
away from the chancellery.

734
01:25:41,920 --> 01:25:45,040
How long can you hold out?
-At most, two days.

735
01:25:46,080 --> 01:25:48,690
Including the government area?
-Yes.

736
01:25:49,730 --> 01:25:54,930
As a soldier, I suggest we
flee Berlin. It's surrounded.

737
01:25:55,460 --> 01:26:01,720
The battle of Berlin killed about
20,000 of our best officers.

738
01:26:01,720 --> 01:26:05,370
That's what young people are for.

739
01:26:06,420 --> 01:26:09,550
What you suggest is insane.
Ridiculous.

740
01:26:10,070 --> 01:26:13,200
Think of the thousands of wounded.
We can't help them.

741
01:26:13,200 --> 01:26:17,900
Mein Führer, the orders have been written.
I give you my word...

742
01:26:18,420 --> 01:26:23,120
The Führer cannot make a honourless
disappearance from world history.

743
01:26:23,640 --> 01:26:27,820
Even if an advance is successful...

744
01:26:28,340 --> 01:26:31,470
...I'll end up in another
troublesome situation.

745
01:26:31,990 --> 01:26:37,210
I'd have to stay in the open air
or on a farm...

746
01:26:37,740 --> 01:26:39,300
...and wait for the end.

747
01:26:40,870 --> 01:26:46,610
Wenck is advancing with the 12th army.
He can join the 9th...

748
01:26:46,950 --> 01:26:51,130
...and give the Russians
the final blow.

749
01:26:51,830 --> 01:26:56,010
Wenck's an excellent fellow.
Send a telegram to Keitel:

750
01:26:59,140 --> 01:27:04,880
Immediately report to me the following:
1. Where are Wenck's vanguard located?

751
01:27:05,920 --> 01:27:08,530
2. When will they attack again?

752
01:27:09,580 --> 01:27:15,320
3. Where is the 9th army?
4. Where will the 9th make a breakthrough?

753
01:27:17,410 --> 01:27:22,100
You'll see, gentlemen.
I'll be right.

754
01:27:22,630 --> 01:27:25,240
Wenck will come.

755
01:27:31,730 --> 01:27:33,810
Wenck will come.

756
01:27:47,060 --> 01:27:51,240
I want to know if Wenck
can do anything at all.

757
01:27:51,760 --> 01:27:56,460
It's unlikely that Wenck's
small amount of troops...

758
01:27:56,980 --> 01:28:01,680
What's unlikely about the offensive?
-Wenck can't do anything anymore.

759
01:28:02,200 --> 01:28:06,380
Then why don't you tell the Führer that?
Has everybody gone mad?

760
01:28:06,900 --> 01:28:10,030
Do you think the Führer doesn't know?
He'll never surrender.

761
01:28:10,550 --> 01:28:14,210
And neither will we. I've been
through that once. Never again.

762
01:28:14,730 --> 01:28:16,820
Come along. I have to go.

763
01:28:26,970 --> 01:28:28,540
Stop right there.

764
01:28:40,620 --> 01:28:42,180
Heil Hitler.

765
01:29:30,970 --> 01:29:33,580
Excuse me. I fell asleep.

766
01:29:34,100 --> 01:29:36,190
Did you get some rest, my child?

767
01:29:39,680 --> 01:29:41,760
In shorthand.

768
01:29:48,030 --> 01:29:51,680
My political will.

769
01:29:52,740 --> 01:29:57,950
More than 30 years have passed...

770
01:29:57,960 --> 01:30:02,650
...since I made my contribution
as a volunteer...

771
01:30:02,650 --> 01:30:06,830
...during the first World War.

772
01:30:07,350 --> 01:30:12,570
During those 30 years,
I learnt to think, act and live...

773
01:30:13,090 --> 01:30:16,220
...out of love and loyalty
for my people.

774
01:30:20,160 --> 01:30:23,800
Excuse me. The shooting.
-Please sit down.

775
01:30:27,520 --> 01:30:30,130
Centuries will pass...

776
01:30:30,650 --> 01:30:34,810
...but from the ruins
of our cities and monuments...

777
01:30:34,810 --> 01:30:40,540
...the hatred
of the people...

778
01:30:40,540 --> 01:30:43,660
...who did this to us,
will continue to flare up.

779
01:30:44,180 --> 01:30:48,350
International Judaism and
its allies.

780
01:30:59,530 --> 01:31:01,610
What is it, Herr Minister?

781
01:31:05,260 --> 01:31:07,860
Imagine this.
The Führer wants me to leave Berlin.

782
01:31:08,900 --> 01:31:10,980
He ordered it.

783
01:31:13,070 --> 01:31:16,710
I've never ignored an order
from the Führer.

784
01:31:25,400 --> 01:31:31,120
But I will ignore this order.
I'll stay with the Führer.

785
01:31:34,840 --> 01:31:36,920
Please, Frau Junge...

786
01:31:39,000 --> 01:31:42,130
...I want to dictate my will to you.

787
01:31:44,210 --> 01:31:47,330
I'm typing
the Führer's will.

788
01:31:48,370 --> 01:31:50,450
Good.

789
01:31:51,500 --> 01:31:54,100
I understand.
Some other time.

790
01:32:01,300 --> 01:32:06,500
Mein Führer, according to the racial law
I'm obliged to ask you:

791
01:32:07,030 --> 01:32:09,630
Mein Führer, are you
of Aryan descent?

792
01:32:14,560 --> 01:32:17,170
Can I see your identity card?

793
01:32:18,250 --> 01:32:21,380
You're talking to the Führer here.
-Alright then.

794
01:32:21,900 --> 01:32:25,540
And you, Fräulein Braun,
are you of Aryan descent?

795
01:32:26,370 --> 01:32:29,500
Then there's nothing
to stop us.

796
01:32:30,020 --> 01:32:33,660
I'm asking you now:
Do you, mein Führer, Adolf Hitler...

797
01:32:34,180 --> 01:32:39,390
...take Eva Braun, present here,
as your wife? Answer 'yes'.

798
01:32:41,470 --> 01:32:45,110
Do you, Eva Braun, take Führer
Adolf Hitler, present here...

799
01:32:45,630 --> 01:32:48,760
...as your husband?
Answer 'yes'.

800
01:32:50,320 --> 01:32:53,440
Then I declare you
man and wife.

801
01:33:32,750 --> 01:33:34,830
Two men here.

802
01:33:37,100 --> 01:33:38,660
Everything will be alright.

803
01:33:40,580 --> 01:33:43,180
You must go to the Führer right away.
-Now?

804
01:34:02,850 --> 01:34:07,020
How long can we hold out?
-Twenty hours, no more.

805
01:34:08,580 --> 01:34:14,310
The Russians are close. At the moment,
we forced them to stop.

806
01:34:14,830 --> 01:34:20,030
You know, Mohnke. The western
democracies are decadent.

807
01:34:20,550 --> 01:34:25,760
They'll succumb to
the people from the east.

808
01:34:28,880 --> 01:34:31,480
All the best. Thank you.

809
01:34:32,530 --> 01:34:35,650
It wasn't just for Germany.

810
01:34:55,550 --> 01:34:57,630
A message from Keitel.

811
01:35:00,760 --> 01:35:04,070
1. Wenck's vanguard are
stuck south of Schwielowsee.

812
01:35:04,590 --> 01:35:08,230
2. The 12th army can't continue
the attack on Berlin.

813
01:35:09,270 --> 01:35:12,920
3. The 9th army is
completely surrounded.

814
01:35:32,860 --> 01:35:38,070
What do we do when the last
ammunition reserves have been exhausted?

815
01:35:39,110 --> 01:35:42,230
I'll never surrender. Never.

816
01:35:44,310 --> 01:35:49,530
I forbid you, and the other
commanders, to surrender.

817
01:36:01,530 --> 01:36:07,270
Listen, Günsche. My wife and I
are going to commit suicide.

818
01:36:07,790 --> 01:36:11,960
I don't want my corpse
exposed by the Russians.

819
01:36:12,480 --> 01:36:15,610
I don't want them to get me,
dead or alive.

820
01:36:16,130 --> 01:36:19,780
I want to be burnt
and never to be found.

821
01:36:23,940 --> 01:36:27,070
Günsche, I want you to promise me...

822
01:36:27,590 --> 01:36:32,800
...that you will do
all that it takes.

823
01:36:33,330 --> 01:36:35,410
Mein Führer...

824
01:36:35,410 --> 01:36:39,580
...this is a terrible order,
but I will execute it.

825
01:37:06,850 --> 01:37:09,980
Kempka.
-Erich, I need 200 litres of petrol.

826
01:37:09,980 --> 01:37:13,620
Are you mad?
Where should I find them?

827
01:37:14,150 --> 01:37:16,230
From the parked vehicles.

828
01:37:17,270 --> 01:37:19,880
What's all that petrol for?
-I can't say.

829
01:37:36,560 --> 01:37:39,690
Come, please.
The Führer wants to see us.

830
01:37:49,140 --> 01:37:51,750
Should I tell the Führer
you're indisposed?

831
01:37:52,790 --> 01:37:55,920
It's only my collapsed lung.

832
01:37:57,960 --> 01:38:00,040
I'll die soon anyway.

833
01:38:45,540 --> 01:38:47,620
Excuse me.

834
01:39:00,190 --> 01:39:02,280
Over here, Herr Professor.

835
01:39:11,280 --> 01:39:13,880
One moment, please.

836
01:39:23,120 --> 01:39:24,680
Excuse me.

837
01:39:58,110 --> 01:40:02,280
I'm sorry to interrupt
your important work.

838
01:40:02,800 --> 01:40:06,970
Mein Führer, keep faith
in the final victory.

839
01:40:07,490 --> 01:40:12,180
Lead us
and we shall follow.

840
01:40:15,970 --> 01:40:17,540
Come along.

841
01:40:24,800 --> 01:40:26,890
Join the gang.

842
01:40:29,120 --> 01:40:31,730
Come. Have a drink.

843
01:40:32,770 --> 01:40:36,420
Besides drinking, there's little we can do.
-Do sit down.

844
01:40:36,940 --> 01:40:43,720
That's better.
Yes, the situation is pretty shitty.

845
01:40:47,890 --> 01:40:51,530
Can we sit down?
-Please do, Fräulein...

846
01:40:52,060 --> 01:40:56,230
Frau...
-That's Frau Hitler.

847
01:40:58,830 --> 01:41:00,390
It's alright.

848
01:41:02,480 --> 01:41:05,080
A pity we can't go
outside anymore.

849
01:41:05,610 --> 01:41:08,730
Only if you want
to die a heroic death.

850
01:41:09,250 --> 01:41:14,990
Fritz, control yourself a bit.
-Yes. Control.

851
01:41:16,030 --> 01:41:17,590
Take cover.

852
01:41:39,060 --> 01:41:42,710
What are you doing here?
-I have to report to the Führer.

853
01:41:43,230 --> 01:41:45,320
You can't right now.
Sit down.

854
01:41:45,840 --> 01:41:47,920
Sit. Drink.

855
01:41:52,090 --> 01:41:54,180
Let me introduce Frau Hitler.

856
01:41:54,180 --> 01:41:58,350
So young and so many decorations.
You must be proud.

857
01:42:01,470 --> 01:42:04,080
Excuse me.
I'm not used to drinking anymore.

858
01:42:05,120 --> 01:42:07,730
You can use our toilet.

859
01:42:15,520 --> 01:42:20,730
If your hand shakes, the bullet
might only hit an optic nerve.

860
01:42:21,250 --> 01:42:25,940
That's why it's good
to also take the poison.

861
01:42:26,470 --> 01:42:31,160
When you bite through the capsule,
pull the trigger.

862
01:42:31,680 --> 01:42:33,760
Will I have enough time?

863
01:42:34,800 --> 01:42:37,410
The poison starts working
after one or two seconds.

864
01:42:54,820 --> 01:42:57,430
Tornow, you too.

865
01:43:06,460 --> 01:43:08,030
Come Blondi.

866
01:43:39,690 --> 01:43:42,290
You know, Frau Junge,
I've known...

867
01:43:43,340 --> 01:43:45,940
my husband for
more than 15 years.

868
01:43:46,460 --> 01:43:51,150
But when I think about it,
I know nothing about him.

869
01:43:51,680 --> 01:43:53,760
Even though he likes to talk.

870
01:43:56,890 --> 01:44:01,580
I longed for Berlin,
but he's so different now.

871
01:44:02,100 --> 01:44:05,750
He only talks about dogs
and vegetarian food now.

872
01:44:06,270 --> 01:44:08,870
I hate Blondi.

873
01:44:10,440 --> 01:44:15,650
I sometimes kick her and Adolf
then wonders why she acts strange.

874
01:44:26,600 --> 01:44:29,200
I think he doesn't want anybody
to really know him.

875
01:44:32,330 --> 01:44:37,020
...he can be so caring
in his private life.

876
01:44:38,590 --> 01:44:43,280
And then he uses
that rude language again.

877
01:44:44,330 --> 01:44:46,410
When he's the Führer, you mean?

878
01:44:47,980 --> 01:44:51,110
Come, let's smoke another one.

879
01:45:12,910 --> 01:45:14,470
I'm sorry.

880
01:45:16,550 --> 01:45:20,720
You have so many worries
and here I am, whining.

881
01:45:21,760 --> 01:45:25,410
Frau Junge, I'm giving you this coat
as a goodbye present.

882
01:45:26,450 --> 01:45:31,150
I like fashionable ladies.
I want you to enjoy it.

883
01:45:32,190 --> 01:45:34,800
What a surprise. Thank you.

884
01:45:36,360 --> 01:45:40,010
I just don't know where and when
I can wear it.

885
01:45:41,580 --> 01:45:44,710
Please, try to get out of here.

886
01:45:46,270 --> 01:45:47,840
Promise me.

887
01:47:17,300 --> 01:47:22,110
Thank you. That was very good,
Fräulein Manziarly.

888
01:47:43,120 --> 01:47:47,290
The time has come. It's finished.

889
01:48:26,130 --> 01:48:28,210
The Führer wants to say goodbye.
Come with me.

890
01:49:00,200 --> 01:49:03,330
You're the bravest mother
of the Reich.

891
01:49:03,860 --> 01:49:08,030
Führer, you made me the happiest
woman in Germany.

892
01:49:32,170 --> 01:49:34,260
Salute my beautiful Bavaria.

893
01:49:57,880 --> 01:49:59,960
Children, what are you doing here?

894
01:50:00,490 --> 01:50:03,090
We want to see aunt Eva
and uncle Hitler.

895
01:50:03,620 --> 01:50:07,270
Have you eaten anything yet?
-Only breakfast.

896
01:50:08,830 --> 01:50:12,480
Stay here, I'll get something to eat.
I'll be right back.

897
01:50:21,680 --> 01:50:26,370
Comrades, this is the
latest news from the outside.

898
01:50:26,890 --> 01:50:32,110
Berlin is full of warehouses: There were
houses here, there were houses there.

899
01:50:37,640 --> 01:50:39,720
Herr Günsche,
I want to speak to the Führer.

900
01:50:41,810 --> 01:50:43,370
Please, I have to.

901
01:50:43,900 --> 01:50:46,500
Frau Goebbels, the Führer
doesn't want to be disturbed.

902
01:50:46,510 --> 01:50:49,630
Please, Günsche,
just for a moment.

903
01:50:50,160 --> 01:50:51,720
Please.

904
01:50:59,190 --> 01:51:01,800
Mein Führer, Frau Goebbels is here.

905
01:51:08,280 --> 01:51:09,840
What is it?

906
01:51:10,360 --> 01:51:14,010
Mein Führer, I beg you:
Leave Berlin.

907
01:51:15,060 --> 01:51:20,800
Don't leave us Führer.
What will become of us?

908
01:51:24,680 --> 01:51:31,980
Tomorrow, I'll be cursed by millions,
but that's how it is.

909
01:51:34,780 --> 01:51:36,870
Get up. Come.

910
01:51:39,480 --> 01:51:41,570
Come.

911
01:51:49,910 --> 01:51:52,510
Aunt Traudl, I like it
when it thunders.

912
01:51:53,040 --> 01:51:56,690
Why?
-Nothing can happen to us here.

913
01:51:57,210 --> 01:51:59,300
Can it?
-No.

914
01:52:08,810 --> 01:52:10,370
Gotcha.

915
01:52:33,400 --> 01:52:37,050
Reichsleiter, it's over.

916
01:52:55,930 --> 01:52:58,540
The Führer is dead.

917
01:53:14,300 --> 01:53:16,390
There's daddy.

918
01:53:27,860 --> 01:53:31,510
Are you crazy?
For that damned petrol of yours...

919
01:53:32,030 --> 01:53:34,120
Erich, shut up.

920
01:53:44,570 --> 01:53:46,140
Stand back.

921
01:53:59,600 --> 01:54:01,170
Come on, continue.

922
01:54:01,690 --> 01:54:03,250
Continue.

923
01:55:32,780 --> 01:55:35,910
No, don't.

924
01:55:37,190 --> 01:55:39,280
Let grandpa go.

925
01:55:45,630 --> 01:55:49,280
Order. Order.
We must have order.

926
01:55:50,330 --> 01:55:52,930
Order has to return.

927
01:56:07,260 --> 01:56:11,440
This way. We know the way.
You can trust us.

928
01:56:12,480 --> 01:56:14,050
Hurry.

929
01:56:20,560 --> 01:56:23,170
I was on the side of
the Red Beasts.

930
01:56:27,210 --> 01:56:29,290
I supported the Bolsheviks.

931
01:56:36,790 --> 01:56:38,350
Let's hope the Russians
got our message.

932
01:56:38,880 --> 01:56:41,480
We'll soon find out.
-Or not.

933
01:56:46,710 --> 01:56:49,840
What news do you have, General?

934
01:56:50,360 --> 01:56:55,570
Adolf Hitler and his wife
committed suicide in the bunker.

935
01:56:58,710 --> 01:57:02,880
The new government
authorised me...

936
01:57:04,970 --> 01:57:08,100
...to start peace talks...

937
01:57:08,620 --> 01:57:14,880
...between our countries, that both
suffered severe losses.

938
01:57:15,920 --> 01:57:20,620
General, if you were me,
would you make peace with you?

939
01:57:21,140 --> 01:57:25,310
My government will never accept
unconditional surrender.

940
01:57:27,920 --> 01:57:32,090
Given the situation,
you have no other choice.

941
01:57:35,220 --> 01:57:37,830
Surrender? Never.
That's shameful.

942
01:57:38,880 --> 01:57:40,960
Years ago, I conquered
Berlin on the Reds...

943
01:57:41,480 --> 01:57:45,640
...and I'll defend the city
to my dying day.

944
01:57:46,680 --> 01:57:49,290
In the short time I have
as Chancellor...

945
01:57:49,810 --> 01:57:53,970
...I'll never sign
a surrender treaty.

946
01:57:54,490 --> 01:57:57,620
It's for the sake of the people.
-The Führer's orders are final.

947
01:57:58,140 --> 01:58:01,780
This is crazy.
We have to start negotiations.

948
01:58:02,300 --> 01:58:05,420
I repeat, gentlemen:
I do not surrender.

949
01:58:06,470 --> 01:58:09,070
Send a message to Marshal Zhukov.
-Zhukov?

950
01:58:09,590 --> 01:58:12,190
What's happening?
-We're surrendering.

951
01:58:12,710 --> 01:58:15,840
Then I must kill you.
The Führer forbids any surrender.

952
01:58:35,920 --> 01:58:39,040
How long does it work?
-Around four hours.

953
01:59:16,150 --> 01:59:21,350
Children, the doctor has the medication
I told you about.

954
01:59:21,870 --> 01:59:24,480
It's a bit bitter,
but it will work.

955
01:59:26,040 --> 01:59:27,600
A sip for everybody.

956
01:59:29,160 --> 01:59:31,240
Who wants to go first?

957
01:59:33,850 --> 01:59:37,490
Heide, you're always so brave?

958
01:59:43,220 --> 01:59:44,780
Have another sip.

959
01:59:47,900 --> 01:59:49,980
See? That wasn't so bad.

960
01:59:55,130 --> 01:59:57,210
Well done.
Helmut.

961
02:00:00,330 --> 02:00:05,020
This medication makes sure you don't
get ill in this humid bunker.

962
02:00:05,540 --> 02:00:08,140
But it's not humid
in the bunker.

963
02:00:12,830 --> 02:00:14,390
Well done.

964
02:00:23,640 --> 02:00:25,200
Helga.

965
02:00:27,930 --> 02:00:28,970
I don't want to.

966
02:00:29,500 --> 02:00:34,130
What's that? Do you want to get sick?
-Please, mama. I don't want to drink it.

967
02:00:37,780 --> 02:00:41,950
Don't cry, baby.
That doesn't help.

968
02:00:42,470 --> 02:00:44,560
You have to drink the medicine.

969
02:00:48,210 --> 02:00:49,780
Helga.

970
02:00:55,510 --> 02:00:58,120
Come on, open your mouth.

971
02:01:19,450 --> 02:01:21,020
Goodnight, children.

972
02:01:31,790 --> 02:01:34,920
One day the lie will fall apart...

973
02:01:34,920 --> 02:01:38,050
...and there will be light
in the darkness.

974
02:01:39,090 --> 02:01:40,650
Please read that.

975
02:01:41,700 --> 02:01:46,390
One day the lie will fall apart
and there will be light in the darkness.

976
02:01:47,960 --> 02:01:51,090
Let's do it differently.
One day the lie will collapse...

977
02:01:51,610 --> 02:01:56,300
...and truth will triumph
once again.

978
02:01:56,820 --> 02:02:00,480
At that moment, we will
stand above everybody...

979
02:02:01,000 --> 02:02:03,080
...pure and...

980
02:02:06,210 --> 02:02:08,300
immaculate.

981
02:06:15,350 --> 02:06:18,480
We don't stand a chance.
-So what? I want to get away.

982
02:06:19,000 --> 02:06:20,570
How do we get
through the lines?

983
02:06:21,090 --> 02:06:23,700
Doesn't matter.
I'm not staying another minute.

984
02:06:24,220 --> 02:06:27,350
We'll die.
-It won't be that bad, surely.

985
02:06:28,390 --> 02:06:31,000
If we stay, the Russians
will get us for sure.

986
02:06:33,080 --> 02:06:34,130
All the best.

987
02:06:34,650 --> 02:06:36,740
Come, let's go.

988
02:08:05,600 --> 02:08:12,340
On 30 April 1945, the Führer
committed suicide...

989
02:08:12,340 --> 02:08:18,070
...and in doing so, he deserted
everybody who was loyal to him.

990
02:08:18,600 --> 02:08:23,810
You, German soldiers, were loyal to
the Führer and were prepared...

991
02:08:24,330 --> 02:08:30,590
...to continue the battle for Berlin,
although ammunition was in short supply...

992
02:08:31,110 --> 02:08:35,810
...and further resistance
was pointless.

993
02:08:36,330 --> 02:08:39,980
I hereby declare an
immediate cease-fire.

994
02:08:41,550 --> 02:08:44,150
Each hour you continue fighting...

995
02:08:44,680 --> 02:08:51,460
...prolongs the suffering of the people
of Berlin and of our wounded.

996
02:08:51,980 --> 02:08:55,630
In agreement with the supreme
command of the Soviet troops...

997
02:08:56,150 --> 02:09:01,890
...I order you to stop
fighting immediately.

998
02:09:02,410 --> 02:09:09,710
Weidling, former commander
of the Berlin defence area.

999
02:09:11,280 --> 02:09:13,360
A glass of water, please.

1000
02:10:19,100 --> 02:10:21,710
I don't need you anymore.

1001
02:10:24,840 --> 02:10:27,450
The game's over.

1002
02:11:35,160 --> 02:11:37,770
It's time.
-Don't you see what's going on here?

1003
02:11:38,290 --> 02:11:41,410
I insist that you help us,
as a doctor.

1004
02:11:42,460 --> 02:11:44,540
Alright, then.

1005
02:11:51,830 --> 02:11:56,520
Go. You did a lot.
Thank you.

1006
02:12:03,270 --> 02:12:09,360
Schädle, hurry. Come on.
-I'm not going anywhere anymore.

1007
02:12:11,960 --> 02:12:13,530
Come along.

1008
02:12:52,130 --> 02:12:54,730
Are you alright?
-Keep going.

1009
02:13:31,530 --> 02:13:35,180
Sturmmann Krüger and his group
defended the Wolf Bridge...

1010
02:13:35,700 --> 02:13:38,300
...and he receives the Iron Cross.

1011
02:13:38,820 --> 02:13:42,990
Sturmmann Wagner took out two
machine-gun nests...

1012
02:13:43,510 --> 02:13:46,640
...and therefore, receives
the Iron Cross.

1013
02:13:47,160 --> 02:13:50,810
Sturmmann Rauch has gotten
messages through the lines...

1014
02:13:51,330 --> 02:13:53,930
...and receives the Iron Cross.

1015
02:14:25,100 --> 02:14:27,180
The others are coming.

1016
02:14:33,820 --> 02:14:35,900
Take cover, Müller.

1017
02:14:55,530 --> 02:14:56,570
Who's that?

1018
02:15:04,230 --> 02:15:06,310
A German.

1019
02:15:11,930 --> 02:15:13,490
Herr Hewel?

1020
02:15:17,140 --> 02:15:19,220
Thank God, you're alive.

1021
02:15:21,310 --> 02:15:22,870
Where are the others?

1022
02:15:25,480 --> 02:15:29,640
I don't know, Frau Junge.
Somewhere. Maybe.

1023
02:15:30,170 --> 02:15:33,290
Most people from my group
must be dead.

1024
02:15:33,810 --> 02:15:36,420
I should never
have left that bunker.

1025
02:15:36,940 --> 02:15:41,630
I should have shot myself,
but I couldn't.

1026
02:15:43,710 --> 02:15:46,840
Eat something first.
There's always enough time to die.

1027
02:16:44,150 --> 02:16:46,760
You stay with the women.

1028
02:16:47,890 --> 02:16:49,450
Come along.

1029
02:17:01,980 --> 02:17:05,630
The Russians have surrounded us.
-What's going to happen to us?

1030
02:17:06,150 --> 02:17:08,750
Maybe you can get through.
You could try.

1031
02:17:09,270 --> 02:17:10,840
I'm not taking another step.

1032
02:17:11,880 --> 02:17:16,570
Think about it. The Russians
are after us.

1033
02:17:17,090 --> 02:17:22,300
As a woman, you might have a chance.
Try it.

1034
02:17:23,340 --> 02:17:24,900
Good luck.

1035
02:17:27,510 --> 02:17:31,680
When you walk past the Russians,
don't look them in the eyes.

1036
02:17:32,200 --> 02:17:35,850
Remember that well. All the best.

1037
02:17:44,870 --> 02:17:46,430
The Russians.

1038
02:17:59,010 --> 02:18:01,620
Gerda, let's go.
-You go.

1039
02:18:02,140 --> 02:18:05,270
I'm exhausted.
-Please.

1040
02:18:07,360 --> 02:18:11,530
I have to give it a try.
Don't be angry with me.

1041
02:18:15,710 --> 02:18:17,270
I'll be alright.

1042
02:18:30,400 --> 02:18:31,970
Herr Doktor.

1043
02:18:32,490 --> 02:18:37,190
My comrades want to surrender.
Can I join you?

1044
02:18:37,710 --> 02:18:41,360
The Führer's dead. Do you want
to continue the war on your own?

1045
02:18:41,880 --> 02:18:43,450
I'm obliged by my oath.

1046
02:18:43,970 --> 02:18:48,670
Then you'd better go
to the brigade-führer.

1047
02:19:17,340 --> 02:19:18,900
The Russians are evacuating the square.
-So?

1048
02:19:19,950 --> 02:19:22,040
No opposition.
No shooting.

1049
02:19:22,560 --> 02:19:25,170
Then they'll be
here within the hour.

1050
02:19:25,690 --> 02:19:27,780
What shall we do?

1051
02:19:27,780 --> 02:19:32,470
We can't surrender.
-What exactly do you mean?

1052
02:19:33,000 --> 02:19:36,650
When the Russians come,
we'll empty our weapons on them.

1053
02:19:37,170 --> 02:19:40,820
The last bullets are for ourselves.
-That's radical.

1054
02:19:40,820 --> 02:19:46,040
Is this prestigious murder and suicide
our only option?

1055
02:19:46,570 --> 02:19:50,220
We're SS officers.
We can't survive the Führer.

1056
02:19:50,220 --> 02:19:53,350
Who agrees with me?

1057
02:21:41,020 --> 02:21:44,150
Come and sit down with me?
-Please.

1058
02:21:49,980 --> 02:21:55,200
Why do you want to continue living?
-And you? Why do you want to die?

1059
02:21:56,770 --> 02:21:58,890
See this?

1060
02:21:59,420 --> 02:22:02,610
The Führer gave it
to me personally.

1061
02:22:03,140 --> 02:22:06,860
As a last decoration?
-Maybe.

1062
02:22:07,400 --> 02:22:12,180
A goodbye present from Hitler.
I had to promise him something.

1063
02:22:12,180 --> 02:22:17,490
If the Russians get me,
I have to kill myself.

1064
02:22:19,620 --> 02:22:23,870
Did he make you promise that?
But why?

1065
02:22:24,400 --> 02:22:27,590
Maybe he didn't want
me to be forced...

1066
02:22:28,120 --> 02:22:30,250
...to say anything bad
about him.

1067
02:22:30,780 --> 02:22:35,030
But, as a diplomat,
you're under international protection.

1068
02:22:35,560 --> 02:22:39,280
Who will benefit
if you stick to your deal?

1069
02:22:39,810 --> 02:22:41,410
There they are.

1070
02:22:54,820 --> 02:22:56,410
Don't shoot, comrades.

1071
02:23:00,410 --> 02:23:05,200
We surrendered.
The war is over.

1072
02:23:06,260 --> 02:23:08,380
It's over.

1073
02:24:43,930 --> 02:24:47,110
Complete surrender took place
on 7 May 1945.

1074
02:24:49,240 --> 02:24:52,430
Hostilities were suspended
on 8 May.

1075
02:24:54,560 --> 02:24:58,280
The war took the lives of more
than 50 million people.

1076
02:24:59,870 --> 02:25:05,180
6 million Jews were killed
in German concentration camps.

1077
02:25:06,250 --> 02:25:11,030
Gerda Christian managed to escape
and avoid imprisonment.

1078
02:25:11,560 --> 02:25:14,750
She died in Düsseldorf
on 14 April 1997.

1079
02:25:15,280 --> 02:25:19,530
Dr. Schenck was released in 1953
by the Soviets.

1080
02:25:20,070 --> 02:25:23,790
He died in Aachen
on 21 December 1998.

1081
02:25:25,380 --> 02:25:28,040
Wilhelm Mohnke was released
by the Soviets in 1955.

1082
02:25:28,570 --> 02:25:32,820
He died in Damp, near Eckernförde,
on 6 August 2001.

1083
02:25:33,350 --> 02:25:39,730
Helmut Weidling died in
captivity, in 1955.

1084
02:25:40,260 --> 02:25:45,570
Werner Haase was arrested
in the bunker, by the Red Army.

1085
02:25:46,110 --> 02:25:49,290
He died in captivity,
in 1945.

1086
02:25:49,830 --> 02:25:53,010
Otto Günsche was arrested
by the Soviets.

1087
02:25:53,550 --> 02:25:57,800
He was released in 1956 and
died in Lohmar, in 2003.

1088
02:25:58,330 --> 02:26:03,110
Hanna Reitsch survived the war
and would break many flying records.

1089
02:26:03,640 --> 02:26:06,300
She died on 28 August 1979.

1090
02:26:06,830 --> 02:26:12,150
Robert Ritter von Greim committed
suicide on 24 May 1945.

1091
02:26:12,680 --> 02:26:15,340
Linge and Hentschel were
arrested by the Soviets.

1092
02:26:15,870 --> 02:26:17,990
Linge was released in 1955 and
died in 1980.

1093
02:26:19,060 --> 02:26:22,240
Hentschel was released in 1949 and
died in 1982.

1094
02:26:22,780 --> 02:26:29,150
Constanze Manziarly disappeared
without a trace, during her flight.

1095
02:26:29,690 --> 02:26:32,870
Albert Speer was arrested
in Flensburg, in 1945.

1096
02:26:33,410 --> 02:26:36,060
He was sentenced to
20 years, in Nuremberg.

1097
02:26:36,590 --> 02:26:39,250
He was released in 1966 and
died in London, in 1981.

1098
02:26:40,310 --> 02:26:46,690
Keitel and Jodl were sentenced to
death in Nuremberg and executed.

1099
02:26:47,750 --> 02:26:49,880
Hermann Göring was
sentenced to death.

1100
02:26:50,940 --> 02:26:54,130
He committed suicide in his cell,
shortly before his execution.

1101
02:26:54,660 --> 02:26:59,450
Heinrich Himmler tried to escape
using a false name.

1102
02:26:59,980 --> 02:27:03,170
After he was found out,
he committed suicide.

1103
02:27:03,700 --> 02:27:08,480
Martin Bormann and Ludwig
Stumpfegger committed suicide...

1104
02:27:09,010 --> 02:27:12,200
...on 2 May 1945,
near the Lehrter Bahnhof.

1105
02:27:13,260 --> 02:27:17,520
Rochus Misch was released
by the Soviets in 1955.

1106
02:27:18,050 --> 02:27:20,170
He still lives in Berlin.

1107
02:27:20,700 --> 02:27:23,360
Traudl Junge was classified
as a 'young follower'.

1108
02:27:23,890 --> 02:27:27,080
She worked as a secretary and lived
in Munich, until her death in 2002.

1109
02:27:27,610 --> 02:27:32,930
All the horror I heard about during
the Nuremberg trial...

1110
02:27:32,930 --> 02:27:39,840
...the 6 million Jews, dissidents
or people of another race...

1111
02:27:40,370 --> 02:27:46,210
...who died, shocked me deeply.

1112
02:27:47,280 --> 02:27:52,060
But I hadn't made the connection
with my own past yet.

1113
02:27:53,120 --> 02:27:57,910
I reassured myself by thinking
I wasn't personally guilty of it.

1114
02:27:58,440 --> 02:28:03,750
And that I hadn't known
about the sheer size of it.

1115
02:28:04,280 --> 02:28:10,660
But one day, I walked
past a commemorative plaque...

1116
02:28:11,190 --> 02:28:14,910
...for Sophie Scholl,
here in the Franz-Joseph-Strasse.

1117
02:28:15,980 --> 02:28:18,630
I saw that she was my age...

1118
02:28:19,160 --> 02:28:25,010
...and that she was executed in
the year I joined Hitler.

1119
02:28:25,540 --> 02:28:30,860
And only then did I realise...

1120
02:28:31,920 --> 02:28:34,580
that youth is no excuse.

1121
02:28:35,110 --> 02:28:41,490
And that it might have been
possible to find out the truth.

1122
02:31:20,550 --> 02:31:23,740
DOWNFALL

