all began so nice.
A bunch of friends
at a cabin in the mountains.
Lots of alcohol, laughter.
We had fun.
And then do you not fucking
a squad nazi zombies woke up.
I know.
It sounds like a cliché,  -
- but that's what happened.
You see, we found something.
Something we should not.
Old Nazi gold.
And so
- all hell broke loose.
they killed us. A
by one.
One of them bit me.
But I knew
how I could fix it.
girlfriend Hanna
Her
They took her and.
I found gold.
Gave it back.
And they let me go.
I thought I was safe.
I was wrong.
Take the damn coin
and go to hell where you came from!
Shit, shit, shit
Okay, Okay
(coughs and gets vomiting)
I knew we should not
Having touched the casket.
Stay awake now.
Stay awake.
That's a good question, Toralf.
Of all migratory birds -
- it's a little critter
that really stands out.
Namely, arctic terns,
or Sterna paradisaea.
coastal bound,
surface-feeding seabirds.
group havterner
Havternen maneuver gracefully
in the air like a
Troops, Sieg Heil!
Talvik FISH
'' Yes?
What have we here?
Martin, can you hear me?
Hello, Martin.
Welcome back.
Martin, you crashed your car.
A nasty crash.
You are lucky to be alive.
There is more than one can say
about your friends.
Have you seen
Have you seen creatures?
The things
Have the police caught them?
Or the army?
Roy and Erlend?
- Hanna?
- We found friends. All of them.
Dead.
Hanna was your girlfriend, right?
Very beautiful.
We found her too.
With an ax driven into the neck.
And your fingerprints on the shaft.
Do you have any idea
how that could happen?
They came up from
From the snow. Creatures. Nazi.
We stuck, but
Nazis coming out of the ground?
Absurd.
Are you sure
that he has brain damage?
Please call the family and say he is awakened.
Ask the Attorney send a car.
And four additional men. You are
ready to be transported.
They are out there yet. They will kill
again if we do not stop them.
We should not stop anyone.
I've seen what you've done.
- You'll be right in jail.
- No one knows what happened there.
Only you know that.
And it's not just bad news.
When we found you, you were badly injured.
Your right arm was torn across.
- It was not torn
- When we found you, it was cold.
The snow had chilled all,
and it was very good.
- And then we found the arm in the car.
- In the car?
It was slightly bruised and quite pale,
bit strange, basically, -
- But the operation was a success.
We managed to stick your arm again.
No, no, no
- It's not my arm.
- Relax.
It is Satan's arm!
Calm down.
No, it's not me!
No!
It's not me!
What the hell ...?
Stop!
Randi?
You need to settle down
removing the denture later.
Tonight I'm ready for a little hue.
From him that got away.
Nameless GERMAN SOLDIERS
WHO FELL IN WAR
Bakken.
Warm.
The men have rotted.
We need more people.
Fittelås!
You scared me, Nils.
I can no more nonsense.
I have been a damn long day.
A wedding, a funeral
and confirmation.
She's one confirmant
was the damn fine, then.
If only I had been ten years younger -
- And not a priest, of course
Nils?
Come on!
Sieg
Heil.
Sieg Heil, Sieg Heil, Sieg Heil
They came down from the mountain.
I saw them.
Hello! Hello!
They are coming!
They're going to kill everyone!
Hey.
Hey, you there. Yeah, you.
Hello.
I saw your arm.
It is really tough.
I took pictures.
It's totally sick. But tough.
I can not really be here.
I snuck in like a ninja.
My name is Bobby.
I'm on vacation with mom.
She ate
something bad fish yesterday,
Tough.
Really tough.
It looks burnt out.
And old.
As a zombie arm.
Zombies are tough.
Zombies?
I must take it. They ask
I can provide more information.
More than just a picture of the arm.
Who? What?
Zombie Squad.
They want to know more.
They are zombie experts from the United States.
They have prepared themselves for
a zombie attack for years.
Can they get here?
Tell them to come here right away.
They can kill the zombies!
- Have you seen them? Fins they?
- Yes.
- Can you let me loose?
- I do not know if I should.
- I have chocolate.
- Have you?
Yes, I have chocolate.
I could brought it to you if
- Double-triple-nougat.
- Oh my God ...!
I'll take this.
Come on.
You can do it.
Help me with the other.
- Can I get chocolate now?
- I have not.
- No chocolate?
- Shut the fuck up.
I need out.
Hello!
That's not what it looks like.
Stop!
(a mobile rings)
Hello?
Daniel Heffernan, looking Zombie
Squad. Can I talk to Bobby?
Bobby. "
-  Bobby, he
- I do not speak the language of Tor.
- Is  Bobby  there?
- Bobby was killed by zombies.
God
- Is this Zombie Squad?
- 10.4, Martin, and willow on the way.
But first we must have the most
information. All you have.
Well
We went up to the cabin,
and there was a bunch -
- Nazi zombies, and the
Yes, they killed us all.
Except me. And
I had to cut off my arm,
but
Now the arm
But then they would have left
his treasure, and
-  Were any  of  you bite?
-  All was bitten.
But we were not one of them.
We just
We just died.
Listen, Martin.
Listen carefully.
It is not ordinary zombies -
- Hungry for human flesh.
These zombies are cursed.
They will catch something
that was stolen from them.
- Or perform a mission.
- They called him Herzog.
They called him Herzog.
Martin from the North, we are on the way soon.
and we'll take care of
this outbreak.
We are professionals.
Meanwhile  -
- So find out what they are looking for,
their goal. Cheers.
Zombie Squad.
they are
They are professionals.
They are bad ass.
Okay, girls.
It appears
that we're going to Norway.
Norway? Not on your life.
It's the other side of the Earth.
And how do we know it's true?
Think about that is nonsense, Daniel?
You saw the picture.
There is a real infected arm.
All the signs are there.
Rotten skin and hair, dark blood.
- This is true.
- It could be dangerous.
There are zombies, damn,
Of course it is dangerous!
We have been waiting for a chance
to prove that we are right.
For years we have said that the only
was a matter of time -
-before the first outbreak occurs.
And what have we got an answer?
Laughter. Spott.
Panties case.
But who was right?
- Who laughs last?
- We, or?
Damn! Was it not therefore
we founded the Zombie Squad?
- He's right.
- Damn so right.
And if we do not go there
and helps them -
- Who should do it?
- What do we do then?
'Yes! '
We need to know as much as possible
Herzog about this guy.
And if Martin and Northern Norway. Everything.
Wait! Owners
must not find out about this.
- Do you mean father and mother?
- Yes, but
- We just can not say it to them.
- Roger that.
official members
Zombie Squad USA
- Oh my God ...!
- Now we are looking.
It went better than usual.
I poured coffee.
- It is the cold.
- Because you're 40 minutes late.
I am in the winter.
The DST system -
- Is completely idiotic.
What do you have?
Not much. The boy at Petra
has shoplift again.
They should have done that in Iran.
Off with his hands. When he had learned.
And Ove dog has pooed
in Olsen's garden.
- Shoot him
- Olsen?
Not Olsen. Shoot the dog!
So we have lectures to school
about the harms of using marijuana.
lame!
There was one thing, then.
From Øksfjord.
Øksfjord?
It is not our district.
Martin Hykkerud
escaped from the hospital yesterday.
Martin Hykkerud? He who killed
his friends on top of the mountain?
Yes. He escaped yesterday and killed
a little boy and a policeman -
- By fling a Mercedes star
in the face at him.
- Kutta the Mercedes star?
- Yes.
- What Oslo?
- About Mercedes star?
About Hykkerud case!
We need additional people,
they get sent a team up.
Sent a team up?
Extra people?
How the hell do I get money
additional people from?
I do not even have money
new batteries for cars.
Okay. Right.
What?
Were we not agree
having a casual look here?
Continue.
OMG I expected Hoth,
but this is much more Ender.
Do you just references
from Star Wars?
- Yes, what else? Star Trek?
- It is based at least in science.
- I've Mirror Martin.
- Where is he?
- Isnestoften.
- Nice. Come on!
Wait.
We have to do something first.
- Yes, I have to pee.
- No!
Arming us.
Where you really ruined it.
It would have been easier
if we could purchase weapons here.
What the hell is wrong with
this country?
MUSEUM
ANOTHER WORLD
Can I help you?
Too much coffee. Just go ahead, you.
Best for you if you continue.
This is a war museum, huh?
Yes.
Yes, and
Do you have any information
about the Germans?
Help!
Listen to me!
I do not have time for this.
They come, and we must stop them!
- I have two kittens at home!
- Shut up!
Just help me.
Please.
- Do you have information about Einsatz?
- Yes.
- Second floor.
Where the hell are you?
- What are you looking for?
- Herzog.
Buddy with Hitler.
- Nice, huh?
- Do not touch the exhibit.
"Herzog became head of Einsatz in 1942.
He was sent to Northern Norway
to protect warships -
- The Germans
kept hidden in the fjords.
He was Øksfjord to inspect
ship Scharnolsht, then
Scharnholst.
When Tirpitz, the German
Navy's biggest warships, -
- Was attacked
by British bombers in Talvik -
- After Norwegian spies
had revealed the ship's position.
Humiliated by the attack on the Tirpitz
Hitler ordered Herzog -
-to kill the entire population
800 men and women in Flintstone. "
Was he
He was on his way?
He was on his way to Talvik the evening
they were slaughtered in Øksfjord?
On behalf of Hitler.
A mission that was never performed.
It is. Exactly what is it.
They will destroy Talvik.
where
Herzog was going from Øksfjord -
- Which is here.
And he was going to Flintstone.
It's here.
Where are we now?
Where are we now?!
Her.
Isnestoften.
It is the in between.
(screaming outside)
They are recruiting!
They make new soldiers.
Can they do it now? Fuck!
Okay, they come here.
They come here.
I will not die in a museum
with a guy in a green jogging suit.
Calm down.
You will die.
But relax.
Not today.
There!
Let
what this thing can do.
What kind of things?
What did you do?
You killed them only without
It's arm, man.
Before I could not control it,
but now makes it known what I think.
You're not even sweating.
Do not worry about it.
They build bigger.
Damn much larger.
There are too many
through the arm.
So much death.
All this unnecessary death.
(whimpering)
Fuck!
You did what he fucker
in the place. You just
- You
- No, it was the arm. It was the arm.
He does not attack
Did you see it?
I hit it!
I did it fuck me!
I hit it right in the eye.
Capture.
- First Zombie Squad murder.
- One, two
Orange ...!
Did you know?
We talked on the phone.
Daniel Blake and Monica.
We are Zombie Squad.
- Damn it
- It's true, people died.
And it was a real zombie.
You killed him.
- It is absolutely unimaginable.
- Conc bit here now.
We're sorry.
We are more professional than this.
- Are you Zombie Squad?
- Yep.
- You are the Zombie Squad.
- Yes, we are.
We're sorry.
I just expected something else.
He did well,
when he woke up this morning.
Because I hit him in the face
with an ax.
- How did you find me?
- We Mirror Your iPhone, of course.
We're fucking nerds.
Technology is our thing. Enough small talk.
What have you found?
What are they looking for?
Revenge.
(engine noise)
It's insane!
You? Have Capability?
The force is strong with him.
Fine, it
Martin,
that's how we defeat them.
- What do you mean?
- I mean
We create an army we.
I gathered as much information
as possible on the way here.
Especially if Herzog. To defeat
enemy, you must know him.
This is Lieutenant Stavarin
from the Soviet army.
Him and his battalion
was captured at Kursk.
They were brought here a prisoner of war.
In 1944 they were sent
to Kvenangsfjellet -
-to build a road.
When the road was completed,
shit was real hell.
All the prisoners were shot.
Shot to death!
None survived.
And the man who directed this?
Herzog.
Their bodies are buried there yet.
Buried in the frozen ground.
Preserved. They are waiting.
- What are they waiting for?
- The same as Herzog.
Revenge. And guess who
to help them with that.
- He who can raise the dead?
- Hell, yeah ...!
You must slow down Herzog,
and give me the most possible time.
- And if it does not work?
- It must.
We just have to find Stavarin,
wake him from the dead -
- And take him to Talvik
so he can fight against Herzog.
Lett. Besides
we help.
Then we go.
He is our last hope.
See, a tank.
(a sound from outside)
- Visit now?
- It was early.
(sound)
Hello?
(baby crying)
Look.
His army grows.
Are there more places
before going Flintstone?
- Only a few houses.
- Good. When he uses the ones he has now.
Mostly. Before he kills
residents of Talvik, and take them.
- How many live there?
- Approximately 3000.
- Holy Father!
- We need to slow them as much as we can.
- See there. Can you run one of these?
- Oh yeah. But I'm from Northern Norway.
I do not know what does.
Lightweight bags, folks.
We're leaving. Now!
What the deepest hell
happened here?
What do engineers?
It is not technical,
Only Tom and Ole in a white coat.
The thought
so a little more professionally out.
NCIS should be herein night.
- Do we have any witnesses?
- If you get the seagulls to chatting happily.
Gulls, yes.
Then you have a damn good invention.
A gadget that translates
seagull language to human language.
He who finds a way
are fucking rich.
Get the bodies of Talvik
before the gulls eat them up.
And take the damn many pictures, otherwise
NCIS cut off my balls.
Here are pictures
from the surveillance camera.
Is not that where ...?
To me at the head of guttefitta mi.
Okay, guys, guys!
We are in a hurry. Come on!
Come on, man!
We have things to do!
There they are.
And they have a tank.
Yes, they stole it from the museum.
Fuck!
- What is it?
- A huge tank and 40-50 zombies.
No, no, no.
There there. What is it?
A copy of binoculars
Han and Chewie used on Hoth.
Did you Nice to know.
All Hoth scenes -
- Was filmed here in Norway.
At a place called Finse.
Could we instead focus a bit
on Nazi zombies?
- What do we do?
- The Daniel said Sinke them.
Look.
We must let them see us,
and lure them out into the marsh.
And when they're stuck, blow
we them with fertilizer bombs ours.
It sounds really impossible.
And how do we lure them out there?
We need bait. Live bait.
We need
someone proves them.
One who is quick on their feet.
One who knows the marsh
and do not get stuck.
What?
No.
I do not go out into the marsh.
I also stuck.
The things there -
- They are zombies
who will rip off my face!
Is not Talvik hometown?
- Yes.
- You must love somebody.
Yes. There is a particular ma ...
A woman I love.
- With long hair and big boobs.
- Do it for "her".
Just run them here,
we'll do the rest. Understood?
You? Martin?
- Yes?
- Are you okay?
Sure.
First, we awaken
one battalion of Nazi zombies -
- And now I'm resurrecting
a bunch of dead Russians.
Your arm, your power, -
- The only thing that can
stop Herzog. Remember that.
Our failure -
- He will get more and more power,
for no one can stop him more.
And that, my friend,
is a huge tub of shit
- We will live in.
God.
It smells disgusting.
How can stink
fill the car already?
- He's just a little carsick.
- It smells awful.
No!
Damn, so disgusting!
It stinks.
I did not know it was
ugly-nosed congress in the city.
Come and get me, then.
Come and get me if you dare.
Move it!
Held!
- They follow him.
- Not Herzog men.
Now they have seen us.
We kill these here, he will take us.
Come on, Glenn!
- Run faster!
- Faster!
Yes!
Come on, Glenn!
Yes, rush
- Run, Glenn!
- Faster!
Run, run!
Please
Yes!
OMG, Blake!
USA, USA!
USA!
Shoot.
Hey. The tank moves.
It bodes well not good.
Run!
My God!
Talvik. Now.
Hey.
- Where are we?
- We are approaching.
But we're stuck.
- Can I push?
- I do not think it helps.
- Is it far? We can go.
- We do not have much time.
If only we could find something -
- We can lay under the car
so we get better traction.
Then I could have got us loose.
(whimpering scared)
- There you are, yes.
- Satan lives to accommodate all equal.
The dress is absolutely stuffed full.
We had to throw the rest in the garage.
- Sounds like a perfect solution.
- Thank you.
Most Germans and French.
Hardly the vacation they envisioned.
To get worn off his head and arms
and get entrails torn out?
Unless they like that kind of kinky stuff.
- Should you do that?
- No.
- Should not NCIS been here now?
- It gave a lot in Alta.
The plane could not land.
They are here in the morning, they say.
- It's perfect.
- What?
It's our chance.
Now, we fucking show people
what we're made of here.
We here at Talvik Police
find Martin Hykkerud itself.
We get him. Vi.
We will be heroes.
Not the goddamn suit-clad,
homofriserte -
- Sushi-eating hestkukene south.
Beef boys
Brief guys. Send photos to
all gossips throughout Talvik.
He stops to pee, I
Knowing the color and smell of urine.
- Odor and color.
- And make ready their weapons.
Now we shoot anything other than gulls,
for once.
Do you really
all this work?
I mean,
seen again, we have raised the Russians.
What we prevent them
to kill us?
I do not know what happens.
But for him to judge -
- You are his master.
I hope I will be yours.
Hopefully.
I do not know.
It has never happened accordingly -
- Mysterious voodoo zombie stuff.
I've never seen anything like this before.
I've seen a thousand zombie movies,
and this is not going anywhere.
You have created a whole new genre here.
Do we have a battalion
Nazi zombies against us -
-there are worse things
than having some Russian zombies.
He must die. Herzog.
For what he did.
We must kill him.
I must kill him.
For Hanna.
- Here it is.
- Yes.
Yes, it's here.
Herzog killed Stavarin
and 50 of his men here.
So they must be buried
here in the frozen soil.
How do we do it?
In the same way -
- As with him.
I put my hand on his head.
Okay. Right.
Digging up all takes several weeks.
You need to wake them,
a one way or another.
Lord.
Hell, yeah!
He was first seen here.
In Øksfjord.
And next time here.
Museum at lsnestoften.
So it looks as if
heading south. Perhaps there.
We have a problem.
A gang dressed as Germans
go bananas out there?
Bananas?
They killed loads of different people.
We have not had a murder since 74,
and suddenly there Ragnarok.
Okay, everybody, listen up!
Shoot first, ask later!
There is no one here.
We have sent the the door.
They are gone.
Since you do not
can complete the mission, -
- You can just turn
and go back to your snow cave.
Some have grown a bit since last time.
Been a little bigger.
I also took a couple of buddies
the dance.
Is not it a bit sour
when someone you thought was dead -
- Coming back to kill you?
Let's kill them.
Troops!
Attack!
Let's kill them all!
What the hell is going on here?
Is the carnival in town?
Is there a tank?
- Damn!
- Run!
Help!
Daniel! Idea.
- Should not we help them?
- Help who?
Those with blemishes in German uniform
or those with blemishes in Russian?
okay
Good boy.
- Jesus, Mary and Joseph Stalin!
- What the hell's going on?
Do as hell.
Looks like a video game.
Behold Martin Hykkerud!
- Yes!
- Should we take him?
No, no.
Wait until it calms down.
There are tactical policing.
Zombie Squad. It was time!
- It's a long story.
- There was a tank.
And one of them took my jacket.
- You found Stavarin.
- Yes, but they outnumber us yet.
We must make the fight more even.
Folks! We lose!
See!
Fuck!
No, no, no
No!
Wait!
We must kill him!
They are associated with him
Russians are to you.
If he dies, the other also.
We set a stop to this.
Untermensch.
Honestly, guys.
No seat belts?
You ask for it.
How damn many more are they?
Is this the end?
Monica, it's like this ends?
No, no.
- Door we now?
- No.
Fuck it.
Now I say only.
I, -
- Glenn Kenneth Toivonen, is
No!
- Blake!
- Glenn?
Monica ..
Why did not you just
on the mountain?
You got's what you should have.
You got the gold. Tax.
But it was not enough.
You were greedy.
Would have more.
Blake
- Monica
- Beware!
- Monica!
- Blake!
Blake! No!
That's why you lost.
Because you were greedy.
You know you lost the war?
Lost everything.
Joined ridiculed.
Pathetic.
And you know what?
You lose again.
No!
My God!
He did it!
- He killed Herzog.
- It worked. I knew it.
Herzog is dead.
He is dead. Yes!
It was damn close.
You did it!
You killed Herzog?
I do not
that it actually worked.
Of course it worked.
Doubted the Zombie Squad?
Kenneth Glenn, is he ...?
He did not.
It has been a true honor
killing zombies with you.
Likewise, Martin.
What is it? Okay.
- You can say it.
- Do it.
May the Force be with you.
Really? The?
Of all the ...? You chose it?
You have a million to choose from,
and then you take it?
- Where the hell are they?
- I know as hell.
Hell too! Bjarne!
Are you in a coma?
Go and find them, dammit!
I would resolve this matter.
Do not end with a hundred new corpses.
Where do we fit it all?
The garage and the freezer is packed.
I do not know! I do not know.
The gulls again. They do not
eaten so well since the war.
We should have
the damn machine.
Whoever translator
seagull language to human language.
Then we would fuck me
Jack the matter as an egg.
As an egg.
(groan)
Translation:
Scandinavian Text Service 2014