How are things back there.
Oh it's fine, slow.
I'm glad we're only a quarter-full.
Yeah, same up here.
Did you hear something
about the weather front?
Yeah, these things used to bother me.
The weather?
No, that we're going
to be delayed getting into Paris.
Please tell me you're panning
on getting some sleep tonight.
I can promise you we'll be in bed early.
Emily why don't you go out with us.
It will be so fun.
Yeah, Paris at night.
Ze Champs Elysee. Ze clubs.
- Ze men with their...
- I will be busy.
Now if you please excuse me ladies
I have some work to do.
Yeah.
That's a hint.
Aye Aye.
So what's the deal with the special cargo?
It is some last minute top leve
I government contractor shipment.
It says there's an armed guard in the hull.
That's a first.
What are we carrying?
I'm not sure I want to know.
Well, looks like al
I the signatures check out
so we are free to take it from the S.O.C.
It says here if there are any
abnormalities involving the cargo area.
Abnormalities?
We are to contact
a Dr. Bennett and Dr. Sebastian.
These were the guys
that secured the cargo.
They're in first class.
Abnormalities?
I'm glad this is my last flight.
Yeah.
Lucas, you need to settle down now.
You're not listening.
We could lose Kelly
and I'm not going to let that happen.
Would you calm down.
You're making a scene.
Now I told you.
I will bring Kelly out of stasis
when we have a controlled environment.
Not before.
We all know this is highly unorthodox.
We had to move quickly.
This is her our, only way out.
Unorthodox?
Hey! She was dying and we saved her.
If we hadn't intervened, she'd be dead.
You god damn well know that.
Now, were we able to reach our friend?
Kolinsky's made all the arrangements
for the transport
and we'll see him in Prague.
Prague?
I though we had a lab set up in Toulon.
Christ, our files have been hacked.
That will be the first place they look.
We are running out of time!
There have always been risks.
But think of the good we are doing.
We will save loved ones.
We will bring them back.
It's why we all have sacrificed.
Kelly knew the risks going into this.
That's easy for you to say.
That's not your wife down there.
Is it? Is it?
Shh, calm down. Sit down.
Sit down. Come on, Come on.
Now listen to me.
I know how you feel. I really do.
But do you for one minute
think I don't know what's at stake.
My entire company depends
on the success of this project,
and I am less concerned about losing
one life than I am of saving thousands.
So I am not going to let you,
or your wife,
or some petty little
Bureaucrat jeopardize this project.
So shut the fuck up
and get back to your seat,
because this subject is closed for good.
Are we clear on this Doctor?
We're clear.
Excuse me.
He's not going to let this go.
Don't worry about it.
Dr. Thorp will not be leaving Paris.
Not with us at any rate.
Excuse me miss,
I'll take a Rum and Coke please.
Oh, sorry Burrows. Rude of me.
Make that two.
Right, how bout a coke.
If a little bit of Bacardi were
to find its way in there,
it would be our little secret, huh.
Anything for you, Mr...?
Uh, Burrows, Truman.
But no thank you.
And I'm Frank.
Frank Lee Strathmore.
It's a name rich with tradition.
My umm, My family...
She doesn't need to know
your family history, Frank.
Look, I don't expect to be tied up long.
Just a couple of parking
ticket kinda things, really.
I mean, how bout you and I meet
at the Eiffel tower around Mid-Night...
I'm sorry to disappoint you but Frank here,
he's going to be a little busy.
That's ok.
Truman, if you guys
need anything, let me know.
Thank you.
OK.
Truman,
Truman.
Hmm. I guess that pretty
well does it for me.
Looks like if you play your cards right,
she could be cuffing you later.
You're going to shut up
and drink your coke.
Hi guys.
Hey.
My god you are lovely.
Hey stewardess. Do you think
I could get some sugar with my coffee?
So, is Ally packed?
She's been packed for five years.
The legendary Ray Bashore retiring.
So why isn't she with you
on your final flight?
She insisted on staying home
to get things ready for our trip.
So where are you two going?
Summer vacation with the grandkids
then we're on a slow ocean cruise
to Alaska. Just the two of us.
That's so romantic.
The ocean cruise maybe, but the kids?
Sounds like a nightmare.
Hey,
that's great Ray, really.
Thank you.
Looks bad ahead huh?
Um, not to worry.
So, I can't wait to go shopping
at Chanel in Paris.
Courtney says that
we have to go to Cariter first,
and then we can go to...
Yeah, well, I can't wait
to go surfing in Biarritz.
Surfing?
Oh yeah, we're going surfing.
ou can go surfing.
Good.
You and that slut Jackie
can go surfing all you want.
Wow, hey, Tony's my friend alright?
We're here to surf and you know that.
And hey, his girlfriend's a total bitch
and you know that.
I don't like her. Ok?
Whatever. OK.
Ok yourself.
You know!
Hey YO, Tone.
- Yeah?
- Gotta go long buddy.
Gotta go long buddy.
- Oh, oh, it hurts to get scored on.
- Stop it.
You're a child.
Wow, nice toss.
Hey!
I'll give it back to you
when I'm done playing with it.
Hey.
Dude, she cannot take the ball.
Obviously she can. Nice toss.
- Excuse me Mr. Freeman?
- Yes?
Can I get your autograph?
Ohh yeah, sure, sure.
That final putt on the last day
of the masters, man,
that was poetry.
Poetry huh?
Yes.
Alright there, here you go.
Thank you.
Thanks Mr. Freeman. Thanks a lot.
No problem.
Why can't they just leave us alone?
You told me this was a trip away from golf
and everything that goes with it.
Look, I promise that for rest of the trip,
I'm just gonna be plain old Billy, alright?
You won't even know Long Shot exists.
I promise you that.
OK.
I love that smile.
Excuse me Mr. Freeman.
Yeah?
Captain Bashore would love
to meet you.
When he has a break later
in the flight,
would you mind
if he stopsby for a visit.
Yeah, it's not a problem.
Thank you.
You know, while you're at it,
if you're done fawning over my husband,
I'd love another Bloody Mary.
Anna.
William. I'm on vacation.
I'll get you a drink right
away Mrs. Freeman.
And make sure
you put some Vodka in it this time.
Cause that's how I like to tee-off.
Hey, there's no reason
to be so rude alright.
You know I'm sure
there's someone back in coach
who hasn't got your autograph yet.
Maybe I'll go back there
and give it to them.
You knew what you were getting
into when you married me.
I thought I did.
You just keep twirling
that little putter of yours.
Cause that's all
you're gonna be twirling this trip.
Wasn't so little last night was it?
You know you've got the wrong man, right?
Yeah,
that's why Interpole
has your picture all over the internet.
It's a classic case of mistaken identity.
Yeah.
Hey.
Burrows, you can't treat me like this.
I'm not guilty. It's not fair.
Bouncing me all over the world
to stand trial here
and there for something I did not do.
I'm not guilty.
No, I have a clear conscience.
Yeah.
What is it going to take
to convince you I'm innocent.
An act of god.
Now shut up before I make you eat
that flotation device you're sitting on.
There we go.
We can fly around it but not above it.
This is a huge system.
It's about 150 miles east
and west of course
so it looks like either way we go,
we are screwed.
It's either that
or we fly all the way back around,
but that's going to add 30 minutes
to our flight at least.
Paris weather is not good
for our arrival.
I'm gonna deviate left
and thread the needle.
That gap might be our only shot
of getting around...
...this system without landing for fuel.
Folks, looks like it's going
to get a little bit bumpy ahead.
I'd like you to temain in your seats
and wear your seatbelts.
We'll probably be through this
in 10 or 15 minutes.
Thank you very much.
Ohh God.
Did you hear that?
Something must have shifted and fell.
As you know Mr. Madison, a combined
strike team of the CIA and FBI
seized the head-quarters
of MEDCON Labs in Los Angeles.
A number of arrests were made,
but we've been unable to determine
the wear-a-bouts of four key individuals.
The first one, Dr. Leo Bennett.
He's a head research scientist
and founder of MEDCON.
Noted for his work with retro-viruses,
and synthetic biology.
He was investigated two years ago
for illegal cloning research,
unfortunately, that investigation failed
to produce any indictments.
So far I've seen nothing
that warrants disturbing the President.
Can we get to the point here?
Look, we're trying
to reconstruct Bennett's hard-drive,
and we think there is cause for alarm.
We believe Leo Bennett is responsible
for the development
of a new strain of the Malaria virus.
And the containment
and transportation of Dr. Kelly Thorp.
Malaria?
Initially we thought it was Malaria.
However, we discovered that it
was something new, something different.
Bennett obtained a DNA sample
from a Mosquito native
to a remote area in Vietnam
which had a 100% mortality rate
within seconds,
which then regenerates that same organism
for a few seconds or longer,
depending on the subject organism.
What Bennett has developed is
a mutation of this same mosquito virus
to restart major organs
for an indefinite period of time.
Now what you're saying
is that his virus kills organs
and then brings them back to life.
Not just organs.
He apparently was experimenting
on the resurrection
of the entire human body after death.
Oh impossible.
I can't go to the president with this.
Jerry, I mean come on.
From what we've uncovered,
we believe he succeeded.
Ah, hello?
What is going on?
What is happening to me?
God damn it.
Jesus, what now?
We have electrical
and communication problems.
We just had a temperature drop
in the cargo hold.
This is Concord 239 to base.
Great, no radio.
With this crap for the next hour.
Perfect.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm sick. I need help.
I need help.
I'm a scientist with MEDCON Labs.
Where the hell is Dr. Bennett?
I need to talk to someone.
I'm coming out. Don't shoot.
Come out. I won't shoot.
What the fuck.
Fuck. Where is she?
Oh god, oh!
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
OK.
Hey will you grab me a Diet Coke
on your way back?
Sure honey.
Thanks babe.
Check out that dime.
Wow, that is one hot little biatch.
Ouch, fuck that hurt.
Oh hi honey.
So I guess that mid-flight blowjob
is out of the question?
Such a dick.
Sweetheart?
What?
Come here.
What? What's wrong?
I mean, what is somebody sees us?
What are you talk...
we're in a bathroom
what are you talking about?
No I... you know what I mean.
You're Peter's best friend.
So what?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, pardon me.
I didn't mean to scare you.
No, it's ok. I wasn't paying attention.
Sir, you actually need to take your seat.
The fasten seatbelt sign is on.
Yeah, yeah, um.
Can I get you some more coffee? Ok.
Yes, thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, Megan, rhymes with Vegan.
I was a vegan.
- Yeah?
- For two days.
Megan Vegan.
It's actually "Megan".
Right, no, I knew that.
Sir, you actually need to take your seat.
Ok, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just, you need to be more careful.
I mean, people sneaking up
on you like that.
You know, there's strange people here.
You never can tell what's going
to happen on these flights.
- Sir you need to take your seat.
- OK.
- Thanks, thanks. Buckle-up.
- You're welcome.
Jesus.
Ha, wow. Cool, huh?
Maybe this little diversion will keep
my mind off of your tasteless cheap suit.
Would you feel better if I was
in a bitch-ass, orange jumpsuit?
Like the one you are going
to be wearing the rest of your life.
There you go getting nasty again
when I am merely offering a criticism
of the sartorial horror show you call a suit.
However, I do like the shirt.
Does it come in a man's style?
And for your information, the jumpsuits
in France are a sort of burgundy. Yeah.
Well you should look nice in that color.
And now I know what color corsage
to get you when big Pierre
makes you his wife.
Someone sounds a wee bit jealous.
Yeah.
I'm going to descend a little.
Is it over yet?
Let's find out.
This is Randy.
It's Stacy.
I think some of the passengers
might have been hurt.
How bad?
I don't know.
It's a mess down here.
Well, we'll do the best we can.
Just stand by.
Looks like we're OK for a few minutes.
Give them the "go ahead" to check.
Let me know what's what.
Well folks, we apologize for the heavy
turbulence we have just experienced.
It appears as though
we're clear for the moment.
However, we are traveling
through some unstable air.
So as a precaution I would like you
to remain in your seats for the time being.
At this time, I would only like our flight
attendants up and about the cabin.
Thank you.
Would you make sure everyone's alright?
Then have one of the Doctors,
Bennett or Sebastian,
check the cargo situation out with you.
The cargo?
I'll get my tools.
Is she ok?
It's her head.
You alright dude. Did you take one?
The fucking bag hit me in the head.
Come on, that was fun.
It was just turbulence.
My god, don't be such a baby.
It didn't hit you.
Relax.
What is your problem girl?
Oh, are you scared we're going to crash?
Relax bitch. Enjoy the ride.
Wow, Jesus, pipe down you psycho.
Shut up.
What hell's wrong with you?
What?
You are a psycho.
You know, and you're a fucking skank.
I'm so sick of your shit.
Stop it!
Everyone just calm down.
Take your seats.
And you take your seats too.
What is wrong with you.
We have several warning lights
we don't usually get,
even with this weather.
It's probably nothing,
but we should look just to see.
I agree, why don't you two go.
Both of us?
Right.
Well whoever is going,
meet me by that exit door.
It usually takes a few minutes
to get down there
and there's no easy way to go.
God damn it.
I told you. I told you both...
Hey, hey, hey. Calm down.
Just go check on the passenger.
If it was a malfunction,
Kelly might be dead.
Yeah listen, don't take your eye off him.
Make sure he doesn't do anything stupid.
You guys ok?
I'm fine.
But do you think
we could move up to business class.
I mean, the planes really empty and all...
- He's kidding. We're fine.
- OK.
Thank you.
Hey, I am trying to help you out here.
She wants you. Make your move.
Go boy go.
I'm sorry if this is a problem.
No problem. I'll take care of it.
It could be dangerous.
Only if you're afraid of the dark.
Come on Burrows.
I need to go to the sandbox.
What?
I got to pee.
No, you heard the PA.
Sit down and hold it.
Fine.
If you should happen
to feel something warm,
just move a little to your right.
You're like a five year old.
Come on let's go.
Easy. Take it slow.
Yes, of course.
Burrows?
Mr. Burrows,
Truman.
Oh my god.
Alright gentleman. Here we go.
Truman.
What?
That little shit.
Flight-deck.
Captain, this is Megan at door 4L.
We've got a problem back here.
OK. How bad is it?
Mr. Burrows, the cop
who brought the prisoner on board,
was knocked out cold,
and his prisoner is missing.
Excuse me, have you guys seen
a funny looking skinny guy,
blue sweatshirt, turtle-neck,
walk through here?
No.
No? No? Alright.
Well that explains
the communication problem.
Fry,
Dr. Thorp?
Kevin?
Fry's not in the jump-seat.
My god. This can't be happening.
We need to get out of her, now.
Come on. We need to seal
the hatch now. Let's move.
Come on.
Lucas.
Kelly.
Oh god.
No, no!
Tony?
Asshole.
Don't scare me like that...
What? Hey, where the fuck are you going?
That hurts.
Hey you two.
You need to be in your seats
with the belts fastened.
Why don't you make yourself
a fucking sandwich while you're at it.
What have you done?
You son of a bitch.
What have you brought on board?
Take your seats everyone. Take your seats.
Everyone just calm down.
Do you know what's going on?
Ray, open up.
What's wrong? Randy!
Ray, bring the plane down.
Bring the plane down right now,
or we're all going to fucking die.
Tell me what the hell happened down there.
Ray. The fucking, the fucking,
the fucking scientists,
they let something out of the cargo-hold.
What are you talking about?
Where are the doctors?
Their dead. Ray, their dead...
- Sit down!
- Look at me man.
Everyone's going to fucking die.
They killed them.
Sit down and calm down.
Sit down.
Now. Sit down.
What happened to you?
Listen to me.
Just listen to me, Ray.
If you don't land this plane soon,
you, me, Emily, everybody
on this fucking plane is going to die.
You know I can't bring her down
without warning
and no place to land. Think about it.
There is something...
it's not human, down there man.
And it's going to kill everyone on board
unless we land this plane.
So whatever you do,
I don't care how you do it, just, just...
- I need you to calm down...
- Find a place, Ray,
and land the fucking plane.
- Find a piece of straight fucking road.
- You know the radio's gone,
and this storm isn't helping our situation.
It's clear we can try to cross.
But I'm turning around
and heading back.
There's a TSA man aboard.
Find out which passenger he is
and get him up here.
Now!
Ray.
Are you sure that's the guy?
Ok, they're dead.
And you say whatever killed them,
wasn't human.
I know it sounds insane.
I saw this happen.
I mean those things,
I mean they ripped those men apart
and they were eating them.
You said there was a fugitive on board.
Is it possible you saw him down there?
No.
I told you. There were two of them
and these... these things aren't human.
I'm going to go find out
what was in those containers.
Where are you going?
I'm going to go talk
to that asshole Bennett cause he knows.
Sit down.
Well, I'll check it out and report back.
Any sign of him?
No.
Shoot.
How's your head?
Better than my ego.
Come on, he can't hide forever.
As soon as the turbulence settles,
I'm going to go look for him some more.
Don't go alone.
Why? Is he dangerous?
Well, he's probably never owned
a weapon before,
but he's more
of a con-artist than anything.
What did he do? Can you tell me?
He posed as an accountant,
stole their Jet and crash-landed it.
And we finally caught up to him.
Everybody wants him.
Why are you taking him to Paris?
You ok?
Yes.
You should take your seat.
OK. Be careful.
OK
Hey look at this.
I think I found Concord 239.
Nobody's been able to reach them
for over an hour.
Los Angeles dispatch,
this is Yellow-Knife-Center.
I believe I have your concord 239
on my screen.
It's in the middle
of two huge weather fronts.
And transponder indicates it's off course.
No, no radio contact yet. I'll try now.
Concord 239, Yellow-Knife-Center.
Los Angeles Dispatch,
yes I understand.
I repeat, you must tell 239
to return to US airspace.
The Canadian government
will not permit them to land
or continue to fly in their airspace.
This decision has come
from the highest level
and the CDC. Is that clear?
Can you tell me what it is
you're transporting in the cargo-hold?
I'm sorry.
My cargo is a highly classified project
linked to our nation's security.
You don't have the necessary clearance.
I'm with the TSA, Federal Air-Marshall.
I need to know what's down there.
Well how fortunate for us to have a man
with your obvious talents aboard.
You seem a bit nervous Doc.
Is everything alright?
Just don't like flying.
Isn't it true your
two colleagues accompanied
the co-pilot down to the cargo-hold
because there was some problem.
No, no problem.
No problem?
It's just a routine mid-flight inspection.
Routine.
What I can tell you,
while the cargo isn't dangerous,
it's highly perishable
and extremely valuable.
So, the cargo area is off limits
to unauthorized personnel.
- Well, can you tell me...
- No, I'm sorry.
I've said more
than I should have already.
Burrows?
Yeah.
Paul Judd, TSA. I believe
your prisoner is in the cargo-hold.
Ready?
Hey Frank.
Frank.
Frank. Get out here.
Dr. Thorp.
Dr. Sebastian.
Anybody out there?
That's a lot of blood.
Somebody's in trouble.
Yeah, if it's Frank's
he needs help now.
Check that out.
Looks like he escaped
through the ducts.
I don't know.
That's an awful lot of blood
for a skinny little shit like Frank.
You go that way. I'll go this way.
Meet back in 5.
Yes.
Hey Frank.
You there buddy?
Why don't you come out
and talk to me, man?
Everything's alright. It's cool.
We can just talk. It's just me.
Frankie.
I'm going to kill that little shit.
Alright, I'm coming up.
Yes.
You're sure?
Outstanding.
Thank you Lieutenant.
They have located Bennett and his team.
Hallelujah.
You know Frank,
sometimes this job is really boring.
This is not one of those times, bud.
You're making this real exciting.
Son of a bitch.
Paul?
Frank?
Oh my god.
Oh my god I'm going to be sick.
Cara where the fuck are you going.
What the fuck?
Tony, this bitch just got shot dude.
There's fucking bullets coming
from somewhere.
Please take your seats.
Take your seats. Everything's fine.
Please, take your seats.
Everything's fine.
Thank you.
Ray, it's total chaos down here.
There were gunshots or something
that freaked out the passengers.
Emily?
Go, take the gun.
My god, this can't be happening.
Get back.
Go back to your seats and stay there.
Go back.
Move, move, move, move.
Get out of my way.
Cara. Cara.
Cara, open the door.
Move.
Cara.
Oh shit.
Dude, what the fuck?
Get back. Get back. Get back.
Get back.
Get out of here. Get out of here.
Cara.
- Stay back there. Stay back there.
- Cara.
What the fuck, dude?
What is this?
- Christ.
- Holy shit.
Get off him. Get off him.
What the fuck? What the fuck?
What the fuck is going on?
Please, please,
please go back to your seats.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, what happened?
What the fuck happened?
Please take your seats.
Flight-deck.
Ray, something's happened down here.
Something attacked one
of the passengers, and he's dead.
You got to get us down, Ray.
Oh my god.
- Megan, listen to me.
- You don't understand.
There's blood everywhere.
And, and Stacy
and one of the other passengers was hurt.
How did it happen?
Who attacked you?
I don't know,
um, maybe the escaped prisoner.
I can't think of anyone else.
Look, Megan
we've turned around and we'll land
the first place we can find.
But the only way back is through
the center of the storm.
We need to get the passengers
back to their seats now.
OK.
I'm scared Meg.
Oh, my god!
Shit.
Help me.
Open.
Oh, shit.
They're going to kill us all.
I really should go check
on the passengers.
Open this door.
Help me.
For Christ's sake,
they are going to kills us all.
Open the fucking door.
God damn it. Help me.
Bill?
Hey. What's going on?
- Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
- What's going on man?
I can't explain.
We've got to get out of here.
- They're going to kill us.
- Calm down and tell me what's going on.
What is going on, man?
We need to hide.
We need to get out of here,
or we're going to die.
Bill, where are you going?
Come on, come on.
Where?
Back-galley. The floors 2 feet thick.
It's the only safe place.
I can't, I can't my wife is upstairs.
Well get her and get back
there as soon as you can.
Come on, now. Come on.
Hey you, come on.
- Help me get this open.
- Tell me something.
It's the only place we can find.
Shh, shh, be quiet.
Hey, you, you get in there.
See if you can see anything.
Go on. Get up. Get up.
See anything?
Help me!
Come on baby.
Come on...
Stacy!
Oh my god.
Are you alright? No bites?
We thought. We thought...
What? That it was me gnawing
on all the passengers?
No. I'm a vegetarian.
The overall feeling among the scientists
working on this is that we are dealing
with a serum transfer virus.
This virus is without
a known vaccine or cure.
But this type virus transfers
only through bodily fluids.
And then most effectively,
blood from an infect victim.
And it enters a cut or saliva.
The MEDCON scientists believed
they could make this work,
despite the side-effects.
That of being brought back from the dead.
In fact, they looked
at these side-effects as a benefit.
Let me paraphrase these notes
that we found on Dr. Bennett's desk.
They wanted this virus as a bio-weapon.
To keep soldiers fighting
after they've been mortally wounded.
To release a captive enemy infected
with the virus and let him infect others
until they all kill each other.
I'm going to recommend
to you and to the president
that we destroy flight 239
before it can reach a populated area.
Let me get this straight.
You want our forces to follow a shoot
to kill order regarding
a civilian aircraft?
We've had no communication with the aircraft.
We must assume the cargo has been breached
and that the virus has spread
throughout the passenger section.
The only chance we have to contain
this is to vaporize every
living thing aboard that aircraft.
Before the virus can reach
a major population center.
Do you concur?
I'm afraid I do.
Can you get me the president please?
Mother of god.
Get off of her. Get off.
Get off.
Oh my god.
Why? Why'd you do this huh?
Hey, I'm talking to you, man.
It wasn't me.
I was just following orders.
They told me it was
an experiment to extend life.
I had no idea there
would be these crazy side-effects.
Well look around you asshole.
Your side-effects
have eaten half the passengers.
Hey, I don't have to listen to you.
You were the one that seemed
like you were giving all the orders.
You were the one
that the cop was talking to.
And you were the one
that sent the others below.
I heard all of that.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
It wasn't me I tell you.
Hey, keep your voice down.
Well you just keep talking.
You'll draw their attention.
It's starting
to get really tight in here.
Yeah, yeah,
I think we're getting closer.
Ray. Ray, I'm hurt.
Open up. Hurry.
Ray.
Hurry.
Oh my god.
I don't know if that's going to work.
It has to work.
Let's get the other side.
OK.
Two in the chest.
One in the balls. That's what I say.
It's barricaded.
Ah, Frank I see you.
You get that?
He is a little pre-vert.
Come on.
- Oh my god.
- Come here Frank.
Where have you been?
Where have I been?
- I have been up and down this plane looking
- So have I.
Hey, back off.
Statistically speaking, the tail section
is the safest place to be in a crash.
- Of course, no one...
- Frank, not now.
Help me with this.
Go get something else.
- Get something else.
- I am.
Do it.
Right there.
I can't lift. There's a... wait.
Frank.
Wait, wait, wait, shh.
Quiet, quiet. I hear something.
I don't hear anything.
Go.
Hold on. Hold on.
Oh my god, baby.
OK, we got to go. We got to go.
We got to go.
Go, go, go, go.
Alright, we need to find anything
that can be used as a weapon.
Does anyone have anything sharp.
They confiscated my toenail-clippers.
Pearl handled with
matching tweezers. Quite lovely.
Damn Frank, you should have brought those.
You could have saved the day.
You never know.
How much ammunition do you have left?
I got five in here and one clip.
What about you?
One full clip. Five more.
Shit.
Maybe we could electrocute
the bastards.
- No, no.
- No, no, no, don't do that.
I guess that could have gone better.
Frank, you stupid shit.
Please tell me you're dead.
Where'd you find him?
The auxiliary lights...
Oh my god.
The auxiliary lights will come
on any second. I hope.
Frank. We need to find weapons.
Still no answer from the cockpit?
Nothing.
I can't believe everyone's dead.
My god, we're going to die.
Megan. Listen to me. Listen to me.
- We are not going to die...
- No?
No, we're not going to die.
I promise you.
I need your help.
I need you to be strong.
Right.
Did you see that?
What the hell was that?
Listen.
Someone's up there.
Don't shoot.
We need to have a plan to get
this plane down safely.
Does anyone know
if the pilot's still alive?
I, I tried to reach him.
Try him again.
OK.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
The captain is dead.
We're on auto-pilot.
So what,
- we just fly around till they get us?
- - No.
Or until we run out of fuel.
Actually, that might be preferred.
- Run out of fuel?
- Yeah.
Hey, we got to get to the flight-deck
to check on the captain.
We got to do this now before
they start coming at us.
I don't think you have enough bullets
to make it to the cockpit.
The guard down below has a weapon.
We need that weapon.
That's our only chance.
- Absolutely.
So what? You're just going
to go down there?
Down there. How do we know
he didn't use all the ammo already.
We don't know, Frank.
It's good to know that you still have
a sense of humor in a time like this.
I know it's not much to look at
but with any luck,
it's going to buy me enough time
to get that weapon
and get back here
without tearing the plane apart.
Why are you doing this?
I made a promise to someone.
I keep my promises.
I have radar contact with Concord 239.
Should have visual in two minutes.
Burrows, in case this blows up
anything important,
do you mind
if I take out your new girlfriend?
Hey Bennett.
Got something for you.
Roger. Try to establish contact.
You have three minutes from my mark.
Mark minus three minutes.
Roger that.
Try to establish contact.
I'm going to circle and signal.
Look.
I'd like to think
that's the Calvary, but um.
What do you mean?
We don't have much time.
Well, aren't they going to save us?
No. They're not going to save us.
There's just us.
Unless we let him know we're alive,
he's going to shoot us down.
They can't do that.
He's right.
Unless we answer them,
they're going to fire the missile at us.
What do we do?
We answer him.
Someone needs to get to the cockpit,
and signal that jet.
Does anybody know how to fly a jet?
Anyone? Anyone?
You can fly a jet?
Well, not officially.
But I know most of the basics.
Basics?
Of course, it's been awhile.
We just need to get to the radio and use it.
We need to go now, Frank.
Alright. Count me in.
No, no, no, Billy don't leave me.
I'll go. I'll go.
No. Stay here.
I'm going to do my part.
- Why?
- I'll see you soon, baby.
I'll see you soon.
Let's go.
Such a big mouth.
Nice drive.
Command, this is 431.
Go ahead.
239 has no one
in control that I can see.
Repeat, 239 has no one
Billy.
- Billy. Billy.
- Let her go.
Billy.
Come on, baby.
You son of a bitch.
You don't know who you're dealing with.
Come on. Let's go. Come on.
Nah, nah, That's it for me.
You guys go.
You guys go. I've got to wait for Anna.
Go. Go.
No response to my signals.
You are clear to engage 239.
Command, please repeat.
Roger that.
Clear to engage contact with 239.
Hold on, baby.
I love you.
I love you too, baby.
I always have.
Is that you Bennett?
Oh shit.
Come on mother fucker.
I want to make sure you keep
that shit eating grin on your face
all the way to hell.
Command, this is 431.
It appears
that engine number 3 is burning.
She's gumming me to death.
Go, go, go, go.
Where's the auto-pilot?
- I don't know. You asking me Frank?
- This is different.
This is different.
Don't yell at me.
I'm not yelling.
I have lock.
We're alive. I repeat we're alive.
Abort. Abort.
Missile away.
Incoming object. Incoming object.
They must have launched a missile.
Frank we got seconds.
- I know. Where is the auto-pilot?
- I don't know.
Collision imminent. Collision imminent.
Here, here.
Auto-pilot off.
What do I do?
- Ready.
- uh-huh
We got live civilians.
Aborting, repeat, I am aborting.
Pull up.
Hold on!
Jesus.
Pull up.
You did it, Frank.
Oh shit.
Frank.
Yes.
Mountain.
Pull back.
Back.
Pull up. Pull up.
You did it my friend.
Did you ever consider going out
with an ex-cop?
I went out with a cop once.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, the only thing he was good
for was scratching my back
when I couldn't reach.
Do you ever get that itch anymore?