♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 1
Madam.  Yu has grown so big.
Congratulations!
Thank you. Thank you.
Wishing our Brother Jiang (Jiang Yu's dad)  good fortune and longevity.
-Thank you. -Wishing the Ling Long Dye Factory a thriving
and prosperous business.  - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
-Congratulations, Young Master  -Mr. Ma Ke (Mark),
Mr. Wei Lian (William), please go inside.
Okay.
Big Brother. Why are all of their names so strange?
Dad says China will need to open its doors to do business in the future.
Everyone will need to collaborate with foreigners so that's why they changed their names to something foreign.
It will make it easier to do business with foreigners in the future. Do you understand?
Your big brother knows so much.
Yu Er, all of the guests are almost here. Why has your dad not returned yet?
The workers developed a new dye.  Dad has been at the dyehouse for the past few days,
waiting for the dye to come out of the vat.  He doesn't have time to care about celebrating his birthday.
Mom, don't worry.  I'll go look for him right now.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Go quickly and hurry back.
Master, look!  Success! It's all a success!
Rich in colour and soft to the touch.  Looks like this dye is really good.
-Agreed.  -We're successful.
Everyone, you've all worked hard.
Master, you've worked hard.
Mrs. Zhou
Master.
How is the head of your family (husband)?
Thank you Master for your concern. The doctor said that he has a chronic disease.
He has to be healed slowly.
Right. Right. Has to be treated slowly and slowly cured.
If you need money urgently, remember to tell me.
We can give you an advance on your wages.
-Thank you, Master. -Master! Master!
Master! Master!
Master, shouldn't we be heading back?
It's your birthday today.  They'll be starting the banquet soon.
Oh. Right. Right. Right.
Then I'll leave the rest to you guys.  Tonight, give everyone additional portions of dinner.
Congrats, Master.
-Get up!  -Congrats, Master.
Excuse me, Officer. May I ask, what are you doing?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Chief Wu, you honour us with your presence.
This is...
I received a secret report.
It said that Ling Long Dye Factory was selling dog meat as mutton.  (to assume a false identity to conceal one's true purpose)
On the surface, it looks like a dye business.
But privately, it is dealing opium.
-Search this place!  -Wait!
-Chief Wu.  -Let's not let personal interests interfere with public duties.
-Search!  -Yes, Sir!
-Go there. Quick.  -Follow me.  -Yes.
This way.
Search carefully. Quick.
Get out of the way. Get out of the way.  Search carefully.
Chief Wu. For generations while in Huzhou, Ling Long has always been a legitimate business.
This is a well-known fact.
You two go to that side!
Sir.
The quality is superior.
Let's talk.
Chief Wu, I repeat, I'm innocent.
This must be someone's plan to frame me.
Please, Chief Wu. I implore you to distinguish right and wrong.
-Help me seek justice.  -In this world, in fact, there's no justice.
If you want justice, it's really simple.
I'll let you use your Jiang family's most important item in exchange (for it).
Alright.
In this room, what do you fancy?
Take your pick.
I want your Jiang family's secret formula for dyeing.
Wu Hong Da,
as a dignified Chief,
you came here to Ling Long to put on such a show.
Just for this?
If you're willing to give me the secret formula,
I can save you from prison.
But if you refuse a toast only to drink a forfeit,  (refuse to do something, but in the end, was forced to do it)
I will make you lose both honour and fortune, confiscate your property, and execute your family.
This trafficking opium issue, if I say it's big, it's big.
If I say it's small, it'll be small.
You're a smart man.  You should know which to choose.
Dream on!
-Get out! Get out!  -My things are still inside.
Let me through. Let me through.
Let me through.  Aunt, what's going on? Where's my dad?
He's still inside.
Let me in.
Dad!
Dad! Wake up, Dad!
Dad, wake up!
Dad!
Opium
is a very strong drug.
It brings people to bad thoughts and evil deeds.
Smoking opium turns a most benevolent person into a monster.
Because Jiang Wen Yuan was using his company to smuggle opium,
he must be severely punished.
According to the law, he must be executed.
Jiang Wen Yuan, fearing punishment for his crimes, committed suicide.
Therefore, the Ling Long Dye Factory and the Jiang family's fortune must all be forfeited.
The dye factory will be closed immediately.  All workers will be dismissed at once.
Quick. Let's go. Let's go.
-Remove everything.  -Yes, sir! Removing them.
-Hurry up. Hurry up.  -What are you doing? Stop!
Stop!
You can't do this.
-Get out!  -Yu!  -Get out! Get out!
Mom! Mom!
-Old Master (Husband).  -Let go of us!
I can't leave!
Get out! Get out!
-Get out.  -Mom!
Old Master! Old Master!
Mom!
This is my house. What right do you have to chase us out?
This is Jiang's household!
Jiang Wen Yuan committed a deadly sin, causing us to lose our Jiang's reputation
Now the Clan Leader is driving you out of the family tree!
You have no right to live here anymore.
-That's right. Go. Get out.  -My dad was framed.
I beg every Uncle to speak justice for us.
Get out. Go.
-Why waste your breath on them?  -Mom!  -Go!
Go away. Nothing to see here.
They broke the clan rules.
Dad, hang on for a few more days.
Once Mom gets this month's pay, she'll be able to buy your medicine.
Once you take the medicine, you'll slowly get better.
Dad. Are you alright, Dad?  Dad, hang on.
Just hang on, Dad.
Mom!  Mom, Dad's medicine has run out.
There's no medicine.
There's no wages.
Ling Long's gone too.
What?
Dad.
Dad. Endure it.
Mom, I'm going out to earn some money.
Shao Tian!
-Mom.  -Fei Fei.
You these black-hearted people. My only son, due to inhaling the smoke,
became someone that is not like a human or a ghost!
- You- -Yu
What's wrong, Yu?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'll bring you to see a doctor. Otherwise, it'll leave a scar.
No need, Mom. I'm fine.
This scar, is a scar caused by Wu Hong Da destroying our family.
Let it be.  It'll be a reminder for me of how Dad died.
Mom, I'm fine.
Let's go.
Young Master Ma! Young Master Ma!
-Young Master Ma.  -I told you I don't have any money to lend you, Zhou Shao Tian.
Everybody knows your family is poor.  Moreover, you have a sickly father.
Lending you money would be like hitting a dog with a meat bun, never to return.
Young Master Ma, I'll just borrow one silver dollar
to buy medicine for my dad.  I'll definitely think of a way to pay it back.
Young Master Ma, I'm begging you.  I just need one silver dollar.
Money... I do have it.
However, only if you are willing to crawl between my legs
and bark like a dog. If you please me,  then I'll lend you the money.
You...
Crawl! Crawl! Hurry up!
Crawl! Crawl! Hurry up and crawl!
Crawl! Crawl!  He's crawling. Good.
Crawl! Hurry up!
Hurry up! What're you doing? Quick!
Hurry up and crawl. Go faster.
Good. That was good.
-This is so fun.  -Alright. Bark like a dog. Bark like a dog.
Bark like a dog.
Good. That was good.
-This is too much fun.  -Come here and see. There's actually someone who, for a silver dollar,
is willing to be a dog.
Young Master Ma, my money.
If you want money, there's none.  But I can reward you with something else.
Come. Give this fall-in-water-dog a good thrashing.  (someone who is down on their luck)
Take this, fall-in-water-dog.  Hit him. Harder.
Hit him. Harder.
We'll beat you up, fall-in-water-dog.
Young Master Ma.  Young Master Ma, I just need one silver dollar
to buy medicine for my dad.  Just one silver dollar can save my dad's life.
I just need one silver dollar.  I'll definitely pay it back, Young Master Ma.
Let's go.
Young Master Ma. Young Master Ma.  Please lend me one silver dollar.
I wish to save my dad's life.
Screw you.
I'm begging you, Young Master Ma.
Please give me one silver dollar.
I wish to save my dad's life.
I'm begging you. I just need one silver dollar.
One silver dollar will be able to save my dad's life.
Here, for you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Endure it. Just endure it a little longer.
Just hang on for a bit.  Shao Tian went out to get your medicine.
He'll be back in a bit.
I'm... I'm sorry.
All these years, to cure this sickness,
not only did we spend all our money,
we also owe a debt.
I beg you to help me do something.
Give me relief.
Let me go.
What are you saying?
Instead of a living dead,
it would be better to have an earlier release.
No, you can't!
Dad.
Not like a person yet not like a ghost, living like this,
I'm really suffering.
Help me find relief. I'm begging you.
Mom!
They dared to move here. I say...
Quickly go away.
Go away! Go away!
Get lost!  If you dare talk nonsense again,
I won't hold back.
Go away! Scram!
Mom!
By the grace of Heaven
and His Majesty, the Emperor
Huzhou Supervisor Wu Hong Da
has positively solved the case of the opium smugglers.
In regard to his outstanding dilligent compliance
and his extraordinary productivity,
he is being elevated to the court official of the 6th rank
and given the reward of five hundred and twenty silvers.
Admire heaven's will ( hear hear).
Great.
Twelve Years Later
Cai Hong, if anything catches your eye, just buy it.
In the afternoon, I'll have Shao Tian pick you up.
Dad, I'm not a kid anymore.  Why do you always ask people to follow me?
Okay. Okay. Anything you say.  Once you're home, give me a call.
I got it.
-Go.  -Dad, take care.
To Ling Long.
Let's go.
Wu Long, what should we get for Dad's birthday?
-Hello, Boss.  -Hello, Boss.
Slow down.
-Please.  -Hello, Boss.
Sir, you've got a great eye.  This Parker Pen
is the only one in Huzhou. Even Shanghai doesn't have one.
Look at this pen tip. It is made with special materials.
The tip is sharp and silky smooth, with gilding on the outside.
If you use it with the Lei De ink, it will write smoothly and legibly.
It's not only just functional, it will also show your status.
This fountain pen is perfect for father's birthday present.
I don't want anything else. I want this fountain pen.
But this gentleman saw it first.
Sir. Could you let me have this pen
because it's very important to me?
If you are willing, I can pay you double.
Here.
You are too generous. We only just met and you are giving me such an expensive gift.
Thank you. I will treat you to a meal on another day.
What do you like to eat? I can treat you to anything.
Where should I find you? Where do you live? What is your name?
I paid for this pen.
If you dare to take this pen and step out from the shop,
I can immediately sue you for theft.
Thanks.
Sir, take care.
Wait!
Come back. What is your name?
Are you going to offer again to buy my name?
But it's a pity that you can't just buy my name.
I have never seen such a rude, stingly and mannerless man like you!
I also have never seen such a willful and unreasonable lady like you.
And you are a blockhead!
You are smelly and stubborn. Do you believe that I can do anything
to find out your name.
I don't believe you.
Let's make a bet then. If I don't spend a single cent to find out your name, the pen is mine.
Let's talk again when you find me.
Just you wait. I will definitely be able to find you.
I'm so furious.
-Rotten Stone Head, you finally found your conscience? -What's wrong?
-Brother Shao Tian -Rotten Stone Head?
It's that guy who fought with me over the pen.
Get up and talk.
Brother Shao Tian. How did you know I'm here?
Because we are able to read each other's mind.
Brother Shao Tian, did you know? I was really unlucky just now.
I actually saw a unique and beautiful Parker pen.
But I just had to meet a person who had to fight with me for that pen. He didn't have any generosity.
This matter is easy to deal with. Leave it to me, I will send
exactly the same Parker pen on your father's birthday.
No need. That pen is very expensive.
It will cost half of your annual salary.
I didn't mean that, Brother Shao Tian. Please don't blame me.
As long as it is something you like, I will definitely fulfill your wish.
Leave this to me.
Good morning, Boss.
Morning, Boss.
Morning, Boss Jiang.
Morning.
Miss. This is what you asked for.
I know. You can leave first.
-Fei Fei-Brother, you came at the right time.
Look at this.
This is from Ling Long.
Our worker used the newest material to create this.
Using dyes from France to dye the materials,
it has such vibrant colours and is soft to the touch,
and there is no traditional smell that hurts the nose.
All our workers started work today.
The five tons of French dyes that we ordered have already arrived at the Shanghai dock.
That time, all the workers would put in their best to work.
That way, our production will surpass Ling Long,
to become the greatest Dyeing Factory in Jiang Hu.-Great.
This is Ling Long's list of customers.
All our fabrics would be sold at a lower price than Ling Long.
Steal all their customers away to our shop.
Brother, everything is prepared.
Everything Wu Hong Da stole from us in the past,
we will get it back.
Wu Hong Da, it already has been 12 years.
I'm back.
- Boss. - Shao Tian, come and sit here.
So how?
Did you profess your love for Cai Hong yet?
Shao Tian is useless. I have yet to find an appropriate time.
You are capable in business but when it comes to women, you are not.
Put in more effort. You have my support.
This is the new generation now.
Cai Hong must agree.
Here, have your tea.
Boss thinks too highly of me. I am not worth it.
Thinks too highly of you? I understand you.
You were born of a poor family but I happen to think of it as your good point.
That way, you are able to withstand hardship and work honestly.
You are also meticulous. I won't get the wrong guy. Drink tea.
Thank you for your trust. I would definitely take good care of Cai Hong.
I will give you another chance then.
Come for dinner tonight at my home.
Thank you, Boss.
Shao Tian, your acting is not bad.
Put in more effort. You will be on the way to become the son-in-law of the Wu Household.
Dad, mom. Please have tea.
Cai Hong. How old are you this year?
Dad. Don't you know that
to ask a Lady's age in the West is considered rude?
Don't you know your father? He's doing this on purpose. How could he not know your age?
Cai Hong. It is that I have seen ladies of your age
already get married, so...
So, you think that I'm unable to get married, right?
Don't tell me that all the good men in Huzhou are already married.
Not all the good men are already married.  I have found one for you.
I think he wouldn't dare to escape.
I think I can still stay
with you for a few more years. I don't want to marry anyone.
Lord, see how sensible Cai Hong is.
- What do you know? - You should learn more.
Mom. Why did you hit me?
For Cai Hong to have a good spouse is the best way to be filial to me.
Okay, I know that you hate me. You don't want me to stay with you.
I'm going to find Wu Long who doesn't hate me.
Look at her. She is blushing.
Shao Tian.
Go.
Okay.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
See how Wu Long is able to understand us,
he left such a big courtyard to ourselves.
Do you know that you didn't scare Wu Long away?
Why are you looking at me?
You are pretty.
Cai Hong. We have known each other for a long time.
I would like to ask you a question.
What is my place in your heart?
You are fine.
I regard you as my older brother.
Older brother?
But I don't want to be your older brother.
Every day, I would like
to eat and chat with you.
- That would be great. - It's not that difficult to do this.
You can visit me often. We can have meals and chat together.
- I'm saying, the both of us... - You are even eavesdropping?
Dad.
This wench. I caught her eavesdropping.
Don't let her disturb you. Continue with where you were going.
Hateful.
Cai Hong.
Shao Tian.
I will help you find the opportunity next time.
There is a big difference between an older brother and a husband.
That year, Cai Hong's mother also said that I was her older brother.
You still said I eavesdropped. What about you?
Why are you not going back?
Shao Tian.
Work hard.
I already prepared the hot water for your bath.
I don't need it.  Just continue to recite your scriptures.
Everyday abstaining from eating meat and chanting prayers not because you are afraid my dad won't ascend to heaven.
It's because you're afraid you'll receive retribution.
We, Mei Fu, wants to order a hundred fabrics!
-Don't squeeze! -Boss.
- Hello. - Brother.
Fei Fei. What's wrong?
Bad news. She has gone missing from the hospital.
Don't panic. I will be there soon.
Sorry.
Fei Fei, where is mom?
Brother. Mom is missing. I went out to buy some snacks and she went missing.
Brother, do you think anything would happen to mom? Could it be that she is trying to commit suicide again?
- Brother... - Don't let your imagination run wild. Mom will be fine.
Don't cry first. Let's split up and find her.
Okay.
Thank you.
Stinky Rock, I don't believe that I cannot find you.
Mom.
- May I ask if you have seen this person? - No.
Thanks.
Have you seen anywho who looks like him?
No.
Hello.
Aunt. May I ask if you have seen him?
This person?
- I saw him.  You saw him?
Who is he and what is his name?
Do you think he's good looking?
What has being good looking got to do with this?
If he's not handsome, why are you looking for him then?
I...
I can only follow her wishes to let her tell me his name.
Yes, I find him very good looking.
You see, he has a strikingly handsome face.
He has a Grecian nose, strong brows and is bright-eyed, with an uncommon demeanor.
No matter how you look at him, he is smoothing to look at, a handsome man.
Do you like him?
Aunt, I'm a girl.
How could I tell you?
Why don't you tell me his name?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
I'm so embarrassed.
How did you get here?
Of course, I have my own ways.
Give me the fountain pen.
Yes, you found me
but what is my name?
Mom, let's go.
This girl is looking for you.
I know.
I will definitely find out your rotten name.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki