♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 2
Boss. You are looking for me?
Ling Long is in trouble.
There's a dye factory called Yao Sheng, selling their products at a lower price, to drive Ling Long out of business.
How can this be?  Our Ling Long is a well-known brand,
with many customers and quality goods.
Yao Sheng used dyes imported from France.
The textiles they produce are okay,  but their price is 10 percent cheaper than ours.
However, the cost of importing dyes is expensive.
How could their textiles be cheaper than ours?
I think that Yao Sheng is disregarding costs,
and doing cut-throat competition.
Have someone look up Yao Sheng's backing.  Also, take a look and see how much money we have left in our account.
We must defeat them this time.
Yes.
Shao Tian.
What's wrong? Why do you look hassled?
Shao Tian. Listen to me. I just transferred the money out.
Wu Hong Da suddenly wants to check the balance of the accounts.
He says it's to deal with the cut-throat competition.
Tell me what we should do.
It was such a big sum of money and you dared to steal it. It's causing a stir now.
You're so scared that you're about to piss.
If they investigate the huge sum of money, we will be in trouble.
You don't know Wu Hong Da. He is very cruel.
Of course, I know what kind of person he is.
I schemed about this money for a long time.
Don't worry.
I'm his eyes. You are his hands.
We know very well what actions he will take.
Shao Tian. Didn't you say that we would leave Huzhou once the money was in our hands?
When will we leave?
Very soon.
I have a plan. Don't be impulsive.
Shao Tian. The money will be in our hands soon. Why aren't we leaving?
It can't be that you really like the Miss of the Wu family?
You want to be their son-in-law?
I'm saying, Shao Tian. Stop dreaming.
If Miss knew you are scheming with her father behind her back, she would chew and spit you out in a second.
Don't get involved in my affairs.
I know what to do.
Have you seen this person?
No.
Hello. Have you seen this person?
Okay, you can leave first.
Manager Jiang.
Madam Jiang's illness is not stable. It's worse than before.
And there wasn't any symptoms before her illness started.
We, the medical staff, have been trying our best to help her,
but have had little success.
When she is discharged, you and Miss Fang must work hard to persuade her.
Perhaps, she might accept the advice of her family members.
It has been many years. When my mom thinks of unhappy events,
she becomes like this.
We have tried many methods and consulted many doctors
but there is no progress.
Mom. What are you doing?
Give me the scissors.
Yu Er. I don't want to live anymore.
If I die, you don't have to suffer so much.
Madam Jiang. Let's talk it over. Your son is here.
- Don't do anything foolish.- It's useless.
They forced my husband to die.
They are thinking of forcing me and the Wu family.
- Mom. - Don't move.
Okay, I won't move. Don't do anything either.
Don't move.
You have suffered for the past few years.
I didn't take good care care of you. Instead, you had to take care of me instead.
When I'm dead, you don't have use your savings to treat me.
I really can't drag you down any longer.
Mom, don't say this. You are not dragging me down.
When I die,
I can be free. You can be free too.
Aunt.
Mom.
Doctor, help me to treat her wound.
Aunt. You said that you wanted to be free and didn't want to drag anyone down.
Actually, you are trying to run away and using the pain as your excuse.
Do you think that if you die, they will really be relieved?
You are wrong.
Your death will only bring them more pain.
They will only hate themselves for not being able to protect their own mother.
They will also be in pain as to why you wouldn't shoulder this with them.
You are also leaving all your pain to them.
They will never be able to forgive you and themselves.
Four years ago, my mom and I were in the same situation as you.
To relieve me, she chose to kill herself.
These years, I've been living in a painful abyss.
If you want your son to be like me,
everyday living while blaming oneself, then do it!
Remember, next time find someplace where there'll be no one around.
No one will disturb you again.
Everything should be alright. Take a rest soon.
Nurse. Where is the outpatient clinic?
Over there.
Thanks.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Sorry about just now.
Your apology doesn't sound sincere.
I never thought you also had experienced the same hardships I did.
My mom was just like your mom.
For many years, she had to endure the pain caused by her illness.
The many years of suffering caused her to turn from gentle to bad-tempered.
Her love for me also
made her decide to free herself for my sake.
When she made her decision, she didn't consider my feelings.
Up until my mom left me,
it was too late to feel regretful.
If before she made this absurd decision,
I could have told her what was in my heart,
she wouldn't have done that.
Twelve years ago, our family suffered a catastrophe.
From then on, my mom developed a mental illness.
For these twelve years, we've always been cautious.
Not knowing which word or which situation would provoke her.
But the more we didn't dare say,  the tighter the knot in my mom's heart got.
Her illness became more serious.
I didn't expect that you causing a scene, would instead undo the knot in her heart.
Since I did you such a big favour,
shouldn't you declare something to me?
Declare what?
That fountain pen.
How could be you so stubborn?
Yes, you did help me but you also hurt my mom.
Hence, we are considered even. We don't owe each other anything.
In that situation just now, if I didn't do that, would she have came to her senses?
Rotten Stone Head. I did you such a big favour
and you are still unwilling to let me have the pen?
Aren't you being a little stingy?
If you find out my name, I will then reconsider if I should give it to you.
- Rotten Stone Head. - And also,
don't hassle the doctors and the nurses.
I already told them to protect the information of the patient.
If not, I will sue them.
I don't need to ask them. I already know your rotten name.
It's Rotten Stone Head.
Brother Shao Tian, why are you here?
I went to your house to look for you. They told me that you were at the hospital.
I witnessed your heroic deed in saving someone.
Our little heroine is injured. Let me bandage your wound.
It's already done.
That fast?
-Who was that man? -Are you referring to Rotten Stone Head?
He is the guy who snatched my pen.
Cai Hong, I like you.
I want to take you for my wife.
Cai Hong. You don't need to answer me right now.
You really don't need to.
You just need to know that in this world,
there is always someone waiting for you by your side.
No matter when or where, no matter the circumstances,
I will always be waiting for you.
Brother.
Here's today's newspaper. It has news about Ling Long.
Petty devil. Petty devil.
You're really narrow-minded.
I saved your mom
and you still won't let me have the pen.
I should visit his mom but I hit her yesterday.
Would she remember and hate me?
No. In order to give my Dad a surprise, I must find out his name.
Wu Long.
Kitty, I don't have time to play with you today. I have a very important task to do.
See you later. Keep the rabbit company.
Who is it?
Come in.
Aunt.
It's you.
-Don't get up. -Come here.
Lie down. Don't get up.
Come and sit.
Aunt, sorry about yesterday.
I'm here to apologise to you today.
You really don't need to apologise to me.
Yesterday, fortunately, you slapped me and made me come to my senses.
Otherwise I would still be bashing my head against a brick wall.
Actually, I have been hurting my family all these years.
Once I'm discharged, I will treat you to a meal.
I don't need the meal but if you really want to thank me,
you can tell me your son's name.
If you have any matters with him, you can wait for him to come later.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
He won't tell me when he sees me.
Why?
It's a long story.
Hello, Mr Jiang.
Mom.
You are here.
Mom, what are you doing?
I'm tired of lying down and wanted to move around.
Yu... Jiang Yu.
Is your work done at the factory?
Jiang Yu. If you are busy, you don't need to visit me.
I'm fine.
Son, don't worry. I'm really fine.
Mom, are you really okay?
What are you doing?
Mom. What is she doing here?
What are you both doing?
We didn't do anything.
I only promised her that I would call your name.
I already know your name. It's Jiang Yu.
Let's go.
I only just called his name. What's wrong?
Take this.
Where is my fountain pen?
Don't you remember what I said the other time?
I said that once you found out my name, we would discuss this again.
I didn't promise that I would give you the pen immediately.
Rotten Stone Head. A kid knows what a promise is.
You are going to be a scoundrel over a pen?
Even I feel ashamed for you.
Okay. Even if I promised to give you the fountain pen,
it was agreed on that you couldn't spend any money.
You bribed my mom. You broke the pact first.
When did I bribe your mom?
Did you make this appear from thin air?
This is to declare my sincerity. That's why I bought this for her.
I didn't have any intentions to bribe her at all.
In any case, I have only two words. Definitely not.
Then I also have two words. Shame-less.
Okay. Seeing how pitiful and miserable you are,
I will give you another chance. Don't spend a single cent or go through my mom,
just find out my favourite food.
I will consider whether to let you have the pen then.
Jiang Yu. You don't keep your promise.
I don't believe that I can't find the exact same pen.
Miss. There was really only one of that pen. I'm not lying to you.
There is only one in Huzhou. It can't be that there is also only one in this world.
Miss. If you really like that fountain pen,
I can send a telegraph to the overseas manufacturer to order another one,
but it will take a long time. It takes around twenty days.
Twenty days? My father's birthday celebration is in ten days. It will be too late for me.
Why don't you look around my shop for another gift?
I don't want to. I only want that fountain pen.
I will treat you to a meal another day. What do you like to eat?
I can treat you to anything.
Stop the rickshaw.
It's really you.
Come. What are you doing here?
Where is your fierce owner?
Did you leave home? Are you afraid of her too?
Why don't we do this? I will take you to visit my home.
Okay, let's go.
Brother. What are you doing?
A cat is here. So cute.
-I picked it up. -You picked it up?
This is not something you would usually do.
- You don't like animals, right? - Who says so?
So cute.
Don't play with her anymore. Go to the kitchen and find her something to eat and drink.
- Okay.  - Go now.
Are you hungry?
Meow, it's time to eat.
Wu Long, it's time to eat.
Wu Long?
Transfer the money back.
- What? - Transfer the money back.
You...
Are you saying to transfer the money back to the company?
Yes.
Transfer the money back to Ling Long.
No. Shao Tian, what do you mean?
At first, I didn't want to touch the money but you forced me to do it. You are reversing it now.
You are not playing with Wu Hong Da. You are playing with me.
Just do what I tell you to do.
You don't have the right to discuss terms with me.
I don't care what methods you use. Transfer the money back discreetly.
Once it's done,
I won't treat you unfairly.
Okay, I will do according to what you say
but Shao Tian, you should know that
for such a huge sum of money, it's not easy to move it.
Now that we are going to transfer it back, it will create problems.
Such a huge amount cannot appear from nowhere. We need to have some kind of contract or something else.
I think we should find a suitable time.
Take action fast
before Wu Hong Da finds out.
I will assist you when necessary.
Brother.
We received news about Ling Long.
They said that the company is in trouble.
They had problems with generating their normal turnover. People are starting to complain.
Relay this instruction down. Starting from now,
we will offer basic unit prices for all small customers
and immediate execution of the given orders.
This will help us to win over Ling Long's small customers
and completely dry off their cash flow.
Wu Hong Da will no longer be considered so almighty.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Come in.
Boss. This lady said that she's your friend.
Miss Lu Man.
I have not seen the handsome face of Boss Wu for few days now.
Miss Lu Man's visit graces our humble home. Is Master Lu in good health?
In very good health. When he knew I was paying you a visit today,
he especially instructed me to send his regards to you.
Shao Tian. Go back to work first.
Okay.
Miss Lu. This way, please.
Please sit.
Miss Lu. Why are you looking for me?
I heard that you ran into a small problem.
Other people are eyeing Ling Long with curiosity.
There is a cashflow problem in your company.
Will those problems not turn Ling Long into a chopping board?
I might have a perfect solution for your current problems, Boss Wu.
Ling Long definitely has a small problem lately
but it's still better that we solve it ourselves.
Boss Wu, the whole Huzhou city is dominated by Master Lu.
Nothing can escape my eyes.
Miss Lu. Why do you want to help me?
You are a smart man.
I'm here today
to use this cheque to buy something.
What do you want to buy?
Ling Long's trade secrets.
All of Ling Long's dye recipes are made public.
I don't have any trade secrets.
Boss Wu.
I am getting bored by this childish play.
What I want is not your trade secrets,
but the secrets of the Jiang family.
You are dreaming.
Miss Lu Man, I am grateful for your kindness,
but I really don't have any trade secrets.
I have never heard of this.
Maybe Boss Wu is just not willing to part with it yet.
So be it then.
I would also frown if you'd give away such precious things so quickly.
This is my phone number.
If you change your mind, please call me.
We can discuss the price.
Brother.
What's wrong?
These acounts are giving me a headache.
There are some which I can't balance. Please help me to take a look.
Where? Let me see.
It's here.
This money is from Henghua Cloth Square, coming through with the start-up funds.
We have agreed on two points per annum, giving them 3 years to pay us off.
Then in what tables should I put it?
I have taught you this so many times already. They go into the receivable accounts.
Here.
I don't want anything except this.
I have never seen such a rude, stingy and mannerless man like you!
You see, he has a strikingly handsome face.  He has a Grecian nose, strong brows and bright-eyed, with an uncommon demeanor.
No matter how you look at him, upon meeting you'll fall for him, he is definitely a very handsome man.
Brother, I spent my most beautiful days in the shelter provided by the Jiang family.
You didn't abandon me during my most difficult times.
In your eyes, I'm so stupid. I can't even do the accounts.
I will still allow you to teach me.
What's wrong?
Are you blaming me for not taking you to find your owner?
Okay.
I will take you to find her tomorrow. Okay?
It's just a darn fountain pen. What's so great about it?
I will knit this scarf myself.
In my Dad's eyes, it will be priceless.
Miss.
I searched everywhere since yesterday and I can't find Wu Long.
Could she really be lost?
- Cai Hong. - Brother Shao Tian.
- Wu Long is missing. I'm going to find her. - I will go with you.
Let's go then.
How are we going to find your owner?
If I can't find her, I will rear you forever. I'm not bad as your owner either.
Okay, I know. Let's just wait a while longer.
Wu Long.
Cai Hong. I already looked over there. I can't find her.
Wu Long went out with me. She must be near the hospital.
She can't really be lost.
Look at how anxious you are. Your head is full of sweat.
I will do it myself.
Let's go home.
Jiang Mansion
Stop the rickshaw.
Forget it. No need.
Wait.
Do I know you?
- What's wrong with you? - Nothing.
- Don't you want the pen? - No.
- Do you want the cat then&gt; - No!
Are you talking about Wu Long?
This is not a new game of yours, right?
It's up to you whether you believe me or not.
I believe you.
If you do this, wouldn't your boyfriend be unhappy if he sees?
First, I don't have a boyfriend.
Secondly, if I had a boyfriend, he would not like you to be so stingy.
The cat is at my home but...
Must I find out what's your favourite food or must I find out where you live?
What I wanted to say was...
I don't have time today but tomorrow is fine.
Okay, state the meeting place and time.
Then tomorrow at 3pm at Chaoyin Bay Bridge.
Okay, it's 3pm then. Don't break the appointment.
If you do, I'm going to throw your cat into the river to feed the fish.
See if you dare!
Let's go.
Why did you call me here?
Shao Tian. There is a big problem.
Wu Hong Da has been conducting investigations for the past few days.
He told everyone to move the ledger books to his office.
Think of a solution.
How can I think of a solution?
Shao Tian. All the ledger books are locked inside his safe.
He is the only one who knows the combination to the safe.
He already doesn't trust me.
I already feel like he is aware of this matter.
It's all your fault. We would have left with the money.
Who would have thought this would come back to bite us one day.
Don't expect me to fix it. You are the only one who can get those books.
Tomorrow is Wu Hong Da's 40th birthday celebration.
He will definitely have a banquet in his mansion.
There will be many people. He definitely keeps the ledger books in the company.
We will take action tomorrow.
Look.
It's really beautiful. Did you draw this?
You really drew this?
Is this me?
- Do I look young? - Younger by five years.
I really look young.
Dad is always a young hero in my eyes.
This is a drawing of the entire Wu family.
If the future, when you go out for business, you can take this along with you.
It will seem like your whole family is with you.
Great.
By the way, where is your sister?
Is she sleeping late again?
This wench.
Who drew this? I already heard.
Dad, today's your birthday. I wish you all the best, joy and peace.
Here's your present.
Sister's present is a high end product. My drawing can't be compared it.
That may not be so.
Here.
Dad, take a look.
This is...
I personally made this scarf.
For me?
- I thought it was for Shao Tian. - Yes, me too.
Let me try it. So how?
It's the first time Cai Hong knitted anything. It's really not bad.
Dad. In the future, I will knit a better one for you.
This is already good enough. I like it.
Dad. I can knit a scarf for you now. In the future, I will cook for you.
I will also help you in your business, when you are too old to do it by yourself.
And I will stick to your side through thick and thin.
Anyways, father, please look forward to your daughter taking care of you.
Okay, I will be waiting for it.
Dad, I can do it too. In the future, I will be filial to you too.
Okay, I will be waiting for the both of you.
Look at how filial they both are. The weather's hot. Take it off.
No. Cai Hong gave this to me. I must wear it every day.
I'm going to the factory for a while. There are some matters I need to settle.
Dad. Today is your birthday. Can't you give yourself a day off?
That's right. Even the workers in the factory thought that you were taking a day off for your birthday.
What's so urgent that you have to settle it yourself?
I made an appointment with a very important person.
I will be back for the birthday celebration.
Come home early then.
Dad, take care.
You both, listen to me.
Regarding this banquet...
No, move it a bit.
Mom. What's wrong?
I'm anxious. Look, the guests are already here.
Your father is still not back yet.
Dad is too much. Once he's busy with work, he forgets everything.
Why don't we do this? You take care of the guests and I will look for Dad.
Okay, go and be back soon.
Don't worry, Mom.
Be careful.
I'm really so anxious.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Who are you?
I am Yao Sheng's boss, Jiang Yu. (yao - brilliant, dazzling; sheng - rise; name of the company)
I'm Jian Wen Yuan's son.
Give it to me.
You said that you are Jiang Wen Yuan's son?
I get it now.
No wonder Yao Sheng was pressing us harder and harder to the brink.
So, you are Jiang Wen Yuan's son.
It all stems from the wrong deed I have committed.
12 years have passed without notice.
I made you wait for a long time.
Those twelve years,
I have been living in guilt and remorse.
Come off it.
When you caused my father to die at that time,
you took away Ling Long together with our family's secret recipe.
For the past 12 years you have been stepping on a river of blood and tears shed by my family.
You have been enjoying things originally belonging to our family.
Did you ever think about how we lived for the past twelve years?
You are telling me now that you have a guilty conscious?
You are here to take revenge.
This is what you should do.
Because that year,
I committed an unforgivable crime to your Jiang family.
It has been twelve years.
I knew that this day would come sooner or later.
I will pay back for everything that I have done.
Now that you are here,
I feel relieved now.
I won't ask to beg for forgiveness.
I'm begging you
to let my family off.
I'm sorry.
Do you think that being sorry
can erase 12 years of our pain and suffering?
I'm back this time,
not only to take back the company and trade secrets.
I'm also going to take back everything which belongs to the Jiang family.
I'm also going to double the pain that we have suffered
and return it back to you.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki