♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫!
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 3
Father!!
Father!
Memorial tablet of Jiang Yu's father.
Father.
I got the recipe back
and I guarantee
Ling Long will soon resurface in Huzhou.
Don't worry.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Father, who killed you?
Master, why didn't you bring me along?
You left me living alone.
What meaning do I have now in living?
-Mother! -Cai Yun!
What should we do?
Stop standing. Pack these things up.
But Madam and Miss have not said anything.
From today onwards,
everyone
has to listen to Secretary Zhou's arrangement.
Why are you still standing? Start moving!
-Lord-Mother.
Mother.
Memorial service for Cai Hong's father
What's wrong?
Are you reminding me to not bring unhappy emotions to her?
You are going to meet your owner.
Are you as happy as I am?
You only know how to eat.
Mother, why not ask Mrs Li to serve and you eat first?
Brother has not come back until now. When he comes back, I'll eat with him.
Fei'er, you eat with me. When your brother works, there is no end.
Who knows what time he'll be back?
Later, let Mrs Li heat up some rice for him.
No worries. I am not hungry yet. You eat first.
Madam, you just eat first.
Miss and Mister have a strong sibling bond.
When Mister drinks hot soup, Miss drinks hot soup too.
When Mister eats cold rice, Miss eats with him.
They go through thick and thin together.
Don't you agree?
Mrs Ling, your words are unclear.
Our family, Fei'er loves to stick with her brother since youth.
The words he says are more effective on her
than my words.
Mother!
It seems to me, that pretty soon
we'll have to call Miss "young Madam." At that time, you can just wait to hold a grandson.
Mrs. Li, what are you saying?
I'll go out first.
Huzhou Jiang Residence
Young Master.
Brother, you only came back now? You have not eaten dinner right? I will bring it to you.
There is no need. I have no appetite.
-Brother-Come in.
I cooked some porridge for you. No matter what, you should still eat something.
If this carries on, how can your body take it?
Okay, just put it here.
Here.
Oh right, I met with Mister Du who came from Hangzhou.
The Du family has a large fabric factory in Hangzhou.
They want to leave all dyeing to our Yao Sheng.
-How was your talk?-He suddenly has something going on so he didn't turn up.
-Suddenly had something going on?-Yes.
I heard that there was an accident on the way to Huzhou. It was unintentional.
I will meet him again in the next few days.
Alright. Fei Fei, have a early rest. It is late already.
Okay. Then you rest early too.
Got it.
If she suddenly has something going on,
it is not standing me up right?
Quickly say yes.
May Buddha protect us.
Are you sick? Just go have it looked at.
Right now, there is money.
You can take medicine. If you are sick, you don't have to bear with it.
May Buddha protect us.
Go tomorrow.
Huzhou NewspaperDied on his birthday: Boss of Ling Long passed away yesterday.
Wu Hong Da is dead.
We only just began a little with our revenge plan.
He then suddenly died.
Could it be that this is retribution?
Brother, then our plan to swallow Ling Long
does it still have to progress accordingly?
Did Wu Hong Da, after forcing our father to die,
let Ling Long go so easily?
Everything progresses according to the plan.
Without Wu Hong Da, this obstruction, our plan
will progress faster and more smoothly.
Return our money.
Return our money. Return it!
Everyone calm down and listen to me.
I am Wu Hong Da's eldest daughter, Wu Cai Hong. This situation is..
What is there to explain? Aren't the facts in front of us?
Yes. I've heard for a while now that Ling Long is no longer profitable!
In the past, we gave Master Wu some face
so we didn't ask for payment.
Now that the rats have left this sinking ship, what will you use to pay us back?
Yeah! Return our money!
-Return our money now!-Let me tell you guys...-Return the money to us now!
Your Ling Long still owes me half a year's payment for goods!
In order to build a new workshop, Ling Long  still owes us several thousand taels!
-Give us back our money now! Exactly!-Return our money! Return our money!
Give us back our money! It's our money!
-Don't worry, everyone, -Give us back our money!-Ling Long has money.
It's just that some of it is at the An Yuan Trading Company in Shanghai. It will mature very soon.
-When that time comes, then we can give you your money back.-Only a ghost would believe you!
I sent someone to Shanghai to inquire about this!
There never was an An Yuan Trading Company!
Ling Long's money has been scammed completely gone!
Return the money! Return the money!
-It's awful! Old Cai is gone - Ling Long's accountant Old Cai has run off!-What? Run off?
If we can't get the money back, let's check the warehouse
to see if there's anything of value in there. Take as much stuff as they have there.
-Hurry!-Don't!
-Go in and grab stuff!-Everyone!
-Everyone, listen to me!-Hurry, let's go!
Don't!
-Take as much as there is to take!-Just a minute!-Exactly!
Take it. Take all of it!
What are you guys doing?!
Quickly grab it! Quickly get out of the way!
You guys put it down, let go!
-Go over there!-Don't take anything!
-Take them all!-Please, I'm begging you!-Move!
Don't take these!
-Let go!-Get out of the way! Go!
Cai Hong,
are you alright?
Don't be afraid.
No matter what happens, I'll always be with you.
Secretary Zhou! Secretary Zhou!
Secretary Zhou, come here!
The Xiang Fa Dyeing Factory is scooping up Ling Long's workers right now.
It seems like they will give workers with experience like us
an increase of one percent in wages. Let's go together.
If you want to go, then go by yourself!
-If you kick us out...-Quickly get out!-Where will we live?
-This is going too far!-Go, drive them out!-Hurry up and get lost!
-Stop!-Aunt!-What are you guys doing?!
Shao Tian! Cai Yun. They said that Ling Long borrowed 50,000 taels.
50,000 taels?!
Yes. This sum of money was due last month.
Look clearly. It's written in black and white.
There is Boss Wu's genuine signature on here.
It is indeed Boss Wu's genuine signature. So it shouldn't be a fake.
The loan agreement said that if this amount is not paid back before the due date,
then we can take the Wu mansion as payment. We came here to collect the house.
-Everyone, can you extend the deadline a few days?-Yes, can you extend the deadline a few days?
I will definitely think of a way to raise money to the best of my abilities.
Zhou, I don't know what your background is.
Even Wu Hong Da himself couldn't solve this mess. And we're supposed to count on you?!
You're like a toad wanting to ascend into the sky. Don't kid yourself!
Enter the house! Go. Go.
You can't do this! Don't close the door!
Open the door! Hurry up and open the door!
Hurry up and open the door! This is our home!
What reason do you guys have to kick us out?!
Yes! Hurry up and open the door!
-Madam, what should we do now?!-Open the door!
How would I know what to do?!
Master,
it hasn't been long since you died,
and these people just bully us like this!
-Madam!-Mom!
Wu Cai Hong...
you have to pull yourself together.
Starting today,
-you will take father's place and support this family.-Open the door! Open the door!
Protect your sister and aunt well.
We're here. This is it.
Come in.
Mom, go. Let's go in.
Go.
Take a look. This is the house you wanted to rent.
-It's nothing. It's nothing. -Are you alright?
This has fallen into disrepair for a while. It'll be fine once I go find a carpenter to fix it.
What kind of a place is this?! How can it be so messy?!
The warehouse in our previous Wu residence
was way tidier than this place.
I'm telling you, no one has lived in this place for a long time.
Also, I'll clean the place up before you move in.
Yes. I think this place is alright actually.
Then if you feel this place isn't bad,
did you want to pay this month's rent first?
- Here. - All right.
Everyone, since you'll be busy, I won't disturb you.
Brother Shao Tian, sorry for troubling you again.
It should be me who apologizes, Cai Hong.
Right now, there really is no other way. You guys will have to live in such a simple and crude house.
At present, I can only do this much with my abilities.
However, trust me. I definitely won't let you live here for too long.
Brother Shao Tian, luckily we have you. If it weren't for you,
our family would already be living on the streets.
We won't be living on the streets. No matter how big a house is,
in the end, it's just a shelter from wind and rain.
The most important thing right now is that our whole family is together.
Cai Hong, I really won't let you live in this place
for too long. Sooner or later, there will be a day
where I can definitely let you live in a mansion again.
Brother Shao Tian, you treat my sister so well. I really admire her.
-Admire what?-Mom!
Silly girl. You need to find someone with a rich family
and take me away from this terrible place as soon as possible.
-This is what is admirable. -What are you talking about?
It's really dirty here.
Shouldn't it be cleaned?
-I'll do it.-I'll go with you.
I'll come too.
What do you mean you're going? You'll get yourself dirty.
Honestly...
Brother Shao Tian. It was really troublesome for you today.
Cai Hong, don't always view me as an outsider.
The house was only a small matter.
As for Ling Long, what are your plans?
I just hate myself for
not learning about business affairs from my dad when he was alive.
Otherwise it wouldn't be like now, with no ideas at all.
All of the inventory and raw materials in the warehouse
have been looted by the creditors.
With Ling Long's situation right now, I reckon there won't be any banks
that would be willing to lend us money. But we still have Ling Long's factory.
The workers are still here,
and we still have Ling Long's sign.
So, what does Brother Shao Tian mean?
Since there is no way we can start operations to manufacture and we also owe so much debt,
how about, selling Ling Long first?
After we pay off the debts, we can discuss other matters at a later time.
No.
Ling Long was dad's lifetime of effort.
How could I sell it off?
Cai Hong, I know that this kind of decision
is really hard for you.
But the circumstances right now are difficult no matter how you look at it.
You can't reason with the market, let alone appeal to its emotions.
Yao Sheng could be planning a hostile takeover right now.
They are most likely already collaborating with the creditors.
One side is demanding debt payment while the other is forcing prices to lower.
But, Ling Long was dad's life and blood.
But if we continue to hold it off like this,
the longer we delay the more passive we'll appear.
If we act now,
we might be able to fetch a good price.
Otherwise, I'm afraid we won't even get the chance to break even.
Perhaps that's exactly what Yao Sheng wants.
I never thought thatLing Long would become forfeit in my hands.
Cai Hong, where there's still life
there's always hope.
Then we'll count on you, Brother Shao Tian.
I'll go take care of some other arrangements first. You take care of yourself.
That's right, Miss Wu has decided to sell Ling Long.
If you'd like to make an offer, you can come over tomorrow and we'll discuss it in person.
That's right. Yes, yes.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Daddy! Hug!
Cai Hong, come here, Daddy will hold you.
Cai Hong, what Dad cares most about right now
isn't titles or money,
it's you.
Everything your dad has done has been for you
and for this family.
Don't worry, I'll definitely live to 100 years
to see you get married, see you have children,
-and to see you live a stable and secure life.-Aiya, I know!
You always want me to get married. Who would I marry?
Dad!
Wei! That day, why did you stand me up?
Something came up. It wasn't on purpose.
"Something came up?" To make up for standing me up,
I threw your cat in the river to feed the fish.
You, to Wu Long-
I, I was just teasing you...
She's fine. Your cat is at my place, eating and drinking so well she's nearly as fat as a pig.
-I was just joking...-I don't like this joke!
Let's decide on a new time and place.
This time, I'll definitely go pick up Wu Long.
Your cat's name is Wu Long?
Then, what's yours? Every time I see you,
I can't just call you “Hey," right?
Contact me soon. I don't wish for your cat to grow too fat to walk,
and for you to resent me for that. I'll wait.
Who was that?
The person who picked up Wu Long.If there are no issues, I'll return first, Brother Shao Tian.
Sure. I won't send you off today.I still have to contact some
parties who might be willing to buy Ling Long. You can go first.
Miss Wu, hello. Our household's young lady has something to discuss with you.
Your household's young lady？
Miss Wu, hello. I am Lu Man.
Miss Lu, how did you know my family name is Wu?
The current head of Ling Long dying factory.Miss Wu Cai Hong,
I'm a loyal customer of your Ling Long.
I hear you now have plans to sell Ling Long,
so I specially came over to discuss it with you.
But I just took over the business.
There are still lots of things I don't understand. It's better that you talk to Secretary Zhou.
But he is an outsider.
How could he become the head of the Wu family?
To add further, there are certain things
that only Secretary Zhou would know.
For example, your asking price.
In addition to your factory, equipment and staff,
is there something like a secret formula?
I know that you are in need of money now. Don't worry.
I will definitely give you a good price.
What's wrong? You are not happy with my terms?
It's not that. It's just that I don't know much about it.
I don't know anything about a secret formula.
It's better that you talk to Secretary Zhou.
Since this is the case,
okay then. Sorry to impose on you.
The shareholders are already here.
A businessman who wants to buy Ling Long is also here.
Cai Hong, don't worry.
Don't be nervous. What you should do is take a deep breath.
Do not add your own distress to this trying time.
Don't worry.
Leave everything to me.
Look. How could they sell it?
-How did it come to this?  -Wouldn't we be losing money?  -Precisely.
How much is it going to cost?
How much could they get from the sale?
I never imagined that Ling Long would be in this state today.
Who doesn't know about this?
- Everyone is here. - Cai Hong is here.
So far only one company, Yao Sheng, is here.
Let's talk while we wait.
Dear Sir, Miss Wu is here.
Can we start now?
It's you.
You are Wu Hong Da's daughter?
You are Yao Sheng's boss?
You both know each other?
It can be considered so.
Let's start now. We invited the shareholders here today
and also those who are interested in buying the company.
We are here to discuss the matter about Ling Long.
The sale agreement that I've drafted, I believe this gentleman has already seen it.
I wonder what is your opinion.
My offer, is five percent of your selling price.
Five percent? Are you kidding?
This is outrageous!
At this price, we'll be getting no return on our money.
- This is our blood, sweat and tears... - Everyone, stay calm.
This gentleman...  After all, our Ling Long is a time-honored brand.
Even though we have run into some problems
Ling Long's buildings, machines
and the experienced workers. These are of valued costs.
So our asking price is definitely reasonable.
If it's as you say, then you don't need to sell Ling Long.
You are taking advantage of us.
Us Yao Sheng isn't a living Buddha.  (meaning a compassionate person)
We are also businessmen.
You are really looters.
Hence, Miss Wu,
you also acknowledge that your house is on fire?- You!
Other than our offer, no one else would want to state the price.
I should say this.
No one would dare to make an offer.
If you don't believe me, you can ask around.
I stated it very clearly. Today's five percent
will be four percent tomorrow and three percent the day after.
Starting from now, it will be less one percent every day.
Everyone, make your decision.
What should we do?
Make it five percent then.
Compared to being bankrupt, I support the sale.
He is the only one offering us silver anyway. (silver was a common currency in this period).
We can always build another factory in the future. Let's sell it. - I disagree.
You don't agree? Even if you don't, we should sell it.
If you don't sell it, we will be paupers.
That's right. Even if we total up all our shares, it's still not enough.
Don't talk to her anymore. What does she know?
Everyone, don't be anxious first.
The Wu family is still the biggest shareholder of Ling Long.
Let's listen to Miss Wu's views.
Give her some time to consider.
What do you think?
Let's just sell it.
What should we do if we don't sell it? This is happening too fast.
How much is it worth?
I shouldn't have picked you up and let stay here.
- Hello. -Jiang Yu.
Can you meet me in half an hour at Chaoyin River's bridge?
Return Wu Long to me.
You don't need to wait anymore.
I already beat your cat to death.
It's true this time.
You bastard! Return Wu Long to me.
Monster.
Cai Hong.
The autopsy report is out.
Dad.
I really never imagined that
she was Wu Hong Da's daughter.
Based on the autopsy report,
it still can't be confirmed if your father killed himself or was murdered.
But there is a great suspicion that he has been murdered.
Wu Hong Da received a fatal wound to the head. But the autopsy showed
that there was also another, not too serious wound on his shoulder.
He also had bruises.
They were obviously caused during a struggle.
Judging from the sight of the wounds,
they were caused by some sharp metal object.
Accordingly to the Ling Long's porter testimony
Yao Sheng's boss, Jiang Yu,
came to visit Ling Long on that very day.
Cai Hong. Could you tell us
what could your father and Yao Sheng's boss be talking about?
Jiang Yu has been planning a hostile take over of the company.
It's possible that he's the killer of my father.
Where is it?
Jiang Yu. You killed my father. You did it.
- Calm down, Cai Hong. - You executed my father to take over Ling Long!
You didn't even hesitate, right?!
Miss. What you are doing now to Mr Jiang Yu,
you need the law to be responsible for this.
Sorry, Mr Jiang. This way, please.
That's right. On the day Wu Hong Da died,
I definitely went to see him at Ling Long but I didn't kill him.
First, when I left Ling Long,
Wu Hong Da personally escorted me to the main entrance.
At that time, Wu Hong Da was still alive.
If the door keeper is not blind, he should have seen everything.
Well, we still need the door keeper to verify this.
Also, when I left Ling Long that day, it was noon.
After that I had lunch with Director Lee.
Shouldn't you call him
and investigate this?
Director Lee, my name is Chen Shijie. It is like this.
I'm investigating Wu Hong Da's case now.
There is a current suspect who said that he was not at the crime scene
because at noon that day, you were having lunch with him.
I'm calling you to confirm this.
Yes. You definitely were having lunch with him?
You didn't find anything out of the ordinary?
Okay, sorry to disturb you.
That's it. Thank you.
Jiang Yu has an alibi that he was not at the crime scene.
Furthermore, his witness is my superior.
Director Lee.
Jiang Yu's alibi sounds true on the surface.
So in theory he can be ruled out as the murder's suspect.
We will still investigate the case. Go back first and wait for my news.
Bastard. Just because you are rich, you think you
are unpunishable, right? - Cai Hong!
Before accusing me of anything,
please review the evidence first.
If not, I will let my lawyer contact you.
Cai Hong! Dad's imploring you.
Take revenge for me. You must take revenge for your father.
Dad.
I can't sit here and do nothing.
I must take revenge for Dad.
I must find the evidence.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I will accept the five percent.
I'm really very sorry.
That was the price before I was investigated by the police.
I have changed my mind now.
My asking price now is
two percent.
How can you loot us in such way?
One and a half percent.
Did you ever think about
how the major shareholders of Ling Long will survive?
One percent.
It's a deal.
Let's have a good collaboration.
But I have a condition.
I want to work at Ling Long.
I hope you
will give me a fair opportunity to earn the money.
In this industry, there is only a winner or loser. There is no fairness.
I don't want to see you again.
You better stay far away from me. If not,
you will regret it.
If you really want to do this,
then, I will
I will tell everyone how you lowered the price for Ling Long
and also before my father's death on that day,
you went to Ling Long to find him regarding this issue.
I will go to all the newspapers.
You forgot that I wasn't at the scene.
The police need evidence but what the reporters
need are stories.
If I leak out the details about you and Ling Long,
I wonder what the reporters will write.
Since you want to remain at Ling Long so much,
I will fulfill your wish.
You better not regret this.
- Leave the side open. - All right.
- Keep it steady. - Be careful.
- Can you do it?  - Place it over there.
Come.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear ♫
♫ when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time ♫
♫ so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, ♫
♫ but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki