♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 4
May we have good cooperation.
I have a request.
I want to work at Ling Long.
Since you want to stay in Ling Long so much,
I will fulfill your wish.
You better not regret it.
Is this alright?
Yes. Pack it up
and tidy it up.
-Towards this side. -Okay
Hold it tightly. Be careful.
-It is done. -Where do I put this?
You put this here.
This is crooked. Towards this side more.
Coming. Coming!
Is it alright?
-Alright. -Wipe this clean.
Today, the new boss is coming.
-Yes. I even heard that the new boss is handsome-Really?
Come, help us to put them in.
Rinse them well, all right?
Miss Wu.
Master.
Take care.
Boss Jiang.
Boss is here.
- It's the new boss. - Hello, Boss.
It has been hard on everyone. Go back to work.
Okay, let's go.
Quick.
Over here.
Come in.
Boss Jiang.
This dress suits you very well.
As a worker, you should look like one.
I'm a secretary,
not a worker.
Aren't you?
Did you memorise the secretary's codes that I wanted you to do?
I have memorised them.
Recite them to me.
First.
The boss will only give the instructions once. His secretary needs to remember everything.
Second.
During working hours the secretary is not allowed to slack off.
Third.
The secretary must be on twenty four hour call
and is not allowed any delays in the tasks given her.
Fourth
Boss orders are to be executed immediately, regardless whether they are right or wrong.
Fifth.
Boss needs should be met with effort and fulfilled unconditionally.
They cannot be refused.
Sixth.
If the secretary neglects any of the above rules, boss has the right to fire her.
Not bad. These rules,
not only must you remember them clearly,
even when you are asleep or dreaming, you must remember them.
If you don't follow them,
I will have you disappear from my sight immediately.
The second condition,
as a Secretary you have to stay close to me.
Never a step away.
Everyone should already know that
Ling Long has gone through an exquisite merger.
I'm your new boss.
New boss?
Miss.
This...
Miss. This...
It's cold.
Since everyone is already part of the staff,
I hope that everyone will be loyal to me.
Staff is the most important.
Some people will have no doubts while others will doubt me.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Are you trying to scald me to death?
What is he doing?
He's being too extreme by doing this.
Miss. This...
Does anyone have any objections?
If you do,
you can leave anytime. Don't force yourself.
I can give you two month's salary
as severance pay.
This...
It's still not hot enough.
Jiang Yu.
What are you trying to do?
It's either too hot or too cold? You have no intention of drinking it at all.
This...
I don't want to drink it. So what?
You are not happy?
If you are not happy, you can go home.
Jiang Yu. You are being too extreme.
If you are not happy either, you also can scram and go home with her.
- Do you think I wouldn't dare to? - Secretary Zhou, forget it.
Brother Shao Tian, don't be like this.
I hope we can cooperate in the future.
If the factory produces good results,
I will not treat you badly.
Yes.
Okay, go back to work. End of meeting.
Go! Let's go!
Brother,
it looks like you won't have peace if Zhou Shao Tian is working in Ling Long.
Why don't you tell him to leave?
He is a long time staff.
I hope that with him around, he will stabilise the emotions of the rest of the staff.
But don't worry.
He will leave anyways.
Cai Hong.
Let's leave Ling Long together.
I know you would prefer to stay in your home.
No, I can't go.
If I leave now, it will affect my plan regarding Jiang Yu.
Maybe, the death of my father...
- I will never discuss the truth about my father's death. - But if you continue to stay here,
you might not find evidence
and waste your time.
I am fine with it.
Shao Tian, you don't need to worry about me.
As long as there is a glimmer of hope, I won't give up.
Cai Hong, I am sorry.
How can I blame you?
I chose it in this way.
Thus, no matter how Jiang Yu treats me,
I am fine with it.
Cai Hong.
As long as you stay in Ling Long,
I will stay with you and protect you.
I think the secretary's post
is still not suitable for Miss Wu.
Why doesn't Miss Wu
decide herself to stay or leave.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I want to go to the bathroom.
I know.
The second condition of being your secretary
during working hours I must
never be a step away.
Take a look if you want to. Don't be shy.
Boss Wang from Suzhou is here.
For this afternoon, I reserved a private room, to give you privacy.
Check the arrangements. I will go over in a while.
Alright.
Wu Cai Hong.
What are you doing here?
Who told you that you could enter  my brother's office without permission?
I am sorry, I will put the files in order as soon as possible.
There is no need to.
You are just a worker. I am the boss now.
Brother,
Cai Hong must have a problem adjusting.
Everything she had is gone.
Boss Jiang.
Wu Cai Hong.
My shoes are dirty. Clean them for me.
If you don't want to do it, you can leave.
- Look. Isn't that Miss Wu? - Yes, it's really her.
She was always so dignified. Now she is pitiful.
That's right. She's really pitiful.
Okay, don't say anymore.
What are you doing? Boss Jiang.
If your shoes are dirty, I will clean them for you.
Between the both of you, who exactly is my secretary?
Look. She's really cleaning his shoes.
The cloth is already dirty. Shouldn't you change it?
Jiang Yu.
Shao Tian.
I am fine.
I am okay.
There is no cloth?
You can use your own hand.
She is using her hands?
That's it.
What are you looking at? Go back to work.
Go back to work.
Come.
I am okay.
Take care of this. Add the water.
I never said your position was allowed (to ride here.).
If in fifteen minutes
you are not in the Zuixian building,
you don't need to come to work tomorrow.
Let's go!
Cai Hong,
Cai Hong. Cai Hong.
Shao Tian.
Let's go.
Sounds interesting.
Let's go!
Watch out. Why are you riding a bicycle here?
Move aside.
Seriously. There are so many people here. Why is he riding his bicycle here?
Be careful.
Move aside.
Boss Wang.
Boss Wang, the price which we quoted you is already the lowest price Ling Long can offer.
What concerns do you have?
I chose Ling Long
because it lays in the old city of Huzhou
and because I could always rely on the quality.
I enjoyed collaborating with Ling Long in the past.
But, I heard that the boss of Ling Long has changed.
I do not know the new boss.
I wonder if the current Ling Long is still the same as in the past.
Boss Wang. I have acquired Ling Long.
It will be just as remarkable as in the past.
I'm sure that you
won't find a company better than ours.
Even one with less cost.
If there are any problems,
I will give you the entire goods for free.
What are you doing?
Be careful of the cage, Cai Wong.
Cai Hong, sit on tight.
Boss Jiang, you are really too young and too arrogant in your pressing.
It's just that the goods I wanted
were personally ordered by the northeast marshall, Zhang Lin Zhang.
If anything happens,
you will lose your head. (be in trouble)
Who told you to come in?
Leave.
Cai Hong?
Uncle Wang.
I haven't seen you for a few years. We finally meet here.
Come, sit down and dine with us.
Sit.
You and Boss Jiang...
She is my secretary now.
I am just learning about everthing
and gaining some experience.
By the way, Uncle Wang,
are you here in Huzhou to order some goods from Ling Long?
We haven't finished the negotiation yet.
It was Marshall Lin Zhang who ordered the goods,
so I need to tread cautiously.
There is a variety of fabrics,
you should get it from Ling Long.
Why do you say this?
From what I know,
there are a number of fabrics, of good quality to choose from.
But Ling Long has changed its owner now.
Even though Ling Long has changed its owner
the skills and workers are still the same.
We are just as good as in the past.
Furthermore, if Boss Jiang had no skills,
how could he sit in the most exquisite position in Ling Ling?
Based on what Cai Hong said,
I think that I don't have to worry anymore.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Boss Wang.
Let's have a good collaboration.
Okay, I will be a bit long winded. (repetitive)
As Master Wang,
we put importance on quality goods.
Between time and quality, there is no room for mistakes.
- Don't worry. - Don't worry.
Boss Wang, don't worry.
I promise this afternoon, we will prepare the dye without delay.
Where is your rickshaw? I will escort you there.
It's over there.
Take care, Uncle Wang.
You can be considered as being a bit useful.
That is
because I'm Wu Hong Da's daughter.
No one should look down on me.
It's very easy for you to fall to your death,
Wu Hong Da's daughter.
Don't forget that you still need to work.
Brother. This woman, Wu Cai Hong, is not that simple as you think.
Think about it. She's Wu Hong Da's daughter.
She's scheming to get close to you.
When you were not in, she overturned your office.
She even had the capability to secure a big order.
If you keep her with you, it's like rearing a tigress.
I know.
You knew and you still...
Brother.
Cai Hong. How were the negotiations today?
It was successful. You know Uncle Wang too.
He was my father's friend. It was fortunate that he put in a few good words about us.
The way he treated you, do you still need to help him make profits?
I'm not helping him.
I'm doing this to help Ling Long.
My father was a good man.
I don't want the business to be ruined.
I also don't want the workers to lose their jobs.
Furthermore, if I'm of use,
Jiang Yu won't be in such a hurry to kick me out.
If I'm with him, I will be able to find evidence.
How do you plan
to investigate Jiang Yu's crime?
I checked Ling Long's account records
and pieced together that large sums of money are missing.
In any case, Old Cai has already run away.
I think there is something odd about it.
But Old Cai's whereabouts are unknown.
It won't be that easy to find him.
Why don't we do this?
Let's find out why Jiang Yu wanted to kill your father.
Once we find out the reason, we will know where to get the evidence.
What do you think?
Perhaps, this is not a bad method.
Let's go.
Brother, something bad has happened.
The dye in the workshop is contaminated.
It's Marshall Zhang's batch order.
All dyes are scrapped.
Look. How could this happen?
Why is it like this?
I don't know. Come and take a look.
What should we do?
Boss Jiang, look.
How could this happen?
We don't know how to revert it back.
The dye was good before we went out to smoke.
When we came back, the dye...
became like this.
Is there any way to salvage this?
-We are missing key ingredients.-It takes a lot of preparation.
These dyes need to be exquisite so the ingredients are very precious.
Madder, bluegrass and saffron are commonly used here.
We also need a lot of fresh roses.
Even if we order the raw materials right now
it will take at least ten days. I'm afraid it will affect the delivery of our goods.
How could this happen?
Check if there are any big rose gardens around here.
And also,
in the end, we will find who deliberately contaminated the dye.
Yes, who could do such a thing.
We can't make anything from this.
How could this happen?
Looks like you are bored.
You don't have anything to do but clean my office.
There is not a speck of dust around.
These days a lot of dust is collecting.
Dye material was intentionally contaminated.
There must be a staff member who intentionally sabotaged it.
What makes you so sure that it was done by a human?
Furthermore, it was done by a staff member at the factory?
It can't be because it has been very windy for the past two days that
dust contaminated the dye.
The Ling Long workshop...
only our workers can get in.
Thus, there is definitely something fishy about this.
But it's very strange.
It doesn't benefit them to do something like this.
What do they gain to accomplish?
By the way,
you know the staff better than me. Investigate this for me before you report for work tomorrow morning.
If you can't find out anything, you can leave immediately tomorrow.
Brother, I already asked around.
Only along the river of Huzhou is where the roses grows,
but no matter what, this Old Madam refuses to sell them.
With good business, secrets are kept but
as long as the price is right, the negotiation can be done.
Leave now.
Aunt. We are tripling our price offer.
- Please reconsider. - No, the price is non-negotiable.
Why aren't you listening to me? Leave now.
- Mrs Jiang. - Aunt.
Sell the flowers to us. It will be of benefit for you.
This will not only be beneficial to us. Let's be honest.
Your flowers are growing in the wild. There is no one to appreciate them, right?
What? Are you saying that no one appreciates my flowers?
Let me tell you. Even if no one appreciates my flowers, I won't sell them to you.
Just because you have an urgent need, you don't need to rip the head off an old woman.
- What do you mean by that? Leave now. - Sorry.
- It's only just the problem with the price. - You!
I'm not going to sell to you. Get lost.
- Aunt...  - Get lost.
Okay, Madam. Don't be rash.
We will leave.
Seriously.
Fighting over flowers!
What are you thinking of?
I'm really furious.
Let's go back first.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Brother. What should we do now?
Looks like we really need to give up on this woman and find another solution.
Of course, we must not give up.
Fei Fei. Get someone to run checks on her.
Everyone has their weaknesses.
She is no exception.
I'm afraid that she really has no weaknesses.
I already asked her neighbours.
Her flowers are in memory of her deceased daughter.
All she has left of her daughter are these flowers.
Furthermore, she doesn't have any needs. If we want to talk terms with her,
I'm afraid it will be impossible.
Wu Cai Hong.
Did you find out who sabotaged the dye?
Who did it?
I don't know.
I couldn't find out anything.
You can get lost then.
I still have something to say.
Speak.
Everyone here are long time staff members of Ling Long.
Many people work hard.
They have been with Ling Long all this while
and have been with my father since it was established.
I'm really very grateful to everyone
for your love for my father and Ling Long.
I am also grateful to everyone for your years of loyalty.
Today, Ling Long,
even though it's now under Jiang,
but no matter how they changed the name,
it's still Ling Long.
It belongs to everyone of you.
Yes, that's right.
We are all really close.
We received an order from Mister Chang,
because of our high quality.
Without a doubt, because of our years of expertise.
But with some careless words
this all can be destroyed.
In order for it not to be ready on time,
someone deliberately contaminated the dye in the workshop.
Who would do such a thing?
Perhaps, this person wants to take revenge for my father.
In doing so, they didn't think things through.
By this all workers will be affected.
Ling Long may go bankrupt.
You will be unemployed.
How many families will lack food and clothing then?
Miss is right. It always has been.
They have wives and children too.
What should we do?
Frankly,
it doesn't matter if I leave Ling Long.
It's just that I want to tell everyone that
Ling Long belongs to each and every one of you.
You must do a good job.
Don't do any foolish things again.
That's right.
Who did this? Why doesn't he stand up for this?
- He's dragging us down. - He's harming all of us.
Who did it?
Miss, don't leave.
I did it. Don't kick Miss Wu out.
He did it.
Miss, I'm sorry.
The hostile takeover
and boss's death
must have something to do with him.
I wanted to take revenge for Old Master.
Hence, that's why...
Okay.
Wu Cai Hong can stay but Zhang Fu needs to leave.
Furthermore, he must compensate for the loss of the dyes.
How could you do that? You clearly know that
Uncle Fu will never be able to get hold of such a large sum of money.
Cut the crap. End of meeting. Go back to work.
Let's go.
Uncle Fu.
Jiang Yu.
Do you know that his family depends on him?
His child has a disability.
In that case he should have not been so impulsive and reckless.
Jiang Yu.
I'm begging you.
Spare him.
Let him off.
You can't even protect your own position.
What right do you have to beg on his behalf?
Yes.
I don't have the right.
I can only beg you.
If you don't agree to let Uncle Fu off,
I will kneel down here.
Do whatever you want.
Get up, Cai Hong.
- Get up. - Don't persuade me, Shao Tian.
If Jiang Yu doesn't accept this,
I will keep kneeling here.
Boss Jiang. I hope that you will accede to her request,
or I will leave Ling Long
and take all the workers along with me.
Are you threatening me?
No matter what you think,
I hope that you will agree to our term.
Do you think that the workers are loyal and will leave with you?
They are staying because of Ling Ling's reputation and their salaries.
If you want to leave, it's up to you
but I want to see
how many workers at Ling Long will leave with you.
Jiang Yu.
You will regret this.
Miss has been kneeling for a long time.
Yes. How could she endure this?
- It has been too long. - That's right.
The colour of her face has changed.
Cai Hong, get up.
Get up.
That rascal, Jiang Yu, will never agree to your term.
Can't you tell that his heart is made of steel and stone?
Don't be naive anymore. Get up now.
Cai Hong.
Take her away.
Do not go against what I say again.
Cai Hong. You are awake.
Brother Shao Tian.
You fainted from heat stroke. Your body is still weak.
You must rest today.
Sorry, I gave you troubles again.
Don't say that.
Cai Hong, leave Ling Long.
I will help you to find the evidence of your father's killer.
I promised my father that I will find his killer.
Jiang You wanted to get rid of me due to the recent problems.
I definitely won't back down.
But, Brother Shao Tian,
you shouldn't remain at Ling Long.
Jiang Yu doesn't trust you anymore.
It is impossible for you to do this task.
Take your talents to another place.
You can do well.
Cai Hong. You are right
But I want to tell you this.
Regardless if whether you are a heiress or a poor man's daughter,
I will always be with you.
My heart will always be with you.
Thus, I will only leave if you leave.
If you stay, I will stay too.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki