♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 6
Two little tigers. Two little tigers.
Ran so fast. Ran so fast.
One doesn't have a mouth. One doesn't have ears.
It's really strange.
Two little tigers. Two little tigers.
Ran so fast. Ran so fast.
One doesn't have a mouth. One doesn't have ears.
It's really strange.
Brother Shao Tian. Save me.
Brother Shao Tian. I'm scared.
Two little tigers. Two little tigers.
Ran so fast. Ran so fast.
One doesn't have a mouth. One doesn't have ears.
It's really strange.
Why did you do that to me?
You are asking me why?
What do you think this place is?
Is this the evidence that I killed your father?
You really hoped that I'm the killer of your father?
Jiang Yu. What are you doing?
Ask her. It's late. Ask her
why she is here.
Yes.  This doesn't concern you.
It's my fault.
You can't treat her like this.
Don't let me see you bully her again in the future.
If she dares to play tricks,
I will bully her every time I see her.
If you have the guts, take her away from here.
Brother Shao Tian.
I guarantee that
this mistake
will never happen again.
I heard it.
What were you doing most of the night?
Don't talk about this anymore. I wanted to find the evidence.
In the end, I was played by Jiang Yu.
Cai Hong. In the future, don't do something like this alone again.
You must tell me in advance.
I didn't want you to worry about me.
If you hide this from me, I will be even more worried.
Okay then.
I will confess to you. The next step in my plan
is to find Ling Long's ledger books.
When your father passed away, the police already checked all the documents.
Everything was disclosed.
A few days ago, the police delivered the documents here.
But now Jiang Yu has them locked up.
Then, do you know where he kept the ledgers?
I don't know but I think
since the police has already investigated,
there should be no problems with the ledgers.
Even so, I still want to take a look at them
and see where the problem lies.
Fei Fei. The Ling Long's ledgers that the police delivered here,
where did you put them?
I let the workers move them to the storage room and lock them up.
Someone must have manipulated the Ling Long's ledgers.
The police couldn't detect anything.
The world is not a perfect place.
Even if the person who manipulated the accounts did a clean job.
In this ledger,
it certainly contains hidden clues.
I don't believe that Old Cai
would dare to touch Wu Hong Da's money on his own.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
You can't leave.
You are burning the ledger?
I didn't burn it.
Someone already burnt it before I came.
You are still trying to deny it? I personally witnessed it.
What did you see? Whether you believe it or not, I didn't do this.
Then why are you in the storage room so late?
If there isn't anything to hide in here
then why do have to burn it?
Have nothing to say anymore, right?
There are only four words to describe this.
Have a guilty conscious.
Okay.
Even if I burned these books, you can't find any proof.
I will find out the truth and get revenge for my father.
Cai Hong.
Where are you going?
Cai Hong, didn't you promise me last night
to not do things alone?
I just want to...
look at Ling Long's old ledgers.
I found it, but I was one step late.
Jiang Yu burned it. He thinks by doing this there would be no evidence.
But he's wrong. The ledgers are burned...
Is he still around?
Are you talking about Old Cai? The police has been looking for him.
I have commissioned a friend to find him.
I'm guessing, he already ran away.
He did business with the temple monks.
I remember Old Cai never missed work and worked many years.
Many workers should know him well.
Ask around about his address.
His hometown may hold more clues.
Cai Hong. I think that Jiang Yu burnt the ledger before you went there.
He is well aware of your actions and
he is watching your every move. He will make things difficult.
He won't do that. I know about the dangers you are talking about
but this is the only way I can investigate my father's death.
I won't give up.
Why are you suddenly taking time off?
Because I'm going to the countryside. My cousin...
She suddenly fell sick. Hence...
Enough.
I don't have the skills to know if you are lying or not.
Just go if you want to.
I will be back soon. Thank you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Bookkeeper Cai lived in Xiaoshan.
I went to his home a few years ago.
Go with me on the trip.
Let's go now.
I'm afraid that I can't go today.
I'm taking my mom to the hospital. She is sick.
Why don't we go tomorrow?
Yes. It's important to take care of your mother.
Brother Shao Tian, go back to work first.
Okay then. I will take my mom to the hospital first.
Let's go tomorrow.
Who is there? Coming.
Brother. What brings here here? Today must be a good day.
Come inside and take a seat.
I'm here to see you regarding an urgent matter. I would like to seek your help.
Why are you asking me this? Your business is my business.
Tell me what it is.
Brother.
Brother. Where are you going?
I'm going to settle some stuff.
- I will go with you then. - No need.
I will be back soon. Don't worry.
Take good care of the factory.
Brother!
Where is he going?
Sir. I would like to ask you a question.
How far is Xiaoshan and what is the cost?
It's not near. It's a silver dollar.
A silver dollar? But I left home in a hurry and didn't bring that much money with me.
Could you charge half the price?
Leave then. Don't hamper my business.
Sir. I would like to inquire.
You don't have a silver dollar, right? I'm not going.
I will take you there for half the asking price.
You are going to take her there for half the asking price?
-I need to go to Xiaoshan. -I'll go anywhere.
Rascal. What are you trying to do?
What do you mean? It's broad daylight and you don't want to do any business?
Are you serious? How do you run a serious business?
Half of the asking price is not even enough for a meal.
How can you even go out?
Mind your business. I'm happy to take her there.
It's none of your business.
Miss. Get in.
Cheap. Is his child sick?
Regardless, even if she is pretty...
Chances are he doesn't know where to turn.
Is this your first time doing this?
Who says so? I have been doing this for ten years.
Why can't you turn the horse around then?
I do know how to turn a horse. I'll try harder.
Giddy up. See? Aren't we moving?
Be careful.
Are you sure this is the way there?
Miss.
I may not be good at this but I know the way.
Let's just say, I don't need road signs.
How do I feel that we are going the wrong way?
Why don't you find someone to ask for directions?
Ask someone? Who should we ask?
How do I feel that we getting further?
We are not. We will get there soon.
But...
This wench. She clearly took the wrong road.
Even when taking the wrong path, she doesn't look back.
How long will it take for us to reach Old Cai's home?
We will be there soon. It's just ahead.
Ahead? This doesn't seem to be the way to Old Cai's home.
Who says so? Miss, look.
Look we need to just go a little south.
I'm certain it is there.
Isn't the Cai family's home just ahead?
There are not mountains in Xiaoshan.
Are you even a real driver?
It can't be.
It should be just ahead.
You are a dead man!
- Why are you hitting me? - I'm going to beat you to death.
- Stop hitting. - You rotten egg.
Stop hitting me. I'm not...
Liar! Bad guy!
Buddy. Did you just transport a young woman
to the Cai family's home?
- Where is she? - How would I know?
She said I wasn't a real driver.
She even hit me. That wench.
The other drivers said I was crazy going to the countryside...
Where did she go then?
I don't know.
It seems to be over there.
Over there?
Thanks.
You... what are you doing here?
Does your cousin live here?
Is there a problem with your brain?
You clearly took the wrong road and you are still walking ahead.
Also you hired a driver that took you to a remote place.
Aren't you afraid that someone will sell you?
You came a long distance
just to scold me, right?
I have only one reason to scold you. It's because you are stupid.
You are the stupid one instead.
Where are you going?
Mind your own business.
There are many wolves nearby.
Can't you walk slower?
Miss. Based on your progress,
we will first be home next year.
If you haven't taken the wrong road, I would be home earlier.
Are you going to leave or not?
I'm not leaving.
Can't you see that I'm injured?
Come.
I don't need you to carry me. Put me down.
Put me down.
You are extremely noisy.
I don't need you to carry me.
Put me down.
Okay, sit here.
I'm going to find food. I will be back soon.
Be careful.
If your boyfriend knows that you are alone with me
and spent the night in this forest. What would he think?
I don't have a boyfriend.
Don't go too far.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Be careful.
This fruit has a sour taste.
They are all for you.
I don't feel like eating.
The fourth code of a secretary.
You can't defy the order from your boss.
Whether right or wrong, you must follow and not hesitate.
Finish them.
- Brother. - Where is Cai Hong?
Didn't I tell you to take her for a ride and then send her back?
I did according to your instruction. I was about
to take her home but talking about this,
I tried to go back but she wouldn't let me say a word.
- She ran off. - Ran off?
A rascal on a horseback came after her later.
How does that rascal looks like?
One look and one could tell that he's a rich man.
I wanted to wait for them to come back but I fell asleep.
- Where did they head off? - Over there.
- Brother, I will go with you. - No need. Stay here and sleep.
- Young Master! - Brother!
Young Master!
- Brother. - Young Master!
Zhou Shao Tian. Stop there.
Where is Wu Cai Hong?
I'm looking for her too.
Our family's coachman has a horse to find them.
Tell me now. Where did they go?
I'm looking for her too.
I'm warning you. If anything were to happen to my brother,
I will never let Wu Cai Hong off.
If anything were to happen to Cai Hong,
do you think I would let Jiang Yu off?
Cai Hong will be lucky to still be alive.
You better stay far away from her.
Miss, there's somebody here.
Young Master!
Wake up.
Young Master.
- We finally found you.  - Brother, are you okay?
- I'm fine.  - Young Master, young master.
- Cai Hong.  - We found them, that's great.
This shirt...
It got dirty, wash it before you return it.
Your leg is injured, I'll carry you.
I'm fine, it's okay.
Are you really okay?
Follow them. Don't let them find out.
Let's go.
I don't think this is the right way.
But it shouldn't be that far from the Cai family's home.
Why don't we check ahead?
Cai Hong, you didn't get to rest last night
and you got injured. How about we go back first?
Let's go the Cai family's home another day.
My leg is fine.
I think I can still go on.
I don't want to wait anymore. I would like to find Old Cai as soon as possible.
That way we'll find out the truth.
Cai Hong, last night...
why were you with Jiang Yu?
I don't know why he appeared either.
Brother.
I looked for you all night long.
Don't you think you should let me know what happened?
I'm tired, let's talk next time.
With everything else, there has always been a reason behind it,
but this time...
Do you know why Wu Cai Hong
was out in the wilderness?
She went to look for Lao Cai.
If I didn't guess wrongly,
Wu Cai Hong and Zhou Shao Tian are already at the Cai family's home.
Didn't Lao Cai run away long ago?
She probably got some information from Lao Cai's family.
But sadly, they were still one step late.
Since they're already late...
why did you still need someone to follow them?
Lao Cai fleeing, what does
it have to do with us?
You went through great pains to help.
Are you trying to help her find the killer of her father?
I'm helping myself.
After acquiring Ling Long, not long after,
a fire hollowed out everything.
It left me no choice but to borrow (money) from the east.
Till now, even the ledger
has been burnt by others.
What do you think will happen next?
Come.
I originally thought we found some information.
But who knew we didn't even find anything.
It wasn't all for nothing.
We found a new lead
I believe, regardless of the bad luck we encountered.
His true colours will eventually be exposed.
I will definitely find out the truth.
Cai Hong, don't think too much right now.
You just need to rest right now.
Just leave Old Cai's matters to me.
I'll let you know first thing.
I caused you to worry this time.
You go home and rest too.
What's most important is you.
I'll get going then.
Cai Hong.
There are certain things in this world,
it's best to let it
forever be a mystery.
Sure enough, it wasn't as expected. Someone moved the signs
and caused Wu Cai Hong to take the wrong road.
Things are starting to become more clear.
We need to turn this around.
Help me to check the whereabouts of Old Cai's wife.
I understand, Young Master. Is there anything else?
How is Wu Cai Long's leg injury?
It seem like it's not a major injury.
Okay, go back to work.
What's wrong, Ah Li?
It's because that lady hit me.
The girl does not play around (go easy)
instead she took advantage and kept hitting me.
Ah Li, sorry. Blame me for this.
I asked for your help and you even got beaten up.
Take this.
Go and buy some medicines.
Brother. How could I accept your money?
I didn't even complete the task you assigned to me.
I even lost her.
I didn't help you at all. I can't accept this money.
You must accept this money. You helped me with the task.
Take this as the expenses for the medicines.
Take it.
I will accept this then.
In fact, regarding yesterday's matter, you could not rely on me.
I thought there would be time to get to know my brother's future wife.
She kept asking me questions along the way.
Don't be blinded by the fact that she looks like Lin Daiyu*, she's more like a dominatrix!  (*Lin Daiyu was a beautiful actress)
She used her shoes to hit my face.
Well... frankly...
when she isn't violent, she is a warm and beautiful person.
When she is violent, that is also like
the female hero, Mulan!
Could she be the one in your heart?
Really? I'm so stupid.
Why didn't you tell me she will be my sister-in-law?
When are you going to invite me to your wedding banquet?
It's still too early.
In Huzhou, my brother is such a great person.
You can't even find someone like that if you tried.
There are ladies in queue behind her. Why isn't she anxious?
I hope so too.
Oh right brother, yesterday I led the small white horse back,
how do you think I should give it back?
That horse isn't missed, it's yours now.
-Mine? -Yours.
I guess it's like Robin Hood. I'll accept it.
Ah Li. I have something on. I'm leaving first. Take care.
- Then do you need anything else?  - Let's drink together sometime.
Invite me to your wedding banquet.
If you didn't take the wrong road, I could have gone home earlier.
- Are you going to leave or not? - I'm not leaving.
Can't you see that I'm injured?
I don't need you. Put me down.
Be careful.
What's wrong?
What is with you and Wu Cai Hong?
What do you mean?
She is the daughter of your enemy. That night...
Do you know how worried I was over you?
If something were to happen to you,
what are mom and I going to do?
If you are worried about this, I have already explained what I need to.
I'm not just worried about this.
Brother. Did you forget about revenge for Dad?
I have never forgotten about it.
Kick Wu Cai Hong out of Ling Long tomorrow then.
Why?
Because she is Wu Da Hong's daughter. She is our enemy.
The devil is always dressed as an angel.
But you must not be lured in by the devil.
As she pulls you in,
you must not forget about Dad's death.
You must never forget the more than twenty years of sufferings that we went through.
You must not be touched by our enemy's daughter.
I have never forgotten about my Dad's death.
I won't let Cai Hong do this.
This is my intent.
Are you really going to be this way?
If not then?
Fine. I hope that you will keep your word.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Strange. Where did I leave it?
Mom.
- Madam. - Mom.
Give it to me.
Let go.
Madam, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Mom, don't scare me.
Everything's fine.
Blood!
Let's go to the hospital. Get the car ready.
Young Master, it's here.
Mom, what's wrong? What happened?
Wu Da Hong is back.
Wu Da Hong is back. He is going to harm our family.
Wu Da Hong is already dead.
He won't harm us.
- He's back. - Don't be afraid.
He is already dead.
- Impossible. - He won't harm us again.
- Are you telling me the truth? - Yes.
It's really true. Mom, Wu Da Hong is already dead.
We didn't want to tell you so you wouldn't be upset.
He is really dead.
It's true. Mom. No one will dare to bully us again.
Everything's fine.
Impossible, he is not dead.
He won't let go, even if he is dead.
HIs daughter will harm us.
Listen to me. It's already in the past.
Everything is already in the past.
Young Master.
Mom. Let's go to the hospital now.
Come, quick.
Quick.
He is not dead.
Why did you let my mother see this?
Take this away and burn it.
So many years, even with mom's illness, she has had good times.
But with you and the house,
it's causing too great a damage to mom.
Brother. Mom is old.
She really can not take much more.
This should end now.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
It's time for you to leave.
Let me send you home, okay?
Come in.
Miss is here?
Young Master is not here?
He went out. If there is anything, you can tell me.
Previously, Young Master told me to check on the whereabouts of Old Cai's wife.
I found out where she lives. I'm here to report it to him.
Give me the address. I will pass it to him.
- Thank you, Miss. - You can go back to work.
I'm leaving first.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki