♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 8
Don't bother yourself with this.
What arrangements? I didn't see any.
She's making your mind restless!
Brother. Don't forget
how father died and mom fell sick.
I'm calculating it in my head.
I don't need you to teach me what to do. Go back to work.
I have already done this.
I wonder how Uncle Fu is doing lately.
I deserve to die. I even forgot about this.
It's time to eat. Come.
Let's eat. It's time to eat.
Everyone , come over and eat.
- Is anyone there? - Coming.
- Miss. - Uncle Fu.
I won't trouble you. I still need to go back to the factory to work.
I came over to visit you. These are snacks.
Dan Ke!
Miss is here. Greet her now.
- Dad. - No need.
Hello, Miss.
I'm fine.
Miss. You are really our great saviour.
I'm not a saviour. Actually, I'm really sorry for last time.
Thus, I specially came here to ask if you had found a new job.
Miss, didn't you already arrange for Dan Ke to work at Ling Long?
You are really a saviour to our family.
Look.
You didn't blame me for my mistake and even got Dan Ke a job. I can grow old without worries.
I really don't understand how I could have secured Dan Ke a job if my own position is still unstable.
Other than you, who would treat us that well?
Could it be Shao Tian?
- Mom, look!  - That's not good, it's so dirty!
Cai Yue. What do you think of this dress?
It's very pretty.
- Mom. - Why did you stop me?
Don't go in. It's not like you don't know that we can't afford these things now.
- Can't I just take a look? - You can't.
- Just a glance. - No.
One glance.
Just a glance.
- Let's go. - Mom.
- Mom, don't go in. - We are already in.
Let's take a look first.
Get a cup of tea for me.
Look at this. Isn't it beautiful?
It looks especially nice.
It's really nice.
Look.
Look at the embroidery...
Isn't this Madam Wu from Ling Long?
I said the wrong thing.
It should be Mrs Jiang.
Madam Zhang, you are here.
- Madam Zhang.- What nonsense are you spouting? We own a factory and
our business is big.
We have made enough money and are tired.
We want to take a break.
Enjoy life!
Miss, don't say anymore.
Madam Wu. This dress is very expensive.
It can easily get snagged on something!
That's right. This dress
was specially prepared for Madam Zhang.
That's right. If you want to buy this, you wouldn't be able to afford it.
- Just don't touch anything. - That's right.
Who says I can't afford it?
I like this very much. I'm buying this today. Wrap it up.
- Mom. - Xiao Lin.
Wrap up this dress for me.
Yes, Madam Zhang.
Give it to me.
Mom, let go.
- Mom! - Forget it.
The dress depends on who the owner is.
With your identity, this dress doesn't suit you.
Who says that it doesn't suit me?
What's so great about you? In the past, you were trailing behind me.
- What are you acting like right now?  - What kind of person are you?!
Madame Zhao, don't mind her!
- It's not worth it. - Who do you think you are?
Do you think you are still Madam Wu of the past?
You have no factory, no money, and no house! I'm being polite by calling you Madam!
Who says I don't have any money? I can't even spend what I have.
- You must be dreaming. - Why did you push me?
So what if I push you?
Your husband is already dead and you still want to dress well? Who's going to look at you?
I know now. It must be for that Zhou Shao Tian.
That Zhou Shao Tian is really something, going around with you three people!
What are you talking about? So shameless. What has it got to do with my daughter?
- So what if I say that about you? - Nonsense!
- Who's spouting nonsense - Who's spouting nonsense?
I'm going to hit you today.
- I'm going to hit you! - Mom!
- Who says you can spout nonsense? - Stop fighting.
- Mom... - Leave now.
Don't shut the door.
Mom, forget it. Don't be so angry.
I'm furious. I have never been this furious before.
Just wait and see. Wait until I'm living well.
I will be back to see you kneel in front of me and beg.
Mom. They have poor taste.
Don't argue with them anymore.
Let's go home now.
Look. Your hair is a mess.
So embarrassing. Let's leave now.
Listen well, daughter. It's up to you whether I can vent my anger in this lifetime.
Mom. What can I do?
You fool.
Youth? Youth is an asset.
Look at you now. You are so beautiful.
You have to find a man with money and power. Help me vent my anger.
Don't be like your sister! That Zhou Shao Tian,
he's so poor.
When I talk about him, I feel so frustrated.
Don't be angry. Actually, I think Brother Shao Tian is a good man.
Mom. Why did you hit me?
Can't I hit you? Just like your sister.
Seriously.
- You are so hateful. - You are hateful.
Let's go. So hateful.
Miss.
- Hello, Miss - Don't call me this anymore.
It's still the same.
Where is Uncle Fu's son working now?
That guy might not be very smart, but he's pretty strong.
He's in the warehouse.
Go back to work then.
I will teach you how to carry goods today.
Look carefully. I will demonstrate it to you.
Kneel down first.
Grab the rope.
Put it on your shoulder.
Come.
Get up slowly.
Use your shoulder to lift it.
These are very heavy, you have to bend your back.
You won't get hurt this way. Try it.
Not this way.
Bend down first so that you won't get hurt.
Get up slowly.
It's okay. Let's do it again.
Okay.
Are you hungry?
Here. Wipe your sweat.
- Okay. - I will take you to have a feast later. Okay?
- Okay. - Okay. What do you like to eat?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
What's wrong?
Thank you.
For what?
Thank you for helping the Fu family.
I'm not concerned about him.
I just pity him.
As for you, don't be so sweet with your words.
You will very quickly regret thanking me.
I'm not surprised that you say that.
Its because I am ready any time.
You are not afraid?
You should be the one who's afraid.
Harming someone is just like harming yourself.
You don't need to worry about this.
Go out.
Wu Cai Hong.
I'm warning you.
You don't need to be concerned about my brother.
If you plan to remain here at Ling Long,
you will definitely regret it.
Perhaps, the person who will regret it is not me.
Do you know that
people like you who are full of yourself... other people find you very hateful.
I don't need anyone to like me.
Don't say that I didn't advise you.
My brother is a good person. But to you,
he is a monster.
There will come a day when he will make you miserable.
Thank you for your advice.
I will personally watch you fall into despair.
You're wrong, I was already in a pit of despair.
Thus, the one who will fall won't be me.
It will be you both.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Headline!
Wu Hong Da's daughter, Wu Cai Hong, has risen to a high position under Jiang Yu!
Wish them a good future relationship!
Headline.
Wait. What did you say?
Give me one.
- Here. - Thanks.
Headline, Headline! Wu Hong Da's daughter, Wu Cai Hong...
This wench has been hiding from me.
Cao Hong, you are back.
Look at you. Why do you look so tired?
A girl should put on more make-up
and have a trendier hairstyle.
Your identity is different now.
You can't be so casual anymore.
What kind of identity do I have now?
Look at you. You don't need to feel bad anymore. You are even hiding it from me.
Look. Everyone in Huzhou already knows.
I definitely agree and give you my consent to be with Jiang Yu.
Aunt, don't believe this rumour.
This child. In terms of wealth and appearances,
he may have nothing to say.
Don't just choose anyone. Don't tell me you are going to choose that poor guy, Zhou Shao Tian?
Who says so?
If it wasn't for Jiang Yu, would our family have come to this state?
You must not say this. The police already investigated and said that he's not the killer.
If you talk about him acquiring Ling Long, then, in the future, you can be Mrs Jiang.
Ling Long will belong to you too.
How can you think like this! If you want to push me to the enemy,
you should ask my father in heaven!
How could you say this?
How could you not understand? I'm doing this for our family.
I only want you and your sister to live a good life and find a good man.
What's wrong with Jiang Yu? What are you still not satisfied with?
What's with wealth and power? Are you living just for wealth?!
After father passed away, I haven't seen you do anything for him!
Sis, Mom. What are you doing?
No matter what, I'm still your stepmother.
I don't need you to teach me.
Stop there.
Cai Hong.
Cai Hong. What's wrong with you?
Look at your face.
Wasn't everything going well? Why did you start fighting?
I'm fine.
My aunt just talks without thinking. I won't take her words to heart.
You're always like this, always carrying the burdens by yourself.
I already told you that I can help you to shoulder your burdens
Although I'm still thankful to Madam Wu.
Why?
By doing that, she let me reflect a lot on myself.
I have alway been someone didn't dare to make any decisions.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I think that this is a declaration of war, not a resignation letter.
It's good that you know.
Whatever harm you caused Cai Hong, I will give it back to you.
I will be waiting.
Starting from now, I will do everything to protect Cai Hong
and make you leave Ling Long. I will make you unable to continue your dyeing industry in Huzhou.
I will also find the evidence that you killed Boss Wu.
Don't let me be disappointed in you.
Goodbye.
Cai Hong, come here.
It's just ahead.
Brother Shao Tian. Where are we going?
Close your eyes first.
Okay, I will close my eyes. Tell me where we are going.
Okay.
Wait.
Be careful. Don't make me trip.
Don't go anywhere else. Just follow me.
We will be there soon.
- Don't open your eyes. - We are not there yet?
We are here.
Don't move.
Brother Shao Tian. Can I open my eyes now?
Okay.
Open your eyes now.
It's yours?
- Is this for real? - Yes.
But where did you get the money from?
It's from the bank.
It's great that you are able to start your own shop. I'm happy for you.
You are right. This shop doesn't only belong to me.
It's yours too.
It should make us happy.
I didn't help you at all.
It's just a small shop now
but I believe that with our hard work,
we can quickly pay off all our debt.
There will come a day with Fu Sheng will be like Ling Long. Moreover, it will also surpass Ling Long.
Brother Shao Tian. Do you know that I have always had a guilty conscious?
I dragged you down and caused you to leave Ling Long.
I didn't imagine that you would start a small shop on your own when you left Ling Long.
I'm really very happy.
Thanks.
By the way, I will operate my shop tomorrow. I hope that you would come.
Of course. I will take leave and come here.
The rest are not important. It's more that important that you will be there alone.
Me alone?
I was just joking. I really need a hand now. I hope that you will come over and help me.
I can't leave Ling Long now.
Why?
Is it because of your father's case?
Even if many people forgot about it, I won't.
Father fell to his death in front of my eyes. If I don't get to the bottom of this,
I won't feel assured.
Aso that I can find out the truth, I can't leave Ling Long.
But I'm worried about you staying with Ling Long.
Why would you worry?
Jiang Yu doesn't have a hold on me, he won't do anything to me.
Don't worry about me.
Okay.
I respect your decision
but Fu Sheng and I will wait for you.
You are welcome to come back anytime.
Thanks.
Thank you too.
-Congratulations.  -This way, please.
- May you prosper. - Please take a look around.
I hope your business prospers.
Please look around.
Boss Jiang. I would like to take time off. I'm going out at noon.
You still need to memorise over thirty types of flowers.
Manage your time.
I know. I will be back.
You are not allowed to go.
But you already gave me your consent this morning.
It's because I just found out that today is the opening of Fu Sheng.
I don't care whether you agree now or not, I'm going.
Fu Sheng won't last for long. It will be a waste of time for you to go.
Are you really going to be like this?
You are really so petty.
I just remembered that I have a party to go to as well.
If you want to go that much, if you don't mind, you can go with a petty person like me.
So how?
Didn't you want to go? Why aren't you moving?
What are you trying to do?
What do you think I'm trying to do?
Someone like you is capable of doing anything.
He personally gave me an invitation.
If I don't go, it will be a waste of his sincerity.
Thank you for hosting this today.
Thank you, everyone.
I hope that everyone will drink and enjoy themselves.
Please stay.
Don't mention it.
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian.
I want to thank your boss.
Without you, Cai Hong wouldn't have come to this event today.
Without you, there won't be a Fu Sheng today.
So polite?
I have seen a lot of this kind of business in Huzhou where they start operations today and fold the next day.
If I didn't come today, I would have made a mistake. missed seeing the business open.
No matter what, I'm better than a person who lives off others.
Looks like I really wronged you.
You both drank quite a lot. Please talk less.
- I will let you talk then. - Boss Jiang, I would like to ask a favour from you.
Let Cai Hong go.
It's me who doesn't want to let her go now
or is it you instead?
Leave with me.
Okay, you can go back on your own today. I will do this myself.
Shao Tian. Who is that?
The new boss of Ling Long, Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu?
His family name is Jiang.
It's really Young Master Jiang.
Be careful.
Stop the carriage. Jiang Yu, are you crazy?
If you want to die, I don't.
What? Do you want to find your Brother Shao Tian?
I won't allow you.
Stop the carriage.
Are you crazy? You don't even want your life?
I can tell that you drank too much. You are the one who doesn't want your life. Let go.
I'm not letting you go.
- Let me go. - I won't. So how?
- Let go. - No.
I don't want to see you again.
- Let me go.- No.
Let me go.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Fine. I respect your decision.
But Fu Sheng and I will wait for you.
- Miss Wu. - Why is it you?
Cai Hong.
- You know each other? - You know him?
He was my neighbour when we were young. His name is Ma Li.
I needed a new employee to help me manage the shop. It just so happens that he also needed money to raise his family.
Thus, he came to help me.
How do you know each other?
You are still talking about it? Previously...
Brother, it's like this.
I was driving a carriage not for long when Miss Wu was my customer.
I wasn't familiar with the road and got lost with Miss Wu.
Miss Wu took me for a bad person and hit me.
I see. This is definitely a misunderstanding.
Ah Li and I grew up together. I know what kind of person he is.
He wouldn't dare to do that kind of stuff.
That's right, too.
If you weren't a bad guy, I shouldn't have bullied you.
Since this was a misunderstanding, don't talk about it anymore. Go back to work now.
Okay.
Cai Hong. Why are you here looking for me?
Actually, I have been thinking about something for a long time.
I think you are right. I shouldn't remain at Ling Long.
Thus, I will come and help you out here.
Really?
Hello, Boss.
Boss. The dye for this month will be running out soon.
Which house is the closest?
Also, we decreased by 10%.
There's also thirteen accounts receivable left, and we reminded them to hurry up with it.
Brother.
Please sign this document.
Wu Cai Hong is becoming more impossible.
She is still not at work yet. Help me to check. You must punish her properly.
Brother, no need.
Wu Cai Hong already sent someone to deliver a letter.
She said that she quit.
Who says she can resign?
What's wrong? You can't bear to see her go?
Ling Long is not a place where she can simply come and go.
Brother, leaving her here is a burden. She finally wants to go,
why must you insist that she comes back?
To add further,
with her here, we'll always be looking behind our backs. Who knows, maybe one day we'll get sent back to the police station!
Where did she go?
How would I know?
But I guess that, other than Zhou Shao Tian,
where else would she go?
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
- Brother. - Wu Long, where are you?
- Come out now. - What are you doing?
The cat made a lot of noise last night. I couldn't sleep.
The cat cried the entire night?
I think it's your heart which had been crying the whole night instead.
Wu Long.
Brother, where are you going?
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
Brother Shao Tian. Don't be affected by what my aunt said.
If not, I really don't know how to face you.
Cai Hong. Whatever others say or think, I don't care about them.
What I care about is what you you think.
When my father passed away,
I remember that you had always been helping me.
You took care of my family.
I'm really very grateful to you.
I don't want to hear your words of thanks.
It's because it makes me feel that I'm very distant from you.
I don't mean that.
I know that.
Cai Hong.
Even though you only take me for a brother, I will always take care of you,
and do anything for you.
♫I can't help but believe in fate♫
This is not something precious, but I made this bracelet from strands I dyed myself.
The bracelet is very similar to you and has the same name.
Frankly,
I didn't know how to hand this to you.
I thought about this for a long time for many reasons too but it couldn't represent my heart.
I finally thought it through.
What I want to say is this.
Cai Hong.
Let's be together and let me take care of you.
♫I've been hurt♫
Cai Hong. Who am I in your heart?
I have always regarded you as my older brother.
I don't want to be your older brother.
Jiang Yu. You are too extreme.
If you are not happy, you can scram and go back with her.
Do you think I don't dare to?
Jiang Yu. What are you doing?
- Ask her. - Don't let me see you bully her again.
As long as you are at Ling Long,
I will stay at Ling Long too.
♫It's like a longtime dream of soaring freely♫
I know that
maybe this gift is too sudden.
Don't be in a hurry to reply me.
I can wait.
I will wait until you are willing.
♫I'm so upset, when you let go of my hands♫
♫As if my mind and senses♫
♫are saying you are the one. It's like a longtime dream of soaring freely♫
You are so easy to love.
♫ You are my beautiful aroma.
Put it on me.
You agree?
Are you being serious?
Cai Hong. Do you know how happy I am?
I'm really very happy.
You finally agreed to be with me.
Brother Shao Tian. Put me down.
Cai Hong. I'm really very happy today.
Trust me. I will treat you well in this lifetime.
If I didn't trust your words, I wouldn't have agreed.
I have been waiting for you. Let's get married quickly.
We don't need to rush this. Moreover, you just started your business.
Of course, I want to rush it.
I have waited for a long time and you finally agreed. How could I not be in a rush?
I will listen to you.
Wu Cai Hong!
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki