♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 11
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You don't like to make others wait, thus, I don't mind. It's okay.
You still remember grudges.
Okay,what would you like to drink? It's on me.
Let me do it.
Waitress.
Sir, Miss. What would you like to order?
- Coffee. - Same for me. No cream and sugar.
Okay, please wait.
You are drinking something so bitter. Are you not in a good mood?
Forget it. What about the collaboration I discussed with you previously?
I'm going to leave Huzhou. My apologies, Miss Lu. I disappointed you again.
It's okay. I have been rejected by you a few times.
It's not unusual.
Here's your coffee.
Please enjoy.
But are you really happy to leave Huzhou?
It's like taking a step backwards.
Jiang Yu has already bullied you into this state and you still want to swallow it?
This is not the Boss Zhou that I know.
It would be false to say that I'm not unhappy
but I think certain things should be left on its own.
Why?
Because of a woman?
Listen more to the music.
It's not easy to find a day like today to come here and have a quiet time.
I really can't tell if you are just a fool for love.
Sorry, Miss Lu, to have disappointed you again.
But I would still like to advise you to think it over again.
Even if you change the location, is that the life you want?
Thank you for your concern during this period of time.
I have an appointment with a friend later.
I'm leaving first.
He is really a fool.
Love can't be touched.
Only with the hand of Fu money and power
it won't leave then.
Here is your money.
It's no hurry.
Boss, thank you for your money.
Okay.
Boss, here is your money.
Let me check. The amount is right.
Ah Li.
Brother, you are here.
I'm still in the same line. (of work)
- Just blame me. - How could I blame you?
I don't care about which job I take.
- Take this. - Brother, what are you doing?
You have been with me for a long time.
This is what I have.
Sorry.
Brother, take back your money. I won't accept it.
Keep the money.
Brother, we grew up together. Without you, I wouldn't have survived.
You are now having a difficult time. How could I use your money?
If you don't accept this money, don't call me your brother again.
-Brother... - Keep it!
Don't worry.
Once I succeed in Tianjin, I will contact you. We will establish Fu Sheng again.
Brother, I will wait for your good news.
Boss Jiang. Are you free this evening?
Tonight my close friend, Miss Cui Quan, is getting married. I would like to attend.
Go then.
Brother. Why don't you know what's in my heart?
What are you thinking about?
Everyone will bring along their partner.
You have many friends. Just choose anyone.
But everyone is taking along a male partner.
Brother. Go with me this evening.
I'm still busy. When will I find time go with you?
Find someone to go with you.
I will just find anyone to go with me this evening.
You are not worried?
With such a temper like yours, it's already good enough that you don't boss anyone around.
Brother. You only just have a sister like me. You are not even going to help me with this?
Okay then. I will find someone else then.
What if someone were to sell me off?
Remember to tell mother not to be sad.
What time is it this evening?
7 pm.
- I get it. - Thanks, Brother.
I'm going home to get ready. I will wait for you at home.
- Hello. -Boss Jiang.
This is Mr Shi from the bank.
What's wrong? What's the matter?
I received news that Wu Cai Hong took a loan from the underground lenders with a high interest.
The money is being used to pay back to the small workshops.
How did that Zhou Shao Tian survive?
He let a woman go and borrow money?
There is no movement from Zhou Shao Tian lately.
- Is your news reliable? - Of course.
She is taking a loan with high interest at this time. What is she going to use to return it?
Does Wu Cai Hong, with her payments, think she is the Robin Hood of the paladin. a knight renowned for heroism
It's not that. Those people are capable of burning and killing.
Miss Wu really has the guts.
Okay, wait for my news.
Okay.
Hello, Mrs Li.
When Miss returns home, tell her that I had some matters to attend to. I will pick her up tonight.
Okay.
What I regretted
is knowing an evil person like you. I don't want to see you again.
Keep your hatred self away from me.
Wu Cai Hong.
What? She ran away?
Don't panic. She won't get far away.
I am not worried. It is not my money that is being floated away.
Let's do this. Send men to the dock and train station.
Also, block off all the exits.
Well I'll find Zhou Shao Tian. He is like a big eyed dragon.
Wait.
It's useless to look for him.
He is Wu Hong Da's good friend. Why would he help you to capture his good friend's daughter?
What should we so then?
Just wait, I have contacted Director Lee.
Boss, your wish is my command.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Move aside. Don't let her get away.
Move aside. Continue to search thoroughly.
Quick. Go over there.
Cai Hong. Boss Qian is searching here.
Leave with me now.
Stepmom, let's leave now.
Move aside.
Hide yourselves now. Cai Hong and I will see if we distract them.
Be careful.
- What's going on? -- Move aside.
Run with me.
They are over there. Go after them.
Quick.
Over there! Quick!
They are over there. Move aside.
Move aside. Over there.
Get down. What are you doing?
- Quick. Are you okay? - I'm fine.
Bastards. Go after them now.
Quick. Hurry up.
Don't let them get away.
Over there. Go after them.
It's so hot. Cai Yun, let's go home.
The boat is leaving.
Where are the tickets?
I don't have them.
You don't have them. Let 's go back home then.
Mom, be careful.
Go inside here first.
They are over there.
Go after them.
Cai Hong.
They are over there.
Let's go now, Cai Hong.
- Let's go. - Zhou Shao Tian.
Move aside.
They are over there. Zhou Shao Tian!
Quick. Move aside.
Stop there.
Young Master. It's getting dark.
We have already searched the entire Huzhou.
- Why don't we go back? - Continue to search.
Yes.
Stop there.
What are you doing? Why did you push my cart?
Move aside.
Let's go.
Stop them.
The ambience is great. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Fei Fei.
Yan Yan, long time no see.
This is...
My boyfriend, Jia Ming.
Jia Ming. This is our class beauty who I have been telling you. She is Fang Fei Fei.
- Hello. - Hello.
Yan Yan mentions you often. It is nice to meet you today.
Sure enough, it's just as she says. Thank you.
Yan Yan. You haven't seen each other for a long time and must have a lot to talk about. I will wait for you inside.
Okay.
Your boyfriend is not bad.
He's okay. Let's not talk about him. Let me take a look at you.
Fei Fei. You are becoming more beautiful.
How can I be compared to you? You have such a good looking boyfriend. You must be really blessed.
I can't be compared to you. You have a childhood love, Boss Jiang.
He is your senior buddy and husband too.
Don't talk nonsense.
Why don't I see Mr Jiang?
He has some matters to attend to for the time being. He will be here later.
I should be able to be at yours and Mr Jiang's wedding banquet soon.
Don't be happy for me.
Who says so? Frankly speaking, our cohorts are already at a marriageable age.
Today is Sister Cui's day,
my wedding is set for the spring of next year. We could celebrate two weddings in the same year!
In this case, you and Mr Jiang's wedding banquet shouldn't be that far ahead.
It's late. I wonder how is my stepmom and sister are doing.
I will arrange for us to find them later.
Let's take a break first.
I am afraid they are behind. I can go on.
Let's take a break.
Cai Hong. I'm useless.
Driving you to desperately flee with me.
Are you afraid?
As long as you are with me, I'm not afraid of anything.
Ma Li told me that in the past,
they lived in the slums
and fought over a hot bun.
I have never imagined that there would be this kind of life.
When my dad was still around, I couldn't even phantom the feeling of starvation.
Not until after my father's death did I understand that reality is harsh.
Also experience the pain that brother Shao Tian experienced in the past.
Cai Hong. Everything is in the past now.
Everything will get better.
Let's work hard together.
There is a carriage over there. Let's go.
Wait!
Wait.
You don't want your life? What if I had knocked you down?
Please help us.
We have urgent matters and need to leave the city. We would like to hitch a ride from you.
Sir, please help us. We are really in a hurry.
It's not that I don't want to help you. Can't you see that my cart is full?
How could I take in any passengers?
Sir, take this. Please help us.
I can tell.
You two are not guilty of anything? referring to a crime
I am not blinded by the dark.
Is someone out there trying to capture you?
Sir, you see our need. What else can we do?
Good people will have good karma. Please help us.
Yes, please help us.
It is obvious that the two of you eloped.
If I were to give you a ride, they will capture me.
I don't want to involved myself. Chances are not only your family but the police will accuse me of it. (helping them.)
I can only bring one of you. That way when I get stopped, I can justify it.
No. We must both leave together.
Look. My cart is very small.
It doesn't matter which goes...
I can't do too much to help.
Forget it. It's still better that you wait...
Sir. Please take him out of the city.
Please help me.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Little rascal. You have a good life.
You met such a good lady.
I really envy you.
Brother Shao Tian. When you wake up,
please don't be angry with me.
Cai Hong?
Stop the carriage.
Wu Cai Hong.
You dare to leave without saying goodbye?
We are not even friends. Why should I tell you when I leave?
You can't leave.
I'm not your slave. You don't have the right to make that request.
Let go.
Jiang Yu, let me down!
Jiang Yu!
Let me down!
What are you doing?
Come here now.
- There is food. - Go ahead.
Come, stop and come over here.
What's your name?
It's late. What are you doing?
Leave.
What exactly is going on? Why are they checking so thoroughly?
Open the cover.
It can't be connected to this little rascal and that lady.
- Slowly. - Open that.
You. Come here. Open this.
Okay, go over there.
Those behind, go first.
Next.
Stop there!
- What's your name? - It's Li Er Gou.
-What is all this?  -Miscellaneous things. Mainly groceries from town.
- Where are you taking them?  - Out of the city to my village.
Who is he?
He is my nephew.
Nephew?
He is sick.
Why didn't you tell me earlier? Leave now.
Stop the cart.
- Little rascal. - Where is Cai Hong?
Cai Hong.
- You are looking for that lady? - Where is she?
The lady gave you one whack and you were on the ground.
I carried you onto the cart. She didn't get onto the cart.
She didn't get on.
She insisted that I bring you out of the city
before I agreed to take you out of the city.
Little rascal. The police are waiting there to capture you.
If you go back now, you will be beaten to death.
Big brother, I can't abandon Cai Hong. I need to find her.
My name is Zhou Shao Tian. I will remember your kindness. I will thank you in the future.
Thanks.
Little rascal, be careful.
This is a passionate and decent kid.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
What are you doing?
Okay, we are leaving.
We are going back then.
Do you want to say farewell to your friend?
Forget it. She doesn't look like she's in a good mood. We might get snubbed.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Brother. You promised me that you would come. You clearly did.
How could you not keep your word?
How could you?
It's just a small gesture. It has been hard on you last night.
Since you have already found the person,
I would advise you that you take her home immediately.
Thanks.
I'm not just a policeman. It's such an expensive item. I can't accept it.
Take this back.
I have never taken back my gifts.
If you like it, keep it. If you don't,
just throw it away.
I will help you to give it to someone who needs it.
Do whatever you want.
Sit down.
Where is Cai Hong?
Tell me where Cai Hong is.
If you dare to harm her, I will never let you off.
She is safe with me.
As long as she is not with you, everything will be fine.
Don't be rash.
There are many people out there who want to get you into trouble.
As long as you hand over the money to me,
I can help you to settle this issue.
How can you just stare at money
without it being an ulterior motive?
Hand over the money. The most you will get is a few years in jail.
As for the other matters, I won't pursue them.
Once you are out of jail, you can go anywhere.
If you still want to do business, I can give you some money.
Is that so?
But why do I still feel that you think I'm the killer?
They haven't caught the killer of Wu Hong Da.
Although the police have now closed the case,
Wu Cai Hong hasn't given up yet.
There are merchants in Huzhou, for their own interests, also urging the police to catch the murderers.
I think
the murderer must have sleepless nights.
What a pity.
I don't have that money.
Nor did I kill Wu Hong Da. I must have disappointed you.
Tell me. If Wu Cai Hong knows that you have a
unknown origin, she would like you?
I predict that she will hate you for the rest of her life.
Stop this despicable underhanded tactics of yours to split us apart.
Do you think you are that noble?
Say whatever you like. If you have the substance, show me the evidence.
Yes, I have a big sum of money.
Where is the money? Where is the evidence? Do you have them?
Boss Jiang, you have always had to justify it.
Let's wait and see then.
Let's see how long you can hide that money.
Boss Jiang. Boss Jiang. Did you find the rascal?
Not yet.
Don't worry. I'm in this line.
In this world, there isn't anyone who doesn't need my money.
It's not that easy as you think.
We already have him in our hands.
I don't trust that devil anymore.
If he refused to admit it, what can you do?
Boss Jiang. What are your plans? I will listen to you.
Zhou Shao Tian. You can leave.
Why?
When I say you can leave, just leave. Stop asking irrelevant questions.
Let me tell you. Return the money soon.
Don't think of running away again.
When it comes to money, don't mess with the boss.
He has friends with the mafia. You won't be able to escape from him.
A small fry like you, even if Boss Qian kills you, you are just like an ant.
Where is this place?
Why did you bring me here?
I brought you here to meet the Brother Shao Tian that you wanted to meet.
Brother Shao Tian?
What exactly do you want?
To show you that he gave you a magic potion to drink. expression - he is lying to you.
If you are angry, just direct it at me.
Don't harm Brother Shao Tian.
Don't worry. I won't harm him.
I guarantee that after tonight, you won't want to see him again.
What exactly are you trying to do?
You took Ling Long away.
You bankrupted Fu Sheng.
What else are you going to do?
I want you to see clearly which exactly is the evil person instead.
What are you doing?
Let me go. Let me go.
Let me go.
Jiang Yu. What are you doing?
Sorry. You will have to suffer for a while first.
If you want to find out who the real killer is,
be a bit more patient.
You didn't want to pay back the loan and tried to run away?
- I already told you that I don't have the money. - No money?
Zhou Shao Tian. Your really know how to pretend.
No wonder Miss Wu has been tricked by you more than three times.
Who told you this? I have never tricked her.
You didn't?
You and Old Cai split half of the money you stole from Ling Long.
I loaned you the money then because I knew that you would be able to pay me back.
Did you really think that I believed that you could expand your business?
Shao Tian, did you actually kid yourself and believe you could
actually pack up and run away?
I already told you that I will think of a solution to pay you back.
Think of a solution?
What solution would you have?
You owe money to many debtors. Will you be able to pay them back?
How much will be left to pay me?
Boss Qian. Don't force me into a corner.
Okay, I won't press you. You should also be frank.
The return of the money from Ling Long will be good enough for me.
The balance of the money will help you and Miss Wu to start anew.
Let's do this. Pay me back the money and we are even.
I don't have it. I already told you that I didn't.
Zhou Shao Tian, if I don't use force,
do you think I'm that weak?
Let's see if your mouth is stronger than my fist.
Beat him.
Enough.
Zhou Shao Tian. I advise you to pay me back soon so that you will suffer less.
I already said that
I really don't have that money.
Fine.
Bring him here.
Let me go.
Do you see him? He is just like you. He owes me money and he didn't pay me back.
Come, cut him.
Don't!
Did you see this? You will be next.
Don't kid yourself and just give up.
If you don't return the money, I will cut off your ear.
Tell me now. Are you going to pay me back or not.
Are you going to pay me back or not? Speak.
Are you going to pay me back or not?
If you don't return the money, I will cut off your ear.
I...
Speak now.
You should be happy to talk.
Speak!
Jiang Yu!
You are really despicable!
What is this trick?
Shameless!
Small minded person!
Brother Shao Tian.
- Brother Shao Tian. - Today, I must...
Cai Hong.
-Cai Hong-Cai Hong
Cai Hong! I'm taking you to the hospital.
Cai Hong.
Just kill me.
Bring it on!
Are you a man?
My greatest skill is to take away your riches and repossess them.
- Miss. - Why are you back alone?
Where is my brother?
Young Master had some matters to attend to.
What matters?
Tell me quick. What exactly is it?
Where is he?
Young Master is with Wu Cai Hong.
Wu Cai Hong is injured now.
Young Master is with her at the hospital. I'm back here to take some stuff for him.
I get it.
Go and get it.
No. It's Mrs Jiang who is not like the rest.
Mrs. Jiang. Those two words have a nice right to them.
Don't talk nonsense. If brother hear this, I'm in trouble.
Who says I'm talking nonsense? You and Boss Jiang,
No. You and your brother were in fact friends since childhood.
The post of Mrs Jiang is yours forever.
That's right. There is no difference whether we call you this now or in the future.
Mrs Jiang.
No one can be compared to you. You have a childhood sweetheart, Boss Jiang, who grew up together with you.
He is senior buddy and also a husband.
We should be able to attend yours and Mr Jiang's wedding banquet soon.
This home is mine.
I will never lose everything.
Doctor. What is her condition?
Her injury is a bit deep but unfortunately, it didn't affect her bones.
She will be fine if she has a proper rest.
If there is anything, just call me.
Thanks.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Did I make a mistake?
Mom.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki