♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 12
- Does it still hurt? - Don't come over.
What did you do to Brother Shao Tian?
What did you do to him?
Don't worry. He's not dead yet.
You are a killer and a monster.
I don't believe what you said. I'm going to find Brother Shao Tian.
Without my consent, you are not going anywhere.
Why should I listen to you?
Why must I get your consent?
If you don't want your Brother Shao Tian to die a quick death,
you better keep quiet.
Let me go in.
Let me go. Let me go in.
Jiang Yu!
Why are you not letting me in?
Jiang Yu.
I want to see Cai Hong. Let me go.
- Stop. - Why are you not letting me in?
Stop. What are you doing?
What right do you have to imprison Cai Hong. You are breaking the law.
You dare to talk to me about laws?
You keep up with them through your own methods.
What do you mean?
Still pretending?
Money, to you, is more important than life.
You are personally saying that I stole Ling Ling's money.
Where is the evidence?
I hold to it follow the law but
you just want to hide
Isn't that so?
Cut the crap.
Let's see how far he can get away.
Let's go.
Cai Hong. Have a good recovery. I will think of a way to visit you.
Jiang Yu, will never let this go.
Brother Shao Tian.
I will wait for you.
Da Chuen.
Mr Jiang. Why did you come?
I came to take a look.
Da Chuen.
Did Shao Tian notice any loopholes yesterday?
He definitely didn't.
Is there really anyone in this world who values money more than life?
This is impossible.
If one has no money but is still alive, he can still work. But if one is not alive...
what's the use of having money?
Sorry, Mr Jiang. I'm an unrefined person. I talk without thinking.
Please forgive me.
You are right. Zhou Shao Tian was definitely acting that day. Where did we go wrong?
Mr Jiang. What are you looking for? Let me help you to find it.
No need. I will do it on my own.
Okay.
Put it on for me.
You agreed?
Miss Wu. Does your wound still hurt?
No, thank you.
It's time for your medicines. This is for the fever and pain.
I have almost recovered. Can I be discharged?
You can't. Mr Jiang has instructed that you should stay here until you are fully recovered.
Nurse. I took a loan with high interest. They won't let me off.
I'm afraid that they will find my home. They will use cruel tactics. They will definitely not let my family off.
Please help me to check if I can go home.
Miss Wu. It's not that I don't want to help you. It's that you can't leave the hospital in your condition.
Our hospital is responsible for our patients.
Here, take your medicine first.
Miss Wu. This is the way. As long as you take your medicine regularly, you will recover faster from your wound.
Thank you, Nurse. I'm tired and would like to sleep.
Come. Let me help you.
Slowly.
Thanks.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
What are you doing here again? Looking for a beating?
Does this hospital belong to you?
Does this bench belong to you?
Can't I even take a seat?
What's wrong?
Young Master.
What are you up to?
I'm taking a seat. So what?
If Wu Cai Hong were to find out your true colour, what do you think she will do?
I was even almost tricked by you.
You are being too serious over a small bracelet.
Jiang Yu, with your crafty ways and the backing of the banks, try to catch me.
You captured Cai Hong.
If you dare harm Cai Hong,
I won't let you off.
Why won't you let me off?
You did a lot of unethical things. Who should be the one who shouldn't be left off?
Take your time sitting here.
I'm going to visit your girlfriend.
Wu Cai Hong.
What's wrong?
- Where is Cai Hong? - Are you blind? Why are you still asking?
Let me tell you, Jiang Yu. You are the cause of this. If anything were to happen to Cai Hong, I won't let you off.
Why don't you find her and you will know? Move aside.
You need to give me an explanation for this.
Stay far away from me. Let's go.
The one who should stay far away from me is you. Find her now.
Go. What are you still doing here? Look for her now.
Wu Cai Hong, come out!
Who are you? What are you doing?
We are looking for Wu Cai Hong.
- She is not in. - Not in?
She owes us money. Do you know that today is the deadline?
Who owes you money? Nonsense. Leave now.
Keep quiet.
Buddies.
Capture this young girl.
Sell her to the brothel.
Let me go. What are you doing?
- Let me go! - What are you doing?
I'm begging you to let me go.
- Mom! - Stop that.
- Cai Hong. - Sis.
- What are you doing? - Wu Cai Hong, you are back just in time.
I'm here to get back the money from you today.
Cai Hong, leave now. These people won't go easy on you. Leave now.
Leave? It's not that easy.
I was the one who borrowed the money.
If you want to kill or cut, do it to me. I would bear it all. Let go of my stepmom and my sister.
Fine. Buddies, let her go.
Sirs, let's do this.
Don't take away my daughter.
You can sell me. I'm not that bad.
I have been to the north and south and am a star. she is worldly and a good luck charm.
I'm not too bad.
Stepmom.
Kiddo, keep quiet when adults are talking.
Let me tell you. I'm not operating an old folk's home. I don't need an old hag like you.
Sir. You are wrong in saying this.
Move aside. Let's go.
Let me go. Let's talk.
Let's go.
Let go of my daughter.
Stop there. Let her go.
Let her go.
- Let her go. - Brother Shao Tian.
What are you bragging about? You want to return the loan on her behalf, right?
Do you have the ability to repay her loan?
Brother Zhou. Cai Hong took out a loan with high interest for you. If you are a man,
you would face these people without me having to tell you.
Zhou Shao Tian. Do you think I don't know who you are? Don't waste my time.
You still owe me the loan with interest. Pay back the loan immediately.
She is such a beautiful girl. If you want to see her again, I'm afraid you will have to go to the brothel.
You!
Brother Shao Tian, stop fighting.
I'm begging you. Let him go.
Scram!
Cai Hong.
Beat him.
- Brother Shao Tian. - Stop. The money that she owes...
Who do you think you are?
Stop.
What did you want to say just now? Speak.
I said that even if you beat me to death,
I can't pay back this loan.
Is that so?
Still pretending? You don't have the money and you are still pretending to be a Young Master?
Enough.
Stop beating him.
Jiang Yu, please help.
I'm begging you.
Still pretending? Are you going to pay back your loan?
I can save him but you must agree to my terms.
What terms?
Speak now.
I haven't thought of them yet. Agree first before I tell you.
Okay, I agree.
Who cares? What is the big deal.
Stop the beating.
How much does she owe you? What's the total?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Brother Shao Tian, are you okay?
I'm fine.
What did you want me to promise you?
Come back with me.
Why should I go back with you?
You just promised me that.
No.
Jiang Yu. I won't let Cai Hong leave with you.
That day, you clearly had the chance to help her
but you didn't. You already made your decision.
Cai Hong is a splendor woman, for that
you will only hinder her. ( hold her back)
Mom. How could you say this to Brother Shao Tian?
Brother Shao Tian. Don't worry about me.
I know what I should do. I will be fine.
No. You can't leave with him. He will harm you.
He won't harm me.
Let's leave.
Cai Hong! ♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
Zhou Shao Tian. Let's see how long you can hang on before you come and beg me.
You paid back my loan and even wanted me to accept your terms.
Speak. What are the terms?
Now you are so anxious to talk to me.
Even if you are evil and have harsh conditions, I will not be afraid of you.
Speak.
Sign the slave contract
and be a servant in our family.
I don't agree.
Do you have any other choice?
I just don't understand.
You paid off such a big loan, this could have bought you many servants.
Why me?
Because torturing you has become my greatest pleasure in life.
You are a pervert.
Check this over. If there are no problems, use your finger print to seal it.
It's three years. You will be free after three years.
It's only just three years.
As for the day you were hurt, the day Zhou Shao Tian would have confessed...
Who would have wanted the money instead of life?
Brother Shao Tian didn't do it. Why should he admit to it?
You're not the devil,
however, with a cut hand comes labor.
Even if you were a monster, I would not believe you.
If I'm a monster, you are a fool.
Think whatever you want. Return the bracelet to me.
Starting from now, you are Jiang family's servant.
Where are you going? Return the bracelet to me.
Brother, where did you go?
I have been waiting for you the whole afternoon.
Fei Fei. Send someone to pay back Wu Cai Hong's loan with interest.
Brother. Why are we helping her to pay off her debt?
Because she signed a three year contract with me as our servant.
Brother, we are not lacking in any servants.
Even more so, what can Wu Cai Hong do?
Enough. Go when I tell you to. I still have work to do.
Finishing cleaning, I'm exhausted.
Mom. I did the cleaning and not you. Why are you tired?
I'm tired just by seeing you hard at work.
Come on. Come on. Sit down. Sit down.
Mom. I was scared to death today.
Your sister is really soft-hearted. We were unable to help ourselves,
but in order to help Zhou Shao Tian, she went to ask for help from the loan sharks.
Those robbers didn't touch her.
Sister is still in the hospital. I'm going to deliver some food to her.
You don't need to worry about this. Jiang Yu is there. She won't starve.
Don't think that he is a cold and emotionless person on the exterior. I can tell that he's interested in your sister.
If not, why would he spend so much money on your sister? What's the problem with going through hardship with him?
Mom. I don't like you behaving this way. Brother Shao Tian and his family treat sister very well too.
I support Brother Shao Tian.
What do you know? He is different from the past now.
If your sister stays with that poor guy, she won't have any future.
Okay, I'm not going to argue with you anymore.
Even if I don't need to deliver any food to sister, I'm going to deliver a change of clothes to her.
By the way, when you go there, help to bathe your sister. It's not convenient for her as she is injured.
Remember to tell her that I miss her.
When she has a good life with Jiang Yu, don't let her forget me. Understand?
Mom. How could you be like this?
What's wrong with being a rich man who will let you eat, dress and live well?
So vulgar.
You!
You remember that.
The doctor says that your body is in good health. What is the problem?
Thus, he prescribed some sedatives.
-Let's take a break now. -Ok
They are now prescribing it.
I am a bit tired.
Also, I should take a break since I am tired.
The last time, you placed the lipstick in my bag and framed me for being a thief. Right?
Why are you saying that I framed you. If you stole,
why did the police catch you?
It was you who framed me. I have never seen anyone as bad as you.
You are the bad one instead. Your sister is a bad person too. Your entire family is bad.
You dare to scold my sister and my family? You are the bad person instead.
So what if I insult you. It's all because of your family's wrongdoing that karma got to you.
Who gives you the right to scold my family?
What's wrong with me scolding you?
- Fei Fei, keep calm. - What are you doing?
- Why are you pushing me? - So what if I pushed you?
- I will beat you. - You dare lay a hand on me?
Why does that sound like Cai Yun's voice?
It's Cai Yun's voice. Am I dreaming?
Let's talk in a civilised manner.
Why are you grasping my clothes?
Stop fighting.
- Who says you can hit me? - Stop fighting.
Let go now.
Mother.
Quick.
-Mother
Mother. Mother.
Fei Fei.
Mother.
Mother, wake up.
-Stop scaring me. -Why you?
Mom, wake up now.
Sister, she won't die, right? I didn't do this on purpose.
Cai Yun. Remember this. Don't say anything at all.
Doctor. Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor! Doc...
Doctor. Doctor!
Emergency Room
Fei Fei. How did this happen?
How could this happen?
I'm sorry. This is my fault. I'm sorry.
It was...
It was me. I pushed Madam Jiang down the stairs.
It was her.
She pushed Mom down the stairs.
Is this true?
Yes.
I fought with Fei Fei just now.
I lost my grip and pushed Madam Jiang down the stairs.
I didn't do this on purpose.
I'm really sorry.
Brother. Just now, Mom and I were walking to the porch to take a rest.
They both came over to cause trouble. They started the fight first
and pushed Mom down the stairs.
Blame me for not protecting Mom. If anything were to happen to her,
what would I do?
Let me ask you again.
What Fei Fei said,
is it the truth?
Yes.
I was the one who pushed Madam Jiang down the stairs but I didn't do it on purpose.
I...
I don't want to listen to your excuses. If anything were to happen to my Mom,
I won't let you off.
Doctor. How is my mother?
Mr Jiang, I'm sorry.
I prescribed whatever treatments I could for Madam Jiang
but she is still unconscious.
Madam Jiang could have a concussion and there are blood clots in her brain.
If the blood clots go down, she may regain her consciousness.
Maybe? What do you mean by that? When will my mother be conscious?
This will depend on God's will.
It may be a few days, months or forever.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
- Why? What did we do wrong?! - Let my sister go!
- Why did you harm my family?! - I'm sorry.
Your father already harmed my father. Why did you harm my mom?!
Why?! Why?!
Why? Why?!
- Keep calm. - Let me go.
You better pray to God that my mother will be fine.
If not...
Madam Jiang, I'm sorry that
this has happened.
I'm really very sad. We really didn't do it on purpose.
But I believe that good people will be rewarded.
God will favor you.
You will definitely wake up.
What are you doing?
Get out.
Wu Cai Hong, I don't want to see you again. Get lost now and stay far away from me.
Doctor, it has been a few days. Why is my mother not a little better?
In fact, Madan Jiang's condition has been improving.
Really?
A few days ago, Madam Jiang could not swallow,
take medication or eat.
This morning,
Madam Jiang already swallowed on her own eating liquid food.
These are signs of improvement.
When do you think my mother will be conscious?
Don't be anxious about this. I can't confirm when Madam Jiang will be conscious.
Half of this will depend on her self will, the other will be Heaven's will.
Mr Jiang. I invited you here to have a talk with you.
Based on Madam Jiang's current condition, I feel that she can be discharged from the hospital and seek treatment at home.
If she goes back to an environment where she is familiar with, this may help her in regaining her consciousness.
So, I can take my mother home?
Based on her current condition, she can seek treatments at home.
Of course, we will still conduct regular tests on her.
Thank you, Doctor.
What are you doing here?
I came here to see if Madam Jiang is conscious. Has she woke up?
My mom will be discharged from the hospital tomorrow. Pack your stuff and get ready to go to my home.
What?
Don't forget that you signed the slave contract.
If my mother remains unconscious, I will settle the score with your entire family.
- Sis. - Cai Yun, don't talk about this matter.
Cai Hong.
- Mom.- Mom.
You drag it to no end.
Cai Hong. You are going to the Jiang mansion, right?
I'm going there to be a maid.
Don't lie to me.
I can tell that Jiang Yu is interested in you.
This is a rare opportunity.
You must hold on tight to this opportunity. Understand?
I'm going to the Jiang mansion to be a maid because I signed a slave contract.
Do you think he will waste his money in repaying my debts?
You are really foolish. What do you mean by a slave contract?
This is only just an excuse.
Is the Jiang family lacking in staff?
Jiang Yu is using this excuse to keep you by his side so that he can see you every day.
What are you talking about?
Wu Cai Hong. You are really stupid.
You have a big fish like Jiang Yu
but you look for a small fry like Shao Tian instead.
People should have ambitions. Idiom: Man should seek his way up.
This is a good opportunity. Don't let it go.
Marry Jiang Yu, have a child and enjoy life.
Listen to your stepmother and don't be complacent.
I'm afraid that I will disappoint you.
This child is so disobedient.
This is the new servant. Her name is Wu Cai Hong.
I want to teach her the rules of the Jiang family first.
I called everyone here to give you a wake up call.
With the dedicated staff here, they can tell you that
you must listen and understand things.
Yes.
Mrs Zhang.
Use discipline.
Teach this wench a lesson. Give her twenty beatings first.
Yes.
It's not that easy to be a servant in the Jiang family.
You must remember what I say.
First, you must obey orders.
Second, you must be loyal. Third, you must abide by the law and behave yourself.
Fourth, our family is fair in measuring out rewards and punishments.
If you commit a mistake, you must willingly accept the punishment and not be angry.
Miss is letting out her temper on her.
What's wrong today?
Did she do something wrong?
Miss is even teaching her the rules herself.
I heard that she pushed Madam Jiang down the stairs at the hospital.
She caused Madam to be in a coma now.
No wonder, Miss is punishing her like this.
It seems to me that she wants her to pay with her life.
Did you remember what I said?
I'm asking you a question. Answer me.
Yes, I do.
Mrs Zhang. In the future, you must monitor Wu Cai Hong and teach her well.
Yes.
Young Master.
Everyone can leave now.
Yes.
Young Master Jiang.
I'm begging you. Let me take care of Madam.
Did I hear correctly?
Do you know who caused my mother to be in this state?
If you dare to go clear to my mother, I will never let you off.
You can give me a chance to redeem myself.
My mom, because of blood clots in her brain also,
was confined to a bed.
This type of condition, if you don't treat it carefully, one's health will deteriorate.
Master Jiang, I beg you.
Give me a chance to redeem myself. Let me take care of Madam.
I will do my very best to regain Madam's consciousness.
Don't pretend to be a good person in front of us. He will never trust you again.
If you don't agree, I will keep kneeling down here.
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Starting from today,
if you take one step away from my mother,
and my mother doesn't wake up, don't think you will have good days ahead.
I will take good care of Madam.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki