♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 15
Change into this and go out with me for a while.
I need to give Madam Jiang some porridge.
Just let your subordinate do it.
Aren't I one?
Are you arguing with me?
Then are you looking at me as a privileged lady?
Do you want me to personally help you change your clothes?
Where are we going?
To a business opening ceremony.
- What if Madam Jiang looks for me? - It will be very fast.
We will be back in the afternoon.
Miss. You look beautiful today.
When Young Master see's you, he will be very surprised.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
You look okay.
Let's go.
Miss. Don't be anxious. Young Master will definitely wait for you.
Get in the carriage.
Get in.
I will get in on my own.
Let's go.
Brother!
Miss, your earrings.
Mind your own business.
Miss.
Congratulations. This way, please.
This way.
Let's go.
- You are here too. - Yes, let's go in together.
Please go inside.
This way, please.
Miss. Please show your invitation.
-Invitation?  -Here.
She is with me.
Okay, please go in.
Thanks.
I don't understand the business here.
Why did you bring me here?
Didn't your father take you to such events?
He said that it was not suitable for women to attend this.
In the business field, everyone was two-faced to our family.
Brother Shao Tian was the one interested in these affairs.
My father hoped that he could hand over the business to Brother Shao Tian one day.
If your dad is watching over you, he would definitely be fuming with anger.
I don't like the way you talk about Brother Shao Tian.
Boss Jiang.
-You came. -Li Ting Zhang, you also came.
Who is the host today that was
able to invite Li Ting Zhang to come is an amazing feat.
Thank you. Look over there. Welcome.
Lu Man.
He wants to establish a dye factory too?
Yes, with that woman by his side.
A woman boss?
Buddy Jiang. Don't under estimate that woman.
After I received the message, she conducted an investigation.
She wanted to find out the origin of things.
Thanks.
She is his lover.
He gets information straight out of doing business in the textile industry. Business is good.
Huzhou dominates.
Since she has brought her business to Huzhou,
it seems others have become victims of her business.
You have met your rival.
If she is here to do honourable business, I will welcome her any time
but even if it's not so, don't worry.
With you here, who would she dare to do anything illegal in Huzhou?
You do not need to flatter me.
We are now starting.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Dear friends, people in the same industry and guests.
Today is the day that Rong Da starts operation.
I really appreciate everyone visiting today.
I am Lu Man who is just an ordinary girl.
For being able to open a dyeing factory in Huzhou,
I'm really grateful to a friend of mine.
After having this friend, I can lead a life of leisure.
I can now have tea at home, watch movies, go shopping and buy clothes.
Rong Da can earn me money while I am sitting at home.
The business dealings of Rong Da,
I let this friend of mine handle everything.
I would like to invite my secret friend up here now.
He is also our Manager at Rong Da. Please come up.
Welcome.
Today is the day Rong Da starts operating.
Rong Da is also now an important part of the Huzhou community.
We are glad you are gathered here for this ground breaking day.
It has special significance for you to be here.
I would like to share my happy event with everyone.
Thank you, everyone.
What's going on?
Looks like the missing money at Ling Long will show up soon.
I'm announcing the start of the ball now.
Excellent.
Let's dance.
Cai Hong. May I have this dance?
I think, at such an event today,
Mr Jiang won't be rude.
Don't be anxious.
How can she dance when she's holding a wine glass?
Go now.
Brother Shao Tian. What's going on?
Cai Hong. Don't be in disbelief.
What you are seeing is the truth.
Everything that I have done was to wait for such an opportunity
for the day when I can stand on equal terms with you
and dance with you.
Brother Shao Tian. What are you talking about?
We have always been on equal terms.
It's not the same. That was in the past and it's now.
It's who I am today that is worthy of you.
You have always been the same in my heart.
Thus,
I love you.
Cai Hong. Everything that I have done,
it's really all for you.
You want to dance, right? Let me dance with you.
Think I'm afraid of you?
You finally couldn't stop yourself. The money that you stole from Ling Long
you used it.
Didn't you hear that my boss is Miss Lu?
I'm the General Manager.
Even with this attitude, you say that you are not the boss.
Technically you are correct. Ms. Lu gifted me 3% percent of the shares.
Is there such a good thing on earth?
Who doesn't know that I helped Ling Long to make profits.
If not, Wu Hong Da wouldn't let me marry Cai Hong.
Do you think I'm her?
What's going on?
Wu Cai Hong. Let's go home.
When you were dancing with Brother Shao Tian, what were you both talking about?
What else could we be talking about? He has already switched sides.
Cai Hong.
Let me introduce you to the next ruling manager.
This is Miss Lu. She's also the boss of Rong Da.
This is my girlfriend, Wu Cai Hong.
Miss Wu. We have met in the past.
Hello, Miss Wu. My name is Lu Man.
How did you know my family name?
You are now managing Ling Long, Miss Wu Cai Hong.
I'm your loyal client of Ling Long.
Frankly. I have always wanted to establish a dye factory in Huzhou.
I just was never able to find a manager.
I heard that Mr. Zhou Shao Tian was your father's favorite.
It wasn't easy for me to get him to help me.
Thank you Ms. Lu for appreciating his talents.
Miss Wu. Don't say that. Without Mr Zhou
I wouldn't have been able to establish Rong Da.
Set your mind at ease. Because he shared his knowledge,
I'm giving him 3% of the shares.
Frankly, you don't need to tell me this. I don't really understand this business.
Miss Wu. You don't need to understand.
Rong Da has Miss Lu's capability and with my support,
it has Mr. Zhou's supervision
Let's work together to make it great.
Cai Hong.
Do you still have some other matters? I'm going to take your girlfriend
back to my home to look after my mother.
Cai Hong. I won't let you stay in the Jiang home for too long.
I will pick you up very soon.
The contract is signed for three years.
Do you understand what that means?
Close presence will have a real effect.
The contract that you signed with Miss Lu,
is bi-monthly. It is not the same type of contract.
Cai Hong.
You know that I am honest and open.
This is my contract with Miss Lu.
I will leave this with you.
I trust you. You don't need to do this.
Take this.
Trust me.
Do not listen to this villain's instigation.
Let's go.
Brother.
The opening ceremony...
why did you bring Wu Cai Hong there instead of me?
In the past, I blamed Wu Cai Hong wrongly.
I just wanted her to take a break from it.
It's not that simple as this, right?
I think you have been seduced by her.
Fei Fei. You are becoming more disrespectful.
It is not ladylike to say these things.
I originally was not a well-cultivated daughter of a rich family.
Now that a well-cultivated daughter of a rich family came
you are starting to complain about me, right?
But Brother, don't forget. It was her who caused the death of our father.
Even though you see her as delicate and ladylike.
Do you know the owner of Rong Da?
I'm not concerned about this.
Zhou Shao Tian is their General Manager.
There is definitely some problem with this. Investigate this for me.
Don't change the topic.
Today was the opening ceremony
and you brought Wu Cai Hong there.
You let her be by your side.
Do you know what this means? I think this is a major problem.
I have discussed this problem with you at length and I do not wish to speak about it anymore.
Brother. So that, you won't continue with this,
I will tell your mom about Wu Cai Hong's identity.
Stop there.
Mom's health just improved. You shouldn't provoke her.
Mom.
What's wrong?
Do you know who Wu Cai Hong is?
She is Cai Hong. Who else could she be?
I just fell and was unconscious for a few days.
Do you think I became foolish from sleeping too much?
- Mom. Frankly, Wu Cai Hong is... - Fei Fei.
Mom.
What's wrong with the both of you?
Fei Fei. You talked about Cai Hong just now. What's wrong with her?
She wanted to ask you about your fall at the hospital.
I was afraid that you wouldn't be happy, thus, I stopped her from asking you.
Don't talk about this again.
You were at fault at the hospital that day too.
Even more so, Cai Hong took care of me for many days.
When I was conscious, she apologized on her sister's behalf.
Fei Fei. Let bygones be bygones.
I get it. I will listen to Brother.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
What are you doing?
I prepared some fruits for Madam. She didn't have an appetite.
Have some.
Okay.
What are you still doing here? Go back to work.
You eat fast, you should slow down.
Young Master. Mr Shao Tian is outside asking to see you.
- I'm not seeing him. - Mr Shao Tian is not here alone.
He brought a lot of people and two crates. It's like a parade.
Let him in.
Cai Hong. That man is here again.
But he looks different this time.
- Who are you referring to? - It's that guy who was drunk that day and created a ruckus.
Subsequently, Miss got him beaten up.
Brother Shao Tian?
I really don't know what his name is
but this time, he's dressed a lot better.
They went into the yard looking important.
Miss.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to pay the debt.
A few days ago, my girlfriend ran into some difficulties.
You helped her to pay her debt.
I now can repay it even specifically two fold.
Hopefully Boss Jiang will have mercy
and let my girlfriend leave.
I'm not that great as you said.
Wu Cai Hong and I, one was the willing seller and the other was the willing buyer.
It was a mutual agreement.
Boss Jiang, let's not exchange words lightl
I'm here today to take Cai Hong away. Money is not the issue.
Name double, triple, or five times the price.
I'm not accepting the offer. We don't lack any money. Who cares how much money you have.
I have only two words. Not selling.
You have enough maids here.
Why are you insisting on not letting Wu Cai Hong go?
The debt is repayed.
It will be easier and more convenient for all of you.
Yes, you are right. Wu Cai Hong is my family's maid.
If I want her to stay, I will let her stay,
It's up to me when I will kick her out.
Can you control this?
You do not like drafts.
I did not know that real money was this important to Boss Jiang.
I brought this here with sincerity.
I hope that you will accept this.
Why didn't you bring me this money earlier?
You are here only just now?
You are too late. Let me repeat myself.
I'm not a good person except that I'm rich.
Take your valuables and
be good and get out of here now.
Don't let your mother worry about you. Be good.
This is not the first time I stepped through your main entrance.
I'm here today to take Wu Cai Hong with me.
I spoke nicely to you but you don't want to listen.
Do not eat anything and live as a monk.
Are you threatening me?
Did you think that by saying a few cruel words, I would be scared of you?
Aren't you going out now? Do you want to see the both of them
fight because of you?
Go and leave with your man to a far place and don't rely on this house for help.
Go now.
Cai Hong.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Trying to snatch her away?
What right do you have?
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Brother Shao Tian.
They are only here to carry the chests.
If you want to fight, let's meet on the outside of Warlord Lu's garrison.
I can always invite them in.
Huzhou has many things to buy and sell,
we should leave it to the police to handle this.
I personally do not want to call Department Director Li Li.
Fine.
Brother Shao Tian, Frankly,
I'm doing well here. It's not what you think.
Cai Hong, don't be foolish. You are like a lamb entering the door of a tiger. Don't you know this?
Don't let this family fool you.
It doesn't matter. He and I signed an agreement.
I volunteered my fingerprints. signed with my own will.
I really don't want to cause any trouble. Please help me this time.
Brother Shao Tian.
Can you guarantee that you will be safe here?
Okay, I will listen to you. I will go back first today
but I will definitely take you out from here.
Fei Fei, come out.
Send the guest off.
Mr Zhou, let's go.
Take care.
Mr Zhou, please take care.
Even though you have prospered
if you want to take away a member of the Jiang family,
it doesn't seem to be that easy.
Miss Fang. Earlier you said you were a member of the Jiang family.
Earlier this may have been true. However,
unless you marry Jiang Yu and become his wife,
why don't you tell the members of the Jiang family that you will forever be an outsider?
You are someone who can't even take away his girlfriend.
What right do you have to say this about me?
Yes. It's because I couldn't do this
that I need your help.
Why should I help you?
Because you will be helping yourself by helping me. We will both get our benefits.
What a joke. You are my brother's enemy.
If I help you, I will be betraying my brother.
Frankly, you have already helped me many times.
Every time when I couldn't find Cai Hong, you were the one who told me her whereabouts.
I know that there is only one reason.
It's because you don't want Jiang Yu and Cai Hong to be alone together.
Now that Cai Hong is already staying at the Jiang's home,
if you don't want to have any regrets, you should help me.
Then, what can I help you with this time?
The contract to let Cai Hong go, get it for me.
Impossible. I can't help you with this.
You can do it
unless you want Cai Hong to be the lady of the house.
When that time comes, I'm afraid that you will regret it.
Think carefully over what I said.
I believe you will help me.
What makes you so sure?
Because what I want is Wu Cai Hong. As for you,
what you want is Jiang Yu.
Are you angry that I didn't agree to Shao Tiao terms of exchange?
If not, you would have been free.
The contract I voluntarily signed.
I will take the consequences.
I won't be angry with you.
It's good that you think this way.
He suddenly brought so much money to buy you.
Don't you find it strange?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Brother.
Brother. Why didn't you allow Shao Tian
to take away Wu Cai Hong? His asking price was very high.
Do we lack money?
We do not lack money. You don't lack bristles. supplies
I just don't want him to take her away. Is there a problem?
Brother. Because of Wu Cai Hong,
are you not afraid of offending Warlord Lu?
I didn't do anything wrong. What should I be afraid of?
As you run this business, we want to run it harmoniously.
Even if you didn't do anything wrong, you can just randomly offend anyone.
Your play thing might offend Warlord Lu.
Is it worth it because of Wu Cai Hong?
Don't be afraid. I have my own methods.
I know that you have your own methods
but this is not your usual style of doing things.
In any case, you don't need to worry.
Our family doesn't lack any money. Who cares how much money you have.
I only have two words. Not selling.
Yes, you are right. Wu Cai Hong is my family's maid.
It's up to me whether she stays or I kick her out.
Can you control when I will kick her out?
Brother Shao Tian.
I'm doing well at the Jiang's home. Don't worry about me.
- Brother. - Ah Li. You are here just in time.
About Jiang Yu's father, Jiang Wen Yuan's case,
I found some of their staff during that year and asked them about this.
Jiang Wen Yuan collaborated with foreigners privately selling them opium.
After the incident, Jiang Wen Yuan died in fear of punishment.
Some people said that Jiang Wen Yuan was a kind man. He could have been framed.
And that year, the person in charge of investigating Jiang Wen Yuan's case was Wu Hong Da.
When Jiang Wen Yuan died, Wu Hong Da took over Ling Long.
Was Jiang Wen Yuan framed then?
Also, he and Wu Hong Da,
what was their relationship?
About this, the old staff of Ling Long are not very clear about this.
But I have asked several people. They said that Jiang Wen Yuan was a good man.
The older employees were consulted.
What do they know?
What we need most now
is to confirm the evidence.
I will continue to investigate thoroughly.
Only it has been a long time.
You have a wide range of experience being in the middle.
After all the experience ranges from the Qing Dynasty to the Republic of the Regime.
Finding it will be very difficult. We need time.
Ah Li. Send more help
and investigate this as soon as possible. This is very important.
I know. I will do it fast.
I'm leaving first.
Uncle Lai.
That man just now is Zhou Shao Tian's confidant.
Zhou Shao Tian seems to be investigating something.
Find someone to follow him and investigate this.
What is their close relationship?
By the way, keep a low profile.
Don't stir up anything.
Mr. Zhou. You have already looked at the house.
Other than the price being a bit expensive, there is nothing to be picky about.
But then again, the price is high.
There is a reason for it being expensive. Don't you think so?
You don't have to tell me about the benefits of this mansion.
I know this better than you.
You are right. I should never question the Master.
Of course, you are very familiar with this house but talking about this,
this Old Wu, not only does he look at the house and the person,
I heard he looks at the potential.
From the get-go Master Wu saw your potential.
Mr Zhou. You prospered on your own ability, right?
To add further, not everyone could afford to buy this mansion.
Since Mr. Zhou has money on his hands, you don't necessarily have to buy this house.
There are other mansions designed in Huzhou to do business.
If you are not happy, I will show you others. So how?
I want to reserve this.
Make an appointment with the owner now to discuss the price.
Mr. Zhou is a frank person. The price,
I already discussed with the existing owner of the house.
It's $1 million.
This price seems to be higher than the market rate.
But don't go to the trouble anymore.
Who told me to like this?
Mr Zhou. You are right. It's hard for this house to meet someone who likes it.
If you like it, then you should snatch it first. If not, someone else will take it.
To add further, everyone in Huzhou knows that
you have prospered. Don't even talk about this house.
You have the final say in the company, Rong Da.
Old Zhang. You don't need to flatter me. Let's do it fast.
Make an appointment with the owner of the house tomorrow.
Don't worry, I will do a good job.
Brother.
What's wrong? What's the matter?
Nothing. Can't I see you without any reason?
Okay, I have something to tell you.
Speak.
With Rong Da, you don't let me pay attention to Zhou Shao Tian anymore.
I didn't investigate the others yet but recently,
he planned to buy the Wu family's house. The deal is almost done.
Looks like this Zhou Shao Tian
really has deep feelings for Wu Cai Hong.
If not, he wouldn't use the money
to buy her previous house.
I think Wu Cai Hong also
has deep feelings for Shao Tian,
to become his wife.
This infatuation of love is in the wrong place when it comes to local business dealings.
Tell Wu Cai Hong to leave with me in an hour's time.
Where are you taking her? I want to go too.
Stay at home.
Where are you taking me again?
Don't ask anything. You will know later.
Come with me.
Wu Cai Hong. What Shao Tian said is right.
I will kick you out from the Jiang home as soon as possible.
Mr. Jiang.
Director Chen Suo.
Minister Lee explained everything to me.
It has been hard on you.
Where are we going?
I don't know what the schedule is for today either. I believe Mr Jiang has already made the arrangements.
Let's go.
- Mr Jiang, hello. - Boss Qian, hello.
What brings you here today? Is there anything you need, your wish is my command.
Please don't ever say this.
Director Chen Suo, you came with Boss Jiang.
What's the matter?
Since you have such a good relationship with Mr Jiang, I won't say much.
Mr Jiang, please.
Boss Qian, I would like to ask you.
Did Zhou Shao Tian borrow any money from you lately?
In the past, he borrowed $200,000 from me.
He only returned the money after a long period of time.
I dare not lend him any money again.
Thus, he has already returned fully what he has borrowed in the past?
Yes. Zhou Shao Tian could have prospered lately
after he became the General Manager of Rong Da.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki