♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 16
Zhou Shao Tian could have prospered recently
after becoming the General Manager of Rong Da.
He returned the money to me in less than two days.
So, you are sure that Zhou Shao Tian lately
didn't come here to borrow any money from you?
Yes. I haven't make a mistake regarding this.
In the past, he forced me to lend him money,
it was for desperate measures.
Didn't you suspect that Zhou Shao Tian stole your money?
Why are you checking on whether he has borrowed any money?
Don't be anxious first.
Record what Boss Qian just said
and let him sign the statement.
- Why are you doing this? - Just follow what I said.
Boss Qian, I will have to trouble you.
If Zhou Shao Tian were to look for you to borrow money again,
please notify me and Miss Wu immediately.
Okay, don't worry. I will.
-Boss Jiang, I bid you farewell. -Alright
Thank you, Boss. Let's go.
I won't be seeing you off.
Have a smooth journey.
We have traveled to all the banks in Huzhou.
Finally, we are at the last stop.
We are here.
Sir, please take care.
Director Chen Suo, much welcome. You took a long drive to visit.
- Please come in. - No need.
We are here today because Mr Jiang would like to ask you some questions. Just answer him.
Okay. Mr Jiang, please ask.
It's very simple. Please check for me if
Zhou Shao Tian came here to borrow money from you?
Zhou Shao Tian?
- Are you referring to Zhou Shao Tian from Rong Da? - Yes.
- He didn't come here. - Are you sure?
Definitely.
Boss Meng.
Please sign the statement here.
And also, if he comes here to borrow money from you,
- please let us know. -Okay, please wait.
Jiang Yu, we were busy all day long with Director Chen Suo.
Can you tell me what you are doing?
You only need to record the results today that
none of the money lenders gave any loans to Zhou Shao Tian.
You still suspect that Brother Shao Tian stole the money, right?
We need to establish the facts.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Please.
Young Master. Mr Zhang is here.
Old Zhang. You are here.
I heard that you are the broker for the Wu house.
I'm interested in it.
Sell it to me.
The cash is here.
This...
You didn't even look at it and you are giving me the money?
What is there to see? I don't need to see it.
Accept the money.
Mr Jiang. I can't accept this because before your offer,
I already promised this to a Mr Zhou.
He already saw the Wu house.
He's going to sign the contract tomorrow.
Rest assured, I have the names of other places.
I will take you to see them another day.
Didn't you just say that
you only made a verbal agreement with that Zhou guy?
I know the rules of selling a house too.
Whoever pays the cash first gets the house, right?
That's right.
The full cash is here.
I will be able to sign the contract with the owner tomorrow.
Cash in exchange for the contract.
What?
You don't trust my financial status?
I have complete confidence in your financial status.
It's just that regarding Mr Zhou,
I really don't know what to tell him.
Old Zhang. How could you be the broker?
You don't even know who you should sell the house to.
I already paid in cash. We can only blame that Zhou guy
for not having a destiny with that house.
To add further, regarding your verbal agreement,
who knows if there will be any changes tomorrow. Isn't that so?
Okay. You are both the buyers.
I can't afford to offend the both of you. Okay.
Since you have paid in cash first,
I can only say that you are destined to own that house.
This is the right way.
If that Zhou guy gives you a hard time tomorrow,
just tell him that I bought it.
Let's see if he dares to say anything.
Okay.
Keep the cash properly.
Thank you very much. Mr Jiang.
I will wait for you news tomorrow.
Hello.
Sorry, Mr Zhou. I'm late.
Where is the owner?
Mr Zhou.
I regret to inform you that the Wu house
has already been bought by Boss Jiang.
Boss Jiang? Which Boss Jiang?
Are you referring to Jiang Yu?
In the entire Huzhou, who can afford to buy the Wu house?
How many Jiangs would there be?
Old Zhang. We already agreed yesterday that
we would sign the contract today.
In a matter of a night,
you accepted someone else's cash
and sold the house.
I couldn't stop it.
You know the rich and powerful Boss Jiang.
He paid in cash yesterday.
According the the rules of the sales of houses,
whoever pays in cash first will get the house.
I can't do anything about this.
You couldn't do anything?
Jiang Yu's face has face.
Doesn't my face have any value either?
I didn't mean that. You are both rich.
I had a chance to do it. (sell)
To tell you the truth, Mr Jiang specifically asked me yesterday.
He wanted me to tell you that the house belongs to him.
Do you think he would give it up?
Return the money to him now.
Pay him back double.
Go and tell the owner of this house again that
I will give him another price.
This house...
I must have it.
Old Zhang.
Your way of doing business is not typical.
You clearly know that I like that house. So how?
- Are you trying to raise the price again? - No.
Mr Jiang. I don't mean that.
I just meant that,
I only get a small commission.
To add further, anyone can buy the house.
The sooner it's done, my business will conclude earlier.
Right?
Tell me.
- What's going on? - Don't you know that
this Mr Zhou is Zhou Shao Tian, the General Manager of Rong Da?
This week was the first time anyone was eyeing this place.
He is willing to pay double the price and refund your money.
It is forcing a bid for the price to buy the house.
The owner of the house will accept the highest offer.
Hence, I'm here today to discuss this with you.
Could you let Mr Zhou have the house?
This is the only reason? You should have told me earlier.
If it's because of money, I have the money and can offer a higher price too.
I like this house.
Why don't we do this, Old Zhang?
I can offer a higher price.
I recommend we take this out on the balcony.
Since Mr Zhou wants to fight with me over the Wu's house,
I suggest an open auction.
The highest bidder gets the house.
You are telling me this for what reason?
This house has been on sale for a long time.
He didn't want to buy it earlier and insisted on waiting for me to buy it first.
He counted his money after I made my offer.
Mr Zhou. I'm only just the runner.
If Mr Jiang is not willing to withdraw his money,
there is nothing I can do.
Old Zhang. What did I tell you?
This house,
I must buy it.
I can offer any amount of money.
How to buy it,
I will leave it to you.
Since this is the case,
where both of you want to buy it,
as fair competition, I will talk to the owner of the house.
Since you will engage in bidding,
you and Mr Jiang can bid for it at the highest price.
What do you think?
Public auction?
Did Jiang Yu give you this idea?
Mr Zhou is wise.
Fine.
I will play this game with him
till the end.
br
Brother. Everyone in the streets of Huzhou are saying that
you are doing this from anger that steams with Zhou Shao Tian.
They are betting that when you buy the Wu mansion,
you are doing it for Wu Cai Hong.
It's quite interesting.
Brother. What's going on?
You are really going to buy the Wu's house?
It can't be because of Wu Cai Hong.
I don't lack a house to live in. Why should I buy a house?
Why are you doing this then?
You can't tolerate unscrupulous businessmen and you don't like publicity.
Yet you are going to do a public auction.
What do you have up your sleeve?
Mom
It's here.
Come and take a look now.
Mom
Be careful.
Man Man. Why are you so careless? Are you okay?
I'm okay. As long as mom is here,
I'm not afraid of anything.
Xiao Man. You are such a good girl.
Mom, can you gift this to me?
Please, mom. Please, mom.
Fine. As long as you like it,
I will leave the best for you.
Thank you, mom. I love you so much, mom.
Who is it?
Miss. It's me.
Come in.
Miss.
What is it?
We already checked into that Ma Li person.
Zhou Shao Tian helped check.
When Jiang Yu's father, Jiang Wen Yuan was convicted, he committed suicide.
Zhou Shao Tian is wondering if Jiang Wen Yuan was wronged.
This didn't concern Wu Hong Da at all.
I get it. Send a few men
and follow Zhou Shao Tian and his henchman.
Miss. Are you interested in the grudges
between the Jiang and Wu families too?
I'm not interested in their grudges at all.
What I'm interested in is whether the Jiang family has the secret recipe.
I want to know
after Wu Hong Da died,
who is holding the secret recipe.
I wonder between Jiang Yu and Zhou Shao Tian,
which is richer?
I think it's Jiang Yu.
Zhou Shao Tian is a rising star
with sudden riches. Then he has money.
I don't think Zhou Shao Tian will win in the auction.
I heard he and Old Wu had history.
I heard that Zhou Shao Tian is the boyfriend of the eldest daughter of the Wu family.
He wants to win her love.
That is how he thought of this idea to buy back the Wu's house.
You don't understand this. Jiang Yu and Zhou Shao Tian
are level headed people. Would they fight over a house?
They are in the same industry. They are not just fighting over this house.
It's for business and to vent.
Everyone, we are starting.
Those who are with Zhou Shao Tian, leave your money on my left.
Those who are with Jiang Yu, leave your money on my right.
Grab this chance now. It's a 50-50 chance.
It's a rare opportunity in our village.
You have to spend money to make money.
Everyone. Let's ask Mr Jiang.
What amount are you willing to bid for the Wu mansion?
It's really just like what the rumours say. He's doing this to win Miss Wu's heart.
Mr Jiang. Do you need to win in this auction today?
- Just wait and see. - How long are you going to continue to compete with Mr Zhou?
Come. Please leave seats for them.
Old Zhang, it's not bad.
You got that many people within such a short period of time.
It's a small task.
Thank you Boss Jiang. In the future, if you need anything, let me know and your wish is my command.
Mr Jiang, Miss Wu. Please take a seat.
- Can we start now? - Yes.
Mr Zhou, what about you?
Dear everyone. Today, I am
commissioned by the owner to head up the auction of this location,
the Wu mansion.
As promised, I will introduce two guests to the auction.
One is the boss of Ling Long, Mr Jiang Yu.
Great.
The other is the General Manager of Rong Da, Mr Zhou Shao Tian.
Great, Mr Zhou.
Mr Zhou.
Our rules are very simple.
The two sides will take turns bidding.
We will wait for the highest bid
and he will then become the new owner of the Wu's house.
This auction will be done in cash,
and the agreement will be signed in public in a fair manner.
I will announce the start of the auction now.
The Wu house is starting at
$200,000.
Mr Jiang offered this price.
It was $100,000 two days ago.
$200,000 going once.
How much money is that?
$200,00 going twice.
Mr Zhou bid for $220,000.
$220,000?
$220,000 going once.
$220,000 going twice.
Mr Jiang offered $200,000.
He is going to raise the offer now.
$250,000.
It's now $250,000.
$250,000 going once.
Guess how much your Brother Shao Tian will spend.
Mr Jiang offered a new price just now. It's $250,000.
Where did Brother Shao Tian get that much money?
You can ask him later.
$250,000 going twice.
Mr Jiang offered $250,000.
Let's see whether Mr Zhou will raise the bid.
Mr Zhou raised the price to $260,000.
$260,000.
$300,000.
$260,000 going once.
Mr Jiang raised his price again.
Mr Jiang bid for $300,000.
It's $300,000.
$300,000 going once.
$300,000 going twice.
Great. Mr Zhou has raised a new price.
$310,000.
$350,000.
$310,000 going once. $310,000 going twice.
Mr Jiang latest bid is $350,000.
$350,000 going once.
Why did you raise the bid that high?
Don't worry. The price I bid for
is higher than Zhou Shao Tian absolute price. Just watch.
Is this the last offer?
He won't dare to counter-offer.
$350,000 going once.
What if he doesn't bid for it?
You should be concerned
about where
he got such a big sum of money from.
$350,000 going twice.
I don't think anyone will counter offer the price.
I think this will end soon.
How could they bid further?
Does Mr Zhou wants to raise the bid?
$400,000.
$400,000! Mr Zhou raised the bid to $400,000.
It's already reached an astronomical price.
Let's see if the bid can go above $400,000.
$400,000 going once.
$400, 000 going twice.
$480,000.
Mr Jiang raised the bid to $480,000.
The Wu's family starting price was from $200,000 to $480,000.
That's an astronomical price!
I wonder if this bid will be a new record.
$500,000.
The Wu's house is now worth $500,000.
It seems like Mr. Zhou is determined to win the Wu house
We have the honor of being in his presence.
This is a legendary moment.
I would like to ask Mr Jiang if he would like to raise the bid.
Or are you going this to start a new rumour again?
- Will this be a new record? - Raise the bid, Mr Jiang.
My money is on you. I can't lose.
If not, we will lose.
We will need to pay.
I'm announcing that Mr Jiang has given up on the bid.
He has given up.
Everyone. Please stay and witness the signing of the contract.
Let's congratulate Mr Zhou again.
Congratulations.
Mr Zhou.
Congratulations, Mr Zhou.
Mr Zhou, congratulations.
Let me make the introductions. This is the owner of the house.
Please hand in the money and sign the contract at the same time.
Once it's done, you are the owner of the Wu's house.
I have never seen this before.
Everyone, keep quiet for a moment.
I would like to take this opportunity to announce something.
I'm going to give away the Wu's house to someone sitting here.
Who is he giving it to?
Miss Wu Cai Hong.
It's Miss Wu.
Everyone heard this.
This house belongs to the Wu family in the first place.
And today, it's returned to its rightful owner.
I'm using this opportunity
to also tell her that
I, Zhou Shao Tian,
starting from today, I will do my best to protect her.
Cai Hong.
I have gotten your family's mansion back.
Where did you get such a big sum of money from?
I'm the General Manager of Rong Da.
Does the General Manger of Rong Da command such a high salary?
Don't try to lie to us.
Your contract is still with her.
I hold 30 percent of the shares in Rong Da.
You just started operations and you are already successful?
I borrowed money from the moneylenders. I will return the loan when I'm successful.
- Not from a bank. - Take a seat.
This
proves that you didn't take out any loans.
Why did you lie to me?
Did my father misjudge the wrong person? Did I too?
What's going on?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Mr Zhou.
Okay, you are still crying?
Isn't it good that you saw his true colours early
before things grew.
Perhaps, that money
was a loan taken out by Brother Zhou from the moneylenders.
Don't lie to yourself anymore.
If he managed to borrow that much money for the house,
would you need to leave Huzhou then?
Young Master. Zhou Shao Tian is here.
He said that it's urgent and he needs to see Miss Wu Cai Hong.
What's so good about seeing her except to listen to his conman stories?
Tell him to leave.
Perhaps, I should listen to his explanations.
Take everything into account
and think over it carefully.
In the past, when you went to check the accounts of Ling Long,
they were burnt. Other than yourself,
who else knew about this?
Fine. If you say that I burnt them. If I really wanted to burn them,
would I wait until that day?
Also, when you when to Old Cai's home,
in the end, you lost your way.
When you arrived, he and his wife already left.
Other than yourself, did you tell Zhou Shao Tian about it?
Brother Shao Tian and the carriage guy knew each other.
It was Zhou Shao Tian who intentionally let the carriage guy brought you there and lost the way.
This wasn't the case. When Fu Sheng started operations,
I met that carriage guy and found out
that he grew up with Brother Shao Tian.
When Brother Shao Tian started Fu Sheng, he asked him over to help him.
Regarding him taking me and losing the way,
Brother Shao Tian didn't know about it.
You believe such lies?
Think about it again. When I brought you to meet Old Cai's lover,
she also got killed in the end.
Other than you,
did Zhou Shao Tian know about this too?
- Sir, I would like to ask you... - You don't have the money, right? I'm not taking you.
Half of the fare? I will take you there.
I'm certain it is there.
The Cai family's home should be ahead.
Why do I feel that we are going the wrong way?
We have gone too far out of the way.
Cai Hong. Last night,
why were you with Jiang Yu?
Miss Wu.
Why is it you?
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian. He...
Do you know each other?
Mr Zhou. It's better that you leave. Miss Wu Cai Hong doesn't want to see you.
Tell me... is it that Cai Hong is not willing to see me
or Jiang Yu doesn't allow her to see me?
Mr Zhou. Please don't make it difficult for us.
I'm only relaying the message. Please go back.
♫ Once I thought to account for the end.♫
♫ I now no longer retreat.♫
♫ My heart is afraid to face it ♫
♫Not willing to compromise.♫
♫ After being hurt, if you cry ♫
♫Love will not be afraid. ♫
♫Suddenly, we all need to believe in fate. ♫
♫ Who are you to me? ♫
♫I am filled with sadness. ♫
♫ When you let go of my tightly clasped hand, ♫
♫my mind is in a lost state.♫
♫ Who are you to me?♫
♫Like a dream of flying free.♫
♫ The love you gave me was too beautiful ♫
♫I laugh in the memories.♫
Sweetness.
When your father passed away, the police took
all the ledgers that were sealed.
A few days ago, when the police delivered the ledgers
they were sealed in secret.
Do you know where he kept in the ledger?
No but I think that
since the police have concluded the investigation,
there shouldn't be any problems with the ledger.
Sure enough, this is not what I expected that
they went to Old Cai's hometown.
Brother Shao Tian, can you go with me when I leave today?
I'm afraid I can't today as I have made an appointment for my mother with the hospital.
She is sick. Why don't we go tomorrow?
It's only just a day's difference.
What Jiang Yu said is logical. Every time,
Brother Shao Tian always had an excuse to delay. Brother Shao Tian,
I don't know how to trust you.
Madam. This is a small gesture.
It's not small at all.
You are rich now. How could your gift be small?
Cai Yun. Brew the best tea for Brother Shao Tian now.
Brother Shao Tian, take a seat first. I'm going to brew tea for you.
Come, Shao Tian. Sit.
Sit down now.
A few days ago, at the auction,
you bought our home. I read it in the newspapers.
You are young and promising! Our Cai Hong
has good tastes for choosing you as her husband.
Madam. Thank you for your compliment.
If you don't mind, I will send someone to take you and Cai Yun there
to let you live at the Wu mansion as soon as possible.
Look at you. Seriously.
Why are you still calling me Madam? Call me Mother.
How distant. Quick, quick, quick.
Come, have your tea.
My husband really had good tastes.
He chose such a good son-in-law.
Cai Yun and I will benefit from your association.
Mom. I remember that in the past,
you didn't say this about Brother Shao Tian.
Child. Why are you butting in when adults are talking.
Go and play over there.
This child.
Madam, don't worry.
As long as I'm alive, I will let you and Cai Yun
live a good life like before.
As for Cai Hong and I, no one can come between us.
Who?
Who dares to stop you? Whoever dares to do that?
As her mother, I will be the first to dissent.
You and Cai Hong are the perfect couple! a talented scholar and a beautiful woman
Your relationship is so good.
As her mother, of course, I will use my hands
and also my legs to approve.
Since this is the case,
there is a favour I would like to ask from you.
You are going to be family soon.
Why are you still asking for favours?
Even if you have a hundred requests, I will agree.
I will thank you first then, Mother.
Sorry to disturb you.
I would like to ask if you are a maid for the Jiang family.
Yes.
What is it?
Could you please pass this to Wu Cai Hong?
- This... - Please.
This is from her sister.
Her mother is sick. She would like her to go home for a while.
Okay, I will help you with this.
Please accept this as a small gesture.
Tell her that her sister sent this.
Don't worry, I will remember this.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
- This is from your sister. - Thanks.
Please watch the fire for me. When the soup is ready, deliver this.
Where are you going?
I have some urgent matters. I'm going to ask Young Master for time off.
What's so urgent?
Someone delivered a note to say that my mother is sick.
I would like to take the day off to visit her.
Is it serious?
I'm not very clear about it either.
In any case, I don't have anything to do today. I will go back with you.
No need. I can go home alone.
What if you need to send her to the hospital or need medicine, do you have the money?
Cai Hong.
Why is it you? Where is my Mom and Cai Yun?
I sent men to take your mother and Cai Yun to the Wu's home.
But Cai Yun wrote to say that my mom is sick. What's wrong with her?
She is fine. I miss you. That's why I asked her for a favour.
You lied to me?
- I'm going to tell them. - Cai Hong.
- I don't want this money from an unknown source. - Don't leave. Listen to my explanation.
Let me go. I don't want to listen to your explanations.
I would like to listen to your explanations on where you got the money from.
Why are you everywhere?
Who are you to Wu Cai Hong?
Why should I explain it to you?
Brother Shao Tian, I'm asking you. The money you used to buy my family home,
did it belong to Ling Long?
Think carefully before you explain.
Once you start a lie, it will be the beginning of a thousand more lies.
I borrowed that money from Miss Lu Man.
Miss Lu Man lent you $500,000?
Why would she lend that to you?
The loan was part of my condition.
What condition?
Lu Man requested a very difficult thing.
It will be very risky to complete the task.
It may be at the expense of my life
but I already promised her.
What task is that which will require risking your life?
It's not very clear now. It seems to have something to do with General Lu Du.
It is a military secret.
Cai Hong.
Other than this life,
I don't have anything else.
If I lose you again,
will there be any more meaning in my life?
Being able to use my life to repay for the kindness of your family,
I think it's worth it.
Are you crazy?
What could be more important than life?
Wake up.
- You could even believe this? - I already signed a life and death contract with Lu Man.
Is your life and death contract similar to your contract as the General Manager?
A shake of a hand and you could get $1 million.
I have only one life.
But for Cai Hong,
I can do anything.
I don't want the house.
I want you to sell it and return the money to Lu Man.
It's already too late.
Don't listen to his nonsense. Let's go.
Cai Hong.
Trust me.
Brother Shao Tian.
I hope that your family and mine will be safe and live in peace.
Also, don't lie to me again.
I'm not lying.
Whether you want to accept the house or not, it's not important.
It's from my sincere heart.
Moreover, the Wu's house belongs to you in the first place.
Zhou Shao Tian.
Let's see how long you can last.
Do you believe what he just said?
I don't know but I really didn't need him to spend so much money
to buy back my family home.
I only hope that he has been sincere towards me
with his sincere feelings.
What Zhou Shao Tian just said,
I don't believe a single word of it.
But the truth is not that far away. I really want to see
how long he can last.
Boss. Do you remember this fountain pen?
Mr Jiang. How could I not remember? This is from my shop.
What's wrong? Is there any problems?
No. I would like to ask you.
Other than me, did you sell this fountain pen to anyone else?
No because this fountain pen is rare.
Do you remember when you first bought this fountain pen,
there was an extremely beautiful woman who wanted to buy it too. She was wiling to pay a higher price.
If I had the product, I would have sold it to her earlier.
Okay, I know.
Sorry, Mr Jiang. We don't sell this fountain pen in my shop.
Only rich and people with status could buy such a fountain pen.
They would have to order this from overseas
and use the local agent to deliver it here.
I would like to trouble you to check
the overseas address of this fountain pen.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki