♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 17
Wu Cai Hong.
Are you okay? Let me take a look.
I'm fine.
- Let me do it. - Don't tidy up.
Come here, quick.
Does it hurt?
Is it painful?
I'm fine.
You are still thinking about Zhou Shao Tian.
I don't know what his place in my heart is.
I remember when my father was alive,
our home was filled with visitors.
My father would always praise Brother Shao Tian,
but in my heart, he was just a good friend and like a brother.
When my father passed away, all my relatives and friends
pretended not to know me.
They ignored me too.
I only had Brother Shao Tian. No matter who abandoned us,
he would think of ways to help us.
At that time, I really didn't know what to do.
During that period of time,
if it wasn't for Brother Shao Tian, I don't know how we would have gotten through.
If Brother Shao Tian took the money from Ling Long
and killed my father, then, in this world,
I really don't know who to trust.
Sometimes, you need to face the truth.
By the way, why are you looking for me?
Have you ever seen Zhou Shao Tian's Parker fountain pen?
Why would Brother Shao Tian have a Parker fountain pen? What do you mean?
Never mind.
Mr Jiang. This is the oversea's address of the fountain pen that you wanted.
Thanks.
Don't mention it, Mr Jiang. If you need anything, please let us know. Our shop can also order goods for you.
No need for the time being.
Fei Fei, please see Boss Fu out.
- Okay. - Mr Jiang, I'm taking my leave first.
Bye.
- Hello. - I would like to trouble you.
Please send a telegram to this address.
Okay.
What is the message of the telegram?
Please keep it short.
Dear Sir or Madam. How are you?
I previously purchased a Parker fountain pen from you.
There is a problem with it now. May I ask if I can use the warranty for repairs?
- Is that all? - Yes.
Okay. Your name, please.
Zhou Shao Tian.
Why are you day dreaming in front of me instead of working?
I would like to take some time off to go out for a while.
Take time off?
Why are you taking time off when my brother has gone out?
Are you going for a rendezvous and are afraid that my brother will find out?
I will be back soon.
I hope that you never come back ever.
Okay, go.
I will take it as I didn't see this
but if my brother were to find out,
and he beats or scolds you, it's your problem then.
Thank you.
Hello, Miss Lu.
Miss Wu. What brings you here?
It's such a surprise. Come, take a seat.
No need.
I would like to ask you if Brother Shao Tian borrowed $500,000 from you.
Regarding this matter,
yes, he did.
He said that he used his life in exchange for it. Is this true?
How could you use someone's life in exchange?
I'm a business woman. There is nothing that can't be traded with business transactions.
What are you going to use Brother Shao Tian's life for?
I don't want Zhou Shao Tian's life but you should know that there is chaos in the military now.
There will always be someone who would trade his life for a task.
Where is he? I want to see him. We will return the money to you.
I'm afraid it's already too late.
He should already be on the way there.
Are you joking with me now?
What did you task him with?
Miss Wu. I think you already read the newspapers.
The Yao Jiangsu and Zhejiang War has already broken out. War between two providences.
The army and Shanghai's army are allies.
Shao Tian is taking cloth on through to the frontline
to give to the General in Shanghai.
Why did you send him there?
It's because this is a very important mission. He must not make a mistake. If he doesn't do it well,
Mr Zhou is an important part of the business.
Of course, a smart person will not go but there is no one as brave as Zhou Shao Tian.
Zhou Shao Tian is the most suitable person that I know.
Especially, when he needed a big sum of money to buy the house.
Who are you to him? It is like you forced him to go.
I really didn't force him. He went willingly.
He really wanted to buy the house back for you.
Instead you should thank me for helping him fulfill his wish.
I don't need the house.
I don't need him to risk his life either.
It's already too late now. The plan is at 12 noon. He should have already left.
Even if Zhou Shao Tian didn't tell you that he's going to the frontline,
it looks like he really loves you very much.
He only doesn't want you to worry.
Frankly, I did ask him why he wanted to buy the house.
He said that it was not just a house.
It contains all your childhood memories. It contains the memories of your mother and her garden.
Also, when he was nineteen years old,
he saw you for the first time. You were reading a book.
It's a pity that there aren't any men in this world who can help me to find my memories that I lost.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have come to this point.
Stepmom!
Coming.
What's going on? Why are you so anxious? Look at her.
Is Brother Shao Tian still here?
He left after he brought Cai Yun here.
Why would he be here?
Aren't he and his mother staying here?
Isn't he living with his mother at his house?
Why would he be living here?
Cai Hong. You just came back. Why are you leaving so soon?
Brother Shao Tian.
Coming.
- Aunt. - Miss Wu, what brings you here?
Is Brother Shao Tian in?
Miss Wu. Let's go in and talk.
Did Brother Shao Tian already leave?
He left about one and a half hour ago.
He said that he's going on a business trip and will be back in six months.
No need, Aunt.
Brother Shao Tian really left?
Why didn't he tell me?
He did so much for me and I didn't know anything about it.
Miss Wu. Please don't blame him.
He has been working night and day ever since he joined Rong Da just to give you a better life.
He didn't tell you about his business trip? It's probably that he's afraid you might worry.
I'm not blaming Brother Shao Tian.
I'm only blaming myself.
Brother Shao Tian is the General Manager of Rong Da
and you are still living here.
He helped me to buy back my home.
It's my fault.
I misjudged Brother Shao Tian.
Miss Wu, don't be sad over this.
Brother Shao Tian and I are used to living here.
He is very sincere about you and thinks on your behalf.
Frankly, I'm very happy.
I was afraid that he would still hold grudges in his heart.
Aunt, what do you mean?
I'm saying that I thought he was being good to you because you came from a rich family
but after having gone through this, I understand now.
Shao Tiao really likes you. I'm very happy.
Aunt, I will visit you another day. I'm going to find Brother Shao Tian.
Foolish child. Shao Tian already left one and a half hours ago.
He has already left the city gate. How are you going to find him?
Aunt, don't worry. Regardless of where he went, I will look for him.
Brother Shao Tian,
sorry.
It's my fault.
You treated me so well and I still suspected you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Why are you standing alone here?
Are you trying to slack off from work?
I made a mistake about Brother Shao Tian.
What did he tell you?
Lu Man lent him money. Brother Shao Tian went to Shanghai to give the General clothes.
but
he needs to deliver it through the Jiangsu and Zhejiang blockage. Battlefield
It will be very dangerous.
If Brother Shao Tian
gets into trouble...
My... my life will be condemned.
It's my fault.
I blamed him by mistake.
He has been totally sincere about me.
I heard that you didn't eat anything for the entire night.
Here.
Eat something now.
Thank you. I don't have an appetite.
Do you know that your form of self-abuse will cause my family problems?
Is he that important to you?
Mr Zhou. We will be able to reach your home in two or three days.
Row faster. It should take us about two days.
Boatman, can you speed up?
This is already very fast, Second Master. I'm more anxious than you. This place is very chaotic.
Bullets could fly past. If I didn't need to support my family, who would want to come here to do this business?
Look. Do you see any other boats here?
This place is very dangerous. Others wouldn't want to come here but why you?
Mr Zhou. I won't hide from you. No one wants to take on such a dangerous task
but I'm not doing this because they paid me double.
My mom is sick and she is waiting for my money to see the doctor.
I wonder if my mom is feeling better.
Take this money. The money that you received in double is not that much.
Use this money to take your mom to the doctor. Don't take on such a dangerous task in the future. Stay home and look after your mom.
Mr Zhou. I can't take this money.
Life is hard for everyone.
If it wasn't, you wouldn't be undertaking in this dangerous task either.
Listen to me. Take the money.
I'm also here because of someone very important.
Your parents are still alive. Grasp the opportunity to show filial piety (to them).
Don't regret it when they're gone.
You will suffer and regret it.
Wu Cai Hong. What do you want to do?
Brother Shao Tian must be lacking in food by now.
He could also be injured.
Why do you always expect the worst?
The day Brother Shao Tian lit up paper latterns,
why didn't I give him a chance to explain?
He waited for me the entire night that day.
At that time, was he in the same mood as I am now?
Listen carefully to me.
You are the servant of the Jiang family. I'm ordering you to eat, drink and sleep
and do your work properly.
Boatman, row faster.
Okay.
Let me take a look. Mr Zhou, you hand is injured.
I'm fine. Boatman, row faster!
- Quick. - Okay.
Miss. Zhou Shao Tian is back.
Did he complete his task?
Yes.
This Zhou Shao Tian didn't disappoint me.
Mr Wu is very satisfied, Miss. He said it went well during a critical time.
Where is Zhou Shao Tian? Why didn't he find me when he' returned?
He is injured.
Thus, I sent men to take him to the hospital.
Is his injury serious?
This won't do. Uncle Lai, get the rickshaw ready. I'm going to the hospital to see him.
Miss. Are you worried about Zhou Shao Tian?
I'm not worried about him.
If I retain this person, he will be able to do other tasks for me in the future.
Uncle Lai. Can you find someone to deliver a letter to Wu Cai Hong?
Since Zhou Shao Tian is in this condition,
I think he would want to see Wu Cai Hong very much.
He did such a big favour for me. I should be happy on his behalf.
Okay, I will do it immediately.
Shao Tian, how are you feeling?
I heard that you were injured and I rushed here.
Doctor, how is his injury?
Provide me with the best medicines. Don't cut any costs.
-Alright. Mr. Zhou's injuries are all exterior but it's a bit deep.
Also, he came a bit late.
But Miss Lu, don't worry. I gave the best medicines to Mr Zhou.
Thank you, Doctor.
Shao Tian, how are you feeling now? Does it still hurt?
You really helped me with a big task. I didn't misjudge you.
Looks like I should thank you well.
I'm going out first. Call me if there is anything.
Have a good rest.
- Thank you. - Thank you, Doctor.
Ms. Lu gave me such a big task. I practically lost my life.
I knew Manager Zhou is full of tricks so I knew you would make it.
Look, didn't you come back safe and sound?
I think you intentionally sent me to seek death.
If I died, you would have benefited the most. Rong Da would have belonged to you.
Who do you take me for?
I have no interest in your petty Rong Da.
What I want is Ling Long's secret formula.
Enough. Didn't you come back safely?
Moreover, your efforts were not wasted.
I already sent someone to ask Miss Wu to come here.
Your lover was crying as if the world had ended so of course, she will come.
Will Cai Hong really come?
She'll definitely come. You can count on it.
Not long after you left, she came to ask me if I really lent you the money.
What did you reply to her?
Of course, I said a lot of good things about you.
Talked about your love, even the gods would be shaking.
I have a good gut feeling about Cai Hong.
You don't need to tell me about your gut feelings.
Okay, I talked too much.
But this time,
you really escaped death.
One must not play with fate.
Was it worth it?
It's worth it as long as she's happy.
Brother Shao Tian.
Miss Lu.
Okay. Seeing that you are alive, I don't have to worry anymore.
I'm leaving first,
so as to not disturb you two.
Brother Shao Tian.
What's wrong with your hand?
Is it serious? Why are you in this condition?
You went to the frontline without even telling me.
Did you know that I was worried about you every day?
I was afraid that you would be hurt and wouldn't be able to eat properly. You are still smiling?
Can't you see that I'm fine?
Cai Hong, it's no big deal. Seriously.
Aren't I back now?
Let me ask you.
Do you still blame me?
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have suspected you.
I would like to apologise to you. Will you forgive me?
I don't blame you at all.
Being able to come back safely and see you, I'm already very happy.
Promise me then.
Promise me that you won't do such foolish things again.
It's not important whether I get back my home or not. I only want you to be safe.
I already lost my father.
I don't want to lose you either.
I promise you that I will never ever leave you.
Promise me too, okay?
Trust me.
We will forever be together.
I promise you.
The doctor told me just now that
I can be discharged early.
I will take you home.
You can really be discharged?
Of course, I can.
Think about it. My mom hasn't seen me for a long time. She must have missed me like crazy.
Moreover, if she sees me taking you home, she will be extremely happy.
I'm back.
Shao Tian is back?
Miss Wu is also here?
Shao Tian, what's wrong with you?
- It's nothing major. - Why are you injured?
Aren't I back safe and sound? Don't kick up a big fuss.
No. How could you be injured on a business trip?
Did you fight with someone?
I helped Rong Da send the General cloth. While traveling through the blockade, we were shot at.
Are you crazy? You want money instead of your life? It was such a dangerous task and you still dared to do it.
Aunt, please don't blame Brother Shao Tian.
He did this for me,
but he already promised me that he will never leave me again.
He also swore that he wouldn't do any more dangerous tasks in the future.
I already swore to Cai Hong that
I won't do any dangerous tasks again in the future.
But I did it for money this time.
It's so that you will have a daughter-in-law and grandchildren soon.
Really?
But my words don't count. Cai Hong still needs to nod her head.
Miss Wu. Will you nod your head or not?
Excellent.
I have been waiting for this day.
Stay here for a meal. I'm going to prepare it now.
Let's go in.
You don't need to see me off.
You are still injured. Stay home and have a good rest.
Look, my wrist's injury is not that bad. Let me take you home.
Brother Shao, don't worry.
I will come again if I have the time.
Okay, be careful on the way home.
Shao Tian. I can tell that Miss Wu is a good girl.
There are certain things that can't be bought in the world.
You must treasure her.
Sorry for coming back late.
Is Zhou Shao Tian back?
He went to the frontline to deliver cloth?
He did this to buy back my home. He almost lost his life.
I made a mistake about him.
Looks like his plan really worked.
You are not allowed to say that about Brother Shao Tian.
Also, stay out of my business.
I don't want anyone to ruin our relationship.
I really want to find out the truth.
I swear that I will not suspect Brother Shao Tian again.
I will believe every single word that he says.
I already told you not to get involved.
So what? Nothing comes out of doing good deeds, right?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
You are allowed to say that about Brother Shao Tian. Stay out of my business too.
I don't want anyone to ruin our relationship.
Brother.
What were you thinking about that caused you to look so captivated?
What's wrong?
This is for you.
It seems to be a telegram from overseas.
Dear Mr Zhou Shao Tian, the Parker pen that you bought from us on April 1923
is a luxurious item so it's under a lifetime guarantee.
If there are any issues, you can send the item back.
Brother. Isn't this telegram for Zhou Shao Tian?
Why is it addressed to you at this place?
Where are you going?
I'm going to find Brother Shao Tian. I already completed my tasks for today.
- Moreover, I already... - Fine, I will go with you to see him.
Even though I'm your maid, regarding the matters between Brother Shao Tian and I, you can't get involved.
Wait until you read this
and see if you still believe Brother Shao Tian.
But I won't look at it.
No matter what you say, I will always trust Brother Shao Tian.
He has another Parker pen from America after your father passed away.
Read it.
Leave this task to me.
I will order the same pen for your father's birthday.
It's a Parker pen.
Impossible.
Brother Shao Tian would never do this.
I'm going to ask him.
Coming.
Miss Wu.
- Aunt. - Young Master Shao?
- Aunt. - Why are the both of you together?
Is Brother Shao Tian in?
Please come in and talk about this.
It's like this. I have something important to ask Brother Shao Tian.
Shao Tian went out.
He has been nursing his injuries for half a month. If you didn't visit him often, he would have gone back to work.
He came back to say that he's leaving on a business trip and won't be back today.
Aunt.
I would like to know if Brother Shao Tian owns a Parker Pen.
Parker pen?
Yes.
It's exactly the same as this.
It seems so. Yes, I saw him bringing out a fountain pen.
He was very careful about it.
He ordered it from overseas.
Do you know roughly when?
Yes.
It was on the day when the incident happened to Old Master Wu.
I'm old.
I can't remember things
but it just so happens that it was on the day of your father's incident.
Thus, I could still remember it.
How could that be? Why would Brother Shao Tian own the same pen?
I'm going to ask him.
Miss Wu.
Young Master Jiang, what's going on?
What's wrong with Shao Tian?
Aunt. Regarding this, it's better that you ask him yourself.
When I was fifteen years old,
when my mother had a stroke, I was reading a book.
Even when her temperament wasn't good,
I would take care of her diligently every day.
I was afraid that every single word and action would make her angry.
No matter what, I would tread carefully around her
but she was still afraid that she would exhaust me.
She left me.
It wasn't easy for me to accept my mom's death.
Now, I need to face my father's death.
I don't know who harmed my father.
During that short period of time,
Brother Shao Tian was with me.
He comforted me.
I thought that I would be able to rely on him forever
but now, I suspect that Brother Shao Tian
is my father's killer.
I don't know why he did that.
There are certain things that will sound cruel when I speak about it, but I still think
you need to know. In fact, you should think seriously about it.
Do you really think that Zhou Shao Tian's life is worth that much money?
Was it really worth Miss Lu paying such a high price just to tell him to complete a mission?
Don't you find it very strange?
But if his money is from Ling Long,
it becomes a different matter of course.
You are too cruel!
Why do you want me to believe that the only person who I trust is the killer of my father?
I don't believe it.
Come in.
Director Chen Suo.
This is the reply from the overseas office of the Parker pen.
It clearly proves that
prior to Wu Hong's death, Zhou Shao Tian purchased a Parker pen and it
is exactly the same as mine.
This telegram contains really important information and it's compelling evidence.
Shi Jie. Since there is new evidence, do your best to break this case.
Give Mr Jiang and Miss Wu an explanation as soon as possible.
Yes.
Mr Jiang, Miss Wu, Director Chen will take care of the matter.
Don't be too anxious,
but Wu Hong Da's case was a long time ago.
The longer the timeframe, the higher possibility that someone tampered with the evidence.
To add further, his injury wasn't from a fountain pen.
A fountain pen doesn't prove that he committed a crime.
Miss Wu, me saying this is not me pushing the blame
on the relationship between you and Zhou Shao Tian. I will not give you the reason of the law to fight.
But don't you worry, the police will not let go of anyone. If it's really Zhou Shao Tian's doing,
he will be dealt with accordingly.
Okay, we know.
Shi Jie. - Superintendent Ting.
I will let you be responsible for this case.
If you face any difficulties, report to me and I will give you my utmost support.
I hope that you can break the case soon and give them an explanation.
Yes.
Cai Hong, don't worry.
I will definitely give your father in heaven an explanation.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki