♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 20
Brother, you caught a cold last night.
I cooked some ginger soup to toxify your body.
Drink more of this.
I don't want to drink it.
I already said that I don't want it.
I know that you find it hard to accept in your heart.
Letting go of your beloved one is very painful.
But if you fall in love with someone whom you shouldn't love, it will only bring more pain.
You need to balance things out.
As the head of the Jiang family, I would like to request that
for the sake of the Jiang family, for mother and my sake,
you must choose the right decision.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
This is Wu Cai Hong's slave contract.
Brother. I am doing this for your own good.
Jiang's Mansion
Young Master.
Come in.
Young Master... Miss, Mr Zhou and Miss Wu are waiting for you.
I get it.
Brother.
I know what I should do.
What's wrong?
Did my father
really do something wrong to the Jiang family?
What your father did to the Jiang family, it's not something that could be forgiven with a mere apology.
Everything you encountered now, compared to during that time,
is considered as a minor crime.
Wu Cai Hong, listen carefully.
Your father caused all the past hardships to the Jiang family.
Every dress that you wore, every meal that you had,
- everything that you used are stained with the blood of the Jiang family. - My father is not that kind of man.
Jiang Yu, tell me.
- Is what she said is true? - Everything that I have said is true.
The grudge that we had for your father started twelve years ago,
the need to support widows and children of Jiang family and to live under Lu's only power.
For twelve years we have thought about only one thing in the time of hardships.
Revenge.
Do you still need me to explain this further?
Acquiring Ling Long. Torturing you...
this was part of my brother and my plan.
We planned this for twelve years.
Swallowing Linglong and always finding a way to torture me...
Was it all for revenge?
Why did you help me to find out who the killer of my father was?
When I was depressed,
why did you take me to the pond to appreciate the lotus flowers?
You even risked your life to save me from the pond.
Was all that done for revenge?
What's wrong? You are still not giving up?
Do you think that by my brother did all this because his heart was moved by you?
Stop dreaming.
How could my brother have feelings for someone whom he holds a grudge against?
Brother, she wants to listen from you personally.
Tell her and let her give up now.
Listen carefully.
Everything that I had done was for revenge.
I caused you to misunderstand and you thought too much about it. Sorry.
Cai Hong.
Did you listen well?
If you did, get lost. Don't let us see you again.
Don't go overboard when you speak.
Cai Hong didn't do anything to harm your family.
I'm here today to let Cai Hong know about the truth.
In the future, if you do anything to harm Cai Hong again, I will never let you off.
Are you done talking?
If you are done, get lost.
Jiang Yu.
If you were doing this for revenge,
your tactics
were really excellent.
Cai Hong.
Everything is clear now. Let's go.
Brother.
Our grudges between the Jiang and Wu families are now in the past.
So, my father
was really the killer of Jiang Yu's father.
Cai Hong. It was a grudge during that era. It has nothing to do with you.
I'm my father's daughter.
I should pay his debts.
Cai Hong.
I let you know this not to cause you pain.
I deserved everything that Jiang Yu did to me.
Cai Hong. Regardless of whether you are Wu Hong Da's daughter or not,
what I did was to protect you.
Starting from today,
I won't let the Jiang family harm you again.
Let's go back.
Jiang Yu is really despicable.
Even if he has complaints against our family and we did something wrong to him,
he should state it clearly. How could he bully such a young girl?
He is not a man at all.
Don't you think so?
What Brother Shao Tian said were lies. I don't believe that father was a bad man.
Sis. Brother Shao Tian is joking with us, right?
Mom. Tell Brother Shao Tian that father was not that kind of man.
Stepmom.
Did you know about the incident twelve years ago?
Child.
How could I know about his work?
Regarding the opium investigation, it was a widely known incident.
Furthermore, Father was the main person in charge. How could you not know?
By the way, that's right...
talking about this, at that time, it seems like...
there was really opium.
At that time,
it was a hot topic in the streets.
What happened to the suspect?
I heard that he committed suicide.
What was his name?
It has been so many years. How could I still remember?
How did my father become the boss of Ling Long?
From that time onwards,
his luck turned around and our family became better.
it did not turned around. He became a ruthless predator.
Sis. How could this be possible? Was father really such a bad person?
You already read it. Dad wronged the Jiang family.
I don't believe it. Father was not a bad person.
He helped some orphans with their education and hospitalisation.
Everyone respected him.
You can't accuse him falsely.
If not, he won't die peacefully in...
Sorry. Cai Yun. I didn't do this on purpose.
I only wanted you to see the truth.
This is not the truth. Father was a good man.
- Listen to my explanation. - I don't want to. You are all talking nonsense.
Cai Yun!
I don't want to listen.
Cai Yun is still young.
She will be fine after a period of time.
My father was a supporter of the foreign efforts movement. He was a rich businessman.
but he was sabotaged by someone later and framed for
for housing opiates. This resulted in my father's death.
The reason that the court officials gave us was that he committed suicide.
When my father passed away,
the factory was confiscated. My house was occupied.
You could say that we went bankrupt overnight.
I kept asking God why he did this to me?
My parents are the nicest people in the world.
Why did they have to suffer all that?
Furthermore, those bad people could escape the law.
It was really a difficult period at that time
but I continue to hang on
because of revenge.
Listen carefully. Everything that I have done was for revenge.
I caused you to misunderstand and imagine too much. Sorry.
I finally understand
why Jiang Ju treated me that way.
Always a tyrant and so moody,
he even tormented me.
Taking into consideration the loss of Jiang family,
his torments to me are nothing.
Cai Hong.
You are too kind.
Moreover, the kindness of that generation had nothing to do with you.
How Jiang Yu treated you,
you can use revenge on him too.
With such a person like Jiang Yu,
you really should not be so kind- hearted.
What should I do then?
Don't tell me that I should be like Jiang Yu harbouring grudges
and let the next generation of the Jiang and Wu families forever harbour this grudge too?
I'm the daughter of a killer.
Even if he torments me,
I don't blame him.
You are really a foolish girl.
I am foolish.
That's why I was foolishly taken advantage by him.
I even harmed you.
Cai Hong.
Everything is already in the past.
Starting from today. I only want you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Mr Zhou. You are looking good today.
One look and I can tell that you have defeated your rival in love and got the fair lady.
Miss Lu. You are joking. It was fortunate that you helped.
Don't worry. I have started to investigate about the secret formula.
Mr Zhou. You are a very smart man. You already know what I want when I didn't even say anything yet.
I wouldn't dare to forget about what you wanted.
Please make it quick then. I have been waiting for that secret formula for more than ten years.
I'm curious about what the secret formula is that it has been committed in your memory.
Once you see this secret formula, you will be like me.
When I was young, I was fortunate to see the textile that was dyed by this secret formula.
It was extremely beautiful. After such a long time,
I can still remember it clearly.
As long as we use this secret formula to dye the textiles and release them into the market,
the big factories in this industry will go bankrupt immediately.
To say it in an extreme manner, whoever gets a hold of this secret formula
will be able to control the dyeing business in the whole nation.
Hence, this secret formula to me, no, to Rong Da,
is of great importance.
But there is something I don't understand.
You have a huge network.
Is there anything else in Huzhou that you are not capable of doing?
Why do you, just because of a minor secret formula,
waste so much energy on it?
You even specially instructed me to do it.
I'm afraid that you are the only person who can get this secret formula.
Thus, please find out immediately.
As to why, you will find out soon.
- Brother. - Enter.
Brother.
Fei Fei, accompany me on a tour of the workshop.
Also, tell the staff that we will have a meeting in one hour.
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
Brother. If you can't forget her,
you will only hurt deeper. Please forget her.
Let time heal your wounds.
Shao Tian, look at you.
You buy so much stuff every time you are here. Do you know how expensive these are?
Don't do this again. I won't be happy.
It's nothing much.
Madam Wu. Cai Yun is not in?
Of course, she's not at home. She has gone to school.
We are a republic country now. Girls should study more
so that they can marry into a good family.
I see.
Brother. Why don't I wait outside for you?
It's such a luxurious place here. I don't feel comfortable.
Cai Hong. Shao Tian is here. Come out now.
Cai Hong.
Come.
- Brother Shao Tian. - Did you have a good sleep last night?
She didn't. In the middle of the night,
I could hear her sighing from my room.
The incident happened so many years ago.
Let it go as it's already in the past.
Even if your father really did that,
he was only doing business. It's a free market in Huzhou.
Why do you keep throwing dirty water at your father?
This child.
I heard that Boss Wu has Jiang Wen Yuan's secret formula.
What secret formula? I have never heard of this.
I seem to have some impression.
That year, he held a piece of paper
like it was something very precious. He wouldn't take it to the factory either.
He hid it at home and wouldn't let me ask him about it.
Was there a special place for this secret formula?
I'm a housewife. I don't know much about this.
Moreover, it has been so many years, I have forgotten about it.
That's right. It has been so many years.
We don't even know where the secret formula is.
It seems like he kept this formula
in his safe.
But after the Wu family's business was acquired, I don't know where it went.
Brother Shao Tian. Why are you suddenly asking about this?
Shao Tian. Is that secret formula worth a lot of money?
Frankly, it's not that simple as it being worth a lot of money.
That's right. On the morning of his incident,
I saw him taking out a piece of paper from his safe.
I think it must have been that secret formula.
Cai Hong. When you last cleaned the safe, did you see it?
No. There were only documents like the house deeds in the safe.
It must be the secret formula that he took that day.
If the secret formula was in Boss Wu's hands,
why didn't the police find it when they were searching the place?
So to say, that killer took the secret formula from my father?
You may be right. The murder's motivation of going there could have been this.
There is only one person who knows that the secret formula was with your father.
Jiang Yu.
Do you have any evidence?
Shao Tian is right. Jiang Yu is your fathers' killer.
He was also the one who took the secret formula.
Forget it. You are still not feeling well. Let's not talk about this.
Let's go out for a walk. It will be good for your health.
I would like to take a walk alone and see if I can find a suitable job at the same time.
Cai Hong.
You don't want to be a lady of leisure and insist on working outside.
Aren't you making it difficult for yourself?
Frankly, it's not a bad idea. We are republic country now.
It's also right that Cai Hong wants to be a new generation woman with a career.
- I will go with you.  - You really don't need to.
Come home early then.
I'm really worried about this child.
I'm leaving, Boss.
Boss, sorry to disturb you. Do you need staff here?
We don't need any more staff. Go and look elsewhere.
Thank you.
Hello, Boss. Do you need any staff here?
No.
Sorry for your trouble then.
Boss. Do you need staff here?
You don't have to pay me first.
When you find that I'm suitable, you can pay me later.
This is not a problem of suitability.
Even if you are suitable, we can't afford to pay you.
Business is not doing well lately.
We are a small set up. We don't need many staff.
Why don't you try Ling Long or Rong Da?
I heard that these two big companies need staff.
I know. Thank you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Put me down.
Why are you shouting? So annoying.
Be careful.
The fourth clause in the Secretary's code is that regardless of whether the boss' order is right or not,
you must obey and do it immediately.
Eat this.
Are you okay? Let me take a look.
I'me fine. Let me do it alone.
Stop packing. Come.
Does it still hurt?
This Zhou Shao Tian really knows how to humour girls.
But it's a pity that
Unfortunately for him, rainbows only come after the rain.
Such a shady person like him, he will never be able to catch the rainbow.
Let's go.
Wait.
Jiang Yu. Wait!
Wait for me.
Stop the carriage.
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
On behalf of my father,
I wanted to apologise to you.
You don't need to apologise.
The grudge between our families has already ended.
Take her home.
In the future, don't come and look for me again.
Thanks.
If Jiang Yu really killed Hong Da,
he must have been discreetly at the scene
but he was not there.
The Police Chief Li Ting may be on good terms with Jiang Yu
but how such a man could go agains the palace order and
helped to be the witness for Jiang Yu.
Where is the loophole?
Reporting, Sir. General Manager Zhou of Rong Da is here to see you.
Invite him in.
This way, please.
Sit.
I came without any notice as I would like to invite you for a meal.
Drunken Fairy Restaurant's Drunken Chicken.
General Manager. Why do you suddenly want to invite me out to a meal?
You even know that I love to eat drunken chicken.
I came here without notice to seek your advice on a matter.
Regarding Wu Hong Da's case, I know that on the day of the incident,
you and Jiang Yu were having a meal at Drunken Fairy restaurant.
You ordered that signature dish, the drunken chicken.
Mr Zhou. Why are you suddenly so interested in this?
I won't hide this from you. Wu Cai Hong is my girlfriend.
Wu Hong Da was my boss for many years.
Thus, the Wu family's business is my business too.
General Manager Zhou. You are a person with heart.
Miss. Brother Shao Tian wanted me to bring you here. There is something he would like you to know.
What is it?
- Look where you are going. Look where you are going too.
- What's wrong with you? - What's wrong with you too? You knocked into me.
If you knock into her, why are you going to pay for it?
Teacher Yao.
You are here. Many of the customers in there
are waiting to eat your signature dish, the drunken chicken.
Teacher Yao, go now.
Tell him to wait. The chickens are still being done.
If they want to eat it, they can cook them at their kitchens.
Who is this guy?
Dear customers, please come inside.
Your chef is really interesting. What time is it now and he just reported for work?
He is not afraid that the customers will bang the tables?
What can we do. That Teacher Yao
is a famous chef in Huzhou.
He just likes to drink.
He would drink till he is totally smashed every day after work.
He would only report for work at noon.
Many of our customers here
would wait till noon
but the drunken chicken that Teacher Yao cooks
is really good. Whoever wants to copy him, they just can't do it.
So, we let him get his way.
Some customers are willing to wait for him.
Also, when I left that day, it just happened to be at noon.
I had an appointment for lunch later with Police Chief Li Ting.
Do you want to call him here for an investigation?
By the way, I would like to ask you something.
Do youperhaps remember whether on the day of the Wu Hongda's accident
Chief Police Li Ting and the new boss of Ling Long, Jiang Yu,
did they dine here?
I don't remember about that day
but regarding Police Chief Li Ting and Boss Jiang,
I can recognise them.
They are famous people in Huzhou.
They are our regular customers.
Especially, Police Chief Li Ting. Every time when he's here,
he orders our signature dish, the drunken chicken.
Thank you.
It's like this. When Jiang Yu was being investigated by the police on that day,
he said that he wasn't at the scene and the witness was you.
Thus, the police called and didn't dare to ask too much about it.
Although, I think that was strange.
Thus, I came here specially to seek your advice.
Yes. Jiang Yu and I dined here that day.
Furthermore, we ordered the drunken chicken.
Do you remember what time Jiang Yu arrived at the restaurant?
I really don't remember. I only remember it was around lunch time.
Do you stil remember
when they served the food?
I remember this because a few of our friends were dining together.
Jiang Yu was a bit late. When he arrived, he was hungry.
We felt bad for him and ordered more food for him.
At that time, when they served the drunken chicken,
he said that he didn't had any appetite and didn't order anything else.
- Hello. - Cai Hong.
- So how, Brother Shao Tian. - I have already confirmed it with Police Chief Li Ting.
The day of your father's incident, when Jiang Yu reached Drunken Fairy restaurant,
the drunken chicken that Police Chief ordered just arrived.
That is to say, it couldn't be earlier than 12:20 pm.
I remember when the incident happened to my father,
it was at noon.
The Jiang family's secret formula was in your father's hands.
It went missing when he died. As long as we can prove that Jiang Yu took it,
he is the killer of your father then.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
What are you doing here? Didn't I tell you
not to show up again?
Did you kill my father?
I won't seek for your forgiveness.
I'm begging you
to let my family off.
Sorry.
Shouldn't your father die?
He even did many unethical things.
Death's too good for people like him.
Jiang Yu. Why did you do that?
Why did you do that?
Why did you kill my father?
It's fine if you take revenge on me
but why did you do that?
I hate you. Return my father to me.
Return him to me. Jiang Yu, I hate you!
- Miss. - Let me go.
- Miss. - Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu, come back.
- Jiang Yu. - Miss, keep calm.
Jiang Yu, I hate you.
Miss.
Cai Hong.
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
Is it because of Jiang Yu?
Cai Hong. I would like to take you to a place
to see someone but you must promise me that
once you are there, you must listen to me and not say anything.
You will know once you have heard what's being said.
This way, please.
I came to disturb you without advance notice again.
I would like to ask you something.
Please ask.
I would like to know about the secret formula of the Jiang family.
This was my good friend who said nothing wrong.
- I got to know him a little.  - Excuse my interference.
That year, when Wu Hong Da wanted to get hold of the Jiang family's secret formula,
he harmed Jiang Wen Yuan.
That is most likely what happened
but when Old Master Jiang passed away,
they never saw the secret formula again.
After that mighty Jiang family declined.
Fortunately now the young Jiang master managed to buy back the house.
Didn't Jiang Yu learn the secret formula?
Young Master Jiang was still very young when his father passed away.
He wouldn't have passed on his secret formula to a kid.
To the Jiang tribe,
if he wanted to learn the secret formula, he would have to wait till he was an adult.
That was why the Jiang family could so casually
kick out Young Master Jiang from the family..
If they knew about the shrewd mind of Young Master Jiang then,
I believe they wouldn't have kicked him out that easily.
So to say, if Jiang Yu wants to get back the secret formula,
he could only find Wu Hong Da.
Yes. If I were Young Master Jiang,
I would ask Wu Hong Da to return the secret formula.
but I am afraid that Wu Hong Da wouldn't give it that easily to him.
Now that Wu Hong Da is dead,
I'm afraid that the secret formula has been lost.
♫ How am I to choose the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me.♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose the colour between you and me?♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, I keep everything inside without telling you.♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. Rest assured that I am also in love with you.♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫