♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 25
Why must you keep harming us?
Aren't you afraid of retribution?
- Sorry. - What's the use of apologising?
How is my brother?
The injuries are only superficial wounds.
Those people were set on harming him but not critically.
So to say, even though he has many wounds his life is not in danger.
He is already conscious. You can go in to see him but there shouldn't be too many visitors.
Doctor. I would like to know more about the injuries.
Fine. Come with me to my office.
What are you doing? Do you still have the face to see my brother?
- Fei Fei.  - How is your injury?
I'm fine.
Does it hurt very much?
How could they beat you into such a state?
Didn't they do this because of the secret formula?
It's because of the secret formula again.
Sorry, Brother. It's all my fault.
If I didn't take away the secret formula,
I wouldn't have caused you to be jailed.
This wouldn't have happened.
Sorry.
Fei Fei.
Don't blame yourself.
This is not your fault.
Listen to me. Everything was
planned by me.
What did you just say?
It started from the first day when they approached me for the silk contest.
I already knew what their motive was.
I made use of you to hand over the secret formula to them.
Sorry.
I used and tricked you.
That secret formula is fake.
Fei Fei. All these years, I know that you have been good to me.
Everything that you have done for my family,
I can see very clearly.
I remember it all.
I'm very thankful that during our most difficult times,
you have always been with us.
You will always be my sister.
I will always be your brother.
We will forever
be a family.
Fei Fei.
Do something for me.
Tell Wu Cai Hong to come in here.
Why do you still want to see her?
Be good.
Go now.
How is Jiang Yu? Is he okay?
Go in. He wants to see you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Sorry.
It's my fault.
You didn't kill my father.
What I can do for my father now
is to apologise.
And also for what I did in the past,
I would like to apologise to you.
You don't need to apologise to me.
I don't care about what you did. Also regarding your father,
I went to see him on the day he died.
When he found out about my identity, he kneeled down in front of me
to seek my forgiveness.
My father
really did that?
Did you forgive him then?
I'm not that magnanimous.
Even if your father knelt down in front of me forever, I wouldn't have been able to bring back my father.
But...
I didn't kill your father.
Today I have set myself as bait in this game.
The motive was to find our father's killer.
Regarding your father's death, I owe you an explanation.
I don't understand.
What is the meaning behind setting yourself as bait?
The truth about your father's death will be revealed soon.
When that day comes,
we will clear our debts and will be even.
Enough.
I have already said what I needed to say.
You can leave now.
Brother. What did you tell her?
Brother. Isn't this bitter for you?
Ever since Wu Hong Da harmed your father,
the fate was already decided between the both of you.
You and Wu Cai Hong
are like a bird in the sky and a fish in the water.
You will never be together.
Mr Jiang. I would like to talk to you.
Why is Mr Zhou so anxious to find me? What's the matter?
I don't know either. See for yourself and you will know.
I'm leaving.
Old Cai. I waited for you for a long time.
Come with me.
This is not a kind request. Lao Cai, you are the prime suspect in Wu Hong Da's case.
This is a warrant.
I would advise you not to rebel. Junior Superintendent.
Take him away.
Uncle Lai. Miss wanted us to follow Ma Li.
Ma Li may have stolen it. secret recipe
But now, the police are one step ahead of us.
How are we going to explain this to her when we get back?
How to explain it to her?
We can only tell her the truth. If not, why don't we snatch him from the police?
Based on my plan, I finally forced Old Cai to come out from hiding.
I say, Jiang Yu. Don't blame me for being angry with you.
Why didn't you tell me about this first before you took actions?
You're actions are desperate.
If anything should happen to you under the hands of my staff,
how could I make amends to you and what should I tell your family?
If I told you about my plan in advance, how would I be able to play the game?
If I didn't allow them to beat me half to death,
how would they have believed that the secret formula is not with me but with Old Cai instead?
Enough, buddy.
In any case, you risked your life for this.
No matter what, in the future, you must discuss it with me in advance.
Fine. Have some tea to cool down our temper.
Don't be like this.
If everything is going well and Old Cai has been captured,
we should be able to close the Wu Hong Da's case soon.
Don't worry. This afternoon, Director Chen will personally apprehend Old Cai.
I believe that this case can be closed soon.
Didn't you instruct these people to torment Jiang Yu? Did you do it?
Yes, I did it.
You answered very cleanly.
Do you know that by doing this, it's a crime?
When did you become so ruthless?
Cai Hong.
I don't believe that Jiang Yu is not the killer of your father.
I also don't believe that he didn't take the secret formula from your father.
I did this to force him to show his true colours so that you would know sooner.
You are talking too lightly about this.
You let those men beat Jiang Yu into that state.
Did you force the truth from him?
Cai Hong. I know that, in your heart,
you chose to believe Jiang Yu.
Thus, no matter what I do, you won't believe me.
I'm only stating facts.
Even if he really is a suspect,
he should be questioned by the police again first.
I would never use such a ruthless method.
Cai Hong, you are not stating facts.
You like him.
Do still remember that day
I heard you say those words
that you wanted to go back to the ways things were with your heart before.
You only had eyes for me. Trust me.
Don't forget that your father forced Jiang Yu's family to become bankrupt?
The feud between your both families gave him the motive to kill your father.
You are as far away from each other as heaven and earth.
Cai Hong, the more you tend to his heart, the more hurt you will be.
I don't want you to get hurt.
I want to protect you.
By doing this now,
you are only distancing yourself from me.
Second... Second Miss.
You are here.
I...
Are you here to see Brother Shao Tian?
Mom.
What's wrong with Xiao Bao? Is he asleep?
Hello, Madam Wu.
What are you doing here?
I heard that Brother Shao Tian came here to look for Miss Wu. I need to find him regarding some urgent matters.
Cai Hong, go and call Shao Tian.
Wait.
I will go and call him.
Go back to your room.
Look after Xiao Bai for me.
Are you cooking porridge for Jiang Yu?
Yes. Look at what you have done to him. I want to apologise on your behalf.
I don't want you to go.
Did you forget about the grudge between the two companies?
I remember Jiang Yu telling me this.
Hate does not necessarily end in hate.
Even in a dirty pond, a clean and pure flower could grow in it.
You are too naive.
Even though, from mud flowers can grow, there are still thorns.
The years of sowing the seeds of hatred is many.
Flowers with thorns won't only just hurt you.
I can't change what happened previously
but now if I don't work hard to try, how could I know?
You can't change the consequences.
Shao Tian, Cai Hong. Whats' wrong?
Aunt, it's nothing. We are only having different views.
By the way, Ma Li is looking for you. He said it's important. He's waiting for you at the front door.
I'm going to see him first.
Thanks, Aunt.
Listen to my advice. Our Wu family is not that glorious life before.
You should change your temper. Frankly, Shao Tian is not bad.
He is good at business.
Catch hold of this opportunity and your happiness. Understand?
I feel that we are not compatible.
Sometimes, I feel that he treats me too well.
The more he does this, I have more of a guilty conscious.
There are certain things that I can't express.
You only see yourself. Always such a stubborn temper.
Frankly, between men and women, it's that complicated.
It's simple. Take advantage of his youth and good looks.
Get married, have children and live a good life.
Isn't it that simple?
Frankly, men who have good qualifications
are slightly bad tempered.
But I can tell that Zhou Shao Tian is not really bad. He treats you well.
Don't spoil this opportunity and think about it first.
- Ma Li. - Brother.
What happened? Why did you come all the way here to find me?
Old Cai has been caught by the police.
Those little bastards are not capable of anything!
Come in.
- Are you being discharged? - What are you doing here?
I personally cooked this porridge.
I don't know if it suits your taste. Would you like to try it?
You are no longer our servant.
You don't need to do this.
I would like to this
to make amends for our past.
Didn't I already tell you very clearly?
You don't need to apologise again.
You don't even need to apologise to me because of your father.
But it's good that you are here.
I promised myself that I owe you an explanation regarding your father's death.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
To a show.
You can say that it's show because you'll regret if you don't watch it.
Old Cai. It really wasn't easy to find you.
We have been watching you for a long time.
Do you know why?
Director Chen. The police were looking for me?
Old Cai. You are a smart man.
I won't beat around the bush.
When you first stole Ling Long's money, you were discovered by Wu Hong Da.
You then killed him. Isn't that so?
Director Chen, this is arbitrary and
I didn't kill Old Master Wu or steal his money. How could there be such a misunderstanding?
Misunderstanding?
When Wu Hong Da died, you went missing.
Is this a misunderstanding?
Director Chen. The police should have evidence.
You can't say that just because I went missing,
I killed Old Master Wu and even stole his money. This is a major crime.
Don't talk about killing someone. I wouldn't even dare kill a chicken.
Old Cai, cut the crap.
After Wu Hong Da died, where did you go? Speak.
It's like this.
Before Old Master Wu's incident,
he had to borrow money to a company named Dachang Trading Company.
Subsequently, there was a problem with the company and he couldn't get back the money.
I was making good earnings at Ling Long just at this same time.
I was afraid that I couldn't explain. Thus, I left.
Based on what you said, you cleared all your responsibilities legally, right?
Yes. Wu Hong Da died.
Undoubtedly he deserved to die, right?
Chen Suo Chang, this matter affects me personally.
If there was anything wrong, as the main supervisor at Lin Ling,
I would have not risked my lord's health but called the police .
Do you think we will fall for your tricks?
- I... - As police, what we say is based on evidence.
Did you think that we would arrest you without any evidence?
This is what we investigated.
These are the transcripts.
Dah Chong Hong is a very small company
What a coincidence.
It is registered under the name of one of your relatives.
You have been with Wu Hong Da for many years.
You should be familiar with his signature.
Can you tell me
whether this is Wu Hong Da's signature?
Or did you find someone to forge it?
This already happened a long time ago.
Someone must be intentionally trying to frame me.
Yes, Lin Long borrowed a lot of money from Da Chang trading company.
It lost a big amount.
And for me, as the treasurer, I had been only monitoring it.
Also, when Old Master Wu passed away, I didn't stay back to clarify matters.
As it was my fault, I could have not done it.
I knew you would say this.
The evidence that you stole Ling Long's money is all here.
Don't even try to deny it.
If you cooprate with us and give out your accomplices,
perhaps, we may give you a lighter sentence.
I already said what I should say. I didn't commit any crime. I didn't have an accomplice.
Fine then.
I will give you some time to think about this carefully.
Take him away.
Cai Hong.
You heard everything.
His confession was very smooth.
Does that prove he's telling the truth?
He had to think about things from long ago. Everything came back to him.
Then what will we do if he strenghtens his defense?
It's okay. I will get the witness here next time
I will do it directly
and see how he denies it.
My father wronged your father
and the Jiang family.
It was also disastrous from my father's end.
Old Cai has been with us for several years.
My father regarded his as his right hand man. I never thought he would embezzle so much money.
Old Cai has been arrested.
We will soon get to the bottom of things.
Everything will then return to its original state.
Could everything return to its original state?
Can everything that has happened be forgotten?
Would you take it as it didn't happen?
Shao Tian. You must save me.
I'm here to tell you that
now that we are at this stage, you should know what you can say and shouldn't say.
Shao Tian, don't worry. I won't say anything.
I have already cleaned up my tracks.
Cleaned up your tracks?
You are too naive.
Now that it has come to this stage, do you think you can still clean up your tracks?
I...
Why?
Think about it. Ling Long lost such a big sum of money.
Wu Hong Da is also dead.
There is only one theory regarding this.
At this point you should disappear
since all the evidence points to you.
If you don't get caught, it will be considered very lucky for you.
But you don't have a good fate.
You are the only one who can bear the consequences.
You... You are adding insult to injury.
Old Cai. Take this fall.
I guarantee your wife and child's safety and will take care of them for the rest of their lives.
If you drag me down along with you, you should know the consequences.
Why don't you think about your wife and child?
After the testimony,
take care of yourself.
Brother, you should have your lunch.
What is this?
Porridge. Pour it away for me.
Pour it away?
Don't you love to eat porridge?
It's already cold. Pour it away.
Did Wu Cai Hong bring this?
Just pour it away when I tell you to.
I think I will throw it away as it is.
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
Go in.
Sit down.
Old Cai. We invited a few witnesses here today.
Director Chen. You didn't need to invite the witnesses here.
I was clueless in the past. I denied it. Now, I'm admitting my crime.
I stole Ling Long's money.
I used a relative's name to set up a fake company.
I then forged Old Master Wu's signature and transferred the money over.
Yesterday, if we were to beat you to death, you wouldn't admit it but you are suddenly confessing now?
Old Cai. What game are you playing?
I came to my senses after going through last night.
Since there are witnesses, I can't deny it anymore.
Why don't I confess instead?
Perhaps, based on my attitude,
you could give me a lighter sentence.
I get it.
You are taking the fall for your accomplice. That's why you are reversing your words.
I don't have an accomplice. I'm telling the truth.
Director Chen. I took Ling Long's money. Accept my confession.
Fine. Let's say that when you stole the money, Wu Hong Da discovered it
and you killed him to shut him up. Right?
I didn't.
- Director Chen, I swear that I didn't kill Old Master Wu. - Cut the crap.
I will ask you again. Was there an accomplice?
I already made a mistake by taking Ling Long's money.
I wouldn't dare to kill anyone, even more so, Old Master Wu.
I will give you one last chance. Did you have an accomplice?
You must know that covering up a crime is a very serious offence.
I really didn't have any accomplice. It's already hard enough to protect myself now.
If I really had an accomplice, I would cooperate with you and lighten my sentence.
Fine. Get him to sign the statement.
Take him out.
Do you think that Old Cai was speaking the truth?
Part of it was.
At the least, he hid the most important fact.
That is another accomplice.
Why do you think so?
His attitude was a complete turn around from yesterday.
It's too suspicious.
I think this matter is not that simple.
We will continue to investigate this.
I think, perhaps, you are thinking too much.
We already know that Old Cai took the money on the day of my father's incident.
It's just that we couldn't catch him.
Perhaps, he has thought it over carefully now
and thinks that he can't deny it any further. That's why he confessed.
- Did anyone visit Old Cai yesterday?  - Zhou Shao Tian visited him yesterday
I heard that Zhou Shao Tian visited you yesterday.
Him?
He did come to visit me yesterday.
He visited you yesterday and you confessed today. Why?
No.
He is the Wu family's future son-in-law. He came here to seek justice for Ling Long.
Seek justice for Ling Long? Did he want you to take the fall alone?
This is what you said, not me.
What did he use to threaten you?
Have you heard the term "murder for money?"
Do you think it's that simple for you to take the fall for this?
The police can use this to decide that you killed Wu Hong Da.
Killing a person is a life sentence.
Think carefully about this.
I admit that I was involved in it
but I really didn't kill him.
Mr Jiang. You must believe me. Tell the police that I really didn't kill anyone.
You were only an accessory?
That's right.
Who is your accomplice then?
Was it Zhou Shao Tian?
Don't pressure me.
Mr Jiang. I admit that I stole Ling Long's money but I'm not guilty of murder.
But if I say something that I shouldn't say, my wife and child will die.
I'm doomed.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Mr Jiang.
Why are you looking for me?
I think Old Cai suddenly confessing is very strange.
Thus, I went to the detention centre to have a chat with him.
Did you find anything new?
I found out the truth.
He is not the main culprit of stealing Ling Long's money.
He was only an accessory.
Okay then. Give me time and I will interrogate Old Cai immediately.
There is no use interrogating him now. He won't say anything.
Because the main culprit already has his family under control.
He is being threatened.
If this is the case, let's save Old Cai's family first.
If not, he won't dare to tell the truth.
I was tortured in the detention centre.
This proves that there are informants in the police station.
This was indeed negligence on my part
to let you suffer.
Sorry.
These informants are great for us.
They can help us.
Let's do this.
I will leak out the news tonight that Old Cai is willing to cooperate.
The condition is that we will save his family.
I will make preparations for my men to go to Old Cai's home to save his family.
As soon as the mastermind behind this gets wind of it, he will try to get to Old Chai's family first. As long as we track those people,
we will then find the location of Old Cai's home.
But Huzhou is so big. Who should we tail?
Zhou Shao Tian.
- Miss. - Why are you so flustered?
I received news that the police have gotten wind of where Old Cai's home is located.
They are going to save his family tonight.
Let's go.
The sky is going to fall soon. Mr Zhou, you still don't know?
What has happened?
My informant at the police station told me that...
What did he say?
Mr Zhou. Do you want to owe me another favour?
What I want,
- you already know, right? - Yes.
The secret formula. Moreover, I already promised you that
as long as I obtained the secret formula, I would deliver to to you immediately.
Miss Lu. You can speak now.
Old Cai voluntarily told the police his address.
He promised the police that as long as they save his family,
he would cooperate.
They are going to save Old Cai's family tonight.
This Old Cai...
is crap.
Miss Lu. Tell me what we should do.
If the police were to save them,
what should we do?
Of course, they won't be able to. You are so smart.
Even more so,
I already told you the news.
Remember this favour that you owe me.
Follow Zhou Shao Tian's henchman and bring Old Cai's family here.
Miss. Why are you doing this?
Of course, it's because of the secret formula that Old Cai is holding.
Once we get his family,
we will have more pieces to bargain with, right?
But Zhou Shao Tian already promised that
he would deliver the secret formula to you once he has gotten it.
Whether it falls into his hands or your hands, isn't it the same?
Of course, it's not.
Save yourself first before others.
Go now.
It's here.
Keep watch over here.
You... Get the child and come with me.
Get the child and come with me!
Quick.
There is someone there. Stop them now.
Go after them. Quick.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki