♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 29
Even if they suspect me, they can't find any evidence now.
Furthermore, I'm the Military Governor's woman.
For sure they don't have any evidence.
By the way, that rotten rascal Ma Li,
ever since we saved him from the police, he has gone missing.
I wonder where he is hiding.
The so-called strong dragon is hiding like a snake.
He grew up in Huzhou.
If he really wants to hide from us,
it will be really hard to flush him out.
Thankfully you were always wary of him, Miss.
Even if Zhou Shao Tian has his own men,
he wouldn't know about us.
Forget it. Let him go.
Let's use our energy to focus on the secret formula.
Miss. Where are you going?
I'm going to see the Military Governor.
I need to serve him well now.
I can't do anything about Police Chief Li now.
This is really hard on you.
What is there to suffer for?
Everything in this world is a transaction.
What I have left now
is just this body.
If I don't use my body as a transaction, what else can I use?
I'm useless.
Miss.
Uncle Lai. What are you saying?
Once I get the secret formula, we will leave for a far distant place.
And start anew.
Sit.
Go out first.
Zhou Shao Tian. Old Cai said that Wu Hong Da was on the phone.
He was going to meet an important client.
That's right. Wu Hong Da told me that he had a very important client that day.
At noon, all three of you weren't at the scene.
Thus, the fourth person that Wu Hong Da met
is very likely to be the killer.
Looking at this now, when Ling Long was facing problems,
and Jiang Yu was in a hurry to acquire Ling Long,
it's possible that person gave him a loan.
I remember that Lu Man visited Wu Hong Da to talk about a collaboration.
Accordingly to the Old Cao's testimony, he was kidnapped because of the secret recipe.
Moreover, it was a young woman.
Thus, I think that the last person to see Wu Hong Da, I'm eighty percent sure that
it was Lu Man. She has been eyeing the secret formula for a long time.
We can try to combine all pieces of evidence together
and create a false plan.
Lu Man went to find Wu Hong Da to get the secret formula but he gave the secret formula to Jiang Yu.
When Lu Man couldn't get the secret formula, she killed him.
She had motive
because she wanted to get the secret formula.
She is the Military Governor's concubine.
My father could have borrowed money from the Military Governor.
So he humbly asked iss Lu for help.
Lu Man killed my father.
Cai Hong, we need to uncover facts.
The way the police works is that we need evidence.
Even more so, since Lu Man is the Military Governor's woman,
before we have any concrete evidence, we must be careful.
Otherwise it will all come to naught.
Cai Hong. Old Cai's testimony already proved that Zhou Shao Tian didn't kill your father
but he embezzled money and faked the ledgers. This is a crime.
We can now sell Rong Da.
The returns from the sale and also the Wu Mansion, we will return them to you
to compensate for your losses.
Director Chen, something's not right.
Look at the deed for the Wu family's home. The name on it is Miss Wu Cai Hong
and not Zhou Shao Tian.
Also,
Rong Da's deed and all the assets
are also registered under MIss Wu Cai Hong's name.
So to say, everything that Zhou Shao Tian stole still belongs to Miss Wu?
Director Chen. It's all in black and white on the documents.
According to this document,
other than cash, Rong Da's assets and the Wu family's Mansion already belong to Miss Wu.
We don't need to settle this anymore.
I get it. You can leave first.
Yes.
Looks like your father didn't totally misjudge Zhou Shao Tian.
He was really sincere to you.
Based on the situation now, did Brother Shao Tian commit any crimes?
The courts still need to decide,
but I guess he could go to prison for a long period of time.
Director Chen. Please help me. I don't want Brother Shao Tian to go to jail.
You can't be emotional.
Zhou Shao Tian committed a crime. He needs to pay the price.
To add further, he's connected to your father's death.
Didn't you want to take revenge for your father?
It was retribution.
If it weren't for the revenge, Brother Shao Tian wouldn't have done all that.
He already returned the money to me.
Even more so, he took Ling Long's money to teach my father a lesson.
He wanted to let my father know what it felt to be penniless. He really didn't want to harm my father.
Furthermore, when my father passed away, he did everything to help my family.
I don't want to send such a kind man to jail.
Director Chen. Please help me.
Cai Hong. I have been a policeman for many years.
I have caught many criminals. Each of them had their own stories.
I always remind myself of this phrase.
Poor person is his own savior.
The law is to protect society.
To punish those who have committed crimes.
I'm a policeman. I can't teach you how to protect a criminal.
Sorry.
Director Chen.
There is really no way to help Brother Shao Tian?
I'm begging you. Please help him.
Director Chen.
I can only tell you that if no one reports this case,
there is no case then.
I get it.
I will withdraw the report for Brother Zhou Shao Tian. Thank you, Director Chen.
Wait a minute.
I hope that one day both your father and Zhao Shan will learn about your good intentions.
They definitely will.
I just talked to Director Chen.
I don't want Brother Shao Tian to be jailed. Thus, I'm going to sign an amicable agreement with him.
You are not even asking me why?
If you don't do this, you are the not the Wu Cai Hong I know.
He committed those crimes because of my father.
Thus, I don't blame him.
Furthermore, I want to do my best to help him.
Thank you, Jiang Yu.
Why are you thanking me?
Zhou Shao Tian owes your family the money. It's not even my money.
Then, can you give me the chance to make amends for my father's mistakes?
What era are we in now?
Is it still a trend for the daughter to pay back?
I have already gotten Ling Long's secret formula. You don't owe me anything.
Zhou Shao Tian.
Brother Shao Tian.
Are you okay?
Cai Hong. I did so many bad things to your family
and you are still helping me. You are too foolish.
Zhou Shou Tian, we already took Ling Long's money as evidence.
But now, I hope there is an out of court settlement and withdrawal your complaint.
Cai Hong. You don't need to do this for me.
I don't want you to go to jail.
Cai Hong.
I'm a criminal and I deserve it.
You don't need to plead on my behalf anymore.
I'm corrupted.
Even if I'm released, I would be unable to live a life out there.
Better to let me stay in prison. Let me stay here for the rest of my life.
It would be a relief.
Don't say this.
This was all my father's faults.
If it weren't for him,
your father wouldn't have died.
Cai Hong. If you both sign this amicable settlement, Zhou Shao Tian will be free.
Let me accept the punishment here.
Brother Shao Tian. I'm begging you.
Don't just give up like this. If you leave, you can start anew again.
Can I really start anew?
Just like when you first helped me, I will do my best to help you too.
They haven't found my father's killer yet.
I still need your help.
Zhou Shao Tian, Cai Hong's good intentions,
I would advise you to accept them.
When you get out, you can pay back Cai Hong and the Wu family.
It will be more meaningful for you than to stay here.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Mom.
Shao Tian.
You are home.
I'm home.
Do you know how worried I was about you?
Thanks, Mom.
Everyone was sure that I was the killer.
You were the only one who believed that I was innocent.
Foolish child.
I'm your mother.
No matter what happens, I will always believe you.
If you have not seek Cai Hong in time to tell her so,
I'm afraid that I would already have been executed.
Miss Wu already told you?
For the past few days,
I have been thinking a lot in the cell.
The threat of an impending death made me want to understand many things.
I didn't understand why when dad died,
you made such a decision.
Mom. I committed many mistakes in the past.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Shao Tian.
You are home.
I'm home.
It's good that you are home.
My Shao Tian has come home.
I'm home.
Let me take a look.
You have lost weight.
I'm fine.
You have suffered.
I'm fine, Mom.
Get up.
Come, sit.
Actually, I really didn't do anything
but you must not forget Miss Wu's great kindness.
I'm just afraid that
I will never be able to lift up my head in front of her again.
Don't think this way.
I can see that Miss Wu treats you very well.
But now,
the only thing that I can do now
is to do my best to help her find the killer of her father.
I won't disappoint her again.
Dear. With you watching over us, our daughter has retrieved Ling Long's money.
Ling Long's factory and the Wu Mansion
belong to us again.
Thank you God for protecting us.
Stepmom.
I would like to discuss something with you.
Cai Hong. Are you crazy?
Zhou Shao Tian is our family's enemy.
If he didn't betray Old Master and steal Ling Long's money,
Jiang Yu wouldn't have acquired Ling Long that easily.
Forget it that we didn't settle the score with him. He even gave Rong Da to him.
What are you thinking of?
In my opinion, Rong Da is not just a sum of money, but also a first class company with great equipment and dedicated workers.
What's most important is that it was due to Brother Shao Tian's hard work.
He stole it.
If he didn't steal Ling Long's money, with his poor state, how could he have set up Rong Da?
He stole Ling Long's money to take revenge against father. He really wasn't in it for the money.
Even more so when Father owes them a life. I want to use this redeem ourselves.
Brother Shao Tian knows about management.
In my opinion, no one is more suitable than him to run Rong Da.
How did Zhou Shao Tian charm you?
When he was doing well, you didn't want to be with him.
Not that he's broke and not worth anything,
you still sympathize with him and you even want to help him.
Do you want to marry him?
After having gone through so many events, it's impossible for the both of us.
Cai Yun. Don't just stand here and say nothing.
Rong Da belongs to the Wu family.
What are your views?
Sister is right. I will listen to her.
You!
I don't care. Even if the both of you can't manage the company,
we can still sell Rong Da.
Why should we give it to Zhou Shao Tian?
Mom. We are already very fortunate to have our home.
Even so, father snatched Ling Long away from the Jiang family.
I feel that Sister is right in doing this.
Just give in to Sister.
- Mom. - Stepmom.
Aunt.
Brother Shao Tian.
Cai Hong, you are here.
- Aunt. - Miss Wu.
- What are you doing? Get up. - Thank you.
Shao Tian and I should publish a notice of thanks.
Thank you for your kindness in saving him.
Thank you for signing an amicable settlement with him and giving him his freedom.
I will never be able to repay your kindness in this lifetime.
Aunt, get up first.
Get up first and we will talk.
When my family was in trouble, he has helped us a lot.
So, this is what I should do.
Cai Hong. Don't worry. I will find of a way to find your father's killer.
I will continue to investigate this.
But I'm here today to discuss something else with Brother Shao Tian.
Speak.
I have decided to let you manage Rong Da.
Miss Wu. We don't deserve this. You are already being extremely kind to forgive Shao Tian.
- With Rong Da, we cannot accept it. - Cai Hong, did you take into consideration that
but by doing this, don't you think it makes me very pitiful?
Brother Shao Tian. I made this decision after carefully considering this.
Rong Da is an exquisite and profitable company.
It's also part of Ling Long.
It's also my father's business.
You should know that Cai Yun and I doesn't know anything about management.
It will only go bankrupt in our hands.
Why don't we hand it over to someone who's experienced to manage it?
I believe that Rong Da will do well under your management.
Huzhou is such a big place.
I'm not the only know who knows about the dyeing industry.
But our Wu family only trusts you.
Your father's death was also caused by my father.
I hope that I can use it to redeem my family.
It's already in the past.
We have already clear this up.
Even more so,
I also wronged the Wu family.
That's because
you feel apologetic towards my family and Lin Long.
Thus, you should manage Rong Da well
and manage my father's business well.
Do you really want to me to manage Rong Da?
Yes.
Okay, I agree.
This is the authorization paper. Brother Shao Tian is the General Manager of Rong Da.
Also,
this bracelet,
I'm returning this to you.
As of now,
we don't owe each other anything else.
Cai Hong.
Is this the answer that you are giving me?
I remember you told me that
we can start anew.
Sorry.
You don't need to apologise to me.
You really don't need to.
This is fate.
I can only hate fate.
If I didn't have any grudges with your family, we wouldn't have come to this stage.
Brother Shao Tian.
This bad deed
met with a wrong opponent.
Thus,
everything was doomed.
As for happiness, it depends on the right time
and the right person.
It's Jiang Yu, right?
Brother Shao Tian. You will meet a better woman than me.
Cai Hong.
Whether you care or not,
whether you respond or not,
or whether you know or not,
that in this world,
there will always be someone watching over you.
Beatiful and bright rainbow,
appears only when the skies are no longer filled with rain.
No matter how, we will never be able to catch it.
Brother.
- Fei Fei. -I got good news.
Wu Cai Hong gave Rong Da to Zhou Shao Tian.
Looks like Wu Cai Hong loves Zhou Shao Tian very much.
Brother Zhou Shao Tian did so many things. She didn't even teach him a lesson.
That's because Wu Cai Hong is too kind.
Good always prevails against evil. We can only hope it can also ever come the hatred.
Brother.
Then... do you still like Wu Cai Hong?
Do you have any other matters?
If no, I'm going to work.
You are going to work now?
When you were injured and stayed in the hospital, you still went out with Cai Hong with your wounds.
I see you are quite bored recently.
Brother, until when are you going to act like this?
I already said many times.
I did this to find out who the killer of Wu Hong Da is.
Do you need to do this?
It has already been proven that you are not the killer.
Who the killer is, it doesn't concern us at all.
You are trying to help Wu Cai Hong to find the killer.
Frankly, you still want to be with her.
Are you done talking?
Miss, Director Chen is requesting to see you.
Director Chen?
Let him wait downstairs.
Yes.
- Miss Lu. - Director Chen.
I didn't notify you in advance. I hope that I didn't impose on you.
Talking about this, you did.
I have an appointment with the Military Governor.
If you insist that I don't go, I don't have a choice then.
Please sit.
Okay.
I wonder why you are here to see me.
Miss Lu. I have a few questions to consult you.
Please speak.
Regarding the previous owner, Wu Hong Da,
do you still remember him, Miss Lu?
Yes.
We investigated and heard that before the incident happened to Wu Hong Da,
you went to meet him.
Yes. At that time, I wanted to set up a dyeing factory in Huzhou.
Thus, I paid him a visit.
The first time was with my father, when I wanted to get acquainted with him.
And the second time was when I wanted to share something with Master Wu.
What's wrong with this?
Looks like Miss Lu is very interested in the secret formula.
I do want the secret formula but within Huzhou,
there are many others who want it too.
Director Chen. Think about this. If Wu Hong Da didn't have the secret formula,
first, I'm not short of money and contacts.
Why would I want to share it with him?
Then, on the day of Wu Hong Da's incident,
did you see him?
It was such a long time ago.,
How could I remember it?
Please try to remember.
It seems like I was with a friend that day.
Director Chen. Since you have the time, why don't you pay that friend of mine a visit?
He should be able to testify.
Listening to you, are you suspecting me?
Of course not.
We rely on evidence in our line of work.
I just want to clear every detail of this case.
By the way, Miss Lu, I would still like to ask you a question.
Wu Hong Da's staff, Old Cai, was kidnapped a few days ago.
It wasn't easy for us to save him.
In the end, he told me that the person who kidnapped him was a young woman.
She also kept asking about
- the secret formula... - Director Chen.
In Huzhou,
there are many young women.
If you came to question me based on a groundless rumour,
I feel it is a little bit inappropriate.
It was Zhou Shao Tian's man, Ma Li who told us that
he told you that the secret formula was with Old Cai's wife.
Yes. Ma Li did tell me.
I also used his tip to find Old Cai's wife
but Director Chen, I looked for his wife to buy the secret formula.
I didn't do anything else.
If this is the case, I can also prove that Jiang Yu went to find Old Cai's wife for the secret formula too.
Furthermore, the secret formula belongs to the Jiang family in the first place.
He would want the secret formula more than I do.
Is this how you conduct your case?
Director Chen. You said that you are not suspecting me
but to me it seems like you are investigating me undercover.
Sorry. I have an appointment with the Military Governor.
I won't be seeing you out.
Miss Lu. I'm only here today on official matters. If I have offended you, please accept my apologies.
Director Chen. I hope that you find concrete evidence first before you return here with official matters.
I'm not this patient all the time.
Uncle Lai, see the guest out.
This way, please.
Sister, what are you doing?
I am packing a milled powder.
- Are you having a fever? - It's not for me.
Is it Brother Shao Tian then?
No.
Sister, where are you going?
To the police station to check if there is any progress in the case. Be good and wait here for me.
Police station?
If she's not going with Brother Shao Tian,
she must be going with Jiang Yu.
Mr Jiang.
Uncle Lai. Prepare the rickshaw.
I'm going to see the Military Governor.
Miss.
Military Governor. What are you here?
Did you come to pick me up?
Who is so brave to make you so angry?
Chief Police Li just phoned me.
He said that Director Chen will be visiting you to have a talk.
I believe you already met Superintendent Chen.
I thought what could happen. It's just this small matter.
You are unhappy.
Is that so?
Human life is such a trivial issue, right?
Yet what else could be bigger than this?
Military Governor.
I have been framed.
I raised flowers to look at them.
I raised a dog out of boredom.
I raised you so that you can live well.
It's to make me happy
and not for you to give me trouble!
Military Governor. I was framed. I didn't do anything.
Don't be so anxious to explain yourself. I am a warlord.
Even dogs hide from me.
I would also never let anyone take advantage of me.
Moreover, you are better than a dog. At least you can talk.
But mark this.
If you give me any trouble and make me unhappy,
I will strangle you to death.
I understand. I won't give you any trouble.
I definitely won't give you any trouble.
I don't care whether you really did it or not.
Don't ever do it again.
I understand.
In the future, I will only make you happy and won't give you any trouble.
Don't be sad. I already talked to Chief Police Li.
If they don't have any real evidence, they won't dare to disturb you again.
I know that you still dote on me.
You said that
I'm better than a dog.
I will be better than a dog.
Do you know that?
Will I really know that?
Military Governor.
I made this drug accordingly to the Chinese medicine' recipe.
It will help the injuries to heal faster.
You can try this.
I'm not even a woman. How could I need to be so fair and clear.
Okay, thanks.
- What a coincidence. - It's a coincidence.
We are here to check if there is any new progress on the Wu Hong Da's case.
I understand this land belongs to Lu Man. So I came to see if I can provide some clues to the police.
Let's go.
I just went to visit Lu Man.
She admitted that she met Wu Hong Da.
She also admitted that she's interested in the secret formula.
Other than this,
we don't have any other leads.
People such as Lu Man are vicious like snakes and scorpions. Moreover, she is obsessed with the recipe.
It's eighty nine percent that she killed Boss Wu.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫