♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 31
On one hand, she cannot accept such brutal facts,
on the other hand, she feels guilty about the victims.
This was her father's fault. What has it to do with Cai Hong?
The Cai Hong that Cai Hong thinks,
it shows she is mature and considerate young lady.
But this young lady cannot shoulder all this burden alone.
Yu Er. You must be good to her in the future.
I know.
I wanted to confess to Madam today
about your family grudge, but I couldn't.
You are already very brave.
I'm really afraid that she won't forgive me.
Let it go.
If you tell the truth, it will be chaos.
It is better not to reopen old wounds.
It is better to keep silent about the truth.
Madam Jiang, let me serve you.
Cai Hong, just let the maids do this.
I already told Yu Er,
you went through so many hardships, you must be exhausted, mentally and physically .
Starting now, stay at our home and take a good break.
Madam, I have more things to do for you.
And maybe when I am occupied
I might think less about it.
Child. Don't keep the issues regarding your father in your heart.
You are still young. If you keep such things in your heart, you will grow even more depressed.
When my husband passed away, I kept thinking
until I was sick.
There were many times when I wanted to join him.
I hated all those ignorant people.
Hated them with all my might.
That hatred couldn't be forgotten.
That's the most stupid thing on earth one could do.
I know.
But some things one just cannot let go.
There is a no way to forget them.
Child. I have experienced how you feel.
That's why, I want to advise you.
Don't act like me. Such life will only trap you into the same tragedy.
- Madam. - What are you doing?
I do not want my life to be trapped inside the same tragedy.
So I want to atone for my father's sins.
Please teach me what I should do.
Child, I can understand your need for atoning for your father's sins.
But wouldn't it be better if we devise a good plan on how to do it first?
Come, get up now.
No, Madam. I need to beg you for forgiveness, beg you for mercy.
I'm willing to do anything for the Jiang family
to wash away my father's crimes.
Cai Hong. What are you talking about?
Madam. I...
My father is Wu Hong Da.
It was my father who wronged the Jiang family, you and Jiang Yu.
I'm willing to be your slave
as long as you are willing to forgive me.
What did you say?
Who was your father?
Get lost now!
You are Wu Hong Da's daughter. Get out now!
Wu Hong Da's daughter is here to harm us.
- Get lost? - I'm sorry. It's all our fault.
- She is Wu Hong Da's daughter. - Mom. What's wrong?
- Madam, I'm very sorry. - She is here to harm us.
Men! Take Madam to the hospital now!
I'm not going to the hospital. I want to stay here to protect Fei Fei and Yu Er.
- With me here... - I'm not going to the hospital.
- Are you happy now? - Don't be like this, Mom.
Tell her to get lost!
Men. Drag Wu Cai Hong out now!
- Madam. - Mom.
Madam, I'm sorry.
- Let's go. - Jiang Yu. Please tell Madam that I never wanted to harm her.
Leave now. Take her away!
Madam. I'm very sorry.
- Wu Hong Da's daughter. - Everything's fine, Mom.
Leave!
Please let me see Madam. I still have many things to tell her.
Just give up. Our Madam will never forgive you.
Miss already told us to tell you to stay far away from us.
Don't let the Jiang family see you again.
Don't shut the door.
Don't shut the door. Let me go in to see Madam Jiang.
Let me see Madam Jiang.
I don't believe it would just end like this.
In this world,
as long as there is a cause, there will be an effect.
As long as there is an effect, there must be a cause too.
If there is a sin, there must be a way to eliminate it.
Young Master.
- What's wrong? - Young Master.
Miss Cai Hong is crying and refuses to leave. She keep kneeling and bowing at the main door and seeks Madam's forgiveness..
Persuade her to leave.
Yes.
- Mom. - Is she okay?
I told you many times that
Madam Jiang must not suffer any trauma.
I gave her some sedatives. Her condition is stable now.
Let her rest and don't give her any more shocks.
- I know. - I'm leaving.
Thanks.
Yu Er. Is Wu Cai Hong really Wu Hong Da's daughter?
Who allowed her to enter the Jiang's home?
Mom. I remember you telling me that
the criminal was Wu Hong Da and not Wu Cai Hong. We must not pin her father's mistakes
on her head.
Mom.
You...
You already knew that she was Wu Hong Da's daughter.
Yu Er. Did you forget how your father died?
Did you forget the crimes that were committed towards the Jiang family?
How could you let a wolf into the house?
Wu Cai Hong is a good girl.
She didn't come here with an ulterior motive.
She only wanted to obtain your forgiveness.
I will never forgive her.
- Mom. - Cai Hong is innocent.
We can't continue our grudges into the next generation.
Mom. You are such a kind person. Why can't you forgive Wu Cai Hong?
There is no forgiveness for evil deeds.
What evil deed did she do?
She lost her parents and her family went bankrupt.
A well brought up lady came to work as a servant in our family
and suffered so many hardships and punishment. What was all that for?
It was so
we could forgive her.
Mom, I remember that
since childhood you always advised us to improve ourselves.
Wu Cai Hong came to redeem for her father's mistakes.
Is this wrong?
Brother. You are saying this
because you fell in love with Wu Cai Hong, right?
You fell in love with Wu Cai Hong?
You fell in love with Wu Hong Da's daughter?
When I didn't know that she was Wu Hong Da's daughter, I already fell in love with her.
When I found out later that
Wu Hong Da was her father,
I wanted to let go of this feeling...
but I couldn't do it.
- Mom. - Dear, I have wronged you.
How could we have such an unfilial son?
- What a misfortune.- Mother.
Is Wu Hong Da taking revenge on us again?
- Mom. - Don't call me Mom.
Go to your father's tablet now and reflect on yourself.
Starting from now, if you still dare to bring Wu Cai Hong here,
I will die in front of you.
Miss Cai Hong. Do you need to do this?
Young Master and Miss will never let you in.
Please let me in to see Madam Jiang. I really have a lot of things to tell her.
Please leave. Madam fell ill because of you.
Young Master is now kneeling down in front of his father's table to do self reflection. If you still don't leave,
you will really cause the entireJiang family to be in an uproar.
But this doesn't concern Jiang Yu. If Madam wants to punish anyone, she should punish me. Please help me
and let me seek forgiveness from Madam.
Leave now.
Leave.
Young Master, sorry. Madam has instructed this.
Dad, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have made Mom sick.
Please forgive me.
Dad, I'm sorry. I'm here today to tell you that
starting tomorrow, I have decided
to face my feelings.
I will not be a coward anymore.
Cai Hong knows very clearly the problems that we will be facing.
She is using her courage to redeem the grudges between the two families.
As for me,
I have always been running away from this.
I did it to deny my feelings
and intentionally hurt her.
I can't keep doing this.
I know very well that she is Wu Hong Da's daughter but she is a very good lady.
Your son likes Cai Hong very much.
I really want to be with her forever.
Dad. I promise you that
I will do my utmost best
and wait with Cai Hong for mother's blessing.
Dad, I hope that you will give me your support.
Mom, I know that your appetite is not good.
I instructed the kitchen to cook porridge for you. Have some.
When I think about my disobedient son, my appetite vanishes.
Mom. Everything is Wu Cai Hong's fault.
It has nothing to do with brother.
Please don't punish brother anymore.
Okay?
Fei Fei. You don't understand.
This love is just wishful thinking.
I won't let him rebel.
Anyway, I will definitely never forgive her.
Mom. Who says I don't understand?
But in this world, is there really such a wishful love?
- Miss. - What is it?
Everything has been prepared. When should we take action?
The police have been keeping watch on me.
The Military Governor is very concerned about his image. He's protecting me for the time being.
But I know that
he is already beginning to suspect me.
So many eyes are watching me.
It won't be easy to do it.
What should we do now?
No matter how bright the moon is, it will be still covered by darkness.
Let's take action tonight.
As long as I get ahold of the secret formula, I will never let them find me.
Yes. I will make the arrangement now.
Tell our men to watch Jiang's house. When the secret formula shows up again,
we must be the first ones to get it. Make sure that our tracks are covered.
I understand.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Cai Hong.
Are you doing well at the Jiang's home?
Did Fang Fei Fei and Madam Jiang give you a hard time?
Cai Hong, I can't be with you
but you must live well.
If you cry or are in pain
let my heart suffer first.
Fire!
Fire! Wake up!
Fire! Help us!
Fire! Take her out now!
Let's go.
- Come here, quick.
Mom.
Open the door.
Come out. Everyone in there, come out now.
- Where is Madam? - I don't know.
- Where is Madam? - She seems to be in there.
Over there.
Is anyone in there?
Men!
Is anyone here?
Madam, don't be afraid. Let's go.
Run now!
Let's go.
Madam. Don't be afraid.
Madam, quick.
- Quick! - Mom.
Mom.
Take her out now. Let's go.
Who isn't out here yet?
Where is Madam?
Mom, are you okay?
Where is Yu Er?
- Yu Er! - Mom.
Yu Er!
Jiang Yu!
Young Master is out!
- Brother. - Mom.- Is everyone okay?
Yu Er. Cai Hong went in to find you. Didn't you see her?
- Cai Hong. - Yu Er, it's too dangerous.
Fei Fei, take care of Mom.
Brother, don't go. It's dangerous.
Jiang Yu.
Cai Hong!
Cai Hong.
- Why isn't Young Master out yet? - Did something happen to him?
What should we do? The fire is so big.
Young Master.
Young Master is out.
- Young Master. - That's great. Young Master is finally out.
Yu Er, are you okay?
- Are you okay? - I'm fine. Take Cai Hong to the hospital now.
Quick.
Cai Hong.
Cai Hong, wake up.
There are still many things I haven't told you.
Hurry up.
Cai Hong.
Hurry up!
God, I don't know what your plans are
but I'm willing to use my life to pray to you.
Let Cai Hong be safe.
Give half of my life to her.
I want to grow old and die together with her.
Brother.
Brother, are you okay?
Yu Er. How is Cai Hong?
She is still in there.
Mom, are you okay?
Let the doctor run tests on you now.
- Go now. - Young Master, you should go too.
Don't worry about me now.
Take my mom there first. Go now.
Yu Er. Cai Hong will be fine, right?
Brother, don't worry too much.
Heaven helps good people. She will be fine.
Yes, I know.
Enough, take mom there now.
Go now.
Doctor, what is the situation?
Miss Wu's injuries are not serious. We have already applied medicine to her wounds,
- but... - But what?
She inhaled a lot of smoke during the fire which caused asphyxia. She has not awakened yet.
We can't confirm if there is any damage to her brain.
What do you mean?
If there is no brain damage due to the lack of oxygen, she could wake up at any time,
but if she has brain damage,
perhaps, she may never regain consciousness.
Mr Jiang. Currently, this is only what we can do.
That's to leave it to God. What we can only do is to wait.
Please keep calm.
Cai Hong.
How is she?
Doctor said she has asphyxia and that she cannot wake up.
Cai Hong.
Wasn't she at your home?
How did this happen?
Cai Hong.
Sister. Wake up.
Talk to me, sister.
Cai Hong. Nothing must happen to you.
If anything were to happen to you, how am I to explain to your father?
Sister.
Jiang Yu. What's going on?
Didn't you say that your home was safe?
- Didn't you say that you wouldn't hurt her? - I'm sorry.
Why is your entire family fine except her?
You bastard!
Brother Shao Tian, don't do this.
Tell me!
Are you dumb!
I'm warning you. If anything serious happens to her,
I will never let you off!
Enough!
Stop fighting!
Jiang Yu. What are you still doing here?
Get lost!
I'm warning you. If anything happens to Cai Hong,
I will never let the Jiang family have any peace!
Get lost!
She is still not conscious?
How could this happen?
They said she inhaled a lot of smoke and that her brain might has suffered from lack of oxygen.
Oh my god.
How could this happen?
Dear.
I really can't forgive Wu Hong Da
but Cai Hong is a good girl.
I pray that she will wake up soon.
Dear, help her from heaven.
Mom.
How many such containers did you find?
We already found four filled up with petrol.
It's very obvious that someone started the fire.
Furthermore, it was an inside job.
Call all the staff of the Jiang family. Don't miss a single one.
Yes.
- Where is the secret formula? - Jiang Yu didn't take the secret formula at all.
I really didn't get the secret formula. Uncle Lai, please believe me. I really didn't get it.
- You really didn't? - I really didn't. Please believe me.
You can search me.
It has been hard on you then.
I really didn't get it.
- Get up now. - Mom.
Stop there!
Mom.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Fu Ching.
Mom.
Take Xiao Ge with you now.
Come.
Mom.
Let's leave now.
Let's leave now, Ge Ge.
Don't!
Miss! Miss!
Enter.
Miss. Did you dream of Fu Ching again?
How is the Jiang family?
Wu Cai Hong was badly injured and hovers between life and death.
As for the rest, they are okay.
Looks like this time,
we have to add another murder to our list to get the recipe.
Jiang Yu will not escape so easily again.
Miss. You must find the secret formula.
You must start anew
and create our flag dress.
Find a way to find someone
to kidnap Madam Jiang.
I want to use Madam Jiang to threaten Jiang Yu.
Yes.
I already know what you did.
Why are you so foolish?
Risking your own life for a dead man's tablet.
Look at the state you are in now.
Cai Hong. Do you know that
when you let go of my hand
and wanted to go to the Jiang family as a servant,
I knew that Jiang Yu had a place in your heart.
But do know that
in my heart,
your life is more important than mine?
You must wake up.
You must get well.
You haven't eaten anything today.
I brought your favourite food. Have more of these.
I'm not hungry.
Brother, don't be like this.
Looking at how you are,
I find it very hard to accept it.
Tell me why Cai Hong hasn't still regained her consciousness.
Brother, don't worry too much about it.
Cai Hong is a good girl.
God will definitely take care of her.
She may wake up tomorrow.
Yes.
She will definitely wake up.
She definitely will.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫