♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 32
Little Friend, why are you here crying alone?
- What's wrong? - My favourite fish has left.
If you liked it why didn't you keep it with you?
Why did you release it?
Sister. I actually reared two fish.
But one died today.
I let the other fish go. I won't be able to see it again. I'm very sad.
But if that fish died, I would be even sadder.
Mom said that I must release that fish into the pond
and let it go free. The fish will be happy and it won't die.
Yes.
When you love someone, you should let that person go and be happy.
It's fine as long as he's happy.
Sister. You are sad too. Isn't that so?
Just like when I released that fish, I'm very sad too.
I will never see that fish again
but this is for the good of the fish. That's why I did this.
Thank you, baby. You are very smart.
I understand now.
If Wu Cai Hong is brother's happiness,
then, as long as brother is happy,
I'm willing to pray that she will wake soon.
I'm willing to let go of my hatred and envy.
I'm willing to accept her.
Cai Hong!
Cai Hong.
I finally found you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Cai Hong. You must wake up.
Cai Yun, your stepmom and I
and also Jiang Yu,
we are all waiting for you.
Brother Shao Tian.
It has been hard for you to take care of my sister the whole night.
Let me take care of my sister during the day.
Go back and take a rest now.
Fine. I will leave your sister to you.
What are you still doing here?
- I want to see Cai Hong. - Is there a need for you to?
- Let me see her. - Haven't you harm her enough?
Jiang Yu. When Cai Hong followed you,
she suffered a lot and received many punishments.
Because of your father's tablet, she sacrificed her life for it.
I know about the grudge between both your families
but it was Wu Hong Da's fault. It has nothing to do with Cai Hong.
I know I was wrong.
I know that Cai Hong's stepmom and sister will listen to you.
I'm begging you.
Please tell them and let me see her.
Cai Yun. Come out first.
I'm letting you in
not because you want to see her.
It's because I know that
Cai Hong wants to see you.
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
He has a strikingly beautiful face, a Grecian nose, strong brows, and bright eyed
with an uncommon demeanor.
No matter how you look at him, he is smothering to look at, a handsome man.
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫ - Let me go. - I won't.
♫ I didn't see through to ♫ I'm not letting you go. What will you do?
♫ your eyes or heart ♫ Jiang Yu!
♫ but I've already fallen in love ♫
♫ with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
I'm here to see you.
Why are you so foolish?
I never even had the courage to face my feelings. I don't deserve you being so good to me.
Cai Hong. Do you know that I have many things to tell you?
You can listen carefully to me today.
Frankly, the first time I met you at the hospital,
I knew that I fell in love with you
but
you were the daughter of my enemy.
I later worked hard to tell myself that
I would forget that I like you.
I did many things to forget you.
To remind myself that I couldn't fall in love with you.
But when love happens, it happens.
No matter how I tried to escape,
no matter how I lied to myself,
love is just like wild grass.
Cai Hong, I told myself that
starting from now.
I won't escape again.
I want to be like you
and face it bravely.
Cai Hong.
You must give me the chance to pay you back.
You must give me the chance to dote on you.
You must wake up.
Cai Hong. Jiang Yu sent you these flowers to wake you up.
Roses are the flower given to describe love.
That is really true.
The beautiful flower and its thorns
Love with injury.
I know you want to escape the despair,
that is why you escape into your dream
and don't want to wake up.
But Cai Hong,
looking at how much pain you are in,
what should I do?
Brother Shao Tian.
Cai Hong, you are awake.
The flowers are very beautiful.
I seem to have slept for a very long time.
I even dreamt that someone was calling me.
Was it you?
You really slept for a long time
but you finally woke up.
This is great.
Are these roses
from you?
Jiang Yu sent them.
Was he hurt?
How is he?
Jiang Yu is fine.
What about Madam Jiang?
Madam Jiang is fine too.
What about Old Master Jiang's tablet?
Old Master's tablet is fine.
The whole Jiang family is fine except you.
Why are you so foolish?
Now you are in this situation.
Brother Shao Tian. Can you tell Madam Jiang
and also Jiang Yu that I have woken up?
Tell them not to worry about me.
I will have to visit them at the Jiang house then.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Cai Hong. It's definitely good news that you are awake.
I'm going to call the doctor to check on you now.
I'm here to tell you that
Cai Hong has regained her consciousness.
Jiang Yu.
I hope that you have thought it over carefully
and thought about your family's problems again before you see her.
I don't want to see her hurt again
because of you.
What Cai Hong did,
Mom was very touched.
It's just that the past has hurt her a lot.
Thus, she still can't accept her.
I understand.
Brother, after all this, do you still intend to contin to suppress your feelings?
Each of you are both in pain.
Don't misunderstand.
I'm not persuading you to give up this time.
I only wanted to tell you that if you think Cai Hong is your happiness,
you should go after your happiness.
I'm willing to accept her as my sister-in-law.
Fei Fei.
Thank you for being able to accept Cai Hong.
Is my acceptance that important to you?
Of course, it's important.
You are my sister.
Your acceptance is not only important to me,
it is very important to Cai Hong also.
Thank you for regarding me as your sister.
Starting today, I will work hard to be your younger sister.
Okay.
Actually, before this incident happened to Cai Hong,
I already decided that
I must confront my love with Cai Hong.
I already told Dad that
Cai Hong and I will be filial to Mom.
I used the emotional aspects as an excuse. It was cowardly,
but I have already thought it through.
I will tell Cai Hong about my sincerity.
Don't worry and go. I will take care of Mom.
Okay.
Stop there.
Yu Er. Kneel down.
Since Wu Hong Da's daughter has regained her consciousness,
your relationship should end now.
Today, I want you to swear in front of your father's tablet
that starting from today, you and Wu Cai Hong will sever ties.
Mom, sorry. I can't promise you this.
You!
- Mom. - Mom.
- Are you okay? - Go away.
Mom, are you okay?
Mom.
When the incident happened to Cai Hong,
I swore that
whether she regained her consciousness or not,
I would protect her.
I won't let her get hurt again.
You.
You stood in front of your father's tablet
and said that you wouldn't hurt Wu Hong Da's daughter?
Aren't you afraid of hurting me?
You are not afraid that you have wronged you father in heaven?
Mom. Do you think that I'm not in pain?
Did you think that I didn't think about you and father's feelings?
It was my inner struggle and me repressing and resisting my own feelings
that led to so many unfortunate things happening to Cai Hong.
What mistakes did Cai Hong commit?
Her only mistake was that she was Wu Hong Da's daughter.
She can't choose her parents.
Furthermore, she is already willing to.
Her father committed wrong
and she used her life to redeem it. Isn't this enough?
If Cai Hong died in the fire,
would we really be at peace?
Yu Er, do you really think that your mother has such a cold heart?
But you must think about it.
If you want to be together with Wu Hong Da's daughter,
how can her last name, her background
be ever included into our family register?
If you both are together,
every time the rites ritual is held,
as a daughter-in-law, the food offerings that she prepares, what right would she have
to offer it to the front of your father's tablet?
If you both were to have children,
do you think that your father in heaven
would be willing to be called Grandfather?
Mom. What you said, I have already thought about it many times.
In the past, I used to think that this was impossible too.
But Cai Hong's courage and perservance
made me think of a reason.
Why can't we change our mindset?
Just like what you said,
in the future, if Cai Hong and I get married,
and we have a child,
we will be happy that it was born.
Unfortunately, we cannot resolve the issues of dead people.
Even the power of love
will not allow us to get rid of all the hatred.
Looks like your
love has surpassed your life.
It made your forget the deep grudge and revenge of your father.
Let me tell you. If, Cai Hong, by saving my life,
could cancel the grudge between the Wu and Jiang families,
I would also tell you that I can't do it.
If this is the case,
I should join your father in the other world so you can share a blissful life with Cai Hong.
Mom.
Yu Er. You don't want your mother to die, right?
Sever the ties today then.
You are awake.
Don't move. You need to rest.
I'm fine.
Cai Hong. Why are you so foolish?
The Jiang family has so many employees. Why did you run into the fire to save them?
Even if you had to do everything in you to save them,
what if something happened to you and you caused me to...
What are you going to do about Cai Yun and Aunt?
Sorry for making you worry about me.
But look, God is taking care of me.
Didn't I wake up?
Let's not talk about this anymore. Take your porridge.
Here.
Once I woke up, I could't use my hands.
Don't force yourself to be strong. My mom cooked this porridge for you.
It tastes really good. Please thank Aunt on my behalf.
What is there to thank? It's more important for you to recover first.
Come.
One more sip. Here.
You are here.
How is Cai Hong's injuries?
If you are concerned about her, go in and see her.
If the Jiang family still can't accept her,
don't look for her anymore.
She gets hurt everytime you treat her good.
Do you know that I thought of giving her up
and letting you take care of her?
In the end, she turned out like this.
Since your Jiang family is unwilling to accept her,
I won't give up again.
Starting today, I will take good care of her.
I won't let her be hurt again.
I will never let this happen.
And what if Cai Hong has to enter the Jiang House at the cost of your mother's life?
Will you be able to accept this?
If you can't give your beloved a future, don't give her any hope.
You want Cai Hong to be happy too.
Are you okay?
Is there a report for the fire?
According to the preliminary investigation report, we believe it was a deliberate arson, done by the missing servant.
But I guess he was instructed to do so.
Can you help me and think who could have a motive to do this?
I can only think of one person.
Lu Man.
I had the same thought as you
but we don't have any evidence now.
No matter what, I still need to report to Police Chief Li.
Warlord Lu is a decent man, he would never cover up a murderer.
I will find the evidence and sentence her according to the law.
It's so beautiful
but it's a pity this is not what I wanted.
Military Governor.
Military Governor, what brings you here?
What did I do wrong that you are beating me?
You bandit. I already told you not to give me any problems.
You should quit pretending to listen to my orders.
Jiang Yu of Huzhou
is not an insignificant person. Many people are watching his movements.
Even if I wanted to touch him,
I would think carefully about the consequences.
As for you,
you even had the courage to set fire on his home and kill them?
Do you know how many people in Huzhou are eyeing my position?
And you still give me problems?
I should have shot you then.
It would have saved me from your scheming.
You said that I set fire and killed people?
Where is the evidence?
Where is the evidence?!
You listen to what others say and you simply believed them?
Fine.
Since you believe that I did it,
just shoot me then.
When you were chasing after me in Shanghai,
I was just a child.
I was very good then.
Now,
you got tired of me so you are using everything against me, isn't that so?
Fine.
If you think I'm that kind of person,
and you are willing to believe them,
I'm going to pack and leave.
I will stay far away from you.
This place has wronged me all the time.
This is my territory. Do you think you can and go as you wish?
Miss Wu, dont move around. Your injuries haven't healed yet.
- I would like to visit Madam Jiang. - No, you must lie down.
If the wounds tear, it won't be good.
- I will be back. - You can't.
When your wounds have healed, I will definitely take you there.
Cai Hong. You must listen to the nurse.
Madam Jiang is really doing well.
Heal your wounds first.
When that time comes, I will go with you to visit her.
What about Jiang Yu? How is he?
He is doing well.
He didn't even come to see me.
Eat something.
Mom.
I miss you.
I know that
I know that no matter how many people have abandoned me,
in your heart,
I'm your most beloved.
The most obedient daughter.
I will rise up again.
I will really rise again.
Mom.
Don't be sad and worried.
When others treat me badly,
I will love myself even more.
I will take care of myself.
Mom.
What are you thinking about?
I have been cooking food for Miss Wu for the past few days.
Is she used to them?
Did she say what she wanted to eat? I will cook it for her.
Is she much better?
Sometimes, I think that I should let her go.
This would be really good for her.
Shao Tian. When Miss Wu is awake, everything will be fine.
As for the rest of the matters, take it slow.
But I also felt that
I was the only one who could do so much for her
and protect her.
I don't know
what to say.
In any case,
when two people like each other, even when they are not together,
their hearts are thinking about each other.
But if one party doesn't like the other,
even if they are together every day,
that person's heart will still be out there.
She is just like the stars in the sky.
She seems very close
but actually, she's very far away from me.
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian.
Did you had a good rest?
It's okay.
Here, have some bananas.
Thanks.
Cai Hong. I'm going out for a while.
Call the nurse if there are anything.
Go and do what you need to first.
Cai Yun will come here to keep me company later.
Mom. Cai Hong is here.
Don't let her in.
Madam. I only just wanted to visit you.
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫