♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The Cage of Love
Episode 34
Tell me then.
What should I use to make you talk?
Why don't we try this needle
and see if you will talk?
Tell me about the secret formula now
and I will let you live.
Dream on.
If it doesn't belong to you, it won't.
You will never be able to get the secret formula.
Does it hurts?
It hurts.
I believe now that
you really don't have the secret formula.
For you, in the future, you can teach him too.
So, we were actually friends.
It will be a beautiful cycle of reincarnation.
Remember what you told me.
You will never make me regret
by handing Cai Hong to you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Shao Tian. Is something troubling you?
No. Don't guess blindly.
Here, have more food.
Shao Tian. I'm your mother. Don't lie to me.
Even though you don't want to say anything,
I know that you have something on your mind.
Mom. You must believe me.
Look...
all these years,
I already experienced what I should experience.
My hard work has paid off.
I have loved.
Earned love.
After letting it go, I finally understood the choice you and Dad made.
Sometimes when you hold it tightly and don't let go,
it doesn't mean that it's good for the other party.
When one choses to left go and leave, perhaps, it's another way to love.
Staying together is a kind comfort,
letting go is difficult.
Dad chose another method
to protect us.
All these years,
I didn't do well.
I'm sorry.
Shao Tian, let's not talk about this.
Eat.
Tonight,
I'm going out to settle some matters. I may be home a bit late.
Sleep early and don't wait for me.
It's almost time, I should leave now.
Mom, take your time eating.
Shao Tian.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Mr Jiang, you are punctual.
Did you bring anyone else here?
Don't worry. I came alone.
Mr Jiang, let's go then.
Go.
You two, stay here and keep watch. Check if we are being followed.
Yes.
Speed up.
Let's go.
Old Master.
Please protect Cai Hong and Yu Er. Let them come back safely.
- Mom, Madam. - Don't stop me.
- Mom, don't do this. - Dont stop me.
Let's talk in a civilised manner.
- Mom.  - Madam Jiang.
I heard that Cai Hong has been kidnapped. Is this true?
Madam Wu. Let's talk calmly.
It's true.
Mom, get up now.
Madam Jiang. I know that the Jiang family hates us.
My husband has wronged you
but Cai Hong is a kind and good girl.
She is really sincere in paying for her father's crimes.
She's really seeking your forgiveness.
Madam Wu. What are you doing? Get up.
- Get up now. - Madam Jiang, I'm begging you.
I'm begging you to save Cai Hong.
I know that the kidnappers want the Jiang family's secret formula.
I also know that the secret formula is very important to your founders.
But this child didn't do anything wrong.
She didn't sin. If she made any mistakes
I don't want to live anymore.
Madam Jiang. I'm begging you. Please save my sister.
My sister didn't do anything wrong.
Madam Wu. Yu Er has already taken the secret formula to save Cai Hong.
- Really? - Yes, get up now.
Really? Jiang Yu went to save her?
It's true.
That's great.
Madam Wu. Even though the secret formula is important
no matter what, our children are more important.
If at this time, I don't hand over the secret formula, am I still a human?
Madam Jiang. Thank you very much.
- Enough. - Thank you very much.
Thank you, Madam Jiang.
It's late and I called you here
because we need to undertake a special mission.
The motive is to save Jiang Wu and Wu Cai Hong.
Everyone, listen carefully. One part of the team will start from here.
The second team will start from here.
We'll meet in the middle.
Remember this. The people we are going against tonight
may have heavy weapons.
It's extremely dangerous. You must be very careful.
Get ready to set off.
Hurry up.
We are back again. Didn't we just pass here?
Did we take the wrong path?
I...
We are almost done.
When we tell you to walk, just walk. Cut the crap.
Go now.
You two stay here. We are leaving.
Yes.
Quick, after them.
Quick.
Watch carefully.
Come here.
Don't move.
Let's go, quick.
Kneel down.
- Speak now. - I will talk.
Take them over there and check if there is anyone else.
Yes. You both, go over there. You two, come with me.
Director. We already searched. There is no one else here.
Come here. Where is Jiang Yu?
He's not here. It's only just me.
I'm telling the truth.
Kneel down.
Before Jiang Yu left, he told me that he would leave some markers.
Did he tell you what the markers are?
He only said to bring this along.
Listen carefully.
Use your torchlights and check
if there are any special markers.
Director Chen.
There is phosphor.
What are you looking at? Let's go.
It's not honest.
Mr Zhou.
Following this florescent path, we have circled the path a few times.
What I see here is that it isn't pink enough anymore.
Mr Zhou, there again is phosphor over here.
What should we do?
Let's do this.
Let's not waste any time. There are only two paths.
You go there and I will go here.
Junior Superintendent, make the arrangements.
Yes.
Let's split.
Okay.
The rest, follow me. Come, buddies.
Over there.
Go in.
Cai Hong.
Cai Hong. Don't be afraid, I'm here.
Why are you here?
Of course, I would come.
If I were captured by someone,
wouldn't you come and save me too?
I was used to lure you.
Even if you came,
Lu Man will never release us.
Don't be afraid.
This is really touching.
Seeing the two of you like this.
If this continues on, it will really make me believe that there is love in this world.
So, it's you.
It's me.
Mr Jiang, now that you see
hand over the secret formula to me.
The secret formula is here.
I can give it to you but you must ensure the safety of Cai Hong.
You must not give it to her. This is from your founder. You must protect this.
Don't do this.
Enough.
The two of you are now my Zushang fish. you are my prisoners.
What right do you have to discuss terms with me?
Mr Jiang. I won't look at the secret formula you are holding in your hand.
Who knows if it's real or fake?
Thus, please dye a piece of cloth for me now
to prove if it's real.
Uncle Lai, prepare a few brushes.
Record Mr Jiang's each and every step.
Yes.
Let's go.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Are you really going to give her the secret formula?
Don't be afraid.
Trust me.
Because this hasn't ended, it may not be a bad ending yet.
What if the ending is bad?
Even if the ending is bad,
we will still die together, right?
You are really foolish.
Enough.
Your time is imminent.
Dye it now.
It's only one garment. It won't take long love.
Come.
Director. This path is not right.
Go back now. Quick.
Ahead.
Director. It's Xiao Shi and Kang Zi.
It's dangerous here now.
Leave now.
Ke Ke. We already tried it.
The colour doesn't run.
Thank you.
Man Man.
Man Man, are you okay?
Mom.
I want to grow up soon.
I want to grow up.
Man Man. You want to grow up.
It's because you want to be able to wear my clothes soon. Isn't that so?
My Man Man. Think about it.
If you were to grow up,
when the time comes, you will be old like me.
My mom will never grow old.
Mom.
You smell very nice.
This is the feeling.
This is really the secret formula.
You already know the secret formula.
Can we leave now?
Since you have already decided to die together,
do you still need to leave here?
Let's go.
Don't move.
- Cai Hong. -Jiang Yu.
Lu Man. You are too despicable.
I just want to be ruthless.
I'm not like your father.
I'll be lenient and let you go to the Jiang home early.
Otherwise we will experience Jiang Yu's revenge.
There won't be today either.
Ke Ke!
Leave now. Ke Ke.
Zhou Shao Tian.
Brother Shao Tian.
So how? Are you okay?
Be careful.
Uncle Lai. How are you?
So how? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Uncle Lai.
Uncle Lai, don't die.
You promised me that
you would take care of me forever.
You promised me that you would take care of me forever.
I'm begging you.
If you leave, what would I do?
Can you bear it?
Brother Shao Tian.
Uncle Lai.
I will take revenge for you.
Come out.
Quick.
Stop there.
Kneel down.
Are you okay?
Come out.
What's wrong?
Police!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Take them away now.
Quick, let's go.
Leave.
I will bomb you to death!
Quick!
Jiang Yu!
I will bomb you to death!
Brother Shao Tian.
Let go.
- Brother Shao Tian. - What are you doing here? Why aren't you protecting Cai Hong?
Let's go.
Brother Shao Tian!
Shao Tian!
Jiang Yu!
Brother Shao Tian!
Let me go.
Don't!
Jiang Yu! - Don't!
- You are awake? - How is Brother Shao Tian?
The doctor said that you can't move around. Go back and rest first.
I'm going to look for him.
- Sit down first. - Let me look for him.
Listen to me. Let me finish first.
- I want to find Brother Shao Tian. - Listen to me. Don't move around.
- Cai Hong, listen to me. - He is already dead.
Sorry, Cai Hong.
That can't be.
Cai Hong, don't be like this.
Cai Hong, listen to me. You must be strong.
You must be strong.
I couldn't do anything at all.
You must continue to live.
Don't let Shao Tian sacrifice his life for nothing.
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian. I'm here to visit you.
Do you still remember
what you told me?
If you could turn back time,
you don't where you will go back to.
If you really could start over
I rather I never met you.
This way,
you will be able to live well.
But we already met.
I want to thank you
for always doting on me.
For letting me feel the tenderness
and being very blessed.
Thank you.
Shao Tian.
What I promised you,
I will definitely do it.
Don't worry.
It's my fault.
I harmed Brother Shao Tian.
It's because of me.
Aunt.
I'm sorry.
Child.
This was Shao Tian's own choice.
I think he will be very happy to use another way to protect you.
Aunt, don't worry.
In the future, I will definitely
treat you like my mother.
I will be filial to you on behalf of Brother Shao Tian.
To serve you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Is this for me?
Of course.
Do you like it?
It's such a beautiful necklace.
My mom just said the same thing.
If Aunt likes this, you should give it to her.
- If not, she won't be happy. - Who says so?
She even asked me why I took such a long time to give this to you?
If you are all like this, it will be hard for me.
Who's making it hard for you?
Did you know when my mom said that to me, Aunt Wu and Aunt Zhou were there too?
They were both talking about me.
What did they say?
In any way, them all living together, they all share the same voice.
I still have a surprise for you.
What is it?
I'm taking you to a place.
Where are we going?
Where exactly are we going? Just tell me.
Don't ask anymore. You will find out later.
Why isn't there anyone in the factory today?
That's right. I gave them the day off.
Is this your surprise?
Is this considered a surprise?
Of course, it's a surprise.
Only when there is a special day at the factory can the employees take leave.
It's really very beautiful.
I finally understand now.
Everything can be let go.
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
Including the pain betrayals and revenge.
Even if it's life or death.
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
But you are the only one whom I can't let go.
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
If I see you in pain,
I will be in more pain than you.
When I see you smile,
I'm happier than you.
I think
this is what love is.
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
So, I told myself that
I must protect you for the rest of my life.
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
Cai Hong.
Marry me, okay?
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
The End
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ I'm aware that you feel reluctant to part with me. ♫
♫ Forgive my hesitation, ♫
♫ but I don't want to fake my fear when I see your sorrowful face. ♫
♫ I really believe that you love me.♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ How am I to choose ♫
♫ the colour between you and me? ♫
♫ The world is too elusive ♫
♫ to know what end result may be. ♫
♫ I hear your question, ♫
♫ I keep everything inside without telling you. ♫
♫ I'm avoiding you, but you keep guarding me. ♫
♫ I know you really love me. ♫
♫ Rest assured that I am also in love with you. ♫
♫ Give me some time so I can find the courage to choose. ♫
♫ Struggling rain paints the sky with the colours of the rainbow...♫
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki