-[breathes deeply]
-[man] What are you doing here, nigga?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
Young man...
I've had a long day.
I'm tired.
But I'm not tired enough...
to ever let nobody call me that word.
You see a nigga standin' in front of you?
[breathing heavily]
Across the street from a building
named after one of our greatest heroes?
-[gun cocks]
-Yeah, a dead one.
[Luke exhales]
[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[Scarfe] You're doing it again.
I hate it when you do that.
Hate it when I do what?
Stare at the photos
like they're about to start moving.
They are talkin' and movin'.
You just have to be still enough
to hear what they're sayin'.
Whatever, Horton.
A clue is a clue, no matter how small.
This was deeply personal.
Well, money invites the beast.
There's nothing in Chico's jacket
to suggest he was capable
of that type of violence.
I don't think he has the stomach for it.
Stomach? [sighs]
There was vomit found at the junkyard.
Inside it were fibers
consistent with that of a winter mask.
One of the robbers didn't have the heart
to go through with it.
My guess, it was babyface Chico.
Uh, he was the last man standing.
You mean to tell me
Benjamin Franklin was wrong?
Well, in this case,
it was all about the Benjamins either way.
[scoffs] Always is.
Somebody got jacked,
and somebody got pissed...
And somebody got dead.
This ain't over yet.
Eh, I just never got into Donald Goines.
[chuckling] Are you crazy?
Donald Goines was a street poet.
-[Pop chuckles]
-[Luke] I didn't say Goines isn't.
But Walter Mosley, George Pelecanos?
[clicks tongues] Boom.
I bet you're into Richard Price.
I dig Price.
Dennis Lehane, too.
What about Chester Himes?
Without question.
[clears throat] My biggest beef
with Donald Goines
is that he wrote about criminals
and he died like one.
[chuckles] You don't have to get
all Fox News about it.
[Pop chuckling]
Goines invented Kenyatta,
the best black hero this side of Shaft.
-[customer] Thank you, my brother.
-All right.
-Keep that magic touch.
-I'll keep working on it.
See you next week, Victor.
So you're saying
Kenyatta is better than Easy Rawlins?
I ain't saying all that.
I'm just saying Kenyatta's my favorite.
He took the fight to the man...
in the streets by his self.
Just like somebody else could
if he wasn't sweeping hair
and washing dishes.
[sighs] Don't start, Pop.
The whole neighborhood
is yapping about how Zip and two goons
got the beat down
at Genghis Connie's last night.
Hmm.
I heard it was four guys.
[chuckling]
I knew it had to be you.
[chuckles] No wonder you came
into the shop so light on your feet.
Either that or someone
finally gave you some trim.
Oh!
[both laugh]
[Pop] Mmm. Mmm.
So that's how it works?
Those thugs shake people down?
They work for Mariah or Cottonmouth?
[grunts]
A little bit of both.
They related?
-Aunt and nephew?
-Cousins.
Their grandma was Mama Mabel.
Who's Mama Mabel?
[sighs] The devil's ex-wife.
They ever come at you sideways?
No.
This place right here is Switzerland.
Everybody knows that.
Where you from, Luke?
Chicago.
You ain't from no Chicago.
Where are you from, really?
Savannah, Georgia.
All right.
Country boy.
You know how the wind feels fluffy,
like you could stuff it into a pillowcase
-right before a big thunderstorm?
-Mmm-hmm.
Harlem's the same.
Trouble smells a certain way.
You can... touch it.
Cottonmouth.
He's gonna fall behind lookin' for Chico.
That's the way that works.
Ain't no secrets uptown.
I mean, you could set a watch
by the way that shit will play out.
[scoffs]
I'm fresh out of singles.
-I ain't gonna break no ten for that.
-[laughs]
[chuckles] Oh, no, no.
-[door opens]
-[bell chimes]
Something real about a razor.
You should let me use my clippers.
You gonna bump up.
Nah. [inhales deeply]
Doesn't have the same feel.
The clippers are idiot-proof.
That's what's missin' nowadays, Pop.
Attention to detail.
Everyone wants things fast, quick.
Me?
I like to take my time.
[Pop] Time is a luxury most...
working class men cannot afford.
[Stokes] True.
Time is precious.
Shouldn't be wasted.
Mmm...
A good razor shave
is like a vacation to me.
It's incredible
how few people take advantage.
[Pop] It's a lost art.
[Stokes] Exactly.
That's the problem with these youngsters.
They want it all.
But they don't want to put in the work.
They'll rob...
lie, cheat, steal,
just to get what they want.
Damn shame if you ask me.
[softly] Yeah.
-Shame.
-Mmm-hmm.
How'd you... cut your hands?
Oh, uh, eh... shaving.
[chuckling] That's why I needed
a professional touch, you dig?
-[Pop] Sorry, brother.
-Twelve feet.
Two guns.
Four seconds.
You gonna move?
No, not yet.
Just 'cause they call you Bobby Fish
don't mean you're Bobby Fischer.
And you ain't Turkish neither, Turk.
Not last time I checked.
[Turk] That's not what your daughter said.
[Bobby chuckling]
Yeah, but your mama confirmed it.
[Turk] Oh, you think you can throw me off
my game talking about my mama?
[Bobby] Oh, no, she is
a well-established ho.
That should not faze you one bit.
Check.
That's a cheap broom.
Old.
I just got home.
College?
Three years this time...
Seagate.
I'm from 'round the way.
Grew up right here.
Everyone knows Pop.
There was this little Puerto Rican kid...
I can't remember his name...
It's like, um...
Rico or, uh...
Chico.
Yeah...
He used to shape me up back in the day.
He was real good, too.
I was hoping he was still around.
People come and go.
You know how it is, right?
Yeah.
[Luke] Pop...
I've got some fresh towels right here.
You've got some dirty ones.
I could take 'em out if you want.
No sweat at all.
I'm good, Luke.
[Stokes] Big man...
you work here, too?
This brother got more jobs
than a Jamaican.
-[laughing]
-[chuckles]
[Stokes] What's your name again?
-Luke.
-Luke. [snaps fingers]
[inhales sharply] Mmm, old school.
Biblical. [chuckles]
I'm all about the old school.
You know that...
eye for an eye,
tooth for a tooth kind of thing.
Fire and brimstone.
[inhales sharply]
See... back then...
do someone wrong,
wasn't no beggin' and pleadin'.
Just took care of it.
Handled your business.
What about turning the other cheek?
Mmm...
Jesus saves...
I don't.
You want a hot towel?
Not today. [exhales]
Gotta keep it movin'.
I'm a working man, too.
[Tone] Chico falls through...
we need to holler at him.
[Stokes] Thanks for the shave, Henry.
I'm loyal to my people.
[Luke] You're forgetting something,
Mr. Stokes.
Unless your last name is Corleone,
Shaft or Riley...
you owe my man $25.
Don't worry about it, Cornell.
Nah, it's all good.
[Stokes chuckles]
Tone, pay the man.
[bell chimes]
[door closes]
They got Shameek.
Cottonmouth did it personally.
Did you see his knuckles?
I'm sorry, Pop.
You never liked him anyway.
That's not entirely true.
Shameek is gone.
I don't condone what he did.
But it's not too late for Chico.
Pop, stay out of it.
Some people you just gotta let go.
I can't just turn my back on him.
You used to find people, right?
That was a long time ago.
It ain't exactly a skill you lose.
Look, this place is Switzerland.
If we can find him before they do,
maybe I can set up a parley
with Cottonmouth.
I don't think so, man.
I'm sorry, Pop.
I can't do it.
Hey... yes.
You are sorry.
Now, I hadn't seen Reva
since she was five.
So when she comes home
with a convict husband
and a shaky-ass story...
I ain't ask her no questions.
And when that same well-read ex-con
comes back wanting to be paid in cash...
and lifting up refrigerators
like they're empty cardboard boxes,
I just nodded my head again.
What did you tell me
about keeping your secrets?
That I owed you one.
Well, time is due.
I'm collecting.
[indistinct chatter]
[boy 1] Whoo!
[boy 2] Hey!
[boy 3] Five-O! Five-O!
[boy 4] Let's go!
[Scarfe] Whoa! Hold up...
Hold up, hold up!
[chuckling] Where's everybody goin'?
Come on, Chauncey.
You know the drill.
Have you seen this kid?
Chico?
[Chauncey]
No, I don't know that dude.
Stop it.
His initials are painted right here.
Just like all the other
St. Nick playground legends.
You seen him or not?
Nah.
Wastin' time, Misty.
Yo, pass me the rock.
[chuckling]
What, you fittin' to play
one-on-one with me?
No. That wouldn't be fair to you.
[all exclaim]
Come on, let's play H-O-R-S-E.
Shot for shot.
And if I win...
you tell me everything I need to know
about Wilfredo Chico Diaz.
What's in it for me?
A get out of jail free card
for any non-violent felony.
[scoffs] Not doin' that shit.
No way.
-[ball bounces]
-We good?
[boy 1] Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Ladies first.
-[all exclaim]
-[boy 2] Come on, Chauncey.
[Chauncey chuckles]
[boy 2] Come on, man.
It's your thing, man!
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, you better shoot like Cheryl Miller,
not Barney Miller.
Sometimes I forget how old you are.
I mean, he gonna hold your purse, too?
[all chuckling]
Wow!
[all exclaim]
Come here.
You see that?
This is my court, too.
Let's play.
[all exclaim]
-[boy 1] Oh, come on, now!
-[all exclaim]
[inaudible]
[men speaking indistinctly]
-[knock on door]
-Yes.
Hey.
Mmm-mmm.
That's not nearly enough.
[laughing] What?
It's not enough.
I need the rest so I can make the deposit.
Well, I need to find the guy who has it.
Look... I borrowed from those donations,
at your request,
so you could refurbish your club.
You go and make
a gun deal with Domingo.
Then you get jacked
and we're all exposed.
You promised this would be
taken care of, but it's not.
You don't give me orders.
We're partners.
You're not my boss.
We're family, Cornell.
But think about it.
Do you really want to go to jail?
-Do you want to lose your club?
-Of course not.
Then you need
to fix this shit right now.
Does your guard dog
want a drink of water?
-[chuckles softly]
-Don't worry about him.
You worry about the politics,
I worry about my job.
Your job is to uncomplicate my life.
And your job
is to turn my water into wine.
Family first, right?
Always.
I'm coming by the club tonight.
[chuckles]
Why? I thought you said
you don't want to be seen there.
I don't.
But I like the music.
I'm going to be on you
until this is resolved.
It's getting resolved.
You best believe that.
[gun cocks]
-You ain't gonna fire that.
-I'll kill you.
Shameek is dead.
They have his half of the money.
Now they want yours.
-Shameek is dead?
-Yeah.
Well, good. [spits]
Then you just want my money
for yourself, don't you?
I couldn't care less.
I came here because
Pop asked me to come for you.
Pops?
For your dad.
[breath trembling]
Why does everybody bring him up?
He was never there for me.
I'm sick and tired of hearing about him.
Pop thinks he has a way
to clear this mess up.
I know you didn't kill Dante...
or Shameek.
All you guys wanted was the cash.
It was an inside job.
Dante's safe idea.
Look...
I found you in four hours for free.
Imagine how fast someone
Cottonmouth pays will find you.
[inhales sharply]
The only chance you have at survival
is if you come with me right now.
Well, I got a half a million new chances
is the way I see it.
Tell Pops... I'm sorry.
He was always good to me.
He deserves better.
Took your rook, rookie.
Hmm.
-It's your move, son.
-[chuckling] Mmm-hmm.
-Don't get scared now.
-Oh, no, no, no...
-[bell chimes]
-[indistinct chatter]
[gate creaking]
[Luke] Want some catfish
with that hot sauce?
[chuckling]
-You count calories, Power Man?
-[sighs]
Fork will kill you
quicker than any bullet.
[chuckling]
I found Chico.
He ain't coming.
You can't save everybody.
You're wrong about that.
What would have happened in my life
if people gave up on me?
I was no angel.
No, I was a beast.
-[man grunting]
-[Pop] I was a beast.
No two ways about it.
[Luke] They call you Pop
because you were the OG?
[Pop] No, it was the sound my fist made
when I knocked a fool out.
Snap, crackle, pop!
Cottonmouth lost three teeth as a kid.
[chuckles] Wilfredo saw him smile
and the name just stuck.
And Fredo was the craziest
little Puerto Rican in black Harlem.
I used to call 'em
Thing One and Thing Two.
Hey, yo, yo, yo.
Can I take your photo?
-Yeah, yeah. Jamel, right?
-Right over here, man. Thanks.
Yeah, yeah. [mutters]
[Luke] What'd that make you?
The Cat in the Hat?
-[shutter clicks]
-[Pop] Something like that.
[Luke] So what happened?
[Pop] We got popped.
Wilfredo went from selling crack
to smoking crack.
I got caught
with a gun and a bag of money.
Kept my mouth shut.
Went on pause for ten years.
My woman was pregnant when I went in.
I haven't seen her or...
my son since he was 13.
I have this nightmare that...
one day, he's gonna come to the shop...
ask for a cut, sit in my chair...
and I'm not even gonna know him.
I didn't have one single skill
when I got out.
I could've gone back to the streets.
But you weren't that guy anymore.
I wasn't... and I'm not.
And that's what I go through every day.
Trying not to be that person.
I'm not that guy either.
I thought you was innocent, Shawshank.
Mmm.
I ain't guilty. [sighs]
But... I ain't innocent either.
I had to balance my dirt...
so I opened up this shop.
So those young knuckleheads
have a place to get away.
Like Fredo's son, Chico.
And certain... muscle-headed fugitives
lookin' for a change of pace.
[Pop chuckles]
After what I did at Genghis Connie's...
for the first time in a long time...
I felt at peace.
[Pop] Mmm-hmm.
I made a decision
when I got back to the crib.
I'm done running.
Boys run.
Men stand.
You're a man.
I am who I am.
Or...
maybe I have a chance to find out
who I could really be.
That's right.
-[Luke] Hmm?
-Yeah.
Come on.
Let's get going.
Hey, Pop.
Damn. Y'all still at it, huh?
-He don't know when to quit.
-Oh, I know.
[Bobby] Until I win.
Gonna leave it open?
Yeah, till we shut the doors...
[chuckles] whether it's empty or not.
I'm gonna go get my smock.
[grunts]
What... were you thinking?
Sorry. I'm sorry!
[sniffles]
[Pop exclaims] You dummy.
-You dummy.
-What's up?
Dummy.
[both sobbing]
You did good.
That's what.
My bad, Mr. Hunter.
Where's the restroom key? Just...
Get out of here.
Go.
You heard me.
You got to get him out of here.
And you know damn well,
Chico ain't gonna show up for work today.
Of course not, but...
Pop will tell us the truth
about who Chico really is.
He's just a barber, right?
Ah, he's a little bit of everything.
Not a very good judge of character.
He's got a big heart.
We should fault him for that?
[Scarfe] Nope.
Gimme a second.
And don't start without me.
Can't do the one-two punch without you.
Turk.
Misty.
I'm surprised to see you this far uptown.
I'm mostly Midtown nowadays, you know?
Puffy ain't got shit on me, baby.
I'm the real bad boy worldwide.
Yeah, your rap sheet got so many hits,
your record could put out a record.
Hey, I just fell through to see my man,
Bobby Fish, and to play some chess.
Well, you need to fall your ass
back downtown,
'cause if I catch you around here again...
it's gonna be checkmate.
Understood? Mr. Barrett?
I hear you...
Detective.
Loud and clear.
Did anyone see you come here?
-Hmm?
-No... I don't think so.
-[door opens, bell chimes]
-Luke, check.
[whispers] Five-O!
You need to go
in the bathroom and hide. Go.
Go!
-Hey, Misty.
-Fish.
-How you doin'?
-Good to see you.
You, too.
[Misty] Is Pop around?
[Fish] He's in the back.
He'll be out in a minute.
-[pats Pop]
-Let me stall 'em. Sit tight.
[chuckles] Whoa.
Detective Mercedes Knight.
It's Misty now, Pop.
You know that.
[Pop] All right, all right.
[chuckles]
Call yourself
whatever you want to, Detective.
-Hey!
-[chuckles] Ooh!
I respect authority.
[both chuckle]
I bet Kelly must be
really proud of you, hmm?
He's still mad I went to Temple
instead of playin' for St. John's.
-Bam!
-Swish!
[both laugh]
Is this your partner?
Detective Rafael Scarfe.
[softly] Okay.
How can I help you?
We're looking for someone
who works for you.
Wilfredo Chico Diaz?
You heard about that shooting...
at the junkyard?
Near the edge of the river?
No.
Really?
There was a shootout.
Looks like a gun deal that was robbed.
Turned into a bloodbath.
Dante Chapman was found dead at the scene.
Shameek Smith was found
about 18 hours later, beaten to death.
Last person to see Shameek Smith alive,
other than a strip club...
was right here at the shop
with his homeboy.
Uh, they were both here.
Chico gave Shameek a fade in that chair,
right next to where you're standing.
That's it though.
That's the last time I saw them both.
You really think Chico killed his friend?
Over money?
You are?
Luke Cage.
Detective Misty Knight.
Detective.
Looks like you found some better clothes
to audit in.
[exhales]
Look... when my guys are here,
they know the rules.
Respect, no street talk.
But when they leave,
I got no control.
Understood,
but Chico is a person of interest
who might have pertinent information.
Pertinent information?
Like, someone saying
who they really are?
Pertinent as in useful.
As in factual.
Like, uh... Chico's number.
You got that, right?
He missed work the last two days.
His booth rent is due,
so maybe he'll return my call.
If you see him, tell him to call me.
Call me anyway.
He may not be safe otherwise.
Will do.
-[chuckles]
-Nice meeting you, Luke.
You too... Detective.
-[door opens]
-[bell chimes]
Really? [scoffs]
We had coffee.
Mmm-hmm.
[chuckles] Right.
You gonna call Cottonmouth?
No.
You need to see him.
What?
He's going to want to see you.
No. I'm afraid our... friends in blue
might have eyes on the shop.
You work at Harlem's Paradise.
You have a reason to go there.
You can't do this kind of thing
on the phone.
[sighs]
Look, man, Wilfredo...
he died... on these streets.
I don't wanna see Chico
go out the same way.
Can you do this for me?
I'm on it.
All right.
[softly] Thanks.
[dishes clattering]
[Nate] You're late.
I have your money.
Cage.
Cage!
Do you hear me?
[indistinct chatter]
Your brother down there told Candace
to send me up a Blue Hawaiian.
Like he gonna get up on me
with a Blue Hawaiian.
[both laugh]
Ah, he lucky I let his ass in here.
I need to speak to your man.
What? You didn't get tipped
at the barber shop?
Pat him down.
He's clean.
Thought you already had a job.
'Cause I could use some more ice.
I'm here for Pop.
Pop is a grown-ass man.
Why ain't he here?
He said you wouldn't wanna hear this
over the phone.
So he sent me.
Ha! The suspense is killing me.
Pop wants to set up a parley for Chico.
He doesn't want him
to end up like Shameek.
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
Those cuts on your hands say different.
[cell phone vibrates and chimes]
All I'm saying is that if you
want to talk to Pop about Chico,
that can be arranged.
All of your goods will be returned.
The only thing our mutual friend
wants is safe passage.
He'll never come back to New York, ever.
I don't speak Chinese.
[laughs] 'Cause that's what
this conversation is to me.
If I got somethin' to say to Pop,
I say it to him my damn self, you dig?
[sighs] There's history.
Pop understands your trouble.
He's just asking you
to remember your history.
[Stokes inhales deeply]
Tell Pop I'll come by
the barbershop for a haircut.
Same time as before.
You understand?
I'll tell him.
By the way...
you're fired.
No, I'm not.
I quit before I walked in.
[chuckles]
-[upbeat music playing]
-[crowd cheering]
We got eyes on the boy.
What do you want me to do?
-Your man say where he was?
-No.
[Stokes] Hmm.
Let it go.
Take care of it in the morning.
You sure?
If he's out on the streets slippin',
handle it.
But if he's not moving around,
I'll deal with it, all right?
[crowd cheering and whistling]
[Faith Evans over microphone]
Now let me holler at y'all for a minute.
'Cause I got somethin' that I need to say.
What y'all know about that thing?
[Mariah] You're wasting your gifts,
my brother.
This gangster life...
not what our ancestors fought for.
Not what our people died for.
This is exactly what they died for.
Self-determination, control, power.
That boy we was
looking for earlier today...
he's at Pop's Barber Shop.
-You seen him?
-With my own two eyes.
How long ago?
A little while back.
Hey!
Yo, what's up with my money?
[clippers buzzing]
[Pop] You need to leave?
I'm just gonna pick up dinner
from Boulevard.
Where's Luke?
-Have you seen him?
-Girl, you just don't quit, do you?
-I just want to take him out for coffee.
-[scoffs]
You know what people remember
besides black martyrdom?
What?
Black money.
Don't you ever get sick
of people calling you a criminal?
[gun clicks]
You gonna at least wait
for Chico to come outside, right?
Right?
What he sayin'?
He'll only talk to you.
Right here at the shop.
I want something better.
-Like what?
-Respect.
It's all that ever really matters.
Money outlasts respect.
Respect will put your name
on the side of a building...
but the money that put your name up there
comes from someplace.
At what cost, Cornell?
When you find out...
you'll tell me.
[all cheering]
What are you doing out here
with that bag, man?
-There's no TV back there.
-Are you serious?
Pop!
[bullet ricochets]
[screams]
[muffled screaming]
[whispering]
Stay dead. Stay dead.
[gunfire stops]
[whimpering]
[gagging]
-You should've waited.
-Shut up, man.
You okay?
Pop!
[softly] Pop.
Oh, Pop... [crying]
[gagging]
-Come on...
-[Pop grunts]
-[wheezing]
-You hear the sirens?
[panting] They're almost here.
They comin'.
Someone call the goddamn ambulance!
[Luke sobbing]
[Pop straining] Swear...
Swear jar...
[crying] I will. I will.
[gulps]
Luke...
[stuttering] Forward... always.
[gagging]
Always...
[stuttering] forward.
[whispers] Always forward.
[mumbling]
[crying] No.
[sniffling] No...
No! [sobbing]
No!
[screaming] No!
[breathing heavily]
[sniffles]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Lonnie] Mommy, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Luke covered me.
He said he didn't move because
he didn't want them to shoot again.
-[Patty sighs] You see who did this?
-[Lonnie] No, Mama.
[officer] Excuse me, ma'am.
Will you come with me?
[Scarfe] You get a look at the shooter?
Nah.
It's a miracle I'm even alive, man.
Luke.
Luke?
Are you okay?
You didn't get hit?
I said I'm okay.
What happened?
They started firing.
The kid, Lonnie,
was in the middle of the room.
So, once I saw the flash...
instincts kicked in.
I grabbed him... and I shielded him.
You... shielded him?
You shielded him with what?
Have the paramedics seen you yet?
I said I'm good.
How long have you been
working here at the shop?
Five months.
Did Chico reach out to Pop
since we were in here earlier?
Was he hiding out here the whole time?
-What did they get from the canvass?
-[Scarfe] Uh, patrol got nothing.
Traffic cam picked up a black Escalade.
Tracked it to Hunts Point in the Bronx,
but it was torched. No prints.
[inhales sharply]
They were after Chico?
-There's no doubt in my mind.
-Hmm.
I checked out Cottonmouth.
He's been at the club all night in VIP.
-So we don't have shit?
-No.
No decent witnesses except for Chico,
but then what else?
Nothin'?
[indistinct chatter]
[man] Yeah, baby. Uh-huh.
-[mouthing] Upstairs.
-I'm coming with you.
-Nah.
-No, I need to be there.
[Stokes] What's wrong, Shades?
-You should've waited.
-Waited? [scoffs]
Bump that noise.
I got the call. It was me.
What happened?
Look, Turk calls me.
Tells me he saw
Chic at the shop, slippin'.
I came and ask you if it was important
if the nigga was breathing.
You seem non-committal...
so I make an executive decision.
[both laughing]
That's what you call...
an executive decision?
[chuckles]
Yeah, okay.
Mmm, so you caught him slippin' outside?
No, bro, I lit that shit up
like the Fourth of July.
[chuckling] It was all so
Django Candyland shit for real.
Lights, camera, action, baby!
[clapping hands]
Somebody call Quentin! [laughing]
I suggested... we wait.
[Tone] Wait?
[stammers] Wait for what, Shades?
You ain't even down with the clique.
You can't give orders.
It was loud 'cause it's supposed to be.
Niggas need to know
you don't rob Cottonmouth!
[yelling] My name is not Cottonmouth!
[Tone] My bad.
My bad.
He's dead, right?
Chico's laid out...
He's done.
It don't matter.
We got the money!
[breathes deeply]
You had to do it, I guess.
Pops can rebuild.
[inhales sharply]
He won't like it
but I'll donate some money...
anonymously.
-It's all gonna be okay. [chuckles softly]
-[pats arm]
What?
Pops is dead.
A casualty of war.
You know...
[stammers] Shit happens.
[Turk] Yo...
Where's my money?
How the hell did you get up here?
I'm Turk Barrett, baby.
The door ain't been built yet
that can hold me back.
Now, where's my money?
Okay, Mr. Barrett.
Tone promised to pay you
for finding Chico, right?
-Yeah.
-That right?
Okay.
Hey, hey, hey!
[screaming]
[panting]
You can collect your money
from Tone downstairs, Mr. Barrett!
I assume that completes our business.
Y'all Harlem niggas are off the hook.
I'm going back to Hell's Kitchen,
where it's safe.
[scoffs]
Is that sufficient?
There's enough there.
You all right, cuz?
With what?
Extortion? Well...
Murder, no!
I'm not good.
Don't expect me to be.
The money's still green.
That it is.
You should get outta here.
You shouldn't be seen associating
with known criminals...
Councilwoman.
Take the side exit.
I got some garbage
to clean up downstairs.
Sorry about Pop.
Yeah, so am I.
I know what he meant to you.
[Stokes sighs deeply]
Believe it or not,
there's supposed to be rules to this shit.
He must have gotten hit.
What?
Luke...
Cage.
He shielded the kid.
He had bullet holes in his shirt.
Blood everywhere, none of it his?
How did he not get hit?
You're drunk.
Not yet.
-[breathing deeply]
-[man] What are you doing here, nigga?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
Young man...
I've had a long day.
I'm tired.
But I'm not tired enough...
to ever let nobody call me that word.
You see a nigga standin' in front of you?
Across the street from a building
named after one of our greatest heroes?
-[gun cocks]
-Yeah, a dead one.
[Luke sighs]
You even know who Crispus Attucks was?
A free black man.
The first man to die
for what became America.
He could've acted scared
when those Brits raised their guns.
Blended in, in the crowd.
But he stepped up!
He paid with his life.
But he started something.
That's what Pop did...
Not me.
I laid in the cut until he stepped up!
And it cost him his life, too.
I ain't laying back no more!
You wanna shoot me?
Do it.
Pull the trigger, nigga!
I ain't got all night.
[breathing heavily]
Do it!
What, you scared?
[breathing heavily] Fine.
I'll do it for you.
Always forward, Pop.
Forward...
always.
[funk music playing]