I should be out there doing my job.
[Krasner] Your job is out there
waiting for you, Detective.
The question is,
how badly do you want it?
You work for the department?
You a shrink?
[Krasner] I was on the job for 15 years.
I left to become a psychologist.
[scoffs]
I'm with the peer assistance program.
I'm a volunteer.
Well, how about I volunteer
my way out of this chair,
tell you to kiss my ass,
and talk to my union rep?
Well, you could do that, sure.
But your inspector would guarantee
that you'll be at your desk,
and the only time you'll see the street
is in the parking lot,
or if you go to get coffee, or...
look out the window.
-This is voluntary, right?
-Mmm-hmm.
-And off the record?
-Absolutely.
So why are we doing this
in an interrogation room?
You'd be more candid at a Starbucks?
Really?
Mmm...
Maybe at M&G's, after a shift.
Still can't believe
that place went out of business.
I miss Copeland's.
[chuckling] Who doesn't?
Whatever.
[inhales sharply] Let's do this.
Detective Mercedes Kelly Knight,
badge 3-0-9-3-5.
You know, you're not being recorded.
Of course I am.
You know this is bullshit, right?
Things got rough with a hostile witness.
You think that's the first time
this has ever happened?
You lost control.
[inhales] And it's all about control
with you, isn't it?
I mean, that's why you were a point guard.
You wanted to be the one
to distribute the ball, right?
It's 'cause I was short,
and it was the only way
I could get on the court, so...
-'Cause you had to play the game.
-It's not a game for me.
Then why get benched
for something as stupid
as getting physical with Claire Temple?
[Stryker echoing] Do you love?
Do you love?
Hmm?
[Stryker] Oh, come on.
You're not gonna beg?
Oh, come on.
Not even a little bit?
[crying]
If you gonna kill me, then just do it.
What shook you?
Was it losing your gun to one suspect
while trying to arrest another
without backup?
Was it the extra eyes because of Scarfe?
Was it this Luke Cage guy?
What pushed you towards career suicide?
[chuckles]
You know how many times
I've been in this same goddamn box
on the other side of the table?
You think you are gonna break me?
Bring it.
Like I said,
this is not an interrogation.
I'm not here to break you.
You've already done that yourself.
The question is, how broken are you?
And can you be fixed?
[truck engine revving]
[groaning]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
[sniffs] Ugh!
Sweet Christmas.
[theme music playing]
[drumming]
Hold up, hold up.
Somebody ain't playing that thing right.
Tighten up over here.
Tighten up over here, all right?
Let's do this, man. We rehearsed it.
Let's get this done.
[playing R&B song]
[singing]
[Shades] So we've checked every truck,
every landfill in every borough.
And for all of that, we've got...
[sighs]
Nothing yet.
[Shades] Nothing yet.
[Stryker] Y'all can't find Luke Cage?
What, he just dissipated?
Like smoke?
See, that's the thing.
Where there's smoke, there's fire.
-[gunshot]
-[gasps]
-Shit!
-[musicians yelling indistinctly]
[Darnell gasping]
-There's nothing magical about it.
-[groaning]
Follow the smoke.
Or the damn garbage truck.
[chuckles] Well...
you ain't Houdini.
And you ain't Rick
from Casablanca, neither.
What?
You thought you could
whisper in Mariah's ear...
have her do your dirty work...
then you're the new king
with the big desk?
Hmm...
Biggie photo...
Delfonics crooning downstairs...
You killed my friend, Shades.
He was my number one seller.
Who do you think gave him
that Barron Claiborne there?
You don't have any friends.
"A man of too many friends
comes to ruin,
but there is a friend
who comes closer than a brother."
Proverbs 18:24.
Cornell Stokes was that friend for me.
And I could trust him
like I could my own brother.
Cornell was losing it.
You trusted me to take care of him.
I trusted you to take care of it,
not him.
What? Did you think I was just gonna
give it all to you?
[cocks gun]
Give me one reason
why I shouldn't splatter
this pristine desk
with your brain matter.
[Zip] Because it won't help you find
Luke Cage any faster?
[laughing]
You're smarter
than your name implies, Zip.
Two rule books
got me through the darkness.
The Bible...
and The 48 Laws of Power.
Do you want to know what the 49th is?
Luke Cage ain't dead
until you find his goddamn body.
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[Megan on TV] And today's top news,
the shootout that occurred
in Harlem last night.
After an ambulance was forced
off the street,
it appears a chase led to a women's clinic
where gunfire was exchanged.
The fight continued
to this historic theater
where severe damage was wrought.
Witnesses described two men
at the center of this fight.
Although police still have not
detained any suspects,
this man, Luke Cage,
is wanted for questioning
in connection with the recent murder
of noted nightlife mogul
Cornell "Cottonmouth" Stokes.
[news anchor] Thanks, Megan.
In business news...
[news continues indistinctly on TV]
-[Krasner] You had it rough recently.
-Where do you want to start?
Who do you talk to when things get bad?
I-- [sighs]
I used to talk to Scarfe.
[stammers] No husband.
A boyfriend?
The last time somebody set me up,
I ended up arresting the guy at the table.
-No.
-Yeah.
I did a background check,
and he was wanted for robbery
in three different states.
They gave the dude a nickname
at my precinct.
-Yeah?
-Called him the Love Bandit.
I still get shit about it.
I see everything and I forget nothin'.
Every investigation, every suspect,
every murder, every crying mother...
It is all in my head.
So who's the last person you dated?
-That's personal.
-That's why we're here.
I met a guy at a bar.
I wasn't nice to him, at all.
[scoffs] But he didn't care.
He was funny.
He wasn't wearing a ring.
And the first time he spoke to me,
even in a low cut dress,
he looked at my eyes...
not my breasts.
-So?
-So, we talked.
I could be myself.
He thought I was pretty
and he told me so.
We had coffee.
[heavy breathing]
I feel a "but" coming on.
-But he wasn't who I thought he was.
-Just like Scarfe?
How does that make you feel?
How do you think it makes me feel?
I didn't want it!
[Mariah] You don't remember Jazmine.
How could you?
She was fly.
So damn fast.
She used to drive Mama Mabel crazy
with all her boyfriends.
Malik was special, though.
He was talented.
Played drums on a lot of those
Sugar Hill Records. The old ones.
I really liked him.
I thought they were good together.
Mama Mabel couldn't stand him.
She knew he was dabbling.
Coke, smack.
Malik wanted you, Cornell.
He did. But he OD'd.
And then Jazzy ran off.
She told me, "I'm not ready
to be nobody's mama."
And she just left.
She left you, and there you were,
[stammering] wrapped in a blanket
in a basket.
Mama Mabel put you
in my hands that very day.
You always thought
I called you Mo for Cottonmouth.
Mo was for Moses.
I wasn't ready
to be nobody's mama, neither.
I did try to protect you from
[stutters] all the shit.
I tried... I tried to protect you
from yourself...
but I didn't.
[sniffles]
[stammering] I'm...
You did what you had to do.
I don't know how this happened.
You made a choice... [sighs]
and now we have to pay the price.
Diamondback is here to collect.
Diamond-what?
He's not happy
that Cornell is dead, and...
Luke Cage is still alive.
Cage is in the wind right now,
and I need your help to find him.
Our frame doesn't work...
if he's not there to take the blame.
[stammers] What, you want me
to call the police?
If it comes to that, sure.
But right now...
we have more pressing concerns.
You keep saying "we."
[chuckling] Well, you.
Like it or not...
the business is yours now.
I have nothing to do with all of that.
You are the face now.
And nature abhors a vacuum.
You have to ensure a smooth transition
for all of Cornell's clients,
or it is going to be
straight up chaos for you.
-[radio static]
-[officer] Dispatch, car 77-0-5.
Sighting possible drunk.
Should we engage?
[dispatcher] Is it our suspect?
[officer] We've a black male,
but need verification.
[siren wailing]
[breathing heavily]
Good morning.
Is there a problem?
No. You tell me.
What's your name, son?
[panting] I'm just taking a walk.
Minding my business.
I need to see some ID.
To walk?
Turn around, take down your hoodie.
-May I ask why?
-Because I said so.
[sighs]
[phone beeps]
-Oh, shit. It is him!
-On the ground, now!
Hands behind your back.
Get on the ground, now!
I'm really sorry, guys.
[officer] You're under arrest!
[groans]
[dispatcher] Car 7-7-0-5, come in.
Car 7-7-0-5, come in.
[screaming]
[panting]
Lemonade?
-Popular drink.
-And it still is.
That story in my file, too?
What story?
You know,
I don't believe everything I read?
I wanna hear you tell it.
[Misty] Summer of '95,
and every other car was playing either
"Shook Ones" or "Ice Cream."
I was hanging out
with my cousin, Cassandra.
My mother told us never to walk around
the neighborhood by ourselves...
but it was hot, and I was thirsty.
And she was taking way too long
talking to some cute boy.
So...
I went to Ruiz Bodega by myself
and got a lemonade.
When I got back, she was gone.
It took the cops two weeks
to find her body.
Disfigured, beaten.
The boy, Mike Jones,
ran a train on her with his crew.
Nobody snitched.
Cops didn't push.
They didn't really give a shit.
She was just another poor, worthless bitch
from the Polo Grounds.
[breathing heavily]
So that's why you became a cop?
I apply foot to ass,
and match lead for lead.
I put murderers in handcuffs.
I don't just seek justice,
I stalk it.
And that much should go in my record.
With your resume,
you could've been downtown years ago.
Hell, you could've been a fed,
but you chose to stay in Harlem.
I know this place,
I know the players...
and I can make a difference here.
Or use some
of those old school connections
to make a little money on the side,
like your partner.
I didn't know anything about Scarfe.
Or anything he was doing.
He didn't buy new clothes,
no new watch, no new girlfriend,
no loose talk, nothing.
But he'd been working
for Cottonmouth for years.
And I trusted him...
so I didn't see it.
And neither did anybody else
in this damn department.
So why do I get singled out for it?
Because you were the closest to him.
It's written all over your face.
Not seeing it bothered you, didn't it?
'Cause seeing is my thing, right?
That's what made me
such a good point guard.
'Cause I could see everything in my head.
I knew exactly where people were gonna be,
so I put the ball
right where it needed to go.
But you couldn't see Scarfe
for what he was.
Or were you blinded by your emotions?
[scoffs] You wouldn't say that
if I was a man.
-Oh, that is not true.
-Bullshit!
Male cops can screw cop groupies
in the back of their unmarked
or their RMP,
and you guys cheer.
They get drunk
and fight each other in the parking lot,
and it's called blowing off steam.
There's always a double standard.
[inhales] And you never screwed anyone
that you shouldn't have
while you were on the job?
No.
But you choked out a witness.
Own your shit.
You went renegade
when you went after Luke Cage alone.
And it got...
[scoffs]
way deeper than it should have.
And this guy took the control
away from you when he took your gun.
[gasps]
Then you're in a room
alone with Miss Temple,
and she insults you,
and you lost control...
and you know it.
I need a break.
[exhales deeply]
[indistinct chatter]
[saw whirring]
[Mariah] What happened in here?
You know what happened here.
Same as you.
Sorry to hear about Cornell.
Hope they get that bastard.
He's bad for business.
Well, yeah, I'm not here
to talk about Luke Cage.
Well, it took a lot for you to walk
through those doors without your people.
Chico, please.
I was from around here
long before you even knew what that was.
Besides, we all contribute to this city,
one way or another.
Contribute?
I never trusted your cousin...
and I trust you even less.
Pretending to rise
to the right side of the law.
Girl, I know where you're from.
That stank don't come off too easy.
The thing my cousin built
needs to continue.
And you're gonna be the one to run it?
No. I need help.
Me?
Not just you.
Cornell had steady customers.
[Domingo chuckles]
Not everybody liked your cousin.
I mean, God respect the dead.
Yeah, he got it done
without a lot of needless violence.
I want everybody to come to the table
so I can discuss a transition.
Maybe even a buyout.
There was something dangerous
behind your eyes...
and this is it, huh?
Cornell was who he was.
I want something different.
I don't want to have
to look over my shoulder, Domingo.
Gather all the bosses.
I have a proposition
that will benefit us all.
[inhales sharply]
So who gets an invitation?
[breathing deeply]
Jacques Alef with the Macoute...
Neville Barnwell with the Yardies.
Juan Carlos Castro with the Cubanos...
And the Chinese, they got their own thing
going on downtown,
but Peter Hong with the Koreans...
he might wanna holla.
When?
Oh, that's gonna take me a few days.
Tonight.
[softly] Abalone shells.
[sighs]
[Luke whispering] Claire.
Claire.
[groaning]
[softly] Everybody's looking for you.
How did you not get caught?
-He shot you again?
-[groans]
Ugh!
Why in the hell is this guy
trying to kill you so bad?
He's even going through the trouble of
using bullets that could actually do it.
Willis was my, uh...
my best friend.
He's, uh...
He's delusional.
Delusional and pissed.
Let me see.
[groaning]
[police sirens wailing in distance]
[Claire] Ugh, your wound
is getting infected.
-[grunts]
-This looks bad.
-Who are you?
-What do you mean?
[sighs] I should say,
"What are you?"
I'm looking at your cells
and I've never seen anything like it.
I've been looking up sea shells to better
understand the structure of your skin.
Like I said...
you're amazing.
Only one man knows the science.
And I am not going back to prison.
And is his name
Dr. Noah Burstein?
[sighs] You gave me Reva's hard drive,
remember?
-Do you talk to him?
-No.
Reva kept tabs...
just in case someone got cute.
But I am not ready to reopen that door.
I don't think that you have
very much choice.
We need to get you out of here.
My mom has a car.
And we haven't totaled that one yet.
[chuckles and groans]
[Alex] Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Madam Councilwoman?
Not anymore.
Have you seen the emails?
The interview requests?
Even Thembi Wallace
wants another sit-down.
Never.
Can I show you something?
Hit the news about 20 minutes ago.
He attacked two cops and stole their cars.
-Cage?
-The cops are alive.
They GPS'd the car,
but someone leaked the footage.
It was too hot to hold back.
-[man screaming]
-[thuds]
Huh. [chuckles]
It's amazing.
I know it's tough seeing the man
that killed your cousin.
[Mariah sighs]
They'll get him, Alex.
Justice will prevail.
You know, Cornell taught me to be strong,
so I will be strong.
People understand the threat...
the kind of person you're up against.
They're not talking about the money,
or where it came from.
I think if you play this right,
you could have supporters
with even deeper pockets behind you,
who see this as a political issue,
and see your cousin as a brave man
who stood up to a freak.
You would use my personal tragedy
for strategic political advantage?
-Madam Councilwoman, I--
-I taught you well.
Go home, Alex.
I'm letting you off early.
[Alex] Thank you.
What happened out there...
that bothers you the most?
I lost my gun.
Other than that,
I wouldn't say it bothered me.
I saw your hand shake the first time
you looked at this photo. Why?
Because I remembered
seeing myself see myself...
wondering what I would look like
in a casket.
I mean, how the hell did I get there?
He got the drop on me.
How in the hell did he do that?
I could have disarmed him,
like, ten different ways.
Why didn't I do any of that?
I couldn't help anybody,
not even my damn self.
He shoved my gun in my face...
and I froze.
And you know what I thought about?
I thought about Pop's funeral.
I thought about my own funeral.
I thought about my father,
and what people would think about me.
And this guy...
this guy was smiling...
[voice breaking]
while he was toying with my life.
It was fun for him.
I didn't have control,
and maybe I never did.
And when Claire
was talking sideways about me,
all I wanted to do
was take my control back.
Oh, my God.
[exhales] What have I done?
[inhales sharply]
[sniffles]
It's like anything else
you've learned on the job.
It's ugly...
but you can't move your gaze.
You have to look...
and learn.
That's how you get answers.
That's how you win.
[sighs heavily]
[groaning]
[Luke breathing heavily]
-[Luke] It's getting harder to breathe.
-[exhales]
-[groans] These wounds are kicking my ass.
-Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You know, it passed before,
it's gonna pass again, okay?
I promise.
Can I get that
with the money-back guarantee?
-[both chuckle]
-[grunts]
Breathe.
[breathing deeply]
See? You got this.
What if this is a one-way trip?
Hey, hey, you are gonna make it.
You hear me?
You're gonna make it just fine.
We're gonna fix this.
Don't even.
-You're not dying in my mom's car.
-[chuckles]
Okay?
[sighs]
It's the part you can't fix
that's bothering me.
What do you mean?
Willis.
Willis Stryker.
He thinks he's my brother.
Diamondback.
He's... he's gotta be lying
about my father. He's...
He's... He can't be my brother.
[knocking on door]
[Claire] Hi.
Sorry to ring so late.
My name is Sandra Lopez.
I'm currently majoring in prison studies
at Boston University, and, uh,
I was just wondering
if I could ask you
a few questions
about your time at Seagate.
My friend said that you worked there?
Your friend was mistaken.
-What friend?
-Carl Lucas.
I don't know anybody by that name.
He's alive, Doc.
-That's impossible.
-Your experiment worked.
It changed him.
Changed how?
You should see for yourself.
-He's here?
-Yes.
Where is he?
What's up, Doc?
I've always wanted to say that.
Let's get him out of here.
-[groaning]
-Put him on the couch.
[Claire] Come on.
Just a few more steps.
-[Luke groaning]
-[Claire] Easy, easy.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Take it easy.
Breathe.
Breathe. Okay.
[Luke sighs]
You've got no scars.
Nothing.
That lab was totally destroyed.
You mean it worked?
Yes... and no.
Until last night...
[breathing heavily]
I was bulletproof.
Jesus Christ, kid.
What did this to you?
They shot me with some crazy bullets.
They exploded inside of him.
[Burstein] He should be dead.
My skin is now tough...
like armor.
I think maybe what makes him stronger
is also pushing the shrapnel
deeper into his organs.
Trust me, it is impossible
to cut into his skin.
Look, I don't know what it is
that you think I can do for you.
My lab is not my lab anymore.
I wouldn't know where to begin.
What if we can help you with that?
Reva took this.
[Burstein gasps]
She shouldn't have done that. [sighs]
Can you unlock it?
[sighs]
[Burstein] Oh, my God.
It's all here. Everything.
Everything you need?
Everything I lost.
So much more....
[Claire sighs]
Reva died for this, didn't she?
Luke refuses to talk about it.
[coughing]
[Claire] You okay?
[gasps]
[Luke groans] They're killing me.
Doc, you figure this shit out.
[Luke groaning]
[Burstein] Watch your step.
-All right. Can you stand a second?
-[Claire] I got him.
[Claire] Okay.
[Luke] All right.
[breathing heavily]
What is all this stuff?
[Burstein] During the cover-up,
I stole whatever I could.
[Luke] What cover-up?
They couldn't advertise Rackham's death,
or the explosion
that supposedly killed you,
or Reva's data dump,
so they... they killed the whole thing.
-Here, let's set him down.
-[breathing heavily]
I was so close to a breakthrough.
That all ended when they thought
you were dead.
-[all groaning]
-[Burstein] I started again from scratch,
but never came close
to replicating the Seagate incident.
[stammers] I'm a nurse.
I know the drill. I can help.
[Luke groans]
Why me?
Why did you pick me?
Because you were strong.
Stronger than most.
[Luke] That's not what Reva said.
She said she begged you to do it.
There's more to it than that,
and you know it.
She begged me, but you were
already tabbed for the program.
-Didn't Reva tell you about this?
-No.
That's not gonna do anything.
-[Burstein grunts]
-[scalpel snaps]
Oh, my God.
Look, I gotta get a blood sample
to cross check with Reva's data.
Your DNA may be the X factor
that made this whole thing work.
-You mean, it could only work for Luke?
-[Burstein] Yeah, maybe.
This wound is too septic
to get a decent sample.
Are you saying
you can't recreate what you did?
It's not as straightforward as that.
You know, penicillin, the X-ray machine...
[groans]
[Burstein] ...the smallpox vaccine,
pacemaker, even... even...
even Viagra.
Those were accidents.
It's the same with Carl.
This could work.
If you go down his throat...
We can puncture his mucus membrane.
-Exactly.
-I like the way you think.
I don't.
Sorry.
All right. Put your head back.
Just open your mouth.
I'll try to make this quick.
Breathe through your nose.
[groaning]
[Burstein] Easy, easy.
Oh, here we go.
[Burstein] It's working.
[Ridley] You see that?
-That's my shield.
-No, no, no.
That's not your shield.
That shield belongs
to the city of New York and its people.
And when you lose control,
go upside somebody's head
because you had a bad day...
or you feel powerless...
-or you screw the wrong person--
-I didn't screw anybody.
Come on, now.
You don't deserve to represent
the people of New York,
let alone protect them.
That's not true and you know it.
I do.
Look, we're wired differently.
We run towards gunfire.
We drink when we're sad.
We screw when we're mad.
And people hate us until they need us.
And I hate that.
But I love it, too.
[Ridley] We walk a higher path.
It's not simple.
It's very hard.
And that is why
people will always need us.
Hero of Harlem, my ass.
[sighs]
Look, if we're talking about a right path,
it's not just about Luke Cage.
You haven't even acknowledged the guy
that held a gun to my head last night.
We will find out who that is.
And we still need
to talk about Mariah Dillard.
She is not innocent in all this.
Look, Mariah's not on the run for murder,
assaulting two police officers.
I need you to focus
on bringing in Luke Cage.
Bullets bounce right off of him.
Reason is the only thing
that's gonna work.
And it has to come
from somebody he trusts.
[Ridley chuckles]
[laughs]
Go get him.
You ready for this?
Like I said, ready as ever.
You need to understand where you are here.
If they sense any weakness,
any hesitation...
you're not just done politically...
you're done permanently.
You're late.
I'm not.
Looks like I'm right on time.
Wagwan?
Now that my cousin is gone,
I'm making a few changes.
I loved my cousin,
but I didn't like what he did.
Until he stopped serving you.
Cut the crap, lady.
What do you want to tell us?
I'm out.
My family is no longer to be associated
with what you all do.
I need to move
in a more legitimate direction.
[Jacques] Need?
That's a weak hand you're playing.
My cousin has valuable assets
and connections.
I'll give them to you...
for a price.
-And you walk away?
-I walk away.
Why do I find that hard to believe?
Because you're smart and stupid
at the same time.
Diamondback, what are you doing here?
You invited me...
by not inviting me.
-Excuse me?
-Now, Peter...
when you don't buy my wares,
or Jacques...
when you get them at a cheaper price
from my competitors,
you're messing with my money.
And that pisses me off.
-[gunshot]
-[Jacques] Hey, man!
[grunting]
[Stryker] Anybody else not made it
to confessional this week?
-[men breathing heavily]
-Your men outside are dead.
Your greed superseded your common sense.
So now, I have the pulpit.
Rich men, camel and needles.
What do you want?
Hey, Neville...
[in mock Jamaican accent]
if you wanna test me...
[stammering] Ease up, man.
I got no hackle with you now.
-We'll listen what you have to say.
-Don't bother.
Just by being here,
you're already dead.
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
Two for the price of one.
[Domingo] What are you doing, man?
You're gonna start a war.
"And then many will fall away,
and they will betray each other
and hate one another.
And many false prophets will arise
and lead many astray.
But the one who endures to the end...
he will be saved."
[Domingo] You're crazy.
Crazy would be leaving you alive
to run a very profitable drug business.
But I got no beef with your cousins
down south of the border...
so today is your lucky day.
But you...
You...
you're full of crazy.
I just killed four people, and...
you didn't even flinch.
You don't scare me.
No...
I don't think I do.
Tell me why we should be friends.
Luke Cage.
Clearly, we both have issues with him.
I heard he killed your cousin.
Allegedly.
Rest assured, I will end him
when the time is right.
But the time is not right.
Have you even seen the dashboard footage
that's all over the news?
You don't you see the opportunity?
You see a man you want dead who won't die.
I see a marketer's dream.
Why spend all your time
killing and intimidating
your criminal customers in the dark
when you should be selling guns
to police departments in the light?
Guns that can handle these new threats.
Go on.
Word is you have a weapon
that can take him down.
Kill Luke Cage.
But if you do, and you go big,
everyone else will come to you
to help take down
the rest of these super-freaks
that are upsetting
the natural order of things.
You gotta go big pharma on this shit.
You invent the disease,
then you sell the cure.
[chuckles]
Oh, Shades, now I see you were right.
I like how she thinks.
And who better to broker the deals, hmm?
No. No, I'm out of this.
[Stryker] No...
You're in...
way into this...
until I decide otherwise.
Domingo.
Sorry about the mess, hermano.
But I have no doubt...
you have people that can clean up.
Why am I still alive, man?
[Stryker] 'Cause no one's coming at me.
They'll ask around, so tell 'em...
I'll murderize everything in sight.
'Cause I don't care and I won't quit.
You can't bargain with me.
You buy or you die.
[Stryker sighs]
You think Peter Luger's is still open?
[R&B song playing]
[singing]
[inaudible]
That footage of Cage and the cops?
It went viral.
What do you want to do about it?
That's great...
That's great.
He's got nowhere to run now.
We'll find him.
-It's all coming together.
-But there's gonna be a--
Shh!
I like this song.
[R&B song continues]
[song continues]
[Burstein] We were working on creating
this artificial skin for burn victims.
We used a process called CRISPR
to fuse the subject's DNA
with another DNA to gain its attributes.
The foreign DNA
was abalone shell, wasn't it?
Uh, yeah.
Where did you do your residency?
145th Street. Um...
and my fellowship in Hell's Kitchen.
Well, you're correct.
We already used abalone to build
better combat equipment for soldiers.
And to genetically enhance
the durability, pliability,
and healing properties of human epidermis.
Okay, so why are these bullets
penetrating his skin then?
Are they dipped in something?
Uh, well, perhaps.
But more likely
because of what they were made from.
You see, uh,
abalone is nearly impenetrable, but...
[Claire] Right.
...its stacked plates can be pushed apart
under the right circumstances.
[Luke] Like what?
Hey.
[stammers] During the experiment,
your skin cells were bonded
with hydrogen covalent bonds
at the exact point of acidity,
-temperature and saline concentration...
-English, please.
Well, see, I can replicate
exactly the acidity
and the saline portions of the experiment
with the information
that's on the Reva drive that you brought.
But the...
the wild card is the temperature.
Because of what Albert Rackham did,
turning up the heat on the bath,
I have no gauge as to the temperature
that catalyzed the experiment.
How are you going
to get this stuff out of me?
Right. Uh... [sighs]
Imagine that your skin
works like a form of Velcro,
uh, under a sort of lock and key.
And in order to cut through it,
he's got to weaken the lock and key,
so we can remove the shrapnel.
-How do you plan to do that?
-[Claire sighs]
Uh, I'm going to dip your skin
in boiling acid,
and then, uh, remove the shrapnel.
What? I've tried it with animals.
He's putting me in a rotisserie spit?
Um...
I think he wants to deep fry you...
like a turkey.
Now, look, we're only gonna have
a short window to do this, uh,
before your skin closes up again.
Just so we're clear,
what could go wrong?
[Burstein] Well, your... your skin
could peel off like wax paper, and, uh,
after about ten seconds,
you'd beg me to put a bullet in your head
because the pain would be so bad.
But your...
your head looks fine, so I... I guess
the bullet would ricochet off your skull.
[Claire sighs]
Sweet Christmas.
If the procedure gets too painful,
just raise your hand in a fist
and I'll shut it down, okay?
Like this?
-Right on.
-[Luke chuckles]
You trust this dude?
Hell no.
[breathing heavily]
If anything happens to me,
if anything goes wrong,
make sure he doesn't keep Reva's data.
It cannot fall into the wrong hands.
I don't care if you have to kill him.
I got you.
But let's not go there, okay?
I'm serious.
-It's too dangerous.
-[sighs]
We can't have guys like me
running around on every corner.
What are you talking about?
There's nobody like you.
All right, let's go.
[Claire] Okay, okay.
[air hissing]
Good? Okay.
Good.
[Burstein] Keep your hands clear.
[Claire] Yeah.
[Burstein] All right. Down.
Hang in there.
It's going to be okay.
[muffled screaming]
How long do we keep him down?
I don't know.
Just have to let the acid do its work.
-Now?
-Not yet.
[muffled screaming continues]
-[beeping rapidly]
-[alarm blaring]
What are you doing?
He's not ready yet.
All right. Hold on.
Damn it.
-Dip him again.
-What?
Again! Again!
One more.
[muffled screaming]
-[rapid beeping]
-[alarm blaring]
-[Claire] We're losing him.
-It's not working.
[muffled screaming]
Why isn't it working?
[Claire] We're losing him!
[Burstein] It's not working!
[beeping continues]
-What do we do?
-I don't know.
-[flatlining]
-Shit!
[grunting]