[Green] All right, here's
the plan. Triple-cuff him.
Alpha team, you take point
positions in the convoy.
Bravo team will bring up the rear.
Remember, we're clear to engage,
so if he so much as looks
at you funny, light him up.
[officer 1] Copy that.
You hear that, freak? I got
something special for you.
This isn't necessary.
Yeah, it is.
[indistinct chatter]
[groans]
No. You need to let us
finish. Ms. Knight. Ms. Knight!
It's Detective Knight, and I'm fine.
I need a moment with Cage.
[Green] Misty, we have special orders.
Mario, come on.
I was just held hostage.
I just need a minute with him.
All right. We'll be right
here. We got your back.
[officer 2] Clear!
You going down.
It's about damn time.
Cottonmouth, Officer Albini,
what just popped off in there...
Look, your friend is in the wind.
They've got public enemy number one in
handcuffs for the whole world to see...
so they're not looking for anybody else.
Every officer in your detail
has those modified Judas bullets.
I wouldn't try anything if I were you...
before I got to the precinct.
You're not that crazy, are you?
Always.
Take his ass to jail.
Come on.
[officer 2] All right,
let's go. We're rolling.
[sirens wailing]
Three sets of cuffs?
Isn't that overkill?
The camera's on. We need to
look like we're in control.
[officer 1] It's a shit detail.
You'd think ESU would be in the
back with those guns pointed at him.
We've got the same guns
and bullets they do.
You know, my wife says
it's the end of days,
people like him popping up.
They've been saying that
since Eve bit the apple.
Cage? He's evolution.
[stammers] Whatever
he is, it's just scary.
Makes me feel small. Insignificant.
Insecure?
You know what they say. Once
you go black, you never go back.
At least that's what your
wife keeps telling me.
I was fast asleep when she came home.
Your daughter already wore me out.
[officer 2] Just sit tight.
God damn it.
Homeless lady. Can't they
move her out of the way?
[Green on loudspeaker] You are
in the path of a police convoy.
Clear the road immediately.
[tires screeching]
[officer 3] Come on!
[Green on loudspeaker] Cage
must not escape. Fire at will!
[officer 3] Go, go, go, go, go!
He went down the south side.
[guns firing]
[officers shouting indistinctly]
[officer 4 on radio] Somebody
give me a sitrep right now!
[officer 5] Team two...
Let's go, let's go!
[officers shouting indistinctly]
[sirens wailing]
[shotgun cocks]
Young cops always wanna chase somebody.
Me, I'd rather be where
they're already going.
They told us these Judas bullets
can kill someone like you.
You don't want to die? Don't run.
I'd rather die than go back to prison.
[scoffs] Live free or die?
You wanna get all New
Hampshire about this shit?
Fine with me.
- Cop killers don't survive these streets.
- I didn't kill a cop.
My problem isn't with you or yours.
It's much bigger than that.
Some people are calling
you a hero for what you did.
Connie's, Pop's...
I'm no hero.
But I do need to take out the
person responsible for all this.
- You don't recognize me, do you?
- [sirens continue wailing]
I've seen you at Pop's before.
Pop cut my hair for 12 years.
He didn't think he was a hero, either.
He was just trying to do some
right after years of wrong.
I hope I'm right about you.
More people rooting
for you than you think.
- What are you gonna tell your people?
- The truth.
I had you in my sights,
but you outran me.
I'm getting old.
Luke?
You better catch that
slippery son of a bitch.
[theme music playing]
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
Moments after the tumultuous
events at Harlem's Paradise,
fugitive and alleged cop killer Luke
Cage was brought out in handcuffs.
And now the city's most...
[Turk] Hey, I'm glad
you called me, Willis.
Luke Cage is on the run.
They got Shades in bracelets,
but they're gonna be onto
you before long, brother.
Best believe that.
Getting ghost and liquidizing
your cash, that was the right move.
- Luke Cage must be approached with...
- [Stryker] I wouldn't touch any of that.
[door opens]
[door closes]
People don't test me more than once.
- I overstand.
- Hmm.
What you need me for?
I understand you're a man
of discretion and taste
with numerous connections willing
to pay full price for my wares.
I can still collect from the shadows.
- Bad news, Diamondback.
- Take those off!
I went to your crib. The
files you had are gone.
[choking]
[coughs]
[continues choking]
[laughs]
- I had you, didn't I?
- [coughing]
[Stryker continues laughing]
I couldn't resist.
I like you, Zip.
You've got ambition.
It'll take you far...
as long as you stay in your place.
The first of the 48 laws of power.
Never outshine the master.
That was the mistake Shades made.
He questioned me. He doubted
me. He tried to reach too far.
He was on some Icarus shit.
Do you know who that is?
Yeah, he had a verse with Kendrick.
- Right?
- No...
Icarus was the boy who flew too
close to the sun with fake wings.
Shades is no problem.
He's still in custody.
Not for long.
- You gonna blow the joint up?
- No, he's going to be bailed out.
The hell for? That don't make no sense!
See? The questioning.
That's how it starts.
[sighs]
I'm gonna have an opening.
You gonna step up?
I'm down to do whatever you need.
- No problem.
- [Stryker] Good boy.
So are you down?
I'm down.
As long as the business is
business, I'm good with it.
Till then, I'm out of here, man.
Show Turk out, Zip.
Romeo would roll over in his grave,
the way you hop-skipping
with these cats nowadays.
He was a man on these
streets. You's a boy.
What the hell are you talking about?
You're down here in
his pocket, same as me.
I'm doing business with him, yes.
But I ain't his boy. And I
definitely ain't his bitch.
- [door slams]
- [Zip scoffs]
These old-ass niggas talkin' about
shit they don't even know about.
So... what's in the box?
One of the seven deadly sins, my boy...
which I plan to unleash
on dear old Carl.
Which one?
Wrath.
[in Spanish] This Diamondback
needs to be dealt with.
Ernesto is right, Domingo. This
is the perfect time to do it.
We've got the muscle.
Plus, with the Cuban, Jamaican,
Dominican and Haitian leaders dead,
we can control the
drugs, guns, all of it...
and walk out like kings.
[in English] I was there
when he took them all out.
Right next door.
We got the drugs.
We got that money.
But with the guns, we
can control everything.
Here, the islands, further south...
We'd be unstoppable. Hmm?
[Ernesto in Spanish]
So what are you saying?
[in English] We take him out.
We go after what's ours.
[Ernesto scoffs and chuckles]
Let's go find Diamondback.
[sighs]
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [officer 1] Turn and face the camera.
[officer 2] All right,
let's go. Move it.
You're supposed to be in the hospital.
Push yourself too hard too soon and
you could make it worse, you know.
- I appreciate your concern.
- No, you don't.
I need you at 100%.
I need to prove Luke Cage is innocent.
Well, the hostages
have all been consistent
that Luke Cage never
held them at gunpoint.
[Misty] He was set up.
You know it, Priscilla.
Half this damn department knows it.
We need to be going
after Willis Stryker.
Well, then why is Luke Cage running?
He's a black man being
chased by the cops...
oh, with special bullets.
Accused of killing a cop,
and you're asking why
he's running? Come on.
Look at how relaxed
Hernan "Shades" Alvarez is.
He knows he's not going
anywhere anytime soon,
so he's resting up.
He knows he's guilty.
See this perp?
Look how his foot is bouncing. Nervous.
- No wonder his street name is Sugar.
- [chuckles]
I don't even have to say a word,
and here come the waterworks.
He's probably innocent...
or less guilty than whoever
he's about to give up.
That's a detectives' wives' tale.
You can't prove guilt
or innocence by that.
Oh, but you can...
- because Luke gave you his word.
- Luke...
Right now, his actions are
speaking louder than his words.
Luke Cage...
saved my life.
I don't dispute that we should
be bringing in Diamondback,
but to get to the truth, we
need to bring them both in.
[indistinct chatter]
Okay, well, let me lead the charge.
Make sure Luke is brought in safely.
He threw away his chance when
he jumped out that damn van.
Now they will shoot him on
sight with the mayor's blessing.
You know what? At least let
me take a crack at Shades.
He's in deep with all the players.
He doesn't scare me.
- Detective...
- I can handle him.
You just got shot.
- I need you to go home, get some rest.
- [sighs]
I'll interview Shades.
[Mariah] My grandmother
loved Harlem's Paradise.
She took care of all the small details.
She loved it.
From the murals...
the glasswork, all the way
down to the table linens.
No fine point was overlooked.
- [glass shattering]
- This was her legacy.
My family's in tatters, and it's
all because of Diamondback. Shit!
[stammers]
Uh, I know, I know...
[sighs] I need to get
out in front of this.
Release a statement about Damon
Boone and how much I respected him.
That is not what I was gonna say.
Well, yeah, just... Please, no lectures.
This is just a thing.
Things can be rebuilt, and when you
do, you rebuild it as your legacy.
Not just the clubs.
I want to be a part of that.
Here's what I think.
Controlling the narrative is everything.
We can't have any loose threads.
So anyone who might have overheard
anything you said to
Diamondback or Shades in here...
is a threat.
You're absolutely correct.
[chuckles]
How may I be of service?
I wouldn't want you to
do anything untoward.
Never.
Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
I don't have time for this.
- [cash rustling]
- [man 1] Don't move.
He'll blow your head
off. He's crazy like that.
Don't try no shit.
My bad, Meth. I grew
up on that Wu-Tang shit.
- But you know how it is.
- [Method Man] Are you serious?
Are you really trying to
have a conversation right now?
I'm just tryin'... I'm just
sayin'... You're the man, yo.
Pull your mask down! You supposed
to be watchin' the damn door, Bryce!
What I say about using my
government name, Michael?
[door chimes]
Damn, homie. You look like you
went through a cheese grater.
Oh, snap, you Luke...
- [gun firing]
- [bullet ricocheting]
- [glass shattering]
- [gasping]
I ain't mean that.
Give me your phone.
The phone, fool.
Yo, my bad, man. You know, I
just got a little nervous and shit
- when you threw my mans across the...
- [grunts]
It's you.
- Yeah, it's you.
- [chuckles]
No, man, it's you.
Yo, man, "P.L.O. Style" was
my joint back in the day.
Sweet Christmas. [chuckles]
Yeah, man, one second.
Hey. It's me.
Yeah, they'll be looking for me.
I'll lay in the cut.
I'll see you in a few.
You a double XL?
[scoffs] Way ahead of you, homie,
Call the cops.
I know a lot of people who would
pay you for this kind of protection.
They can keep their money.
Salute.
[laughs]
You ever see anything like that before?
Harlem, baby.
Harlem.
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Candace] Detective Knight?
- Candace?
- Yeah.
What number are you calling me from?
A prepaid phone I picked up from CVS.
I need to see you.
- Come into the precinct.
- No. No.
You saw how quickly Mariah sent
that lawyer and got me out of there.
You didn't wanna talk to me
before. What makes you trust me now?
Because Luke Cage does.
He saved my life. And
you saw right through me.
- You want the truth, right?
- Where are you?
- Look, if you can't help...
- Candace.
Tell me a place, and I will be there.
[Ridley] You should be at Rikers
right now, but I held you...
because I think you
have something to say.
Lawyer.
[chuckles] I know your
record, Mr. Alvarez.
Came up in Harlem, rolled around
with Cottonmouth in the late '90s,
spent some time at Spofford, Sing Sing,
then you made it to the
big time, went to Seagate.
[sighs]
Lawyer.
Cornell Stokes is dead,
but you're still alive.
And I've never seen an
arraignment happen so quickly.
Two million dollar bail...
and someone paid it in cash.
Who's your new sponsor?
Is it Willis Stryker?
Law...
yer.
You were part of a
hostage situation, Hernan.
Even if your lawyer does get you out...
you won't be walking away from that.
That's multiple kidnapping
and weapons charges.
How does 25 years to life
sound to you? Minimum.
Are you serious?
Yep.
Okay.
[scoffs]
I... I was in the club.
[clears throat]
I saw what happened.
I know who did it.
- Okay.
- [inhales deeply]
We can protect you, but
I need a name to verify.
Who was it?
Was it Stryker?
He goes by...
lawyer.
You need me to spell it?
[laughing]
[door slams]
- You call this safe?
- We're hiding in plain sight.
I've got you. For now.
Lie to me again, Candace, I walk away
from here, and you are on your own.
- It's not bullshit.
- We'll see.
How did you even get out of Harlem's
Paradise without being stopped?
They were so busy trying to
arrest Luke, I just walked away.
So what is it?
What do you need to tell
me that's so important?
[sighs]
I was at the club the
night Cottonmouth died.
I already know that.
I mean right after.
[sighs]
[beeps]
Mariah killed him.
[Shades] The trash bag is for
the clothes you're wearing now.
Every stitch goes in. Jewelry, too.
Someone from Spurlock's
will incinerate them.
The secret to any good lie is it
has to run parallel to the truth.
[Misty] How do you know this?
[Candace] I heard them talking about it.
[Shades] Do what I say.
[Candace] The guy who always
wears sunglasses, he was there.
It was his idea to say Luke
Cage killed Cottonmouth.
[grunts]
I was so scared.
I snuck out of there,
back to the lockers.
And, um, I was trying
to calm myself down.
When I went upstairs,
the guy with the glasses
offered me $50,000 to tell a story.
So I told one.
- Why are you coming clean now?
- 'Cause I can't live with this.
Especially after Luke saving my life.
If you can guarantee my safety,
I will testify about
everything I just told you.
[phone beeps]
Mariah scares me more than Cottonmouth.
I asked her if she thought Luke did
it, mostly to see if I could trust her.
To see if she would tell me the truth.
She looked me right
in my eye and said...
"You never know what
anyone is capable of."
[breath trembling] It
was the way she said it.
She... she would kill me if
she knew I was speaking to you.
I truly believe that.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm gonna nail Mariah
Dillard's ass to the wall.
- Who else knows that you're here?
- Just my friend Leslie.
Don't call anyone else, not even Leslie.
As a matter of fact, give me your phone.
Come on.
Okay. Now, I picked this
up... on the way, just in case.
It's already got my
number programed in there,
so if I call or text, you know it's me.
Is your arm okay?
[sighs] My trigger finger is just fine.
Come on, let's go.
- Where?
- Soledad's.
Her daughter Claire
is the one who treated your
ankle at Harlem's Paradise.
She'll be there, too.
I'm gonna take you there myself.
[Method Man] No lie. Bullets
was flying everywhere and shit.
You trying to tell me that
those are bullet holes?
Man, Meth, I love you,
but get out of here.
I... I don't believe that.
HB, I thought the same thing...
until shorty pulled the
biscuit and let two off on Cage
and they bounced off.
Bullets ricochetin' and shit.
[stammers] Look, I'm
telling y'all the truth.
I see y'all over there,
y'all don't believe it.
Trust me, it's the truth.
[stutters] And after he
smacked fire out these dudes,
he left the hoodie, told me
and Gomez to call the police.
You know I ain't calling
no po-po. Then he bounced.
- Say word.
- Word, Sway. I'm telling you.
He even balled the dude's
gun up like some old homework.
But my thing is, though, if he
innocent, so what he running for?
Bulletproof always gonna
come second to being black.
HB, you should know
that. You from Jers. Jers!
Wow! Sound like he
stunted on you right there.
He did stunt. It was a
stunt. It was a stunt.
- Why you gotta stunt on me?
- [laughs]
No, I mean, seriously.
Seriously, though, what I'm just
saying, like, if that was me...
- [Heather B] Right.
- And I was on the run.
- Why even get involved?
- [Sway] Hmm.
But he did.
And those dudes was nervous,
so anything could've happened.
As far as I'm concerned,
Luke Cage saved my life, man.
That's what's up, man.
You know what, that don't
sound like no cop killer to me.
For real, for real.
You know, there's somethin'
powerful about seeing a black man
that's bulletproof and unafraid.
- Come on, y'all. You know?
- Yeah, yeah.
[Method Man] Streets
got mad love for Cage.
I got mad love for Cage, man,
and... and he one of ours.
Yeah, yeah. But you know what?
We got mad love for you, too.
- No doubt.
- You one of ours, man.
You know, the show's almost
over, man. You gonna spit for us?
- Of course.
- Oh, man! He 'bout to spit!
- Citizens, you are in for a treat.
- [hip-hop music playing]
One of the best to pick up the
mic, the one and only Method Man!
Hey, yo, Sway. You all ready?
I'mma dedicate this one to the hardest
individual on the street right now.
Luke Cage, you already know.
"Bulletproof Love" your
way, brother. Let's get it.
Listen.
♪ Man, it is what it is ♪
♪ Can't understand a man If
you ain't lived what he lived ♪
♪ Roaches in the crib Ain't
got no food up in the fridge ♪
♪ Plus the crime runnin' rampant
And it's screwin' up the kids ♪
♪ Sway, admit What kind
of paradise is this? ♪
♪ I just want my 40 acres And
some carats on the wrist ♪
♪ But these snakes Is tryin'
to gather in the pit ♪
♪ Where you get a cottonmouth
Pluckin' ashes off the clip ♪
♪ Off the rip, now a challenger exists ♪
♪ And he bulletproof, shoot
What kinda caliber is this? ♪
♪ Got thugs in the store With
the barrel on your lips ♪
♪ Sayin', "Empty out the drawer"
Before he pound you with the grip ♪
♪ Lord, who to call When
no one obeys the law ♪
♪ And there ain't no Iron Man
That can come and save us all? ♪
♪ Power to the people
And Luke Cage the cause ♪
♪ And the cops got it wrong
We don't think Cage involved ♪
♪ Look, dog, a hero, never had one ♪
♪ Already took Malcolm and
Martin This is the last one ♪
♪ I beg your pardon Somebody
pullin' a fast one ♪
♪ Now we got a hero for
hire And he a black one ♪
♪ And bullet-hole
hoodies Is the fashion ♪
♪ We in Harlem's Paradise
Tell the Captain ♪
♪ That I'm about to trade
the mic For a Magnum ♪
♪ Give up my life For
Trayvon to have one ♪
♪ Yeah, 'cause this
is bulletproof love ♪
♪ And you already know
What a bulletproof does ♪
♪ So you can take it
From a bulletproof thug ♪
♪ The hood got his back,
dog Bulletproof love ♪
♪ Blood thicker than mud ♪
♪ And who am I to judge If
you get a gun in the club? ♪
♪ 'Cause you already know
What a bulletproof does ♪
♪ When the hood got your
back, dog Bulletproof love ♪
[music continues playing]
Shout out to Pop. RIP, my brother.
The streets is crazy right
now, you know what I'm sayin'?
People say we don't need another
hero, but now we got one.
Whether you like it or not, Luke
Cage, please believe it, sir,
the streets got your back.
You're already bulletproof love, baby!
Yeah! That was dope. You got it
right here on Sway's Universe.
The homie, Method Man, HB, and
the bulletproof thug, Luke Cage.
Law enforcement is in a
frenzy looking for Luke Cage.
There have been
numerous false sightings,
with some people wearing
hoodies with holes
as a sign of solidarity with an outlaw
some people still perceive to be a hero.
Sway in the Morning.
What's on your mind, citizen?
[man] Yo, I remember when Larry Davis
was on the run back in the day.
Cops came at him 'cause
they were just as corrupt,
dangerous and jacked up as he was.
I don't think we're getting the full
story on Luke Cage yet, for real.
[Sway] I wouldn't put it
past the government, man.
Um, you know, we're gonna be
searching for the answers for you,
and once we get the facts,
we're gonna put it right here
on Sway's Universe, all right?
Thanks for your call, citizen. We
got another person on the line.
- [beeps]
- [smooth jazz playing]
- [man] Now. Come on!
- [woman] All right.
[indistinct shouting]
Oh, come on, man. You
know he's not here.
I understand playing against the computer,
but, um, how do you beat yourself?
Chess is a game of anticipation.
If you know every single possible move,
you can anticipate your adversary's
next move before he does.
Oh.
That's deep.
If we find out you've been hiding
him, there'll be hell to pay.
Yeah, well, just don't break the
hinges on that door on your way out.
I just got it fixed.
[smooth jazz continues on radio]
That was a close shave.
Bad pun.
What the hell did you
even come back for, man?
[sighs] I had to.
For Harlem.
Take care of Diamondback before
he made it bad for everybody.
Well, forget Harlem.
Forget your brother!
You're on the road in a brand
new car and a woman that fine?
And you're bulletproof.
[scoffs] You'd have never
seen my black ass again.
I'd rob the occasional
bank and never look back.
[chuckles]
You got every cop in the
city looking for you, brother.
Negroes writing Luke
Cage ballads and shit.
So... what's the plan?
To box in all the players.
Well...
Shades is in jail.
Mariah's out, but she
ain't exactly on your side.
Now you could tail both of 'em,
but no telling how long that'll take
for them to lead you to your prey.
What about Misty?
No, she's got her hands full already.
She's trying to clear my
name inside the precinct
and bring me in at the same time.
- We gotta be careful with her.
- [sighs]
That leaves you one other option.
Someone else to find Diamondback.
[softly] Here.
Turk.
Turk may be a pawn, but he's not dumb.
If he thinks he's being
set up, he'll disappear.
[dialing]
You let me worry about that.
Hey, Turk, it's Bobby.
Listen, I might be able to get my
hands on about 30 pairs of Jordans.
They're the vintage Air Jordan 5s.
Let's just say they fell
off the back of a truck.
Okay, when?
Who's this?
First name Law, last name Yer.
Must be pretty damn connected to get
a lawyer and not even know who she is.
Membership has its privileges.
[indistinct chatter]
He sprung you?
You think this is funny, don't you?
You got this all figured out, huh?
No...
actually, I don't.
When did Diamondback bring in new hires?
Well, after the club, he
had to change things up.
Recruit some new faces.
I bet while you were inside,
cops tried to do some
recruiting of their own.
Don't ever question my loyalty.
- The man upstairs?
- [scoffs]
You are just full of questions.
Matter of fact...
[groans]
[straining]
[thudding]
[grunting]
[Shades gasping]
[gunshot]
[panting]
[laughs]
Let's go to the penthouse.
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
- [door slams]
- [breath trembling]
I was just following orders!
You're a goddamn puppet.
Who gave you the order?
[grunts]
- Who?
- [grunts]
Diamondback!
You stopped playing your
position. Asked too many questions.
Diamondback said you
needed to be dealt with.
Romeo would be ashamed of you.
[Zip laughing]
You're such a disappointment.
You're the second person
who told me that today.
I'm my own man, Shades.
Tell him yourself.
[chuckles]
Nice.
[sighs] Sorry, Romeo... He had to go.
[sirens wailing in the distance]
It's a good thing her friend
Leslie knew where she was.
- I'm glad you found the park.
- Mmm-hmm.
So where is she now?
She left with Detective Knight.
Traffic got thick and I lost them.
I'm sorry. I'm not used to
doing anything like this.
We'll find her again.
Just knowing that she
can't be trusted is helpful.
You did a good job, Alex.
Hey, you're my rock!
Later.
[cell phone ringing]
What do you want?
[Stryker] That's no way to
speak to a business partner.
After what you did to my club,
do you really think I'm
gonna shuck and jive with you?
You might wanna check your attitude.
If you're not of any use to me,
then you're not useful to anyone.
Shades would tell you,
if he was still alive.
What the hell are you talking about?
I had to let him go.
So now, I'm giving you the chance
to tell me where you stand.
I've taken Shades and Damon Boone
off the table so you can grow.
I'd hate for us to part, too.
I wasn't particularly fond of Shades...
and the death of Damon
Boone, although unnecessary,
was appreciated.
But you need to know this.
I'm out of the political game.
I'm focusing on Harlem's
Paradise. Using it for a...
a power base for community relations.
That's a smart move.
But you've made some dumb ones also.
You should never talk about
murder on an open line.
Open it.
Seed money... for your New
Harlem Renaissance project
and refurbishing the club.
My apologies.
It's a very generous donation...
but nothing in this world is free.
You're right.
My only condition is loyalty.
Stick with me and Harlem will
be remade in your own image.
We'll be doing this for years to come.
Harlem is already in my image.
You staying?
Once I'm finished with
Carl, I'll evaporate.
But don't worry.
You'll still feel the
occasional cool breeze.
Sweet dreams, Mariah.
[door opens]
[sighs]
[door closes]
- [thudding]
- [Turk gasps]
- You ratted out Chico.
- [breathing heavily]
You got Pop killed.
Man, the writing was on the wall.
Somebody would have seen
him. Might as well be me.
How was I supposed to know Tone
was gonna shoot up the shop?
Whole damn world know Pop's
was Switzerland. Forever.
I should crush you.
[chuckles] You won't,
though. You need me.
[inhales sharply] Where's Diamondback?
I don't know... [screaming]
What the... [yelps]
- Hey!
- You still stalling?
[Turk whimpering]
All right! All right!
He's at a warehouse by the Harlem River.
Near 145th, all right?
I gave you what you
wanted! Now let me out!
Sit tight, Mr. Barrett.
Trash pickup is tomorrow.
You can breathe just fine.
There's food in there, too.
[banging]
You can't leave me in here!
There's baby diapers in here, man!
Hey!
Come on!
[door opening]
[door slams]
[Domingo] Looks like you downgraded.
I liked the club better.
I'm a man who needs his space.
Space is a good thing.
- Especially when you come to kill a man.
- [guns cocking]
Whoa, whoa.
[guns cocking]
Someone did your boy
Zip and his two homies.
That's not Cage's style...
so I'm guessing Shades didn't
appreciate you bailing him out.
You know when a rattlesnake is
at its most dangerous, Domingo?
When it's cornered.
I'm gonna rip your head off!
[groans]
[gunshots continue]
- [whirring]
- [chuckles]
"And behold a pale horse...
and he that sat upon
him, his name was Death."
[exhales]
[sniffs]
You really need a security system.
- You waiting for me?
- No.
I bet he told you I was dead.
Diamondback got to you, didn't he?
No, he didn't.
[scoffs]
What are you doing with
a gun? It's not you.
Shut up.
[sighs]
I have something for you.
Figured...
you'd want this.
Your prints... Cornell's blood.
Then you'll have nothing
to blackmail me with.
I don't need it.
We're in this together now.
[bottle thuds]
You and I have come a long way.
You know, sometimes you have to reach
across the aisle to get things done.
You're talking about Luke Cage?
It's incredible... how
much you and I think alike.
We're at war.
And right now, the enemy
of my enemy is my friend.
Maybe. But it might not take.
You did beat his ass
and give him his powers.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And...
Cornell's flunky killed Pop. You
think he really is gonna jump?
Just jump on our bandwagon?
Absolutely.
'Cause we have something that
he wants more than anything.
His old life.
A chance to clear his name. Right here.
If we send Luke after Diamondback
and they kill each other...
all of our problems are swept away.
- [exhales]
- No matter who wins.
[chuckles] Even better.
[Domingo groaning]
I should've known you'd
turn up. [breathing heavily]
What the hell happened here?
Diamondback.
[groaning]
[faint beeping in distance]
[beeping continues]
Sweet sister.
[Luke panting] Slow.
Take it easy.
What did he use?
How did Diamondback do that?
[breathing heavily] Something
I've never seen before.
[siren wailing in the distance]
Even you can't stop him.
[exhales softly]
These just came in.
- [sighs] Elephant punches all over again.
- Mmm-hmm.
That's gotta be Cage, right?
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Luke] Hey, it's me.
You guys find Domingo?
- Yeah.
- Meet me.
Where?
Should I thank you for this?
All credit goes to Diamondback.
I don't suppose we'll find his body.
We found Zip's, though, and two
other thugs in an old building.
Shot up. Right after they
picked up your other boy.
Shades.
Don't you ever get tired
of people getting out?
Yes.
Look, it's not safe for you to be
here. If you don't find Diamondback...
Then he wins, and my life
is forever a living hell.
Is there anything I can do?
See what else Turk knows.
He's in a Dumpster in an alley on 123rd.
Near Mount Olivet and the shop.
A Dumpster?
[sighs]
Even if we handle Diamondback...
he's not gonna forgive us for
framing him for Cornell's death.
We could hurdle that easy.
The only people who know what
really happened in the club
are you and me.
I'll regret that night
for the rest of my life.
You did what you had to do.
You shouldn't regret that.
What were you even doing
at the club that night?
I was going there to kill him.
You beat me to it.
Cornell never needed my political money.
And he was never going to pay it back.
He just wanted me in all the way.
So what are you saying?
He saw things in me... that
I avoided my whole life.
Now I am becoming that
person he always saw...
and I always denied.
You ready?
I stay ready, baby.
I should've kept my coat
on. Hell just froze over.
[door closes]
- Where's Luke Cage?
- I'm right here.
- We have a problem.
- So do I.
I can't decide which one of
you I'm gonna knock out first.
- Where's Diamondback?
- I don't know.
The parley between the three
of us is more important.
You have the nerve to use that term?
Right here? Where Pop died?
Cough up Diamondback's location,
or I'll stomp you like
we were back at Seagate.
Luke, be cool, brother.
Whoa, whoa. No one
needs to stomp anyone.
Pops made this place
Switzerland for a reason.
Cage, we have a mutual enemy,
and the only way to bring him down
is for us all to come together.
There's no way I'm helping you.
We came to offer you a truce.
In exchange for helping
you find Diamondback,
you drop your beef with us.
You both framed me for murder.
There's nothing you can offer me
that's going to make me let that go.
Uh... how about your freedom?
Right here is everything you need
to prove that Diamondback
framed Carl Lucas.
Even if Carl Lucas is exonerated...
Luke Cage is now wanted for
the murder of Cottonmouth.
I'll tell them the truth.
Diamondback killed
Cornell and Damon Boone.
You'll go free.
What the hell is this?
Mariah Dillard, you're under arrest
for the murder of Cornell Stokes.
I thought you said you
were going after Turk?
[Misty] I've been tracking
you since you called.
I wasn't going to let
you just ghost me again.
Hey, hey. Whoa, whoa,
whoa. Shades, back off!
Misty, stand down.
We're working this out.
Oh, so you workin' with them now?
- He knows where Diamondback is.
- I didn't say that.
Well, whatever you know, Hernan, you
should share it with the whole class.
I ain't telling you shit.
Grenade!
[screaming]
[car alarm blaring in distance]
[Mariah coughs]
What the hell?
What type of Jean Paul
Gaultier shit is this?
What are you, a pimp stormtrooper?
No, I'm the angel of death.
- You told him to meet us here?
- No.
Damn! Look at Hernan the cockroach.
Your mama should have named you Pedro.
Shades!
[bullets ricocheting]
[Bobby] God damn it!
I just fixed this place
up all perfect and shit!
Y'all can't take this outside?
- No.
- No!
All right, just... just sayin'.
- Don't let Mariah get away.
- I won't.
Kick his ass, Luke.
You know I'm gonna kill
'em all later, right?
You have to get past me first.
Oh, I don't go past.
I go through.
[both yelling]
[funk music playing]
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com