[Green] All right, here's the plan.
Triple-cuff him.
Alpha team,
you take point positions in the convoy.
Bravo team will bring up the rear.
Remember, we're clear to engage,
so if he so much as looks at you funny,
light him up.
[officer 1] Copy that.
You hear that, freak?
I got something special for you.
This isn't necessary.
Yeah, it is.
[indistinct chatter]
[groans]
No. You need to let us finish.
Ms. Knight. Ms. Knight!
It's Detective Knight, and I'm fine.
I need a moment with Cage.
[Green] Misty, we have special orders.
Mario, come on.
I was just held hostage.
I just need a minute with him.
All right. We'll be right here.
We got your back.
[officer 2] Clear!
You going down.
It's about damn time.
Cottonmouth, Officer Albini,
what just popped off in there...
Look, your friend is in the wind.
They've got public enemy number one
in handcuffs for the whole world to see...
so they're not looking for anybody else.
Every officer in your detail
has those modified Judas bullets.
I wouldn't try anything if I were you...
before I got to the precinct.
You're not that crazy, are you?
Always.
Take his ass to jail.
Come on.
[officer 2] All right, let's go.
We're rolling.
[sirens wailing]
Three sets of cuffs?
Isn't that overkill?
The camera's on.
We need to look like we're in control.
[officer 1] It's a shit detail.
You'd think ESU would be in the back
with those guns pointed at him.
We've got the same guns
and bullets they do.
You know, my wife
says it's the end of days,
people like him popping up.
They've been saying that
since Eve bit the apple.
Cage? He's evolution.
[stammers]
Whatever he is, it's just scary.
Makes me feel small.
Insignificant.
Insecure?
You know what they say.
Once you go black, you never go back.
At least that's what your wife
keeps telling me.
I was fast asleep when she came home.
Your daughter already wore me out.
[officer 2] Just sit tight.
God damn it.
Homeless lady.
Can't they move her out of the way?
[Green on loudspeaker]
You are in the path of a police convoy.
Clear the road immediately.
[tires screeching]
[officer 3] Come on!
[Green on loudspeaker]
Cage must not escape. Fire at will!
[officer 3] Go, go, go, go, go!
He went down the south side.
[guns firing]
[officers shouting indistinctly]
[officer 4 on radio]
Somebody give me a sitrep right now!
[officer 5] Team two...
Let's go, let's go!
[officers shouting indistinctly]
[sirens wailing]
[shotgun cocks]
Young cops always wanna chase somebody.
Me, I'd rather be
where they're already going.
They told us these Judas bullets
can kill someone like you.
You don't want to die?
Don't run.
I'd rather die than go back to prison.
[scoffs] Live free or die?
You wanna get all New Hampshire
about this shit?
Fine with me.
-Cop killers don't survive these streets.
-I didn't kill a cop.
My problem isn't with you or yours.
It's much bigger than that.
Some people are calling you
a hero for what you did.
Connie's, Pop's...
I'm no hero.
But I do need to take out
the person responsible for all this.
-You don't recognize me, do you?
-[sirens continue wailing]
I've seen you at Pop's before.
Pop cut my hair for 12 years.
He didn't think he was a hero, either.
He was just trying to do some right
after years of wrong.
I hope I'm right about you.
More people rooting for you
than you think.
-What are you gonna tell your people?
-The truth.
I had you in my sights, but you outran me.
I'm getting old.
Luke?
You better catch
that slippery son of a bitch.
[theme music playing]
Moments after the tumultuous events
at Harlem's Paradise,
fugitive and alleged cop killer Luke Cage
was brought out in handcuffs.
And now the city's most...
[Turk] Hey, I'm glad you called me,
Willis.
Luke Cage is on the run.
They got Shades in bracelets,
but they're gonna be onto you
before long, brother.
Best believe that.
Getting ghost and liquidizing your cash,
that was the right move.
-Luke Cage must be approached with...
-[Stryker] I wouldn't touch any of that.
[door opens]
[door closes]
People don't test me more than once.
-I overstand.
-Hmm.
What you need me for?
I understand you're a man
of discretion and taste
with numerous connections
willing to pay full price for my wares.
I can still collect from the shadows.
-Bad news, Diamondback.
-Take those off!
I went to your crib.
The files you had are gone.
[choking]
[coughs]
[continues choking]
[laughs]
-I had you, didn't I?
-[coughing]
[Stryker continues laughing]
I couldn't resist.
I like you, Zip.
You've got ambition.
It'll take you far...
as long as you stay in your place.
The first of the 48 laws of power.
Never outshine the master.
That was the mistake Shades made.
He questioned me. He doubted me.
He tried to reach too far.
He was on some Icarus shit.
Do you know who that is?
Yeah, he had a verse with Kendrick.
-Right?
-No...
Icarus was the boy who flew
too close to the sun with fake wings.
Shades is no problem.
He's still in custody.
Not for long.
-You gonna blow the joint up?
-No, he's going to be bailed out.
The hell for?
That don't make no sense!
See? The questioning.
That's how it starts.
[sighs]
I'm gonna have an opening.
You gonna step up?
I'm down to do whatever you need.
-No problem.
-[Stryker] Good boy.
So are you down?
I'm down.
As long as the business is business,
I'm good with it.
Till then, I'm out of here, man.
Show Turk out, Zip.
Romeo would roll over in his grave,
the way you hop-skipping
with these cats nowadays.
He was a man on these streets.
You's a boy.
What the hell are you talking about?
You're down here in his pocket,
same as me.
I'm doing business with him, yes.
But I ain't his boy.
And I definitely ain't his bitch.
-[door slams]
-[Zip scoffs]
These old-ass niggas talkin' about shit
they don't even know about.
So... what's in the box?
One of the seven deadly sins, my boy...
which I plan to unleash on dear old Carl.
Which one?
Wrath.
[in Spanish]
This Diamondback needs to be dealt with.
Ernesto is right, Domingo.
This is the perfect time to do it.
We've got the muscle.
Plus, with the Cuban, Jamaican,
Dominican and Haitian leaders dead,
we can control the drugs,
guns, all of it...
and walk out like kings.
[in English] I was there
when he took them all out.
Right next door.
We got the drugs.
We got that money.
But with the guns,
we can control everything.
Here, the islands, further south...
We'd be unstoppable. Hmm?
[Ernesto in Spanish]
So what are you saying?
[in English] We take him out.
We go after what's ours.
[Ernesto scoffs and chuckles]
Let's go find Diamondback.
[sighs]
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[officer 1] Turn and face the camera.
[officer 2] All right, let's go.
Move it.
You're supposed to be in the hospital.
Push yourself too hard too soon
and you could make it worse, you know.
-I appreciate your concern.
-No, you don't.
I need you at 100%.
I need to prove Luke Cage is innocent.
Well, the hostages
have all been consistent
that Luke Cage
never held them at gunpoint.
[Misty] He was set up.
You know it, Priscilla.
Half this damn department knows it.
We need to be going after Willis Stryker.
Well, then why is Luke Cage running?
He's a black man
being chased by the cops...
oh, with special bullets.
Accused of killing a cop,
and you're asking why he's running?
Come on.
Look at how relaxed
Hernan "Shades" Alvarez is.
He knows he's not going anywhere
anytime soon,
so he's resting up.
He knows he's guilty.
See this perp?
Look how his foot is bouncing.
Nervous.
-No wonder his street name is Sugar.
-[chuckles]
I don't even have to say a word,
and here come the waterworks.
He's probably innocent...
or less guilty
than whoever he's about to give up.
That's a detectives' wives' tale.
You can't prove
guilt or innocence by that.
Oh, but you can...
-because Luke gave you his word.
-Luke--
Right now, his actions
are speaking louder than his words.
Luke Cage...
saved my life.
I don't dispute that we should be
bringing in Diamondback,
but to get to the truth,
we need to bring them both in.
[indistinct chatter]
Okay, well, let me lead the charge.
Make sure Luke is brought in safely.
He threw away his chance
when he jumped out that damn van.
Now they will shoot him on sight
with the mayor's blessing.
You know what?
At least let me take a crack at Shades.
He's in deep with all the players.
He doesn't scare me.
-Detective--
-I can handle him.
You just got shot.
-I need you to go home, get some rest.
-[sighs]
I'll interview Shades.
[Mariah] My grandmother
loved Harlem's Paradise.
She took care of all the small details.
She loved it.
From the murals...
the glasswork,
all the way down to the table linens.
No fine point was overlooked.
-[glass shattering]
-This was her legacy.
My family's in tatters,
and it's all because of Diamondback. Shit!
[stammers]
Uh, I know, I know...
[sighs] I need to get out
in front of this.
Release a statement about Damon Boone
and how much I respected him.
That is not what I was gonna say.
Well, yeah, just--
Please, no lectures.
This is just a thing.
Things can be rebuilt, and when you do,
you rebuild it as your legacy.
Not just the clubs.
I want to be a part of that.
Here's what I think.
Controlling the narrative is everything.
We can't have any loose threads.
So anyone who might have overheard
anything you said to Diamondback
or Shades in here...
is a threat.
You're absolutely correct.
[chuckles]
How may I be of service?
I wouldn't want you
to do anything untoward.
Never.
Okay.
[indistinct chatter]
I don't have time for this.
-[cash rustling]
-[man 1] Don't move.
He'll blow your head off.
He's crazy like that.
Don't try no shit.
My bad, Meth.
I grew up on that Wu-Tang shit.
-But you know how it is.
-[Method Man] Are you serious?
Are you really trying
to have a conversation right now?
I'm just tryin'... I'm just sayin'...
You're the man, yo.
Pull your mask down! You supposed to be
watchin' the damn door, Bryce!
What I say about using
my government name, Michael?
[door chimes]
Damn, homie. You look like
you went through a cheese grater.
Oh, snap, you Luke--
-[gun firing]
-[bullet ricocheting]
-[glass shattering]
-[gasping]
I ain't mean that.
Give me your phone.
The phone, fool.
Yo, my bad, man. You know,
I just got a little nervous and shit
-when you threw my mans across the--
-[grunts]
It's you.
-Yeah, it's you.
-[chuckles]
No, man, it's you.
Yo, man, "P.L.O. Style"
was my joint back in the day.
Sweet Christmas. [chuckles]
Yeah, man, one second.
Hey. It's me.
Yeah, they'll be looking for me.
I'll lay in the cut.
I'll see you in a few.
You a double XL?
[scoffs] Way ahead of you, homie,
Call the cops.
I know a lot of people who would pay you
for this kind of protection.
They can keep their money.
Salute.
[laughs]
You ever see anything like that before?
Harlem, baby.
Harlem.
[cell phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Candace] Detective Knight?
-Candace?
-Yeah.
What number are you calling me from?
A prepaid phone I picked up from CVS.
I need to see you.
-Come into the precinct.
-No. No.
You saw how quickly Mariah
sent that lawyer and got me out of there.
You didn't wanna talk to me before.
What makes you trust me now?
Because Luke Cage does.
He saved my life.
And you saw right through me.
-You want the truth, right?
-Where are you?
-Look, if you can't help--
-Candace.
Tell me a place, and I will be there.
[Ridley] You should be at Rikers
right now, but I held you...
because I think you have something to say.
Lawyer.
[chuckles]
I know your record, Mr. Alvarez.
Came up in Harlem, rolled around
with Cottonmouth in the late '90s,
spent some time at Spofford, Sing Sing,
then you made it to the big time,
went to Seagate.
[sighs]
Lawyer.
Cornell Stokes is dead,
but you're still alive.
And I've never seen
an arraignment happen so quickly.
Two million dollar bail...
and someone paid it in cash.
Who's your new sponsor?
Is it Willis Stryker?
Law...
...yer.
You were part
of a hostage situation, Hernan.
Even if your lawyer does get you out...
you won't be walking away from that.
That's multiple kidnapping
and weapons charges.
How does 25 years to life sound to you?
Minimum.
Are you serious?
Yep.
Okay.
[scoffs]
I... I was in the club.
[clears throat]
I saw what happened.
I know who did it.
-Okay.
-[inhales deeply]
We can protect you,
but I need a name to verify.
Who was it?
Was it Stryker?
He goes by...
lawyer.
You need me to spell it?
[laughing]
[door slams]
-You call this safe?
-We're hiding in plain sight.
I've got you.
For now.
Lie to me again, Candace, I walk away
from here, and you are on your own.
-It's not bullshit.
-We'll see.
How did you even get out of
Harlem's Paradise without being stopped?
They were so busy trying to arrest Luke,
I just walked away.
So what is it?
What do you need to tell me
that's so important?
[sighs]
I was at the club
the night Cottonmouth died.
I already know that.
I mean right after.
[sighs]
[beeps]
Mariah killed him.
[Shades] The trash bag is for the clothes
you're wearing now.
Every stitch goes in.
Jewelry, too.
Someone from Spurlock's
will incinerate them.
The secret to any good lie
is it has to run parallel to the truth.
[Misty] How do you know this?
[Candace] I heard them talking about it.
[Shades] Do what I say.
[Candace] The guy who always
wears sunglasses, he was there.
It was his idea to say
Luke Cage killed Cottonmouth.
[grunts]
I was so scared.
I snuck out of there, back to the lockers.
And, um, I was trying to calm myself down.
When I went upstairs,
the guy with the glasses
offered me $50,000 to tell a story.
So I told one.
-Why are you coming clean now?
-'Cause I can't live with this.
Especially after Luke saving my life.
If you can guarantee my safety,
I will testify about
everything I just told you.
[phone beeps]
Mariah scares me more than Cottonmouth.
I asked her if she thought Luke did it,
mostly to see if I could trust her.
To see if she would tell me the truth.
She looked me right in my eye and said...
"You never know
what anyone is capable of."
[breath trembling]
It was the way she said it.
She... she would kill me
if she knew I was speaking to you.
I truly believe that.
Thank you for helping me.
I'm gonna nail
Mariah Dillard's ass to the wall.
-Who else knows that you're here?
-Just my friend Leslie.
Don't call anyone else,
not even Leslie.
As a matter of fact, give me your phone.
Come on.
Okay. Now, I picked this up...
on the way, just in case.
It's already got my number
programed in there,
so if I call or text, you know it's me.
Is your arm okay?
[sighs] My trigger finger is just fine.
Come on, let's go.
-Where?
-Soledad's.
Her daughter Claire
is the one who treated your ankle
at Harlem's Paradise.
She'll be there, too.
I'm gonna take you there myself.
[Method Man] No lie.
Bullets was flying everywhere and shit.
You trying to tell me
that those are bullet holes?
Man, Meth, I love you,
but get out of here.
I... I don't believe that.
HB, I thought the same thing...
until shorty pulled the biscuit
and let two off on Cage
and they bounced off.
Bullets ricochetin' and shit.
[stammers] Look,
I'm telling y'all the truth.
I see y'all over there,
y'all don't believe it.
Trust me, it's the truth.
[stutters] And after he smacked fire
out these dudes,
he left the hoodie,
told me and Gomez to call the police.
You know I ain't calling no po-po.
Then he bounced.
-Say word.
-Word, Sway. I'm telling you.
He even balled the dude's gun up
like some old homework.
But my thing is, though, if he innocent,
so what he running for?
Bulletproof always gonna come
second to being black.
HB, you should know that.
You from Jers. Jers!
Wow! Sound like
he stunted on you right there.
He did stunt.
It was a stunt. It was a stunt.
-Why you gotta stunt on me?
-[laughs]
No, I mean, seriously.
Seriously, though, what I'm just saying,
like, if that was me...
-[Heather B] Right.
-...and I was on the run.
-Why even get involved?
-[Sway] Hmm.
But he did.
And those dudes was nervous,
so anything could've happened.
As far as I'm concerned,
Luke Cage saved my life, man.
That's what's up, man.
You know what,
that don't sound like no cop killer to me.
For real, for real.
You know, there's somethin' powerful
about seeing a black man
that's bulletproof and unafraid.
-Come on, y'all. You know?
-Yeah, yeah.
[Method Man]
Streets got mad love for Cage.
I got mad love for Cage, man, and...
and he one of ours.
Yeah, yeah.
But you know what?
We got mad love for you, too.
-No doubt.
-You one of ours, man.
You know, the show's almost over, man.
You gonna spit for us?
-Of course.
-Oh, man! He 'bout to spit!
-Citizens, you are in for a treat.
-[hip-hop music playing]
One of the best to pick up the mic,
the one and only Method Man!
Hey, yo, Sway.
You all ready?
I'mma dedicate this one to the hardest
individual on the street right now.
Luke Cage, you already know.
"Bulletproof Love" your way, brother.
Let's get it.
Listen.
♪ Man, it is what it is ♪
♪ Can't understand a man
If you ain't lived what he lived ♪
♪ Roaches in the crib
Ain't got no food up in the fridge ♪
♪ Plus the crime runnin' rampant
And it's screwin' up the kids ♪
♪ Sway, admit
What kind of paradise is this? ♪
♪ I just want my 40 acres
And some carats on the wrist ♪
♪ But these snakes
Is tryin' to gather in the pit ♪
♪ Where you get a cottonmouth
Pluckin' ashes off the clip ♪
♪ Off the rip, now a challenger exists ♪
♪ And he bulletproof, shoot
What kinda caliber is this? ♪
♪ Got thugs in the store
With the barrel on your lips ♪
♪ Sayin', "Empty out the drawer"
Before he pound you with the grip ♪
♪ Lord, who to call
When no one obeys the law ♪
♪ And there ain't no Iron Man
That can come and save us all? ♪
♪ Power to the people
And Luke Cage the cause ♪
♪ And the cops got it wrong
We don't think Cage involved ♪
♪ Look, dog, a hero, never had one ♪
♪ Already took Malcolm and Martin
This is the last one ♪
♪ I beg your pardon
Somebody pullin' a fast one ♪
♪ Now we got a hero for hire
And he a black one ♪
♪ And bullet-hole hoodies
Is the fashion ♪
♪ We in Harlem's Paradise
Tell the Captain ♪
♪ That I'm about to trade the mic
For a Magnum ♪
♪ Give up my life
For Trayvon to have one ♪
♪ Yeah, 'cause this is bulletproof love ♪
♪ And you already know
What a bulletproof does ♪
♪ So you can take it
From a bulletproof thug ♪
♪ The hood got his back, dog
Bulletproof love ♪
♪ Blood thicker than mud ♪
♪ And who am I to judge
If you get a gun in the club? ♪
♪ 'Cause you already know
What a bulletproof does ♪
♪ When the hood got your back, dog
Bulletproof love ♪
[music continues playing]
Shout out to Pop.
RIP, my brother.
The streets is crazy right now,
you know what I'm sayin'?
People say we don't need another hero,
but now we got one.
Whether you like it or not, Luke Cage,
please believe it, sir,
the streets got your back.
You're already bulletproof love, baby!
Yeah! That was dope.
You got it right here on Sway's Universe.
The homie, Method Man, HB,
and the bulletproof thug, Luke Cage.
Law enforcement is in a frenzy
looking for Luke Cage.
There have been numerous false sightings,
with some people
wearing hoodies with holes
as a sign of solidarity with an outlaw
some people still perceive to be a hero.
Sway in the Morning.
What's on your mind, citizen?
[man] Yo, I remember when Larry Davis
was on the run back in the day.
Cops came at him
'cause they were just as corrupt,
dangerous and jacked up as he was.
I don't think we're getting the full story
on Luke Cage yet, for real.
[Sway] I wouldn't put it
past the government, man.
Um, you know, we're gonna be searching
for the answers for you,
and once we get the facts,
we're gonna put it right here
on Sway's Universe, all right?
Thanks for your call, citizen.
We got another person on the line.
-[beeps]
-[smooth jazz playing]
[man] Now. Come on!
[woman] All right.
[indistinct shouting]
Oh, come on, man.
You know he's not here.
I understand playing against the computer,
but, um, how do you beat yourself?
Chess is a game of anticipation.
If you know every single possible move,
you can anticipate your adversary's
next move before he does.
Oh.
That's deep.
If we find out you've been hiding him,
there'll be hell to pay.
Yeah, well, just don't break the hinges
on that door on your way out.
I just got it fixed.
[smooth jazz continues on radio]
That was a close shave.
Bad pun.
What the hell did you
even come back for, man?
[sighs] I had to.
For Harlem.
Take care of Diamondback
before he made it bad for everybody.
Well, forget Harlem.
Forget your brother!
You're on the road in a brand new car
and a woman that fine?
And you're bulletproof.
[scoffs] You'd have never seen
my black ass again.
I'd rob the occasional bank
and never look back.
[chuckles]
You got every cop in the city
looking for you, brother.
Negroes writing
Luke Cage ballads and shit.
So... what's the plan?
To box in all the players.
Well...
Shades is in jail.
Mariah's out,
but she ain't exactly on your side.
Now you could tail both of 'em,
but no telling how long that'll take
for them to lead you to your prey.
What about Misty?
No, she's got her hands full already.
She's trying to clear my name
inside the precinct
and bring me in at the same time.
-We gotta be careful with her.
-[sighs]
That leaves you one other option.
Someone else to find Diamondback.
[softly] Here.
Turk.
Turk may be a pawn, but he's not dumb.
If he thinks he's being set up,
he'll disappear.
[dialing]
You let me worry about that.
Hey, Turk, it's Bobby.
Listen, I might be able to get my hands
on about 30 pairs of Jordans.
They're the vintage Air Jordan 5s.
Let's just say
they fell off the back of a truck.
Okay, when?
Who's this?
First name Law, last name Yer.
Must be pretty damn connected to get
a lawyer and not even know who she is.
Membership has its privileges.
[indistinct chatter]
He sprung you?
You think this is funny, don't you?
You got this all figured out, huh?
No...
actually, I don't.
When did Diamondback bring in new hires?
Well, after the club,
he had to change things up.
Recruit some new faces.
I bet while you were inside,
cops tried to do
some recruiting of their own.
Don't ever question my loyalty.
-The man upstairs?
-[scoffs]
You are just full of questions.
Matter of fact...
[groans]
[straining]
[thudding]
[grunting]
[Shades gasping]
[gunshot]
[panting]
[laughs]
Let's go to the penthouse.
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
-[door slams]
-[breath trembling]
I was just following orders!
You're a goddamn puppet.
Who gave you the order?
[grunts]
-Who?
-[grunts]
Diamondback!
You stopped playing your position.
Asked too many questions.
Diamondback said
you needed to be dealt with.
Romeo would be ashamed of you.
[Zip laughing]
You're such a disappointment.
You're the second person
who told me that today.
I'm my own man, Shades.
Tell him yourself.
[chuckles]
Nice.
[sighs] Sorry, Romeo...
He had to go.
[sirens wailing in the distance]
It's a good thing her friend Leslie
knew where she was.
-I'm glad you found the park.
-Mmm-hmm.
So where is she now?
She left with Detective Knight.
Traffic got thick and I lost them.
I'm sorry. I'm not used to doing
anything like this.
We'll find her again.
Just knowing
that she can't be trusted is helpful.
You did a good job, Alex.
Hey, you're my rock!
Later.
[cell phone ringing]
What do you want?
[Stryker] That's no way
to speak to a business partner.
After what you did to my club,
do you really think I'm gonna
shuck and jive with you?
You might wanna check your attitude.
If you're not of any use to me,
then you're not useful to anyone.
Shades would tell you,
if he was still alive.
What the hell are you talking about?
I had to let him go.
So now, I'm giving you the chance
to tell me where you stand.
I've taken Shades and Damon Boone
off the table so you can grow.
I'd hate for us to part, too.
I wasn't particularly fond of Shades...
and the death of Damon Boone,
although unnecessary,
was appreciated.
But you need to know this.
I'm out of the political game.
I'm focusing on Harlem's Paradise.
Using it for a...
a power base for community relations.
That's a smart move.
But you've made some dumb ones also.
You should never talk about murder
on an open line.
Open it.
Seed money...
for your New Harlem Renaissance project
and refurbishing the club.
My apologies.
It's a very generous donation...
but nothing in this world is free.
You're right.
My only condition is loyalty.
Stick with me and Harlem will be remade
in your own image.
We'll be doing this for years to come.
Harlem is already in my image.
You staying?
Once I'm finished with Carl,
I'll evaporate.
But don't worry.
You'll still feel
the occasional cool breeze.
Sweet dreams, Mariah.
[door opens]
[sighs]
[door closes]
-[thudding]
-[Turk gasps]
-You ratted out Chico.
-[breathing heavily]
You got Pop killed.
Man, the writing was on the wall.
Somebody would have seen him.
Might as well be me.
How was I supposed to know
Tone was gonna shoot up the shop?
Whole damn world know
Pop's was Switzerland. Forever.
I should crush you.
[chuckles] You won't, though.
You need me.
[inhales sharply]
Where's Diamondback?
I don't know--
[screaming]
What the-- [yelps]
-Hey!
-You still stalling?
[Turk whimpering]
All right! All right!
He's at a warehouse by the Harlem River.
Near 145th, all right?
I gave you what you wanted!
Now let me out!
Sit tight, Mr. Barrett.
Trash pickup is tomorrow.
You can breathe just fine.
There's food in there, too.
[banging]
You can't leave me in here!
There's baby diapers in here, man!
Hey!
Come on!
[door opening]
[door slams]
[Domingo]
Looks like you downgraded.
I liked the club better.
I'm a man who needs his space.
Space is a good thing.
-Especially when you come to kill a man.
-[guns cocking]
Whoa, whoa.
[guns cocking]
Someone did your boy Zip
and his two homies.
That's not Cage's style...
so I'm guessing Shades
didn't appreciate you bailing him out.
You know when a rattlesnake
is at its most dangerous, Domingo?
When it's cornered.
I'm gonna rip your head off!
[groans]
[gunshots continue]
-[whirring]
-[chuckles]
"And behold a pale horse...
and he that sat upon him,
his name was Death."
[exhales]
[sniffs]
You really need a security system.
-You waiting for me?
-No.
I bet he told you I was dead.
Diamondback got to you, didn't he?
No, he didn't.
[scoffs]
What are you doing with a gun?
It's not you.
Shut up.
[sighs]
I have something for you.
Figured...
you'd want this.
Your prints... Cornell's blood.
Then you'll have nothing
to blackmail me with.
I don't need it.
We're in this together now.
[bottle thuds]
You and I have come a long way.
You know, sometimes you have to reach
across the aisle to get things done.
You're talking about Luke Cage?
It's incredible...
how much you and I think alike.
We're at war.
And right now,
the enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Maybe.
But it might not take.
You did beat his ass
and give him his powers.
-Mmm-hmm.
-And...
Cornell's flunky killed Pop.
You think he really is gonna jump?
Just jump on our bandwagon?
Absolutely.
'Cause we have something
that he wants more than anything.
His old life.
A chance to clear his name.
Right here.
If we send Luke after Diamondback
and they kill each other...
all of our problems are swept away.
-[exhales]
-No matter who wins.
[chuckles] Even better.
[Domingo groaning]
I should've known you'd turn up.
[breathing heavily]
What the hell happened here?
Diamondback.
[groaning]
[faint beeping in distance]
[beeping continues]
Sweet sister.
[Luke panting] Slow.
Take it easy.
What did he use?
How did Diamondback do that?
[breathing heavily]
Something I've never seen before.
[siren wailing in the distance]
Even you can't stop him.
[exhales softly]
These just came in.
-[sighs] Elephant punches all over again.
-Mmm-hmm.
That's gotta be Cage, right?
[cell phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Luke] Hey, it's me.
You guys find Domingo?
-Yeah.
-Meet me.
Where?
Should I thank you for this?
All credit goes to Diamondback.
I don't suppose we'll find his body.
We found Zip's, though,
and two other thugs in an old building.
Shot up. Right after
they picked up your other boy.
Shades.
Don't you ever get tired
of people getting out?
Yes.
Look, it's not safe for you to be here.
If you don't find Diamondback--
Then he wins,
and my life is forever a living hell.
Is there anything I can do?
See what else Turk knows.
He's in a Dumpster in an alley on 123rd.
Near Mount Olivet and the shop.
A Dumpster?
[sighs]
Even if we handle Diamondback...
he's not gonna forgive us
for framing him for Cornell's death.
We could hurdle that easy.
The only people who know
what really happened in the club
are you and me.
I'll regret that night
for the rest of my life.
You did what you had to do.
You shouldn't regret that.
What were you even doing
at the club that night?
I was going there to kill him.
You beat me to it.
Cornell never needed my political money.
And he was never going to pay it back.
He just wanted me in all the way.
So what are you saying?
He saw things in me...
that I avoided my whole life.
Now I am becoming
that person he always saw...
and I always denied.
You ready?
I stay ready, baby.
I should've kept my coat on.
Hell just froze over.
[door closes]
-Where's Luke Cage?
-I'm right here.
-We have a problem.
-So do I.
I can't decide which one of you
I'm gonna knock out first.
-Where's Diamondback?
-I don't know.
The parley between the three of us
is more important.
You have the nerve to use that term?
Right here?
Where Pop died?
Cough up Diamondback's location,
or I'll stomp you
like we were back at Seagate.
Luke, be cool, brother.
Whoa, whoa.
No one needs to stomp anyone.
Pops made this place Switzerland
for a reason.
Cage, we have a mutual enemy,
and the only way to bring him down
is for us all to come together.
There's no way I'm helping you.
We came to offer you a truce.
In exchange for helping you
find Diamondback,
you drop your beef with us.
You both framed me for murder.
There's nothing you can offer me
that's going to make me let that go.
Uh... how about your freedom?
Right here is everything you need
to prove that Diamondback
framed Carl Lucas.
Even if Carl Lucas is exonerated...
Luke Cage is now wanted
for the murder of Cottonmouth.
I'll tell them the truth.
Diamondback killed Cornell
and Damon Boone.
You'll go free.
What the hell is this?
Mariah Dillard, you're under arrest
for the murder of Cornell Stokes.
I thought you said
you were going after Turk?
[Misty] I've been tracking you
since you called.
I wasn't going to let you
just ghost me again.
Hey, hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Shades, back off!
Misty, stand down.
We're working this out.
Oh, so you workin' with them now?
-He knows where Diamondback is.
-I didn't say that.
Well, whatever you know, Hernan,
you should share it with the whole class.
I ain't telling you shit.
Grenade!
[screaming]
[car alarm blaring in distance]
[Mariah coughs]
What the hell?
What type of
Jean Paul Gaultier shit is this?
What are you, a pimp stormtrooper?
No, I'm the angel of death.
-You told him to meet us here?
-No.
Damn!
Look at Hernan the cockroach.
Your mama should have named you Pedro.
Shades!
[bullets ricocheting]
[Bobby] God damn it!
I just fixed this place up
all perfect and shit!
Y'all can't take this outside?
-No.
-No!
All right, just... just sayin'.
-Don't let Mariah get away.
-I won't.
Kick his ass, Luke.
You know
I'm gonna kill 'em all later, right?
You have to get past me first.
Oh, I don't go past.
I go through.
[both yelling]
[funk music playing]