AOI-YA
Hyottoko, Beshimi, Shikijo, Han'nya...
RUROUNIKEN SHIN
NEW KYOTO
Well? Have you carved one
that you find agreeable?
I am afraid not.
I cannot picture the face of a
Buddha that will save our world.
Then just use my face.
What inscription would go with it?
Let's see...
"Those who are strong live;
those who are weak die."
Survival of the fittest.
Although crude,
perhaps the more basic a concept is,
the closer it draws to the ultimate truth.
Fuji again...
Mastering one's powers is
hardly an easy task, Anji.
Usui's grave, is it not?
You are most kind, Yumi.
There is no need to mourn the loss
of someone who dared to defy Shishio.
Everyone, each one of us, was originally
killed by what we call the Meiji Era.
In our own ways, we were persecuted by
the era and stripped of our reasons to live.
Even so, we were able to find the
light by serving Master Shishio.
Light? Even though Shishio
ruined both of Usui's eyes?
The desire to take revenge upon
Master Shishio was Usui's very reason to live.
Even that could be light.
It's nothing so sweet.
Master Shishio!
Time to leave.
At long last!
Yeah, our ship will sail to glory.
WARBLE OF LIGHT
KYOTO
OSAKA
IGA
During the Battle of Toba-Fushimi
in the Boshin War,
Yoshinobu Tokugawa fled to Edo
by boat from the Port of Osaka.
HAMAE
OWARI
MIKAWA
TOTOMI
His actions played a large role
in the loyalist army's victory.
If Shishio is taking an ironic approach and
turning their cause of victory into his own,
SAGAMI
SURUGA
IZU
his true target lies to the east.
MUSASHI
TOKYO
SURUGA
He is going after-
Seconds!
Tell the person over there, not me!
Certainly!
CAFETERIA
OCCUPATIONAL
HEALTH
MANAGEMENT
You came to Kyoto on your own
without food or water.
Hmph, how pathetic!
First that girl and now you.
I am amazed how you hold that
man in such high regard.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I didn't come all the way to Kyoto
just to give Kenshin a hand!
Here! Thanks fer waitin'!
I came to fight my own battles.
I don't care who you are!
I won't tolerate anyone that does something
as cowardly as stabbing another in the back.
You were a Sekiho Army soldier...
I could never bring myself to
forgive the Meiji government.
They dirtied my master's name by calling
him a traitor and then killed him!
But if he plays dirty in his fight against the
government and involves innocent lives,
that makes him no different!
I see.
If I'm gonna hunt Shishio down,
it'll go faster if I stick with you.
Isn't that right, Captain of the
Shinsengumi's 3rd Unit?
So, where are we headed?
Did nothing I said enter those
ears of yours, Bird Head?
I believe in fully enjoying the
taste of my rice when I'm eating.
Osaka.
Huh? Osaka?
According to Saito's information, Shishio
is headed there to carry out his secret plan.
Does that make the Great Kyoto Fire a bluff?
No. He has invested the majority
of his subordinates in that.
He has something so powerful that he
could still win with a small group of men.
What? How's that work?
For instance... a black ship.
A black ship?!
Well, that was merely an example.
But Tokyo is still scared by the
arrival of the black ships.
If what appeared to be a battleship
were to drop anchor,
that alone would inevitably create turmoil.
Miss Kaoru?
What made you decide to
tell us about all of this?
If I kept my silence, well...
I feared you may do something rash...
What?! How could you say that?!
Excuse me for being a rash woman!
Good grief! Did you come all of the way
to Kyoto for a lover's quarrel?
I rashly followed you all of the way to Kyoto!
Good grief! Did you come all of the way
to Kyoto for a lover's quarrel?
N-no, stop! Scram!
A messenger pigeon?
It's Lu No. 1.
What's the matter, Kenshin?
AOI-YA
Here you go.
I am sorry to impose at a time like this.
It is fine. We have some spare rooms anyway.
Stay as long as you like.
I appreciate it.
Is that right? It was Aoshi...
Master Aoshi... was no longer
the Master Aoshi I once knew.
I don't know where justice lies,
but I don't care about that anymore.
I want you to defeat Master Aoshi,
no, Aoshi Shinomori!
Aoshi Shinomori, why have you
decided to join us in arms?
That is not my intent.
That man claimed he would prepare a stage
where I may face Himura Battousai
in our final battle without interruption.
I am here for that alone.
Soujiro?
I invited him to serve as a
replacement for Chou and Usui.
Was that uncalled for?
The man who has obtained Shakku's
final piece may indeed come after us,
but he is not the one I am after.
I shall leave that man to you.
You may perform a spectacular opening act.
Guys!
Listen up! From this moment on,
I am the head of the Oniwabanshu!
He wouldn't!
Shishio and his men will use the
chaos created by the fires to set sail.
I would like all of you to prevent
any casualties in Kyoto.
You got it, but what about Shishio?
As for that...
You intend to shoulder it
on your own again, don't you?
Miss Kaoru...
I know.
I will stay and help Misao in the fight here.
So... let's be sure we go back
to Tokyo together, okay?
Yeah.
I swear it.
Bear in mind what will happen if you dare
to break your promise with me.
Missh Haoru...
Please don't mind them. They're always like this.
You got that, Kenshin?
Okay...
It's just so obvious, Gramps.
If Himura were in the wrong,
he would not have someone who loves him so.
In that case...
Master Aoshi is...
I'm going to get fresh water.
I'll swap with you.
But...
We are going to protect Kyoto together.
Doesn't that make us friends?
It isn't that easy to become
friends with someone!
It is quite difficult to earn a person's trust.
Really? I guess.
Hmmm, what would it take to earn your trust?
Oh, I know! Why don't we spar?
During a sword fight,
you learn how the other feels.
S-sorry. This isn't the time for that, is it?
You're just like him!
Pardon?
Himura, I mean. It's like you're inept, or...
maybe you'd call it "sassy."
It kinda feels like you're speaking
straight from the heart.
Himura trusted and relied on me.
Both Himura and I trust you and the boy.
Let's fight together! Guard duty starts tonight!
Kuro, Shiro, Masu-Kami, Omime,
everyone, get changed!
The Oniwabanshu moves out tonight!
Yahiko, please take care of Kyoto...
and Miss Misao.
Yeah! This is my chance to show how
great the Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu is!
Oh, right! I had a message for you, Kenshin.
It's from that geezer, Hiko.
Hiko? Seijuro?
He has finally obtained what he
once lacked with the sword.
What's that mean?
If all you do is slice each other's flesh,
you have not truly crossed swords
with your opponent.
Through the sword, you must touch
your opponent's heart.
Otherwise, you cannot threaten your foe's
life in the true meaning of the word.
"Mind, skill and body."
All martial arts share this concept.
In swordsmanship, you use the sword to
learn about your foe as well as yourself.
It is essential that it comes from the heart.
Through the sword,
you must touch your opponent's heart...
Kenshin, was that drunken geezer really your...
He is my master. Thank you, Yahiko.
You have done a fine job
delivering the message.
Go, go, go!
Hey, will Kyoto be okay?
I have made preparations.
What's this?
Apparently a man from Tokyo named Fujita
rounded up 5,000 police officers.
Well, I appreciate what he's done.
But the ones to protect Kyoto will be us,
the onmitsu Oniwabanshu! Got that?!
Yeah!
Kaoru!
Yahiko?
She's ready for a fight!
Wow!
Hey, Sou! Quit ogling the ship
and give me a hand!
Okay, okay.
Is that me?
You said to carve "Survival of the Fittest," into it.
That I did.
In which case, when you lose your life,
this Buddhist statue will cease to speak the truth.
It will transform into a puppet
stained with falsehoods.
Was that meant as encouragement?
No, as a provocation.
Hmph... You fallen monk...
Isn't this taking a while? We should
be able to see the fires in Kyoto by now.
They are up against 5,000 police officers.
It is only natural for them to run into problems.
There is no need to hurry.
But the soldiers might be bailing out on us.
That would be unforgivable!
How dare they betray Master Shishio!
They may flee if they so wish.
But would they truly do that?
They already know; there is nowhere
in this country for them to hide.
That is precisely why they chose to follow me.
It's that simple.
They may betray me for all I care.
Each of them has his own battle.
Master Shishio...
Master Shishio!
Have the blazes begun to soar?
No, that's not it.
There is a carriage headed this way.
Oh, one of them is spewing out steam!
Is that the one? It doesn't look
like a massive black ship to me!
It is just as I had anticipated.
Your bird brain may not understand,
but that is called "camouflage."
What's that?
It means appearances can
deceive a bunch of morons.
Got it! False security makes for a fierce enemy.
A survivor from the Shinsengumi
has come to see me off.
Too bad it wasn't the one you longed for, Boss.
Now then, how to go about attacking a ship?
We'd never make it if we swam.
True enough.
I will stop you.
I would like you to turn back now.
Otherwise, I will be forced to pray
for your souls once you are dead.
Although I am not a devout believer,
I feel somewhat uncomfortable
with fighting a monk.
In that case, leave this lug to me!
From the looks of it,
he doesn't have a weapon on hand.
If it's a fistfight, then it's right up my alley!
Then he is all yours, but don't take him lightly.
Got it! False security's dangerous and fire's hot!
You bastard! You're one destructive monk!
It's a bit early in the year
for swimming in the ocean.
Saito sure is trying his hardest!
I'm going to use "that." Sou, give me a hand!
Huh? You mean THAT?
Hurry it up!
Yeah, yeah.
Go ahead. It will fire once you turn the lever.
Now breach the surface!
Where are you, Hajime Saito?
Sou, load her with more ammunition!
Okay, okay!
That is enough of that.
Master Shishio!
If one of the last surviving Shinsengumi
got shot and became fish food,
it would mortify him on the other side.
I shall face him myself.
Shishio's actions are never
contradictory, are they?
Subsequently leaving us with nothing to do.
It makes things easy, doesn't it, Yumi?
Welcome aboard my vessel, Hajime Saito.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I call myself Makoto Shishio.
My subordinates gave you a rude welcoming,
but for coming to see me off,
I would like to show my
appreciation with this sword.
How does that sound?
I see. It would appear you possess
the prowess needed to bind a group.
In which case, I shall fight you
with all of my might.
Come.
Wow! Did you two do this? I called for the police,
so let them bind these men.
How is Misa-er, the boss?
Misa-er, the boss is doing
a good job directing us.
We've caught just about all of them.
You two should drop by the Aoi-ya.
Misa-er, Boss, thanks to civilian assistance,
I believe we were able to extinguish
all of the fires.
I did pretty good for my first job, didn't I?
Isn't it great how we were able to protect Kyo-
Lu No. 1?
Hey, what's wrong, Lu No. 1?
It's on fire?! The Aoi-ya!
As expected, you are powerful!
I had a good eye when appraising you.
My greatest obstacle is indeed you,
Hajime Saito!
But to be honest, I am also disappointed.
You wield such power, so why has one
who was once called a Wolf of Mibu
lowered himself to serving as
a government dog?
Does this era satisfy you?
A defanged wolf...
What would possibly make you
wag your tail for this era?
"Kill. Evil. Instantly."
"Kill. Evil. Instantly"? Am I evil? What is evil?
In my eyes, raw power is justice.
Weakness is evil.
Saito, your strength comes from your conviction.
You are different from Battousai.
Let us see whose beliefs are right.
Bear your fangs and howl!
Kill.
Evil.
Instantly!
Gatotsu!
Zero Stance.
Take this!
It would seem we've found our answer.
You were close, but once a wolf has lost his
fangs, he is little different from a cur.
Now there are no obstacles standing in my way.
Yumi, increase the engine's power.
Upon Anji's arrival, we set sail.
Saito, I shall bring you with me.
I will show you the evil
Meiji government's demise.
Sou, treat his wounds.
Gramps!
Okina!
Misao!
AOI- YA
Save me!
Run! Run for it!
He's a monster!
Kaoru?!
Yahiko, we'll strike at the same time.
Don't take your eyes off of his sword!
Yeah!
Ochika, look after Gramps!
Misa-Boss!
I didn't realize you monks could be so strong!
With all of your skills,
why do you serve under Shishio?
Although I may have fallen, I am still a monk.
Now that I am unable to
believe in God or Buddha,
I require a subject to pray to
or I will no longer even be a monk.
I don't know if Makoto Shishio
is some higher being or not,
but I won't let you create a world
where we worship scum who're blind
to the pain of the weak!
I'll give this my best!
Turn to the right.
Y-Y-Yes, sir! I am on it.
Master Shishio, are you all right?
Yeah, thanks to my head guard.
Are we still waiting for Anji?
We are.
Saito's companion is giving him a hard time?
We will wait a while longer.
It would seem the "boss"
is still waiting for his man as well.
We have Sou here,
so I am going to cool down my body.
Am I not hot?
It matters not.
In this era that deliriously cries "peace,"
I had lost the ability to see my true dream.
You are the one man who shows me
a dream from which I shall never wake.
Yahiko, get down!
Saito, you sure are strong!
Wasn't that move called Gatotsu?
For a moment, I thought you had won.
Once you recover from those wounds,
please fight me.
I promised Himura I'd fight him,
so it would have to come after that.
Sure, but only if you defeat him.
Hmmm. You hold Himura in
high regard, don't you?
Well, I am sure that's only natural since you've
been rivals since the end of the Shogunate.
If you've crossed blades with him,
then you should already know why.
You must be rather dense.
You intend to fight him again, correct?
He has finally made his appearance.
Gramps, run for it!
Yahiko, get back! Yahiko!
Kenshin left this place in our care.
I refuse to take a single step back!
I can't pull back!
Y-Yahiko, run!
This will be the end of him.
I've been looking for you, kid!
The old man!
Hmm, so it was a sakabatou.
Sakabatou: A sword that cannot kill.
Shakku must have wavered clear to the end.
Only the strong will survive.
It is so simple, and yet he failed to understand.
That is a defective sword.
It is an appropriate sword for you,
who always hesitate to kill.
I will not cast aside my hesitation.
There are people who I have met
precisely because of that hesitation.
Seijuro Hiko...
You left before I was done with you!
Wh-what?!
I expect you to repay me!
You'll have to work hard to cover
the cost of the pot you broke!
Wh-what are you going on about
at a time like this, Geezer?
It would seem your debt is about to grow again.
What?
A massive body filled with too much power...
Unable to master his own strength,
he must have suffered under that armor.
His heart does not wish to fight,
yet he finds himself unable to resist
his natural instinct to do so.
He came to Shishio,
who had accepted that about him.
I shall put your suffering to an end.
Here you will find a man whom you
cannot defeat, even at full strength.
It is all right.
Show me! Let me see the real you.
Let us begin.
Your new sword is quite impressive.
And you are even able to
keep up with my speed.
This isn't right when you you are
no longer the Battousai, Himura!
A sword and katana that cannot kill
shouldn't be this powerful.
What Saito said is also eating at me...
It makes me sick.
I do not want to acknowledge you.
Hesitation must never defeat conviction!
It must not!
I shall fight for keeps.
I can win! I will defeat you!
Why?
When you lacked emotions,
I was unable to predict your moves.
But right now, you...
I see...
Himura, you used your sword
to read my emotions...
I have lost, for you have awoken my emotions.
You now possess a different power from
the one you wielded in your Battousai days.
I may be dense, but now I finally understand.
But... that will not work on Shishio.
Shishio burns through life without
a breadth of hesitation.
His heart is the color of a black flame.
He's crying...
Seijuro Hiko...
He saw through that monstrous
man's misery as a warrior,
having never known what it meant
to feel fulfillment.
He is a fearsome man.
Misery as a warrior...
The same is also true of Shishio.
Everyone who has gathered under Shishio
has been left at the mercy
of the patriotic extremists.
They have been hurt in both body and mind.
That is precisely why they depend on strength.
They depend on power.
And then...
We seek the light.
Light? Is that how you guys
view Makoto Shishio?
Monks must always seek salvation for the world.
I would do anything to save the world!
Do you think you'll find salvation
beyond destruction?
If that's what the Shinto and Buddhist
gods want, then it is what it is.
But humans have no right to do that!
I'll never accept your salvation!
Take that!
Now... I see.
I can tell, when we throw our punches.
Tell what?
I get it! You...
In Shishio's eyes, you are the light.
He is searching for salvation.
Makoto Shishio... does not
yearn for his own salvation.
He wants to be the burning flame
that will arouse the era.
He would use himself as the tinder...
At this rate, Makoto Shishio will...
I ask: What is your light?
My light?
When I felt despair for the era
and had given up, a friend...
...made me decide to believe
in the future once more.
This signal indicates that Master Shishio
is setting sail for glory.
Make it spectacular.
Yes, Ma'am!
Fire!
Makoto Shishio once said, "Our world is Hell."
While in Hell, he would don the flames of truth
and thrust forward with a large ironclad warship.
It-it's a black ship?!
That...
...is Purgatory.
PURGATORY
Purgatory...
Welcome to Purgatory.
You downed Soujiro using
Shakku's last sword? Fascinating.
I had prepared an opening act for you, but it
would seem you have already been wounded.
Why don't we skip to the main show: a battle
between brother swords, my predecessor?
Let's. That is why I have come... with this sword.
The ship has left port.
Let's go all the way to Tokyo together.
When we reach Tokyo, which of our
corpses will have taken the helm?
Now you have the face of a warrior!
He touched... that man's heart.
His heart?
This is the Infinite Blade, Homura.
That is the name Shakku bequeathed this sword.
Infinite; it promises unending victory
no matter where I go.
This is the sakabatou, Keishin.
This sword is the embodiment
of how Master Shakku felt in the end.
Then the equinox of his revelation was
a hell on earth that tumbles in bloody mud!
Kenshin, will you be able to
touch Makoto Shishio's heart?
Hate to say it, but you cannot defeat me
with a sakabatou, my predecessor!
A sword is a tool used for murder.
If you hope to defeat me, reverse your blade
and become the Battousai once more!
I will not reverse my blade,
not so long as this sword takes the form of
an earnest desire for an age of peace!
You cannot change the world through ideals.
You will only be devoured by the
law of "Survival of the Fittest."
So they made it in time.
Adjust the angle for error!
Load the next cannons!
Sir!
Officer Saito, don't die!
Do not let that ship leave the bay! Fire!
Those government dogs
are putting up a decent fight.
Yumi, change course.
That's right. The bombardment is
most likely coming from Mt. Tenpo.
Silence them with a counterattack.
Turn to the left.
Yes, Ma'am.
Raise the angle of projection a little.
Keep this position!
Four, three, two! Commence fire!
Don't falter! Continue firing!
Tokyo will share the same fate.
Such is Purgatory's power.
This is the Engine Room. The cannons
are making the engine gush steam.
The high temperatures prevent
us from approaching it!
Hurry and shut it down!
My predecessor, it must be karma for
the terrible things we have done,
because we never seem to have
much luck when it matters most!
Can you feel what makes me boil,
my predecessor?
I will not die!
I am strong!
Even if your swords touch one another's hearts,
you cannot win if your
opponent devours your heart.
Can you win, Kenshin?!
Master Shishio!
The light...
He touched the light?
He touched his opponent's
heart through his sword.
Kenshin...
Hurry! Abandon ship! Evacuate!
I have been waiting.
On a sinking ship where
everyone is about to die,
no one will come to interfere.
This is where we shall hold our final battle.
Because of you, I have lost my friends...
I have lost everything.
I will defeat you and decorate their tombstones
with the flower called "the title of strongest."
You have not lost everything.
There is a young lady who adores you
and hopes to save you!
I was asked by that very young lady...
to defeat you.
If we could have touched his heart,
would this have turned out differently, Gramps?
If we could have touched Master Aoshi's heart...
I cannot grant Miss Misao's wish.
I will bring Aoshi Shinomori
back home to Miss Misao.
But first, there is the Aoshi Shinomori
before me who writhes in darkness.
I must slice away the these delusions that
Miss Misao hates with my sakabatou, Keishin!
Hey!
Saito.
Once the fire reaches the armory,
this ship will be dust.
I would like to be gone before then,
but I can't row the boat with my legs like this.
I want you to take me to the shore.
Fine, fine.
Misao...
Kenshin!
Master Shishio, look. It is on fire.
Our world is burning so brilliantly.
Everything has proceeded just as
you wished, Master Shishio...
Yumi, you're so lucky!
I am the only one who got left behind.
Saito, I blame you! Really!
The black ship, Purgatory, is sinking!
Yeah.
We have protected Tokyo. Next comes...
So in the end, this was the only place
that got hit by the Great Kyoto Fire?
It's great that the damage
was minimal! It's great!
It's not great!
Now, now.
Kenshin!
And Aoshi!
Aoshi!
Ao...
Master Aoshi!
Kenshin.
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Come to think of it, where did
that geezer Hiko go?
ELIXIR
I will party again tonight.
The Infinite Blade, Homura.
Even as my father dreamed of an age of peace,
he continued to forge swords meant to kill.
The sword that most strongly represents
his contradiction...
...shall be sealed here as an offering to the gods.
Take this.
Please, I would like for you to keep it.
Master Seiku...
My father placed all of his
feelings into that sakabatou.
I am sure that you understand!
Then I would be most grateful
if you let me borrow it.
Himura!
In a world of true peace, even a
sakabatou will become unnecessary.
Nor will there be a need declare
that I will not take one's life.
When such a world comes...
Someday, I would like to
humbly lay down the sword
and place this sakabatou next to Homura.
Humbwee!
Humbly?
He means Himura!
Humbwee! Humbwee! Himura ish humbwee!
Kaketa kotae ga ikutsu mo aru no
Several answers have left me wanting
Tadashisa dake ja tarinai
Simply being correct is not enough
Futatsu kasanete mita kedo, chigatta yo
I tried overlapping two, but it wasn't right
I feel so
Mitasarete mieru keshiki wa yasashii
The seemingly satisfied view is gentle
Anata no me ni utsuru mono mo onaji
It is the same as what I see in your eyes
Nee zutto
We're forever
Kieteshimau na yo
Never disappear on me
Atarashii ibuki yo
Give voice to your
Koe ni dashite hibikasete
New breath of life and let it ring
Furesasete ite yo
Let me touch you
Tada hitori kokoro ubawareta
You are the only one to steal my heart
Itoshisa kogarete
Longing for your love
Nana iro no kaze ga fuku
The rainbow-colored wind blows
I feel you
Mitasarete mieru keshiki wa yasashii
The seemingly satisfied view is gentle
Anata no se ni utsuru mono mo onaji
It is the same as what I see in your back
Nee motto
Give me more
Mezameru koro ni wa mabushii kimochi wo
By the time I wake, give voice to your
Koe ni dashite hibikasete
Dazzling feelings and let it ring