Note: The Kan'ei Era was from 1624 to 1643.
Even when the drought of the
Kan'ei Era came to pay us a visit,
this well had remained unperturbed, but now...
Oh, hello, good sir from Aoi-ya.
Mrs. Oshige, how do you fare?
The rainy season has yet to come,
but the heat is fierce.
It would be dreadful if it fails to rain soon.
People are praying for rain...
What has happened to the Eastern rain?
The Chief of Internal Affairs
was assassinated in Tokyo...
The one who struck him down
was Soujiro Seta of the Shishio Faction.
What of Makoto Shishio?
Sir, he and several subordinates
have come to Kyoto.
Sorry to trouble you with this upon
your arrival in Kyoto, Officer Fujita.
It's fine.
Makoto Shishio. Born in Shingetsu Village.
DAILY KYOTO NEWSPAPER
He was allied with the Choshu Faction.
This man inherited his predecessor's job
to slay men from the shadows."
But I thought that he was killed
in the Boshin War.
Makoto Shishio is a treacherous individual
whose lust for ambition and conquest
is beyond comprehension for normal men.
MAY 1878
NO. 4
REPORT ON MAKOTO SHISHIO
KYOTO POLICE DEPARTMENT
whose lust for ambition and conquest
is beyond comprehension for normal men.
Some of his assassinations were
of such great import
that if brought to light, they could uproot
the foundation of the Meiji government."
Had Shishio survived to greet the new era,
there was a possibility that he would
take advantage of such weaknesses,
allowing him to hold Japan
in the palm of his hand."
As such, the government took advantage of the
chaos in the Boshin War to dispose of him."
It claims that they doused his
corpse in oil and set it aflame...
B-but he still managed to survive?
He may indeed be... a ghost.
Absorbed in his hatred and
desire for vengeance,
he has forgotten that he is human.
At any rate, HE will most likely be
the key to defeating Shishio.
Who do you mean?
When he moves,
so moves the era.
And Aoshi has been missing since?
The person Aoshi encountered while in Tokyo...
That man is also making his way to Kyoto.
I see. He must be chasing after Shishio as well.
Do you know of him?
Yes, his name is...
Misao! As a member of the
onmitsu group Oniwabanshu,
could you try to eavesdrop on a
conversation or two more eloquently?
Tell me! Tell me about the guy
who was with Master Aoshi!
If I find him, I'll find Master Aoshi!
His name is...
...Himura.
Kenshin...
I can't let you handle subduing
Shishio all on your own!
Note: Hitokiri - literally "Man cutter" or Manslayer.
Hitokiri Battousai...
If it is still in you to speak of restorations,
sing of this nation's future. I dare you.
RUROUNI KENSHIN
NEW KYOTO
CAGE OF FLAMES
Himura... Battousai!
I-I'm just fine, Lu No. 1!
Well, I get that you're afraid.
After all, we're going up
against Himura Battousai.
Formerly a revolutionary for the Choshu Faction,
he was feared as the "Hitokiri Battousai"
during the end of the Shogunate.
Supposedly the land of death
spreads to wherever he goes.
A cross-shaped scar?
He's short and skinny.
Is that wimpy-looking guy really Himura?
You're right! As a member of the Oniwabanshu,
I must first confirm that he is the enemy.
Go, Lu No. 1!
Lu No. 1?!
Hey, you are tickling me!
I can't believe Lu No. 1
warmed up to him just like that!
Now then, what did you need with me?
Himura Battousai, spill it!
Where is Master Aoshi?!
You know him, don't you?
I know, right?
He IS in the onmitsu Oniwabanshu
that defended the lmperial Castle in Edo.
Hey! Wait for me!
Whoa!
How the heck... did you get across this?
I won't let him go!
I do not know what your relationship to Aoshi is,
but down the path of pandemonium,
danger is always by your side.
What?!
Who are you to tell me that?!
You should sever your feelings
for the man and forget about him.
It is for your own good.
Don't you dare give me that crap!
I CAN'T forget him!
That's why I'm searching for him!
Don't be crazy! Stop!
How the heck could forgetting about the person
I care for the most make me happy?!
Until you tell me...
I won't leave your side.
I swear it!
Straight ahead, there is a manor-
Is that where Master Aoshi is?
Makoto Shishio is there.
The man we sent on reconnaissance claims
to have seen Himura Battousai at Hakone Pass.
Unfortunately, that is where he lost sight of him.
What became of that man?
I wound up killing him.
Master Seta!
You're being most unseemly. What is it?
Well...
Please, this way.
You brought a woman?
The hot springs located here in
Shingetsu Village soothes my burns.
It also tightens the ladies where it matters.
A-and where does it matter?!
I believe this was the village of your birth,
was it not, Makoto Shishio?
Just what I'd expect of my predecessor.
You know me well.
Shingetsu Village was exploited by the
government, turning it into a ghost town.
Even this therapeutic hot springs resort
was an unfortunate legacy
that financially destroyed the village.
This village reflects the true
shape of the Meiji government.
And my body reflects its true nature.
However, my motive is hardly
something as trivial as vengeance.
What I seek is power.
I want to create a powerful country.
Our current world is a façade.
Even though the Shogunate was replaced by
a bureaucracy, nothing has actually changed.
They use false pretenses of peace as bait,
grow fat on their profits,
and secretly dispose of any
they find to be a nuisance.
These are stopgap measures.
The government is rotten to the core.
In order to create a new world that
is not a façade, strong power is-
You plan to destroy this country yet again
so that you may pluck the government
from its roots and plant a new seed?
Exactly. This body has
made me accept the truth.
The ruling law of our world is that
"the strong eat the flesh of the weak."
In that case, I shall use my power
to destroy all indolence...
...and burn away all falsehood!
This false world may be the one to writhe in
agony as you engulf it in those flames,
but I cannot allow you to fill this era
with the screams of the innocent-
of those currently living in peace!
Your sword... Didn't Shakku Arai
forge it in his final days?
The same is true of this one.
In other words, they are brother swords.
However, Shakku filled my sword with an
infinitely pure bloodlust
when he forged this blade.
In comparison, your sword that cannot kill
is no different than our current era.
It is merely a product of confusion.
It can't kill?
Our swords match their owners.
In which case, the relationship you and I share
is that of brothers who are complete opposites.
Are you certain?
Yeah, play with him in my stead.
It is too soon for a
showdown between "brothers."
Then I shall do as I please.
Will Sou be all right on his own?
Don't worry. His strength comes
directly from his lack of emotions.
Does that mean you can't read his mind?
Pitted against Hiten Mitsurugi-ryuu,
he could prove to be the ultimate foe.
Battou-jutsu, which would give him the lead,
may prove effective.
But lacking the emotion "sadness,"
murder does not trouble Soujiro's heart.
How will the Battousai and his tepid resolve
to not kill fare against such a blade?
No, he is no longer the Battousai.
It is clear how this battle will end.
Victory goes to me, doesn't it?
No, it's a draw!
Huh? Wow, this is amazing!
Not that I care. This belongs to Shishio anyway.
There were no winners or losers in this bout.
I must take my leave for today,
but please fight me again.
Be sure to get another sword
before that time comes.
Not that Shakku is still amongst the living.
Himura...
What are you going to do?
I do not mind staying where I am.
If you didn't have the funds to cover two rooms,
we didn't have to stay here.
In your search for me, you never
stopped running, not even to sleep.
Your feet cannot take much more...
Don't patronize me!
I am not patronizing you...
Yes, you are! If everything was right in the world,
I would be a kunoichi,
working by Master Aoshi's side.
And I could tell going by your stances.
There is no way you could possibly
lose to that Soujiro guy!
He said that you can't kill.
And then there's that sakabatou.
Are you seriously trying not to kill anyone?
He called you his predecessor.
Who is this Makoto Shishio?
It was because of me...
that his fate was thrown askew.
If one darkness were to vanish,
there would be need for a new one.
I thought I understood that, and yet...
The night birds... are hooting.
Indeed, they are.
I... For some reason, I've been afraid
of the night ever since I was little.
But when I was with Master Aoshi,
I could handle it.
Master Aoshi always goes on ahead,
telling me what lies ahead in the darkness.
Your name?
I never told you?
Misao! I'm Misao Makimachi.
If you continue to meddle
in my affairs, Miss Misao,
it will only feed the darkness
that frightens you so.
If it's for Master Aoshi, I don't care!
It's not like I'm doing him any favors or anything.
FOUND HIMURA BATTOUSAI.
LOOK FOR A MASTER SWORDSMITH.
But I have to find out about
this Shishio guy anyway.
Lu No. 1.
What gives?! Why isn't there a
single teahouse around here?
Yahiko, that sounds pathetic.
I can't believe we got off at Owari Port!
You should find out what the destination
is when you pick out a boat.
This is part of our training.
As we are right now,
wouldn't we only get in Kenshin's way?
Then maybe we shouldn't have
come to begin with!
That's...
Damn!
C'mon! C'mon! You look pathetic, Kaoru!
Your feet aren't moving!
Yahiko!
Good evening!
No one's home?
Wow, he's got a bunch of stuff!
This is all pottery.
But, dang, this is covered in cracks!
These suck. He stinks at this.
It broke, I see.
Uh, I am sorry. We came inside
without your permission.
The veins of pottery teach us
the laws of the human world.
Aw. I dropped it 'cause you startled me.
But sorry about that-
Yahiko!
You shall pay with your body.
Hot!
So hot! You're burning me!
I'm dying!
Are you?
That's okay! I don't care if I die!
You can't! I will force you to live.
This heat is the warmth of life.
I shall use it to burn away
the rotten government!
With the heat of life, I will bring Kyoto
and our lethargic era to a boil.
To think you planned your strike
for when I was enjoying myself, Usui.
Hardly! My Mind's Eye cannot
perceive actions of this nature.
MIND'S EYE
It merely worked out that way.
Really!
I have a job for you since you
have interrupted our fun.
Hajime Saito, a former member of the
Shinsengumi, is sniffing around our trail.
Keep an eye on him.
And Himura Battousai?
I am not interested in one soon to die.
Understood.
That man still hopes to take
your life, Master Shishio.
It's best that way.
This is where those with power gather.
There are those who I have saved,
those who serve me,
those who rely on me, those who use me,
and those who are burning with the desire to
kill me after suffering defeat by my hands.
But only true power, even if it be evil,
could keep this group together.
Master Shishio...
Those who are strong live,
and those who are weak die.
As such, I simply need to be the strongest.
Nothing may strike fear into the man who will
burn down the era with the flame called "power."
Shakku's last sword, ya say?
Yes, although I am certain
he will catch wind of it as well.
What say you, Chou?
Does it stir your blood as a sword collector?
You bet, but there is no way Shishio's
gonna let me face Himura Battousai.
It's fine. Do as you will.
Shishio!
It was not Himura's sakabatou that broke,
but his beliefs.
Miss Misao, I...
It's fine, it's fine! Just you leave this to me.
Lu No. 1!
It's from Okina!
Shakku had a son with whom
he entrusted all of his arts.
His name is Seiku Arai.
SMITHY
REPAIRS
Hello.
I am sorry, but may I turn
down that commission?
What?! Why?!
My father used to say, " I will create
a new world with my swords."
But the swords my father created
under that philosophy
stole the lives of many who carried
the weight of the new era.
Now it is the Meiji Era.
The age of peace has finally come.
Samurai have abandoned their swords.
As such, I wish to abandon
my work as a swordsmith.
This is an age of peace?
It is.
What were you making?
Oh, it is a pellet drum for Iori, my son.
Really, I'm embarrassed
by how poorly it turned out.
I don't seem to have a knack for it
like I do forging blades.
Oh, it's a little bent.
I apologize for having asked the impossible.
Himura?
We shall take our leave now.
B-but, hey! What are you going
to do without a sakabatou?
Hey, Himura!
Step into it quicker.
Don't rely upon your arm strength!
You won't finish before lunch at this rate.
Damn it!
Really, why must we do this?
We don't have time for this crap!
That man...
We need to hurry and find Kenshin.
Oh?
Are you learning the sword
from Kenshin Himura?
Huh? Don't be stupid! My sword is
that of Kamiya Kasshin-ryuu!
lts sword is meant to protect.
Don't lump it together with battou-jutsu!
Then why are you chasing after him?
Well, it's obvious!
I can't leave that goofball to his own devices.
Kenshin... Do you know Kenshin?
That's right! How do you know him?
My, my...
Tonight, we party!
Huh? But weren't you just drinking?
While away from his master,
my pupil has been growing and maturing.
It is a rather pleasing thought.
He has finally obtained what he
once lacked with the sword.
Wait up! You can't fight
without a sword, can you?
Master Seiku lives in an age of peace.
It is not my right to destroy that peace.
Yeah, but...
A-are you all right?
What's the matter?
I-Io... Iori was taken from me!
What?!
Why?! Why would someone do that?!
The man said he wanted your father's
last sword... And then he!
This happened... because I wanted a sakabatou.
What?! What are you talking about?
This and that are two different-
Himura?
The poor thing! To think they dumped
Shakku's last work out in these boonies.
Watch it! Don't pull my hair.
Dang, I don't much care for babies.
If you keep hurtin' me,
I'll cut you down in one fell swoop!
Broom! Broom!
I seriously don't like ya.
Iori!
Let that babe go!
Himura...
I see. So I take it yer the
infamous Hitokiri Battousai?
You want Shakku's last piece, huh?
Scary! Yer scary!
I'm gonna kill ya right quick and then test
Shakku's famous blade on that baby!
Himura, you don't have a sword!
He's using his sheath against
someone with a sword?
I must never offer the sword to that man...
The light shining forth from Himura's eyes...
has vanished!
Himura's eyes had seemed so gentle,
yet battle has turned him into a demon!
Hitokiri Battousai...
Hey, weren't ya against killin' people?
I will not kill you.
So ya can do anything ya want so long
as it don't kill me? Ain't you nice!
It was my job to fight,
but somewhere along the line, I forced
the tainted name "Hitokiri" on Shishio.
Himura!
But now... I shall accept the taint unto myself;
the taint needed to protect a world of peace.
N-no! That is just-
A contradiction.
Iori!
Thank the Heavens!
Iori...
That was really awesome.
If yer totally empty-handed,
I actually stand a chance!
The taint... needed to defend the
peace and protect our loved ones...
Father, I... I want to defend our peace!
But... But...
Now ya can't run around and
dodge my blows, can ya?
Himura!
For you! This blade was meant for you!
That is Shakku's final masterpiece.
B-but...
Isn't this...
...a sakabatou?!
Shakabato!
Master Shakku, I shall live by your ideals!
What?!
Himura, you did it!
Yeah, it's okay. Broom Head didn't drop dead.
Broom! Broom!
I'm going to make sure that you
get turned over to the police.
It will be okay.
The unvarnished wood simply couldn't
withstand the power of your attack.
KEISHIN.
SLAYING MYSELF,
MY FORGED BLADES AMASS.
HATED BY MY CHILD,
I DO THIS FOR MY
GRANDCHILD'S FUTURE.
"Slaying myself, my forged blades amass..."
"Hated by my child,
I do this for my grandchild's future."
Himura, after seeing you in battle,
I believe I understand my father a little better.
This sakabatou is the embodiment...
...of the way you, Himura, and my father lived.
Himura, my father longed for the coming of
a peaceful world more than anyone, didn't he?
Yet even so, he lived amidst the turmoil
during the end of the Shogunate.
He could neither pull back nor
stop to consider his actions.
He had no choice but to
continue making swords to kill.
He had no choice but to go directly against
his wishes... to live a contradicting life.
Yet even so, he accepted that contradicting
lifestyle because he wished to protect someone.
Isn't that right, Himura?
Master Seiku...
The sakabatou, Keishin. Please take it with you!
I believe that is what my
father would have wanted.
At this time, it is what I need most of all.
I shall humbly accept your kind offer.
Himura!
Humbwee! Humbwee!
Himura ish humbwee!
He's saying, "humbly"!
For now, let's go to Aoi-ya!
I'll introduce you to Gramps and the others.
I am confident they will help...
Himura?
It is time we parted ways, Miss Misao.
From this point on,
I must fight this battle on my own.
Miss Misao, I must not...
draw you further into my affairs.
What are you talking about? This is nothing!
I don't care if I get caught up in this.
Th-that's right! You still haven't told
me anything about Master Aoshi!
Han'nya...
Shikijo, Beshimi and Hyottoko...
Those are the guys from the Oniwaban!
All of them... have passed away.
You're lying!
All of them? Because they
got tangled up with you?
But you don't kill people, right?
I did not directly bring an end their lives...
But even so, if they had not chosen to fight me,
their lives would not have been lost.
Himura Battousai!
RESTAURANT AND INN
AOI-YA
I'm home!
Misao!
What's going on?
Oh, well, uh, you see...
Where's Gramps?
If-if you mean Okina...
Misao...
Answer me. Come on, Omasu!
Where did Gramps go?
If Gramps pulled out his old
shinobi uniform and weapons,
then this has to be something serious!
The preparations are complete.
I've burdened you.
If it is within the capacity of a woman
such as I, who cannot fight,
I will do anything.
I have faith in my subordinates.
But I could not entrust this to anyone but you.
I can leave everything in your able hands.
You chose me not for my appearance,
but for who I am.
Master Shishio...
That certainly took you a while.
Slaying 50 men took some time.
I merely said to keep an eye on Saito.
I was not on a child's errand.
I merely did this on the side.
Fifty men. As you can imagine,
I am still throbbing with excitement!
May I request a reward for
completing my errand?
Yeah, but of course.
I have no interest in taking this country!
All I want is to take your life!
Usui!
Very well.
It is a man's privilege to take that
which he desires with his own might.
I shall face you.
I just so happened to be
itching for a fight myself.
Let us fight until we are fully satisfied.
Master Shishio!
How are you faring, Himura?
Hajime Saito.
Rumor has it that your
sakabatou has been broken.
Even in Kyoto, do you keep your oath not to kill?
True, I have kept my oath. But that is all.
If I could have the honor of seeing the
Hitokiri Battousai here in Kyoto,
it would make for a most pleasant sight.
Last night, the fifty police officers I enlisted
in the fight to subdue Shishio were murdered.
It happened shortly after I issued their orders.
Someone must have been watching me.
Also, I have some information from Chou,
the member of Shishio's faction that
you captured this afternoon.
Okay. Please deal with him.
I am Goro Fujita, the one placed
in charge of torturing you.
Yer Hajime Saito! Didn't ya used
to serve in the Shinsengumi?
And speakin' of Shinsengumi,
y'all are famous for putting poor old
Furutaka under cruel torture
to make him fess up before
the lkeda-ya Incident.
You ain't the guy who did the dirty deed, are ya?
You are lucky. That was absolutely correct.
This is too much! I ain't the type to tough it out.
If I snitch, Master Shishio'll kill me.
So if yer willin' to protect me,
I'll tell ya anything ya wanna know.
Naturally, I will guarantee your safety.
I doubt anything could best the
power of the state. Talk.
Keep me safe!
Master Shishio's plan is
based upon the scenario
written by the radical loyalists
from the lkeda-ya Incident.
He intends to set Kyoto afire,
assassinate the leaders of the Shogunate,
and take the emperor to Choshu.
It's a massive plan to set the
thousand-year capital on fire
since they didn't pull it off last time.
He's got 500 subordinates who will
spread fires all across Kyoto.
During the confusion of the fire, they will
assassinate all of the civil servants in Kyoto!
He has taken measures for the
loyalists that burned him
to get a taste of the major offense they had
attempted during the end of the Shogunate.
Whatcha think? Whether you
believe me or not is up to you.
If it was all bullshit, yer welcome to
do whatever ya like with me!
Ain't like I can run away or hide.
Is that all you know?
I have information that verifies your statement.
What you said can be trusted,
but I doubt that is the whole of it.
He wants to avoid a repeat of
what happened in lkeda-ya at all costs,
assuming Shishio is not a fool.
It is only natural that you don't know more.
A careless slip of the tongue,
and the plan would fall to pieces.
If I were in Shishio's shoes, I would
NEVER disclose important information
that could affect the success of the operation
with an untrustworthy subordinate.
Master Shishio ain't like you!
There's no way I woulda followed him
if he was such a narrow-minded prick!
Oh, so do you know what is
going on behind the scenes?
You bet! Everyone's in on it.
But even if ya tortured me, I ain't talkin!
That'd be the same as betrayin' Master Shishio.
Anyone can gloss over the truth.
You cannot deny the possibility
that you were fed false information.
That ain't true! I saw it with my own eyes.
Right in the Port of Osaka!
That is all I needed to know. You saved me
the trouble of having to torture you.
Thank ya.
The Great Kyoto Fire...
He will topple the people's trust
in the government
by burning what has been ingrained in the hearts
of the Japanese as the symbol of our capital.
This is Shishio's declaration of war.
As for the other scheme that he kept secret...
You and I will stop him.
I take it you have no objections?
Where is Himura Battousai?
Your desire for information on Himura
has led you to attack your old hideout, Aoi-ya.
You have grown twisted!
It is too late to hammer out your distortions!
I must crush you.
Oh, boy. They are fighting for keeps.
Sou!
Do you think Shishio intends to kill him?
And here Usui could prove
to be a powerful asset.
It is fine, Sou.
This is his form... of justice.
To stop the Great Kyoto Fire,
we will need the assistance
of a group that knows Kyoto well.
I know who to ask.
"Fight a group with a group," is it?
lt'd be great if you could find
replacements for the fifty men I've lost.
Perhaps the outcome will prove promising
if I further confuse a heart already in turmoil
as you resist returning to your Hitokiri ways.
Two people have followed you here from Tokyo.
They have already arrived in Kyoto.
I made it in...
Master Aoshi!
Never appear before me again.
How was it, Usui? Were you boiling?
Yeah...
We're not done yet.
See how I burn before you go.
I will show you directly through those
festering eyes, not through your Mind's Eye.
I saw it...
What did you see?
Your... body... as it burns in flames.
That is exactly what I desire.
Yahiko! Yahiko!
Really! Where could he have gone? He ran off...
Oh, Officer Fujita! What impeccable timing.
I've got a man in custody
who picked a massive fight in town.
He's terribly insistent that I let him see you.
I think he said you know each other...
Just like I thought!
Instead of blindly searching around,
I just needed to get in trouble
with the cops to catch you!
Meeting up that way is a whole lot faster.
So it was you after all, moron!
Pfft, course it was!
This is Sanosuke Sagara's
grand arrival in Kyoto!
Kenshin...
Ummm, I...
Why?!
Why did you come?
Are you... mad?
Partly.
Huh?
My other half says,
"Thank you."
You guys! Why are you enjoying some
emotional reunion without me?!
Because you just had to wander off somewhere!
Nature called! Figure that out
for yourself, Ms. Dense!
Going to pee isn't all that
embarrassing for a guy!
Just be straightforward about it, Yahiko!
I'm still going through puberty!
Or so you'd like to think! You're still a little brat!
You suffer embarrassment as you mature!
I just... don't know anymore!
There is no stopping now!
Neither for you, nor me...
If you can stop me, I dare you to try!
I can no longer turn back.
Until I defeat him,
my battle will not come to an end.
I... will never leave your side again.
Even if I cannot see what lays ahead,
I will keep walking...
...with this sword.
Kaze nara yurusou
If it were the wind
Nani mo kamo
All would be forgiven
Sayakeshi nijizora
The vibrant rainbow in the sky
Tokete yuku
Begins to dissipate
Ishidatami ni wa
On the stone pavement
Okizari no hana
There is a deserted flower
Semete daite yaritakute
At the very least, I want to embrace it
Ato sukoshi utsukushikereba
If it were a little more beautiful
Orarezu ni ikita darou ka
Could it have lived without getting plucked?
Itazura ni yume no inochi wo
Who is the one that mischievously
Kimeru no wa dare darou
Determined its life's dream?
Katamuku hoshi-tachi
Sinking stars
Soba ni ite
Stay by my side
Yoake wa nana iro
The dawn has seven colors
Dare no tame
But who are they for?