The Cage of Love
Episode 27
Zhou Shao Tian.
Do you have anything else to defend yourself with?
Shao Tian. Say something.
Didn't you swear to me that by using your father's name that you didn't kill Old Master Wu?
You didn't kill him. You are not a killer. Say something.
If you create a scene again, I will kick you out of the court.
Zhou Shao Tian. Based on the allegations by the police
the court will conclude the present case.
Is there anything that you need to explain yourself?
Zhou Shao Tian. Since you have nothing to say,
with that, the court will move the case for sentencing.
We will announce the verdict now.
Ling Long's weaving and dyeing factories original owner and Secretary Zhou Shao Tian
used his position
together with Old Cai, the original Ling Long Treasurer,
embezzled RMB$10 million.
After that, Zhou Shao Tian killed Boss Wu of Ling Long.
There is very clear evidence,
for the court to sentence Zhou Shao Tian with murder charges
and subject the death sentence three days from now.
Why did he faint? Old Cai!
- Stay calm.
- What's wrong?
In regards to the Rong Da weaving and dyeing factory and the Wu home,
because Zhao Shao Tian acquired these through illegal means,
the court judgement
is to return everything to the Wu family.
Court dismissed.
We can still save him. Send him the the emergency department of the hospital now.
Don't delay. Go with me to the hospital now.
You both, guard here.
Yes.
Hello. What do you think of your son being a killer?
Don't ask me. I don't know.
Don't leave. Please say a few words.
Please comment.
Stop.
Where is the ambulance?
I can't believe this.
I really can't believe this.
God finally opened his eyes.
Old Master can rest in peace now.
Mom. Let's go.
I really never imagined this.
May I ask, you are...
We are doctors from Fu Yan hospital. We just received a call from the police.
We heard that someone fainted in court.
We came as fast as we could.
But a doctor already came just now.
- He took the patient away.
- How could this be?
We have limited hospital staff. Another doctor couldn't have come.
-Director.
- What's wrong?
Old Cai has been taken away.
What?
Don't tell anyone. Find him and get him back immediately.
Yes.
Hello.
Boss Jiang. The verdict has been announced.
Zhou Shao Tian has been sentenced to death.
- I get it.
- But Old Cai has been taken away by someone.
Zhou Shao Tian, goodbye.
♫I used to think ♫
♫that one day I will stop running away ♫
♫ from the heart that is afraid ♫
Brother Shao Tian. You are a really good man.
♫and not willing to compromise♫
Do you know that I heard
♫not willing to compromise♫
many nice ladies in the city want to marry you?
♫If we are hurt to tears, ♫
Who do you want to marry?
I...
♫love will eventually wither ♫
If you find that this is not bad,
♫Together with all other people♫
would you like to pay for this month's rent first?
♫we have to believe in fate ♫
Here.
Sorry, Brother Shao Tian. I brought you trouble again.
♫You are the reason why I am sad♫
I should be be apologising instead.
♫When you are unclasping our hands♫
With my present power, I can't do anything either.
♫its like I can feel the taste of my heart♫
But believe me, I won't let you stay here for too long.
♫You are the one♫
♫that makes my dreams fly♫
I only want to say this.
Cai Hong, let's be together.
♫Your fast paced love is so beautiful♫
Let me take care of you.
♫ that you have left a laughing aftertaste ♫
♫ on my mind. ♫
Cai Hong!
Brother Shao Tian!
Beat him.
Stop beating him.
Brother Shao Tian!
♫ If we are hurt to tears♫
Stop it.
Brother Shao Tian!
♫ Iove will wither away♫
Believe it.
♫Together with all other people♫
What you see now is reality.
Everything that I had done was to have a chance to dance with you.
♫we have to believe in fate. You are the reason ♫
Do you know that the times when I'm with you are my happiest moments?
♫ why I am sad when you are unclasping our hands♫
I love you.
♫its like I can feel the taste of my heart♫
♫ Who are you to me? ♫
♫You are the one♫
♫that makes my dreams fly♫
♫Your fast paced love is so beautiful♫
♫ that you have left an aftertaste ♫
♫ on my mind ♫
Headline! The Wu Hong Da case has finally been solved.
Perfect son-in law receives death penalty! Execution follows in 3 days!
- Give me one.
- Headline.
He will sentenced to death in three days.
Miss Wu.
Aunt, please get up now.
I'm begging you. Please help Shao Tian.
- I don't know how to help him.
- Shao Tian would never kill anyone.
I'm begging you. Please help him.
Aunt. You also saw
the statements by others.
The court also found him guilty.
Brother Shao Tian didn't want to defend himself.
I really can't help him.
Shao Tian didn't defend himself. He must have his reasons.
Shao Tian would never kill anyone.
I have something to tell you.
Please let me finish talking first.
Aunt. Let's go in and talk.
Aunt, please sit.
Have some tea.
Aunt. What do you have to say to me?
Miss Wu. The police said that Shao Tian stole Ling Long's money.
I believe this.
Moreover, I knew about it. He planned it for a long time.
There are certain things you may not know.
Ling Long belonged to the Jiang family ten years ago.
I know.
My father framed Old Master Jiang
and closed down Ling Long.
I know that my father caused the death of Old Master Jiang.
But there are certain things that you don't know.
Shao Tian probably didn't tell you.
What is it that I knew nothing about it?
Many years ago,
I was working at Ling Long factory.
Shao Tian's father was very sick.
Fortunately, with Old Master Jiang's help,
we had some money to let my husband see the doctor.
Later, something happened at the factory,
your father had Ling Long searched.
He fired all Ling Long's original workers.
Our family was going to starve to death.
I could only just watch Shao Tian's father
suffer in pain in bed on that day.
We didn't have money to buy medicine.
I didn't have any choice.
It was me who personally used my hands to strangle him to death.
To help him ease the pain.
It was also to let Shao Tian have food and survive.
Shao Tian personally witnessed everything.
Aunt... What you mean is that...
if my father didn't frame Old Master Jiang,
and didn't search Ling Long, you wouldn't have lost your job
and nothing like that would have happened?
No. Miss Wu. I didn't mean that.
I don't blame Old Master Wu.
This is my fate as a poor person.
But this matter affected Shao Tian a lot.
Subsequently, your father took over Ling Long.
Shao Tian schemed to get into Ling Long and get close to your father.
I think he stole your father's money to make him feel what it was like to be penniless.
But no matter what,
even if he did not kill my father, he fancied the idea to do so.
Shao Tian would never kill anyone, Miss Wu.
Shao Tian joined Ling Long to get close to your father as part of his plan for revenge.
But...
he fell in love with you.
He couldn't control it.
This wasn't part of his plan.
All these years, he has been living in pain.
As his mother, I could see that.
I'm not speaking on behalf of my son.
Miss Wu. Think about it.
If he killed Old Master Wu, why didn't he leave then?
It's because he couldn't give up on you.
He would never kill anyone.
Why then, when Brother Shao Tian was in court,
didn't he defend himself?
He didn't even say anything.
This must be a misunderstanding. Shao Tian must be in some difficulties.
Previously, when Master Jiang brought the fountain pen to my house, I asked him about it.
He swore on his father's name.
He said that he didn't kill anyone.
I believe my son.
Miss Wu, don't be so haste in naming Shao as the murderer.
Think about his sincerity for you. Think about how good he was to you.
I'm begging you, Miss Wu.
Aunt, please get up now.
What you have said,
I will think carefully about this.
Thanks.
Shao Tian joined Ling Long
to get close to your father. It was part of his plan.
But he fell in love with you.
Furthermore, he couldn't control it.
This wasn't part of his plan.
If he killed Old Master Wu, why didn't he leave then?
He couldn't give up on you.
He would never kill anyone.
He swore on his father's name.
He said that he didn't kill anyone.
I believe my son.
What brings you here?
I'm very confused. I don't know how I got here.
Aunt Zhou told me a lot of things I didn't know today.
I have not imagined that my father's greed would cause so much tragedy.
What should I do?
What did Aunt Zhou tell you?
Uncle Zhou's death was connected to my father.
It was my father who took away Ling Long and caused Aunt Zhou to lose her job.
Because of this, she didn't have the money for medical fees.
At that time, Brother Shao Tian personally witnessed everything.
His mother strangled his father to death.
So Zhou Shao Tian, all these years, just was taking revenge for his father?
Aunt Zhou said that Brother Shao Tian stole Ling Long's money as part of his plan.
He wanted my father to experience what it was like without any money.
But he didn't kill my father.
I have known Brother Shao Tian for seven or eight years.
I can't accept that he killed my father.
I can't believe it either
but he didn't say anything.
He didn't defend himself himself and he's going to be executed soon.
Jiang Yu. You are very smart. You must have a way to save him.
Please help me to save Brother Shao Tian.
Ever since Old Cai got taken away,
I find that everything feels strange.
Zhou Shao Tian has already been found guilty. Who else would do that?
Who else wanted Old Cai?
I think it's possible that someone wants the secret formula.
They think that the secret formula is still with Old Cai.
I heard from Director Chen that there was someone else who was looking for Old Cai.
If that person is connected to the secret formula,
then wouldn't they had something to do with your father's death?
Let's look for Brother Shao Tian and check with him.
Could you go with me?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Aunt Zhou came to look for me.
She doesn't believe that you are the killer.
Brother Shao Tian. I don't believe that you killed my father either.
I would like to hear this personally from you.
The court has already given the verdict.
Do you need to ask again?
You have been with my father for ten years.
How could you have done it?
No matter what,
I still don't believe it.
You are going to die in two days.
Such a refined gentleman as you will probably say there is nothing to be afraid of.
What is there for me to be afraid of?
Since you want me to tell the truth, I would like to ask you something and you should answer truthfully too.
Before we exchange the truths...
I am a dead man walking.
I have nothing to lose. Would you dare?
Why wouldn't I dare?
Fine.
Let me ask you then. When Wu Hong Da died, was the secret formula with you?
Give me an honest answer and I will tell you the truth.
You are right.
The real secret formula was with me
but I already burnt it.
So, the secret formula was with you.
Jiang Yu. You are very sly. You tricked so many people.
Wu Hong Da personally gave me the secret formula.
It's not what everyone thought so, that I killed him for it.
Why didn't you tell me then?
You said that you waited 18 years for making the final steps in getting the formula.
Did you lie to me?
I did this to flush out the real killer of your father.
The Jiang family's secret formula
is being passed from generation to generation orally.
My father told me it when I was young. It's all in my memory.
And your father sharing the formula with me was the second step.
As for that secret formula, I still had to wait till I was eighteen years old before I could get it.
Okay, it's your turn.
Did you kill Wu Hong Da or not?
I didn't.
I know that I committed a lot of wrong things but I really didn't kill your father.
I didn't do that.
If it wasn't you,
why didn't you deny?
If I denied it, would you believe me?
So to say, you took Ling Long's money
and used the fountain pen to injure him but you didn't kill him.
- Is this the case?
-Yes.
When Wu Hong Da discovered that his money was transferred out,
he suspected me and Old Cai.
Bye.
Enter.
Boss. You are looking for me?
Explain each and everything to me.
Boss. I...
I only borrowed a bit money for another company.
- As for the other, I really don't know anything about it.
- A bit of money?!
You call the lion share of Lin Long's profit for so many years a bit of money?
You loaned the money out?
Do you know that this will affect Ling Long?
Boss.
I swear that I really don't know anything.
That company said that they were in urgent need of cash and they would give me five percent interest.
I also wanted Ling Long...
- Five percent?
For all those years you have been feeding your private acount! Do you really want me to believe this story?
Let me tell you. This is not a lapse.
It's a conspiracy.
Boss. You must believe me. I have been loyal to you.
You must believe me.
I... I was also tricked by others.
Okay, tell me who tricked you then.
Speak.
Boss. Cai Hong said to pick you up and go back together.
I thought you already settled your work.
Go back first.
Wait for me in the office tomorrow morning.
Yes.
Boss. Can we leave now?
I still want to meet a
very important client.
Okay.
Shao Tian.
Don't you have anything else to tell me?
- Boss. Is there still something else?
- Speak now!
Why did you conspire with Old Cai?
and scam Ling Long of its money.
Was I lacking in warmth with you all these years?
Why did you do this?
Speak. Old Cai is an outsider.
I won't find it strange that he did this. As for you,
I have always regarded you as my son.
I regarded you as family.
publicly and secretly.
I already told you many times.
I thought of you as my successor.
Ling Long will be yours sooner or later.
What else are you still unhappy with?
Are you complaining that I have lived too long?
You wanted me to die earlier, right?
Frankly, this is not what you think it is.
Okay. Tell me then. What is it all about?
I will listen to you now. Speak.
You have nothing to say?
God, Zhao Sheng. In vain I have told you many times that growing a business is painstaking.
You still want to marry my daughter now. Dream on!
Okay, if you don't want to talk. Don't say anything at all.
Ungrateful person. Wait here, I'm going to call the police.
Get lost.
Let go.
You...
I'm going to call the police now.
Give it to me.
You ungrateful brat. Why did you do it?
I was forced to do it.
You were forced you to do it?
What do you mean?
You stubborn...
In the midst of the confusion, I used the fountain pen to injure him.
Are you trying to kill me?
In the end, I rushed out
I wounded his shoulder,
but it wasn't life threatening.
I didn't kill him.
Who killed my father then?
When he died,
where were you?
I was with Old Cai. I tried to console him.
He was extremely scared and wanted me to leave with him.
If we don't leave, it will be too late. We will really go to jail.
When I quarreled with the boss, I injured him.
- I didn't want to do that.
- Leave with me then.
Wu Hong Da will never let you off.
No. I must explain to Cai Hong.
If I leave now, I won't be able to explain myself.
I... You are a man.
Why are you so indecisive over a woman?
Cai Hong. You said that when you rushed downstairs,
you heard a noise around Maifu hospital at noon.
At that time,
Old Cai and I heard the alarm too.
Looks like only Old Cai can prove your innocence.
Hence, what we need to do now is to find Old Cai.
Did you already know who took away Old Cai?
You also figured this out now?
Old Cai has no value on his own.
I suspect now that she is the killer.
That's what I think too.
That person is...
- Lu Man.
You are finally conscious.
You... who are you?
Why did you tie me up here?
Don't ask what you shouldn't ask.
If you know who I am,
do you think you will stay alive?
Okay, I won't ask
but why did you capture me and bring me here?
I brought you here because I wanted to find out where the Jiang family's secret formula is.
As long as you hand over the secret formula, not only will I guarantee your safety,
I can also guarantee that you will live comfortably for the rest of your life.
What secret formula?
I don't know anything about this. I don't have the secret formula.
You are playing dumb with me.
Let me tell you. If you don't hand over the secret formula,
you will die.
Miss. I'm begging you.
I really don't have the secret formula.
Fine.
Since I talked to him nicely and he doesn't want to talk,
let him try some of your torture then.
I'd like to see if he will still fool around after being hellishly whipped.
Beat him cruelly.
Miss. I'm begging you.
I'm begging you to let me go.
I really don't have the secret formula.
It's useless even if you beat me to death.
Beat him cruelly.
Beat him until he hands over the secret formula and then contact me.
Yes.
What are you thinking of?
I was thinking of using the secret formula in exchange for Old Cai.
Secret formula?
Are you referring to Jiang family's secret formula?
You are really willing to use it to exchange for Old Cai?
What I mean is to use the secret formula as bait,
to find out where Old Cai is.
But if you hand over the secret formula and Lu Man denies it, Old Cai will die in her hands.
- Come with me.
- Where are we going?
Let's find Zhou Shao Tian and think of a solution.
A bad person will know another bad person better.
This plan won't work. Lu Man, that wench,
has gone crazy over the secret formula.
In order to get it, she's capable of doing anything.
Let's think together about how we can make Lu Man admit that she is holding Old Cai.
Seek her out at the refuge at her brother's house.
Tell her that the secret formula is with Old Cai's wife.
This is not a bad idea.
If she deals with Madam Lin, Lu Man will be more assured.
Furthermore, if we say that the secret formula is with Madam Lin, it's more believable.
Whether Lu Man will believe this or not,
what happens next will depend on you.
No problem. Leave this to me.
- Young Master.
- Spread this.
Let everyone in Huzhou know that I'm looking for Old Cai's wife's whereabouts.
Yes.
By doing this, you are letting Lu Man believe that the secret formula is with Old Cai's wife.
So how? Did Old Cai hand over the secret formula?
He is still saying that he doesn't have the secret formula
but...
But what?
But Jiang Yu's men are also looking around frantically for Old Cai's wife. We heard about this.
It seems like Old Cai got his hands on the secret formula.
Looks like the secret formula is definitely with Old Cai.
Uncle Lai.
Find someone to watch Jiang Yu.
Also, continue to torture Old Cai.
I don't believe that
even if he dies, he won't hand over the secret formula.
Yes.
Still not talking?
I'm begging you.
I really don't have the secret formula.
Just kill me.
Stop torturing me.
Miss. This rascal has a tight mouth. He still won't hand over the secret formula.
You just said that it's better to be dead, right?
Let me tell you. You are still far away from death.
Even if you want to die, it's not that easy.
I will capture your family and slowly torture them.
Thus. before you die, you should think of them first.
No.
Miss. I already sent men to find his family.
Finding them is not such a difficult task.
Don't.
I'm begging you. Let my family go.
They really know nothing. I really don't have the secret formula.
If you are worried about your family, hand over the secret formula now.
Don't waste your time with him. Break his limbs.
- See whether he will talk or not.
- Don't!
I'm begging you. I really don't have the secret formula.
I'm begging you to let me go.
Throw water on him to revive him and question him again.
If he still doesn't talk, cut off his limbs.
I want to see how high his tolerance level is.
Who's there?
It's me.
Jiang Yu?
Is it convenient to talk?
Come in.
Jiang Yu. It's late in the night. Why are you looking for me?
Zhou Shao Tian wanted me to look for you to do him a favour.
My brother will be sentenced to death in two days.
Weren't you behind all this?
He didn't kill anyone.
I know. I don't need you to tell me this.
I looked for you today to prove his innocence.
He has already been sentenced to death. Could there be anything worse than this?
Why would I still need to harm him?
What do you want me to do?
The only one who can prove Zhou Shao Tian's innocence now
is Old Cai but he has been taken away by someone.
Zhou Shao Tian thought of a plan to find Old Cai
but he needs your help.
Okay, I will do it for my brother.
It's really very beautiful.
It's already so late. Why are you still dyeing the textile?
Come here.
Only if we have this textile, Lu Man would then believe that
the real secret formula is with Old Cai's wife.
Brother Shao Tian went against you in the past.
Even while in locked up,
he shied not from lynching you.
Thank you
for helping him this way.
I'm not helping him.
Isn't it the same for you?
You clearly know that Zhou Shao Tian stole Ling Long's money and caused it to go bankrupt.
But ultimately, you are still willing to believe him.
All of this happened because of my father's greed.
It was my father who had wronged the Jiang family.
Furthermore, he even harmed Brother Shao Tian's family.
The mistakes keep repeating.
The night of the incident,
Brother Shao Tian told me that
if he could start anew,
he doesn't know
if he should go back to the way it was or start anew.
I think I finally understand now
how helpless he was
and what kind of torment he has suffered everyday.
Blame my father for this.
He personally planted a poisonous seed.
That's why it grew into a poisonous flower.
And prickly fruit.
Due to the previous generation's race to power,
next generation has to bear the consequences.
Your father may have been wrong
but he had such a good daughter like you.
Your appearance
was the greatest gift of god given to him.
I'm not that good as you think I am.