The Cage of Love
Episode 22
Why isn't Jiang Yu not making any moves?
Eh?
Why is he standing there and not making any moves?
Looks like he will be out soon.
Why isn't he moving? There is not much time left.
That's right. The incense stick will burn out soon.
What's going on? What is he doing?
Why isn't he making any moves?
He's making us so anxious.
What is he trying to do?
Boss Jiang. Is there a problem?
No.
He seems to be moving. Why is he holding a brush?
I don't know. Just watch.
Cai Hong. He is not dyeing the cloth. Why is he drawing?
Brother, what are you drawing?
Look, he's using the brush to dye the cloth.
If God wants to give me money, no one can stop him.
Mom. Why isn't he dyeing the cloth? It's not like he doesn't have the materials.
Let me tell you. It must be that he doesn't know how to dye.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
The Jiang family has been in the dyeing and weaving business for many generations.
Does Jiang Yu know this technique or not?
If he doesn't,
he could have sent his master instead.
It's like a drawing.
Time's up.
Both, please show your skills.
Great!
Rong Da, beautiful!
Great.
Rong Da!
Beautiful! Great!
Great.
That's great.
Amazing.
Great.
Jiang Yu is really something.
Perhaps, grudges shouldn't end in revenge.
Just like in this dirty pond,
such a clean and pure flower could even grow in it.
Great.
Fortunately, I didn't lose everything.
However, it was very exciting.
Yes.
Governor Liu.
Is this considered a dyed cloth?
In regards to the remark,
there are dyes on this cloth. Don't tell me this is not considered dyeing?
Whether it's accepted or not, let's the audience decide.
Everyone, isn't this so?
Okay, let's start the vote now.
Give your lily to the one whom you like his work best.
Let's start with Warlord Lu and President Zhang.
Great.
Come and vote.
Ling Long!
Mr Zhang, please start first.
Okay.
I...
One stalk for Ling Long.
One stalk for Rong Da.
Miss Lu. Why aren't you voting?
For fairness, we can only vote once as contestants.
I will leave my vote to someone else.
Why do you still need to consider? Of course, you should choose Rong Da.
Brother Shao Tian's cloth is indeed beautiful but it's not second to none.
But Boss Jiang's cloth was personally drawn on.
It can be considered as second to none.
Who cares about that? I bet a lot of money on Shao Tian.
I will be stupid if I don't vote for Shao Tian.
Thirty four stalks for Ling Long.
Thirty five stalks for Ling Long.
Sixty one stalks for Ling Long.
I think we can't tell who the winner is for this first round.
This is how a contest should be.
This way, it's more interesting.
- Isn't that so?
- Rong Da has one hundred stalks.
No. There will be a clear victor soon.
One hundred and twenty stalks for Rong Da.
One hundred and twenty seven stalks for Rong Da.
Ling Long also has one hundred and twenty seven stalks.
I really didn't imagine the result would be like this.
Both their votes are equal.
Since this is the case, I will now announce that they...
Wait.
I haven't voted yet.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I remember you said that grudges
shouldn't end in revenge.
And that even in a dirty pond, a clean and pure flower could even grow.
At that time, I really couldn't forget my unhappiness.
But you also told me that
you couldn't forget the grudge about that person who killed your father.
I think
I can't forget it either.
Miss Wu Cai Hong gave the vote to Rong Da.
This is the first part of the contest.
No one could imagine that this would be the result.
Yet Zhou Shao Tian's cloth
is very deserving.
The winner is Zhou Shao Tian.
The second part of the contest will be the day after tomorrow.
Let our honourable guest announce the winner.
Xiao Man. Your silk contest is rather interesting.
Mr Zhang. After you first.
Warlord Lu, please.
Brother, I am not convinced about the dye.
What was so great about Zhou Shao Tian's cloth?
Leave first.
What's going on?
I couldn't dye it.
Why?
Someone tampered with my cloth. I couldn't dye it.
Why didn't you stop the contest then? Someone is playing around with it.
How am I to stop it? I was the one who personally brought the cloth.
Cai Hong. You did well in the voting.
It's right that you gave it to Shao Tian.
You should thank Cai Hong properly today.
Stop there.
What's wrong? Not happy with losing?
Competing in the silk contest with such despicable people like you
is only bringing us exquisite shame.
If you have the substance, you should compete fairly.
You sabotaged the cloth. Do you call yourself a righteous competitor?
- You...
- By the way,
you are not a righteous competitor at all. You are a bandit.
Who are you calling a bandit?
You should know clearly in your heart what you did.
Fei Fei, let's go.
What are you talking about?
Enough, stepmom. Cai Yun, go back with her. I still have matters to attend to here.
Okay, mom.
Be careful then.
- Mom.
- Let's keep the money.
I would like to check both the clothes.
How could this happen?
Did you sabotage this?
I don't know what's going on.
They were both here when we came in. I didn't do anything to this.
You have mistook me.
There are many things
which doesn't require sabotages.
The motive of this silk contest
is to let Jiang Yu take out his secret formula.
It's not important to sabotage anything.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Congratulations.
Don't get involved between me and Jiang Yu. I can win fairly,
Isn't it good enough that you win? The method is not that important.
If not, how will we force Jiang Yu to resort to his method?
- I think the last battle...
- I already told you that
I wanted a fair contest with Jiang Yu.
If you hadn't gotten involved today, I wouldn't have won that fairly.
If you didn't sabotage it, I wouldn't have any misunderstandings with Cai Hong.
If you get involved again, don't blame me
for voiding our contract.
Okay then. I promise you that I won't get involved again.
I will wait for your good news tomorrow.
Wu Cai Hong will die in my hands one day.
Shao Tian, you are becoming more capable.
Winning the silk contest is such beautiful thing.
My deceased husband really didn't misjudge you.
Cai Hong is in there. I will call her for you.
Cai Hong.
What are you doing? He came here especially to see you and you are leaving? So rude.
Have a good chat between the both of you.
Stay here for dinner. I'm going to the kitchen.
I know that you are angry about the silk contest.
Please believe me. I didn't do that.
You didn't do it? It can't be Miss Lu...
It was Miss Lu. She was afraid I couldn't defeat Jiang Yu
and that Rong Da would have to withdraw from Huzhou.
It's because of me again.
I forced Miss Lu to take this step.
Who would be willing to withdraw from the dyeing industry from Huzhou?
She doesn't has anything to do with me but she helped me.
It's because of you.
Did I give you a lot of trouble?
If it weren't for me, you wouldn't have to owe her such a big favour.
Don't say this. If it weren't for you,
I couldn't have beaten Jiang Yu. I already told Miss Lu
that I could win fairly against Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu already lost the first part. If he loses the second part,
he will have to withdraw from the dyeing industry.
Thus, he may use the secret formula. As long as he uses it,
we will have the evidence.
I will tell Director Chen and he won't let him get away.
So, the motive of the silk contest is to make Jiang Yu
admit that he killed Old Master Wu to get ahold of the secret formula?
Sit.
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
I was afraid that he would catch wind of this. If Jiang Yu finds out,
he will never take part in the silk contest. Especially,
if he use the secret formula, he will then be admitting that he is the killer.
Brother Shao Tian is right. Director Chen, you must help me.
We have been investigating this case for a long time. I will like to find out the truth too. I will be there to observe on that day.
If Jiang Yu uses the secret formula, it will mean that he is the killer.
I will arrest him.
A few workers resigned this afternoon.
One of them was a skilled master.
They have all gone to Rong Da.
Brother, we only lost the first time. What should we do next?
It's my fault. I already said that
I didn't want you to get involved.
Yet until the end, I still need you to take the burden with me.
Brother, we are family. We should share the burdens together.
I have watched him working so hard
and suffering so much before you could come back to Huzhou to start anew.
I can't just watch and see you lose everything.
Fei Fei, don't worry. We will never lose.
As long as we use the Jiang's family's secret formula,
we will never lose.
Secret formula?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Father.
Please don't blame me.
- Who are you betting on?
- I'm betting on Rong Da.
Are you sure Zhou Shao Tian will win?
If you want to bet, bet now.
How much do you want to bet?
I bet too little yesterday. Today, I placed a big bet.
Do you think you will win?
Of course.
- How could that be such a good thing?
- That's right. Your winnings will be big.
Bet on this and you will get rich.
Yesterday's contest was really exciting.
I thought it would end in a draw.
I didn't think that ultimately, the winner would be Zhou Shao Tian.
Human affairs are hard to predict.
It's not confirmed yet who will be the final winner today.
Go now.
You too.
$50? $100?
Let's make it $100.
- Governor.
- Why are you only back now? Did you buy it?
- Yes.
- How big is the bet?
- $100.
Okay, leave.
$100.
I must win back everything what I lost yesterday.
Everyone, the second part of the contest
starts now. Let's invite our four judges.
Everyone, let's welcome them.
First is the Dean He of the Jiangnu School of Dyeing.
He has been in the dyeing industry for over thirty years.
Second is Miss Ma Da. She is from a famous dyeing factory in Jiangnan.
Third is the owner of the department store in our Huzhou, Mr Li.
He has been engaged in fabric sourcing for more than two decades.
The fourth is our city's most prestigious teacher in printing transfer.
Master Li, whose works are real masterpieces.
Great.
Not bad.
Judges, please take a seat. Next, I would like to introduce
the second theme for this part of the contest.
The second theme is reproductions.
Reproductions?
Before the incense stick burns out...
they must reproduce an exact replica of the original cloth.
They will be judged by our esteemed guests.
Similarly, the one with the most votes will be the winner.
How did you know that it will be reproductions?
I have my own methods,
but I want you to lose to Jiang Yu this time.
Why are you using this opportunity to kick out Jiang Yu?
Don't forget what our initial motive is.
What we need is the secret formula. This is just a reproduction.
Jiang Yu will definitely not use the secret formula.
Even if you win, what about the secret formula?
The last two parts will be even tougher.
Even if you lose, you won't embarrass yourself. Think about this carefully.
The first part, you sabotaged Jiang Yu.
The second part, you want me to deliberately lose to Jiang Yu.
Why can't Jiang Yu and I have a fair and open competition?
Fairness? You should know better than me that,
In this world, there is no such thing as fairness.
Don't forget our first goal just because you want to prove yourself.
If you win this part, you won't be able to force Jiang Yu to use his secret formula.
When that time comes, so what if Jiang Yu leaves the dyeing industry?
Wu Cai Hong won't be able to get the proof that Jiang Yu is the killer.
She will probably not forget this for the rest of her life.
Brother Shao Tian.
Brother Shao Tian. What are you thinking of?
Nothing.
I don't want you to lose just because of me.
You started picking up the skills when you were very young.
You picked up very good skills during the past ten years.
In this silk contest,
all the seniors in the dyeing industry are watching you.
You have your pride.
If you don't do your best,
how would Jiang Yu know that we are his true rivals?
In any case,
I don't want you to lose the contest just because of me.
Thank you.
Let's invite the two contestants on stage now.
Great. Victory to Ling Long!
Victory to Hong Da!
This cloth is from the Tang Dynasty.
It requires the use of beeswax as an anti-agent.
Then heating the wax into the pattern on the back will be crucial
to continue printing
on this quality of silk.
As experts in dyeing we have high demands.
Moreover, this is the most famous creation in the Tang Dynasty.
This art was made with superb printing.
It will be difficult to reproduce its charm.
Next, I'm announcing that
the contest will begin.
Victory to Hong Da!
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
For this part of the contest,
that rascal, Zhou Shao Tian is working very diligently.
Jiang Yu is not slacking either.
Jiang Yu doesn't depend on it.
Is Zhou Shao Tian your man?
Didn't we agree that we would have an open and fair contest?
Time's up. Please display your works.
Excellent!
It's really beautiful. It looks exactly the same.
Rong Da will definitely win this time.
Rong Da's performance is not bad.
Time's up. Why didn't you hang it up yet?
Did you ruin the dye?
Hang it up.
That's right. If you can't do it, just admit your defeat now.
- What's the hurry?
- Mom, don't say anything anymore. Sit down now.
It's great!
Ling Long!
Look, it's not bad.
I think Boss Jiang's cloth has surpassed that of the original.
What are you talking about?
Why can't I see it? So what about Jiang Yu?
The cloth may be dyed better but why is it superfluous?
So what if there are extras? Shao Tian is definitely the winner.
- That's right.
- How could you say that?
It's definitely great.
Everyone, please tell us your views about this contest.
Please come up with sound advise.
I will speak first then.
We all saw the rules with the standards.
Based on the rule of the contest, I feel that Mr Zhou's cloth is closest to the original.
I don't care about new trends. Rules are rules.
Based on the rule, Mr Zhou's cloth is closer to the original. He should be the winner.
Fine. Well said.
I think Boss Jiang's is more remarkable.
Even though the flower motifs on his cloth
is not close to the original, it's very innovative.
It is fit for our currently developing trends.
People like us in this industry should go for innovations.
Not only does it has a new approach, Boss Jiang's innovation
deserves compliments.
But the big national development should be vigorously promoted.
I support Boss Jiang.
Dean He has already said what's in my heart.
I support Boss Jiang too.
In this case, do we still abide by the rule?
The newly appointed President sent Mr Zhang to purchase the goods.
Looking at how young Mr Zhang is, he is definitely for the new style.
Huzhou needs to show this side.
That's right. Master Lin.
Do you think that Boss Jiang's skill is not up to scratch?
Of course not.
On the contrary, it's excellent.
Since this is the case, Master Lin,
let's be harmonious and have a mutual consent.
That's right. Let's be harmonious.
Fine.
Everyone, please continue.
Development and innovation must be awakened together.
Isn't that so?
Brother, why did you dye it differently? You clearly could do that.
Regardless of how I dyed it,
I will definitely win this part.
How could this be possible? Why are you so sure?
After the four judges have done their assessments, their verdict is...
Ling Long dye factory.
- Great.
- How could I lose again?
How could you say that? What's going on?
- How could it be this way?
- Mom. keep quiet.
Brother, we won. You are too amazing.
I already said, what benefits did Jiang Yu give you?
Don't leave.
How did this benefit you? I'm not done with you yet.
Explain this clearly to me. I'm so angry.
I lost everything.
Brother Shao Tian.
In my heart, you won.
This is very subjective.
If everyone goes after the new trends,
who will satisfy our clients?
I only care how you feel.
Jiang Yu can see your ability now.
If he wants to beat you, he can only use his secret formula.
He won't be complacent for too long.
Wu Mansion
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
What's wrong? Are you still frustrated about losing to Jiang Yu?
I can tell that Jiang Yu is deliberating testing us today.
His last piece was superfluous. overdone
But it's good too.
Today, other than those older Masters,
I'm close with the rest of them.
Before the contest, I already talked to them.
I told them that this time, I must let Jiang Yu win.
But looks like your skills today is not as strong as Jiang Yu's.
Miss Lu.
I know very well what you are up to.
If you still want to achieve your goal, keep quiet now.
Okay, I talked too much.
All men need their face and pride.
But don't blame me for telling you this today.
What you lost today is just the contest.
You still have the chance to reverse it in three days.
But if you had lost a woman today,
the loser will be Rong Da.
I'm afraid it won't be that simple as losing face.
I won't lose face.
Don't worry. Because of Cai Hong,
I will definitely force Jiang Yu to use his secret formula at the final part of the contest.
Okay, don't forget what you promised me.
Please do your best in three days
to make Jiang Yu hand over the secret formula.
Can't you just do it for me?
I just overheard your conversation with Miss Lu.
Suspend the competition.
If Jiang Yu really doesn't have the secret formula and Rong Da loses in the end,
I really don't know what I should do.
Cai Hong.
Don't you have any confidence in me?
Are you afraid that I will lose to Jiang Yu?
- No.
- Don't tell me to give up then.
I'm not only doing this for you.
I want to continue with this contest too.
Okay, go back and rest first.
I still need to prepare for the final part of the contest.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Am I being too selfish and thinking only of myself?
I have never thought of Brother Shao Tian's difficulties.
Jiang Yu, are you affected by the impass as well?
I really hope that you don't have the secret formula.
I really hope that this didn't happen.