The Cage of Love
Episode 10
I promise, after this,
you will have no regrets.
Boss Jiang, you also offer a final inspection of the product.
That's right.
I heard that Boss Zhou of Fu Sheng
orders are intended to be made of this.
Let's go to visit the Miss of former Mr. Wu of Ling Long.
- There are some things that will fly.
- Yes, yes.
Prices are good also.
They even will allow us to do the water test. Let's go over to their shop.
Okay, everyone.
Let's go over to Fu Sheng to take a look again. After all, we are businessmen.
It makes sense to go where there is stability.
Let's go.
-Boss Luo, wait. There are other styles in our store...
-Fei Fei.
Don't stop them from leaving.
Boss Jiang. Apologies, we are taking our leave.
Dear everyone. I won't be seeing you off. Take care.
This way, please.
Take care, everyone.
The colours are nice here.
Brother Shao Tian, the dye orders today compared to the original are bigger.
We are working overtime to rush out the orders.
Jiang Yu's face must be black.
Brother.
Miss. We have another client. I heard that they came over from Ling Long.
Their prices are too expensive. Thus, they came here.
Let's go.
Let's go out and take a look.
Since Zhou Shao Tian joined together with the business federation,
they lowered their prices. We lost quite a number of clients to them.
They abandoned orders which are filled up in our warehouse.
- What should we do, Brother?
- Don't worry.
Everything will come to light soon.
Don't bother about the issue regarding Fu Sheng.
They are at an advantage now.
Isn't there someone?
What someone?
Send men over there to tell their staff that we will offer them a high salary.
We are still increasing our staff. We are already having problems selling our products.
I get it. As long as we can lure their staff here
they won't have anyone to produce their goods.
Brother, great move.
If Zhou Shao Tian wants to save Fu Sheng,
he will need a big sum of cash.
I understand now. I will get this done immediately.
Okay.
-Grab your Rose Candy.
- Thank you.
Rose Candy.
Hold this carefully.
-I'll have Rose...
Rose Candy please.
Okay. Are you together?
We are not together. Split the purchases.
Take care.
My mom has already been discharged from the hospital.
If you want to see her, I can take you there.
Please hand this to Madam Jiang.
You haven't come to your senses yet?
I should be the one saying this.
You always saw Fu Sheng's capability.
So what? Are you afraid?
You will see the true face of that person next to you in Fu Sheng soon.
I already see it very clearly.
You appear as a Yiguanqinshou.
immoral person
A peer pressure to dominate the market
You even used disgusting tactics to frame my sister.
What is this? There are so many words here. What does it say?
It's a recruitment notice. What is it for?
What is written there?
- What's wrong?
- It's a recruitment notice.
Because of vacancies, there are several openings, especially for Journeymen,
Monthly payment of salaries. Between the two companies, the pay is higher. There are bonuses.
The conditions aren't bad!
They're just saying that.
How could it be? Ling Long is a big company!
If they said it, it must be true!
Then what are we still doing here? Let's go work at Ling Long!
- Let's go.
- But Boss Zhou treats us pretty well.
Money is more important. We'll be satisfied once we have it in our hands.
Regarding this, both of the companies are doing the same thing.
I say that we should go to whichever one pays higher and has better conditions.
Yes, exactly. Are you coming or not?
Let's go!
Wait for me! I'm here to sign up.
I'm here to register!
Line up!
Where are the others?
They all went to Ling Long.
I couldn't stop them.
I'm sorry, owner.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Jiang Yu, you despicable person! To use such means to get rid of all our business!
Let go.
Don't worry, let him go.
All I did was mention a higher salary.
As long as you offer a higher salary, all your workers will come back to you.
If you're capable, then do it. Doing it like this doesn't prove anything!
In business, strength is one thing, strategy is another.
If you have the courage to open a shop, you have the courage to lose.
I won't lose to you.
I also don't want you to give up so soon.
It'll be resolved once you show the money.
What money?
Let me remind you,
the Ling Long that I acquired was just a shell.
The money on the ledgers disappeared.
Where could such a large sum of money have gone?
Think carefully about how you're going to keep Fu Sheng.
Please go carefully.
Hello, who are you looking for?
Boss, Fu Sheng's owner has already
been waiting for you for a long time.
He hasn't left yet?
Boss, there's a call for you.
I know, it's okay.
Hello?
Boss Jiang, hello!
What do you need, just tell me!
You want to deposit some money? Of course!
That's great, thank you so much!
Don't disturb your workers, I'll go there personally to collect it.
What?
Zhou Shao Tian?
He's not a big client of mine.
I already knew that he couldn't do business, so I shouldn't have lent him money!
I'm making many mistakes.
Okay, wait for me.
I'm coming right now.
Boss Qian!
Boss Qian, I had something to discuss with you.
Boss Zhou, I have to leave for some business.
It's like this, can you lend me some more money so I can turn around my situation?
As long as it turns my situation around, I will definitely pay you back with interest.
I can lend you money, but what can you pawn?
It's true that I don't have anything to pawn right now.
However, you know my skills and personality.
In the future, I will invest all of Fu Sheng's earnings here.
Boss Zhou, look here. I'm also a businessman.
You didn't even return all the money you borrowed last time, how do you expect me to lend you more?
Also, who doesn't know about Fu Sheng's current situation?
Boss Qian, help me one last time. Give me one last chance.
I have urgent needs to attend to.
How about this, Boss Zhou.
Let's have a cigarette.
Take Boss Zhou to talk in the back.
- Hurry up!
- Okay, okay.
Let's go. Boss Zhou, welcome.
Get out!
Boss Qian, what's the meaning of this?
The meaning?
Zhou Shao Tian.
If you stand there not moving, how am I supposed to continue my business?
Let me tell you,
people are from different classes.
A pheasant will never become a phoenix.
You are not fit to be a businessman.
There's no way I'm lending you money.
Let me also remind you that you have to return the money that you borrowed,
or else
don't blame me for not being polite.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Stop! You can't go in.
I'm looking for your boss, Jiang Yu.
Please move aside.
These are the factory's newest dyes, look over it.
Okay.
I have something important to discuss with him.
- Miss!
- Move aside!
Miss!
Wu Cai Hong, why did you come?
Fei Fei.
You can go outside.
Jiang Yu.
Fu Sheng is a very small shop. There's no way it can compare with Ling Long.
Why are you so bitter? Why do you have to make it hard for him?
Every time you appear, it's to argue with me.
Before, I did treat you like this. I did a lot of things that made you angry.
But you can't direct your anger towards Shao Tian. He's him and I'm me.
Jiang Yu, I'm begging you.
Can you let Fu Sheng go?
This is the first time you begged me for Zhou Shao Tian.
Does Zhou Shao Tian support you
coming to beg me?
Then what do you want?
Sorry.
I will definitely force Fu Sheng out of business.
Why can't you let Fu Sheng go?
Let Brother Shao Tian go?
In your eyes, I'm cold-blooded.
So I can only resort to the facts in order for you to see the truth.
I will only accept what I see right now.
I can see clearly what kind of person you really are.
Then we don't have anything more to discuss.
What can I do so that you will let Fu Sheng go?
And let Brother Shao Tian go?
I am not an immoral person.
However I am not lenient and won't show mercy.
You will get your retribution.
Did you hear?
Zhou Shao Tian is asking for a loan for more money.
This is a way for them to feed their families.
Is Zhou Shao Tian going to force us to death?
Yes. He's going to force us to death.
Who will lend him the money now? If he doesn't get a loan, our money will be in hot soup.
That's right.
Aren't there goods in his shop now?
Take his goods as collateral. It's better than nothing.
Yes. Let's take his goods as collateral.
Let's go.
Let's go in. Take these away.
Take them away.
Put down my goods.
Put them down.
The deadline is not due yet.
Confiscate them.
You are stealing my goods.
- Sis, what are you doing?
- Nothing.
Brother Shao Tian. I was just about to look for you.
Will this help you?
No need.
I don't mind. It's only this.
Brother Shao Tian, take this. This is my mom's personal...
You are giving out your mother's funeral money.
- What are you trying to do?
- Stop hitting her.
I will remember what you have done.
But for the rich, they are utterly inadequate.
Thank you, everyone.
Who is it that failed to give you light direction?
Why don't you let Cai Yun buy French perfumes instead?
Mom.
Kneel down.
Zhou Shao Tian, return our money immediately.
If not, it won't be that simple next time.
Let's go.
Brother. I have been thinking about this for the past two days.
What do you know?
So what if you have lost once? This is all crap.
You are just going to give it up like that?
Let's start anew.
Brother.
I'm not good with words.
Brother, you really have the talent.
I believe that you can make a comeback.
Cheers.
Trust me, Ah Li.
I will definitely make a comeback.
I believe you, Brother.
My great worry now is that when I don't have any money,
it's frustrating.
When I have money,
it's even more so.
Money?
Brother, you are saying that there is no way to gain power.
It's not power.
It's money.
Is there something like this in the world?
You have money and you can't spend it.
This is impossible.
Yes.
This is the situation.
Brother. You really know how to joke. I know that in this world, there are things that money can't buy.
-The perfect color is not created with money.
-Be quiet.
If you have money and you don't spend it, it will force one to die.
If you want to spend the money, you will cause someone to die.
What do you mean?
All I know is that one can not live without money. On the other hand,
this person will suffocate by money.
I also want to walk away
but in my heart, I can't let this go.
Brother, how much is something worth
when it begins to be taken away.
Brother, where are you going?
Brother, be careful.
Brother Shao Tian. You have drank too much.
This is bad for your health.
I'm fine. I've only been drunk a few times in my lifetime.
I like that you are finding it hard to accept
but when a person is facing hardship, you must bring your spirit up.
Don't you think so?
Don't worry. I won't do this again.
By the way, I went to visit a few of my father's friends...
- Hence...
- Cai Hong,
I have already thought it through.
I will take you away from Huzhou. Let's move far away.
What about Fu Sheng then?
Anywhere where you are at, Fu Sheng will be there.
Fu Sheng is not important. You are important.
But we still owe a lot of debts.
We will pay them back gradually.
However much profits we made, we will pay them back.
Is this okay?
Let's go to Tianjin. No one knows us there. We can start anew.
But I haven't taken revenge for Ling Long and my father yet.
We can't leave at a time like this.
Cai Hong. The situation now
is that Jiang Yu has forced us into at tight corner.
If this continues, our business will really go down.
Why don't we find a hideaway first
and wait for this to die down before we come back for revenge?
Brother Shao Tian.
Your decision is too sudden.
Let me think about it again.
Brother.
Zhou Shao left today.
Has he started his move?
No. But the situation is already like this,
he still haven't got the cash for Fu Sheng.
He quite tolerant about it
Brother. Perhaps, you have guessed wrongly.
Maybe it wasn't Zhou Shao Tian who teamed up with Lao Cai to empty Ling Long.
If it wasn't him, who else would it be?
Brother. I'm a bit suspicious now.
If you go against Zhou Shao Tian this way,
you will need an elixir.
What do you mean?
You don't understand what I mean?
I really hope that you don't understand what I'm saying.
Brother, don't be sad. Where there is life there is hope.
I would like to add fire to the flame. I know the boss would not give me this opportunity again.
Miss Lu. Are you making a joke out of this?
It's common for soldiers to fail. Mr Zhou, it's you who are taking this too hard.
When you fall, you can still get up and start anew again.
Look at the state I am in now.
I don't have any money left.
I am making a point
and thinking of a way to reverse this.
I can help you.
Really? That's great.
Miss Lu hasn't finished talking yet.
Yes.
Boss Zhou knows me very well.
What can I do for Miss Lu then?
The secret formula.
What secret formula?
The secret formula of Wu Hong Da.
I don't have the secret formula.
I don't know what the secret formula is. It doesn't concern Ling Long.
Fu Sheng started a business for only a few days and it was brought down by Ling Long.
Are you really going to swallow this?
That's right, Brother.
Let's do this, Boss Zhou. Think about this
but don't let me wait for too long.
A woman doesn't like to be kept waiting.
I won't be seeing you off.
Brother. Why didn't you take up her offer? It's a great opportunity.
I really don't have the secret formula.
Yesterday stepmother did tofu. She especially liked it.
This child of mine doesn't like to eat greasy and oily food.
She doesn't like to eat fish. She said that they have a fishy smell.
That's right. We still have half a fish left from yesterday.
Go and buy some vegetables.
Remember to bargain with them.
Stepmom, don't worry. Deliver the food to Cai Yun now.
Candied fruits on sticks.
What are you going? What's going on?
- Don't you look where you are going? This dress is very expensive.
- Sorry, I didn't do it on purpose.
- It's so dirty.
- Let me wipe it off for you.
She is from a dye factory. Her husband committed suicide by jumping down. Look at her, she's still wearing such bright and floral clothes.
- Seriously.
- Stop wiping, it's so dirty.
Stop wiping. Don't touch me. Go away.
What are you doing? Why are you bullying him?
Who says I'm bullying him? Look at my dress. It's very expensive.
So what if it's dirty? Just go back and wash it. Why are you creating a ruckus here?
Seriously.
She broke my eggs. Compensate me for these.
- Compensate me for the eggs.
- Why should I pay for them?
She pushed me and made me fell.
Look at my dress.
The eggs have broken shells.
- Do you know how expensive it is?
- Don't leave. You must pay for it.
- Stepmom.
- What are you doing?
- She broke my eggs.
-How much are they?
- Take a look. Pay for them.
Just this sum of money? It's not enough. Look at the amount of eggs.
In any case, it's not enough.
This should be enough, right?
Consider that I'm unlucky.
Seriously. Why did you pay her?
Stepmom, don't be angry.
What are you looking at? Go away.
Leave now.
Let's go.
I will deliver this to Cai Yun.
Go back home and wash up now.
I'm so unlucky
to encounter such an unlucky incident.
I'm leaving first.
- Wu Cai Yun. You are a thief.
- I'm not a thief.
What are you still doing here? We don't welcome thieves here.
- I didn't steal.
- What are you doing? Stop it.
-She stole and has a criminal record.
-That was an injustice.
Ah Xue, say something.
- What right do you have to say that she is at thief?
- Wu Cai Yun is the poorest student in the class.
Isn't it common for her to steal?
How could you just simply say this? I'm going to sue you for defamation.
You are going to sue me for defamation? My mom also heard that Wu Cai Hong stole something.
She has even planned to petition the students to kick her out of school.
My mom said that she doesn't want me to be in the same school as a thief.
You have gone overboard.
- Cai Yun.
- We should have kicked her out a long time ago.
That's right. Let's kick her out.
Cai Yun.
Wait for me. Just ignore them.
Sis, Why was I framed?
Why am I being misunderstood by them?
Why must I live such a life?
I don't want to study anymore.
What's the status of the task?
Don't worry about Zhou Shao Tian.
I'm keeping a close watch on him.
But Miss Wu has been asking for help from her father's business friends for the past two days.
That Miss Wu, this kid is really not bad
I heard that she's swearing on her dad's reputation.
Do it as soon as possible. Close it.
Okay. I will acquire Fu Sheng tomorrow.
Boss Jiang.
Okay, let's do this. I still have some matters to attend to.
Okay.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Now the only thing left is to hand him over.
Why did you come here?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Jiang Yu. You are here every day.
Don't you feel my father's soul has been following you?
What are you trying to say?
What I'm trying to say?
You forced Brother Shao Tian into a dead end and caused my sister to be unable to continue her studies.
What else are you still thinking of?
Let me tell you.
You harbour grudges about my family. You will never change.
I never planned to be the saviour of the Wu family.
Even if Wu Hong Da didn't pass away, I would still have acquired Ling Long.
Why should I bother. Give yourself the trouble of it.
Devil's words.
There will come a day when you will regret everything that you have said today.
What I regret is meeting such an evil man like you.
You should go back and keep calm first before you talk again.
I'm very calm now.
Don't be full of yourself.
Look, it's such a beautiful day but you can't appreciate it.
It's because people like you have a dark heart.
Even now if you have an exquisite life, you are not kind.
I don't want to see you again.
I'm not going. I don't want to go to Tianjin.
It's so far away. I like living here.
Stepmom. It's a dead end for us here.
When you go there, you can start anew.
No one is forcing you. You are only forcing yourselves.
You didn't stay at the great Ling Long. You quit such a great job. You didn't choose the great Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu acquired Ling Long and now, Fu Sheng has been brought down by him.
If we continue to stay here, we might be his next target.
Why would he target us?
Fine. Even if Ling Long was acquired by him,
that's business. Kiddo, what do you know?
The words you've spoken, aren't you afraid that dad would be disappointed?
I heard that it's winter six months of the year in Tianjin.
I'm afraid of the cold. Moreover,
I won't be able to drink longjing tea
or eat Rose flower candy.
I don't understand the way the people talk that too. How could I live there?
Mom. I believe that Brother Shao Tian will let us live well there.
What do you mean? When he started Fu Sheng, he said that he would make the business expand.
(Where are) The results?
The situation we're in was caused by Jiang Yu.
Don't tell me you still want to be laughing stock here?
Cai Yun's schoolmates look down on her. Since this is the case, why don't we start anew there?
That's right, Mom. Just agree.
Give me a few days
to prepare.
To buy longjing tea and Rose flower candy.
Stepmom. I will get all these for you.
Once I have gotten them, we will set off tomorrow.
That fast?
Heavens, I have so much clothes. Let me go and pack first.
It's okay. She will pack for you.
Mom.
Shao Tian, you are back.
Pack your stuff and get ready to leave.
- What's wrong?
- We are going to Tianjin tomorrow.
- We won't return again.
- What happened that we must relocate?
- Did you...
- It's Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu?
Jiang Yu forced me into a dead end.
I have no choice except to leave.
Is Jiang Yu that bad?
He is not bad? Is it me then?
I don't mean that. I'm just saying if it was an misunderstanding.
- Shao Tian. Even though you didn't tell me about Fu Sheng...
- Fu Sheng doesn't concern you.
Does Jiang Yu have anything to do with it?
I don't want to talk about this. Pack up.
Big Brother.
This way.
It's her, Miss Wu.
I heard that you want to borrow money from me.
Yes.
Do you know what this place is?
- You know and you still dare to come here?
- I will definitely return the loan.
- Let me tell you.
My interest is very high.
Your Wu family has gone bankrupt and Fu Sheng is also in dire straits.
How do you plan to return my loan?
I will definitely pay back the loan.
You need collateral to take a loan.
What do you plan to use as the collateral?
I will use myself as the collateral.
You are a smart person. When you take my loan and can't return it when it's due,
don't blame me for not being polite to you.
Since I'm already here, I won't have any regrets.
Whether you lend or not, you should give it to one's heart's content.
Happy.
You do realize what you would be giving up.
Your sister and you are renowned beauties in Huzhou.
If you can't return the loan,
I may sell you to the brothels.
Did you think it over carefully?
Are you going to take the loan or not?
I will take the loan.
Fine.
Wait here.