The Cage of Love
Episode 21
If Wu Hong Da is dead,
the hidden place for the secret formula will be gone.
In addiction to your workshop, as well as equipment,
is there something like...erm...
a secret formula?
That's right.
On the morning of Old Master's incident, I saw him take out a piece of paper from his safe and keep it with him.
I think it was that secret formula.
If I were Master Jiang, I would definitely find Wu Hong Da for the secret formula
but I'm afraid Wu Hong Da won't give it to him that easily.
Wu Hong Da is dead.
The secret formula may have been lost.
Brother Shao Tian. I have decided to work at Rong Da.
But I want to find the secret formula too and the proof that Jiang Yu is the killer.
Just like what you said,
if Jiang Yu did it,
I will leave it to the police to take care of it.
But if it's not him,
I will sever all ties with him.
Fine.
I will definitely help you.
Headline!
Cao Kun was elected the fifth president of the Republic of China.
There will be an extravagant celebration showing off the best made silk fabrics.
Headline!
Kiddo, give me one.
Here.
Mr. Zhang, on behalf of the president, we welcome you to our office.
Your first stop was at Ling Long. We are very grateful.
Now that the president has taken office,
he is in need of a lot of silk.
I heard that the silk at Huzhou is second to none.
Your Ling Long also has a hundred year old history in Huzhou.
Hence, I came here especially to visit you.
It's just that I didn't know there was a change of ownership.
The owner may have changed but the product is still superior.
Is that so?
Looking at how confident you are, I can be reassured.
But...
President Cao is not an ordinary person.
Don't worry. Our products are not ordinary products.
Mr Zhang. Let me show you around the factory.
Okay.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Hello, General Manager Zhou.
Cai Hong. Why are you making yourself suffer? I didn't let you come here to do such tasks.
I just knew you would be like this.
Give me some time.
I will get back everything for you here.
We will live happily just like in the past.
Previously I watched casually.
It was my father who created this palace success.
I did not know he would one day collapse.
But now, I can use my own hands
to work honestly.
This is also another kind of happiness.
It has been hard on you.
By the way,
since the President has come into office, he has come to Huzhou to buy silk.
Of course, everyone is talking about this.
I heard that he has gone to Ling Long. I was thinking, should't Rong Da compete with him?
Of course, we should.
Furthermore, I think this is the best opportunity for Jiang Yu to use his secret formula.
What has this to do with Mr Zhang?
- A silk contest.
- What?
Let's have a silk contest.
Silk contest?
For the presidential celebration let's hold a silk competition
to choose the best silk in Huzhou.
You and I know the implication of the silk contest.
The party who loses will have to withdraw from the dyeing industry in Huzhou.
We can use this as contest. As long as Jiang Yu is willing to take part,
he will have to use his secret formula.
As long as he uses the secret formula,
he won't be able to disassociate himself from my father's death.
But this is just my own views.
I can't let Rong Da take on such a big risk.
If we lose, we will have to withdraw from this industry in Huzhou.
My Rong Da is also your Rong Da. Miss Lu has given me free rein.
After all, Rong Da is exquisite and has potential. Ling Long will have to leave the community. It'll be one less rival.
I can tell that you are determined to get the proof of your father's killer.
I'm very happy that you are willing to trust me.
I would also like to help you find the evidence that I didn't misjudge Jiang Yu.
- But what if Rong Da loses...
- There are not buts.
Cai Hong. You should know very well how my skills are. I won't lose to Ling Long.
We can force the secret formula out from Jiang Yu.
Okay. Even if we bring up the silk contest,
Jiang Yu is such a sly person. He won't take the bait so easily.
Unless Miss Lu is willing to help us fully.
Let's go and see her now.
Silk contest?
This is a good idea.
I also wanted to know who is better. Rong Da or Ling Long.
But the risk is extremely high.
The loser will have to withdraw from the industry in Huzhou.
Even more so, I don't want to drag Rong Da down because of this.
This is not a problem. It's more important to find the killer of your father.
Don't worry. I will definitely help you with this.
To add further, don't you trust Mr Zhou?
Miss Lu, I would like to thank you first.
Don't thank me. I didn't really help you much.
By agreeing to the silk contest, you have already helped me a lot.
Brother Shao Tian. I will go back first and notify the reporters
and tell them to go to Ling Long.
Thank you for just now.
What is there to thank me for? Stop pretending to be clueless.
Rong Da is not my company, it's yours.
As for me, I'm only just acting along with you.
I'm thanking you for playing along with me.
Frankly, there is something I don't understand.
Tell me.
With your talent, you can work anywhere where people are considered top.
What is the secret charm of Miss Wu?
Unless you'd rather be King Zhou in a war drama saving your princess.
It's not that complicated. Cai Hong only wants to find out her father's killer.
I'm only doing my best to help her.
As long as I can fulfill her wish,
I will be satisfied.
Zhou Shao Tian is clearly an amazing person.
Actually, he's a major fool.
As long as I use his weakness for Wu Cai Hong, I will be able to control him.
Yet would a woman want such a fool like him?
What a pity that not everyone is just Wu Cai Hong.
Be careful.
You said you are a very shrewd woman, yet you seem to be envious of others.
My shrewdness was forced, so I have no choice but to be shrewd.
But if there is someone to rely on, which woman wouldn't want to be a princess
and be protected?
Not bad. Ling's Long's silk is beyond comparison.
With this, the President will be satisfied.
I think I don't need to visit the other companies.
Congratulations, Mr Jiang.
The people of the President will take an extreme fancy to your product. You have really good luck.
At the same time, it's also great advertisement for Ling Long.
What you said is extremely right.
I am also extremaly grateful to you, Mr Zhang, for giving us this opportunity.
Let's do this.
If you are not in a rush, why don't you stay a few more days in Huzhou and let me show you around.
Fine.
Welcome Mr Zhang to Huzhou.
Mr Zhang, please look over here.
I heard that President Hang came to our area to buy silk,
but you only visited Ling Long.
It seems like there is only one dyeing factory in Huzhou and that is Ling Long.
I say, Governor Liu,
by making this arrangement, you are making the other dyeing factory envious and not be of service.
It's like this. I brought Mr Zhang to Ling Long dyeing factory
because Ling Long is our long standing dyeing factory.
I didn't intentionally want to be biased.
How may I address you?
Let me do the introductions. This is Miss Lu Man, the boss of Rong Da.
She is also a good friend of the Military Governor.
Miss Lu.
Nice to meet you.
Let me do the introductions too.
She is the daughter of Huzhou's biggest dyeing factory, Boss Wu Hong Da,
Wu Cai Hong.
So this is Miss Wu. I still remember your father was very famous in the capital.
It's such a pity.
Miss Wu. Shouldn't you be working at Ling Long?
I'm working with Miss Lu now.
Rong Da?
Yes. Zhou Shao Tian is our General Manager at Rong Da. He was also my father's most capable man.
Moreover, our goods are very cheap.
Mr Zhang. Why didn't you consider us too?
What are you trying to do? You even come here to steal our business.
Isn't this too much?
Fei Fei.
Dear reporter friends, Mr Zhang's came to buy the finest silk in our area.
It's a blessing to Huzhou.
Our company also wants to participate in this event.
Is there anything wrong in this?
There is nothing wrong.
Mr Zhang, since you have come here to buy the finest silk,
the procurement of goods should be preferential.
Don't you think I'm right?
It's logical.
Ling Long is the biggest dyeing factory in Huzhou and it has also been established for a hundred years.
Our Rong Da might be just a beginner, but I do not want to lose such a good opportunity to offer the President our goods as well.
Thus, I would like to invite the reporters to be our witness.
We want to compete openly and fairly with Ling Long.
Compete opening and fairly with Ling Long?
What should we compete in?
Silk contest.
The seniors in Huzhou know that any dyeing factory
can compete with each other.
The losing party will lose the business
and withdraw from the industry.
But I wonder if the other party is willing.
Do you really want to use this method?
If we don't use this method, how would we know
how could we know who has the best silk in Huzhou?
Fine. In front of all the reporters now,
I challenge Ling Long to a contest. If Rong Da loses,
we will withdraw forever from the Huzhou dyeing industry.
Mr Jiang. Do you dare to accept our challenge?
Miss Lu is a true heroine.
Ling Long will accept the challenge.
Okay. If Ling Long wouldn't show this courage,
how could it maintain its old name and fame, huh?
Silk contest? I have heard of it but have never seen it.
- Are you okay?
- We have never seen or heard of this.
This is something we haven't seen for a long time.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Brother. Wu Cai Hong has gone overboard.
She chose to go against us.
Brother. Why did you accept Rong Da's challenge for a silk contest that easily?
They definately have bad intentions.
I know.
They are using this to go against Ling Long.
Lu Man is an outsider. How could she possibly know about the silk contest?
Wu Cai Hong must be behind this.
And that Zhou Shao Tian, what the devil is he up to?
He even got the reporters there to stir the fire and gave us no chance to back out.
Enough. I already know this.
Are you okay?
What could happen to me?
Brother. You are not cold towards Wu Cai Hong.
She is going against you by doing this. I'm afraid that you won't come to your senses and would feel hurt.
Why would I think of that?
Ever since her father caused the death of my father,
we have both decided to be mere acquaintances.
It's good that you think this way.
Brother. You must win the silk contest.
Miss Lu said that if you lose, you will withdraw from Huzhou.
She is just an outsider. If she loses, she loses
and can just leave but we can't lose.
The brand of Ling Long is due to father's blood, sweat and tears.
I have my own solution.
Enough, go back to work.
I would like to be alone.
Okay, I'm going out first.
Jiang Yu. Why did you do this?
Why did you do this?
Why did you kill my father?
Why? It's fine if you take revenge on me
but why did you do that?
I hate you. Return my father to me.
Return my father to me.
Jiang Yu, I hate you!
Miss Lu is great.
You forced Jiang Yu into a corner
and obediently agreed to accept our silk contest.
I have already set the stage for you.
How we force him to use his secret formula will depend on you.
I have only one motive. Get the secret formula for me.
I will do my best.
I never imagined that Wu Cai Hong could think of such a cruel tactic
to let him take out the secret formula and leave the industry.
Beautiful.
But our security pledge is too big.
We have pledged everything.
Do I help you with this before the contest?
Thanks.
I was fifteen years old when I joined Ling Long. Just like then, I followed my teachers
and learned how to dye. If I didn't even have confidence in this,
Wu Hong Da wouldn't have kept me by his side as his right hand man.
Don't worry. I will use the fairest methods
to force Jiang Yu to take out his secret formula and lose badly.
Fine. Even though I didn't personally fund Rong Da
but since I have shares in it, even if we can't get the secret formula, we can't lose.
If we won't be able to quadruple our profit,
my own name will be on stake.
Don't you live up to the trust I have in you?
But of course.
It can't be that your father shouldn't die?
He did so many unethical things.
Even death is too good for such person.
What do you want now?
I know that you don't want to see me here.
I didn't want to come here either.
I only wanted to tell you to come to discuss the rules for the contest at Drunken Fairy restaurant tomorrow.
There are so many people at Rong Da. Why did they send you instead?
I already said what I needed to say.
You forced Ling Long and Rong Da into a situation which we both can't back out from.
Do you think I don't know what you are trying to do?
I'm going to kick you out of Huzhou.
Twelve years ago, your father kicked us out of Huzhou.
This time,
don't even dream about it.
Brother Shao Tian. I would like discuss the rules for the contest with Ling Ling tomorrow.
What's wrong, Cai Hong? Did something happen?
Why do you look so bad today?
It's nothing.
I only just want to find my father's killer as soon as possible.
Don't worry. I will do the preparations immediately.
Headline. Rong Da competes with Ling Long.
- Headline.
- Give me one.
Headline. Rong Da competes with Ling Long.
Wait.
You want a newspaper too?
Give me one too.
Here.
I can't read. Could you read it to me?
Look. Ling Long is going to compete with Rong Da in a silk contest.
The rule is that the loser will withdraw from the dyeing industry.
Madam. Go back and read it slowly.
Headline!
Everyone is talking in the street that you and Ling Long are having a silk contest. What is going on?
This doesn't seem to concern you.
Miss Wu is already back.
Why do you still want to pressure Jiang Yu
especially when the Jiang family was our saviour?
Old Master Jiang helped us. It was his business.
Jiang Yu stepped over our heads everywhere. I was even framed for murder.
I need to prove my innocence.
I know that you are innocent. You don't need to prove anything.
I'm doing this to prove my innocence to Cai Hong.
Mom, take your medicine.
Why haven't I seen Cai Hong for the past few days?
Where did she go?
Did something happen to her family?
She and her friend started a factory recently.
Now that she has money, I sold her contract.
So to say, she's going to marry someone?
She won't be back anymore?
She won't be back again.
Cai Hong, seriously.
She left without telling me first.
It's such a pity.
Frankly, I have an affinity to her.
If you don't find it funny,
I wanted to marry her off to you.
Everyone must have already heard.
The silk contest is in three days.
This is an opportunity.
We must use our best flowers to create the best silk
We must show off Rong Da's great product.
But don't worry. We will redouble your wages for your hard work.
All right?
The dyes are here.
Your hands are stained.
I'm going to wash them now.
Pull it up.
So beautiful.
That's great.
Brother, are you tired? Let me wipe off your sweat.
No need.
Hold this properly.
- How could you suddenly change?
- My bet is on Rong Da.
- Rong Da!
- Ling Long!
My bet is on Ling Long.
Come.
It's a rare sight.
Okay, thanks.
It has been a long time since we saw such a major silk contest.
So many people! Were it not for the President wanting to buy silk, we would not have such treat.
Hurry up.
Let me through.
The bet is not small. Rong Da.
I want to bet on Rong Da. Rong Da looks good. Although I have not won at the auction before,
I won't be wrong this time.
Come. Do you have any money?
My bet is for ten dollars.
I'm betting on this. Thanks.
Bet on Rong Da.
Second Miss. Madam Wu.
Madam Wu.
You also...
Madam Wu. You look extremely good today.
Is that so? How about Shao Tian today?
He is also extremely good.
That's great too. I bet with quite a big sum.
Mom. Do you only know about money
and others?
Second Miss is right.
What did you say? My daughter and I are talking. How dare you butt in?
Tell me where to go now.
When you go through the door, it's on the right...
What did you say? How could we hear you if you cover your mouth?
Where is it?
Once you enter the door, keep walking to the right
and you will see the stage. Next to it is Rong Da's seat.
You can just sit over there.
Where is it? Take us there.
I can't do that. I'm waiting for Miss Lu Man. She will be here soon.
Okay, let's go then.
Madam Wu, take care.
Brother Ma Li, see you later.
Brother Ma Li?
See you later.
What are you looking at? Where are the entrance tickets?
Why were you smiling at that idiot?
- I find him interesting.
- He is an idiot.
- He is not.
- He keeps looking at you.
He must have bad thoughts in his mind. I have seen enough of such men.
- Understand?
- Ma Li is not that kind of person.
Have you seen many people?
Because of you I had to walk even further.
Which side is it?
We came in from that way.
Where did we exactly come in from?
Ma Li seems to have said that it's on the right.
- Seriously, you.
- I'm right.
You can't even tell the difference from left and right.
You dragged me to the wrong place. If I didn't call you, you would have brought me to the wrong place.
Isn't it over there?
You were the one who dragged me along.
It's clearly you who were the one who dragged me instead.
Enough, let's sit over there.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
You two. Are there any problems with cloth appliances?
- No problem.
Fine. Since this is the case, please take a rest in the rooms next door first.
We will call you out later.
It's such a big event. Did they need to do this?
Did you buy it?
- Yes.
- Show it to me.
- It's $50 on Ling Long.
- Okay, leave.
Governor.
You bought it too?
Yes. So what if I bought it?
Don't tell me that you didn't buy it?
I wanted to but I'm keeping guard on this. How could I go out?
Governor. Please get someone to watch this. I will be back soon.
You, seriously.
We have already checked the items here and you want someone else to keep watch over them?
Bet less.
If you bet too much, you will lose a lot.
What will you do if your wife runs off with someone else?
You must keep guard over these items carefully.
Yes.
Bet less?
For the past nineteen years, I haven't even gambled once.
I must bet on this.
Victory to Rong Da!
Governor Liu.
Madam Wu. You are here too?
- And Miss Wu too?
- Hello, Governor Liu.
Madam Wu. You are really blessed. Your second daughter is tall and pretty.
These youngsters still need a lot of guidance from you.
Who says so?
By the way, where are Cai Hong and Shao Tian?
They are at the room behind. When the contest starts, I will call them out.
It has been hard on you.
Madam Wu. Sorry, I need to take my leave.
Governor Liu is a good man. He is very upright.
- How do you know?
- Of course, I do.
I played mahjong with him. He is a nice man.
- Stepmom, Cai Yun.
- Sister.
Cai Hong. Why did you come out? What are your preparations?
We are almost done.
Warlord Lu, President Zhang, thank you for coming.
Please pardon me.
Miss Lu, you worked had.
It has been hard on you.
Governor Liu is known for his heartwarming speeches at General Assembly.
Guilty as charged, isn't it?
I'm here for the fun of it.
Yes. To be able to have such competition,
is really an eye-opener.
By the way, Governor Liu,
do you mind if I watch this?
How could I have any objections. It's my honour to have you both here.
- Warlord Lu, please.
- No need.
I will only stay a while.
Mr Zhang, please make yourself at home.
I will, it's Governor Liu to you.
Yes. Mr Zhang, this way, please.
Look. There are already many people ahead. This way, please.
After you.
This rascal, Zhou Shao Tian, has already given you a lot of trouble.
What is he doing with this silk contest?
General Du, don't you know about this?
The silk contest is to force Jiang Yu to take out his secret formula.
As long as the secret formula shows up, it proves that Jiang Yu killed Wu Hong Da.
When that time comes, wouldn't the secret formula belong to us?
You can do this
but you also put me into the spotlight.
If there are any troubles, I will not let you of the hook.
General Du, how could you say this?
I have been with you for a long time.
Have I ever let you down?
That's good then.
The President is responsible before the Hong people.
He even received personal orders to get the silk from here.
I also hope that Rong Da will get this business.
Don't worry. I will definitely do my best.
Welcome everyone to the silk competition.
We are very honoured that
Warlord Lu, as well as President Zhang graced us with their presence.
We are very thankful.
Great.
The silk competition is the biggest event in Huzhou's weaving and dyeing industry.
Even though silk is a so-called light good,
the event cannot be taken lightly.
I, Governor Liu, am very honoured to be the host of the silk contest again.
The last silk contest was sixteen years ago.
At every silk contest, there will always be a losing competitor who has to leave the industry.
Sixteen years ago, Ling Long factory was the one who remained.
Sixteen years later, the one who was challenged to the contest
was the Ling Long factory.
Let's invite the contestant from Ling Long, Boss Jiang Yu
to the stage.
Great.
Ling Long!
Victory for Ling Long.
Today, the owner of the exquisite Lin Long factory is challenging
Rong Da factory. Their contestant is
their General Manager who is also someone we are familiar with in the industry.
Mr Zhou Shao Tian.
Great.
Victory to Rong Da.
Go, Rong Da!
Great.
Both Lin Long and Rong Da are the pride of our district.
I hope that both of you, as well as our audience will behave gracefully.
This silk contest will take place in three parts.
This Sunday we will have the first round.
Both parties need to, before the incense stick burns out,
produce a textile that is second to none.
The time is the time it takes the incense stick to burn.
When it ends, everyone here will vote.
The one who receives the most votes is the winner.
Everyone, when you entered the door, you were given a lily. It's for you to use as votes.
Great.
Okay, I will now announce
the start of the silk contest.
Brother.
What are you doing? Why are you doing anything?
Everything's fine. Go back.