Episode 7
Did you see this? Just do  accordingly to the instructions.
I get it.
Boss. Take a look. This is our new product.
It is easier to dye with color.
It simplifies the dying process.
Right. Take it to the workshop to test the dying process.
Okay.
Why do you keep staring at me?
Did you force Old Cai's family to move?
In your heart, you are already sure that
I was behind this.
Furthermore, you are very clear that no matter how you ask,
I won't admit to it.
Don't tell me you don't want to explain this?
What is there to explain?
You will find out the truth sooner or later.
You don't need to accompany me today. Go to the rickshaw.
Take record of the newly dyed fabrics.
I'm returning these clothes to you. I have already washed them.
If you are going to complain, you can throw them away.
Fei Fei.
You are looking for me?
Brother. Ah Fa came just now.
She said the mistress of the house is looking for accommodations.
- Put these away for me.
- Where are you going?
To speak to Lao Cai's mistress.
I'm going with you.
Don't go. I'm not going there for fun.
Wait for my news.
Come, let's go.
Come with me to a place.
Jiang Yu. If you don't tell me anything, I'm not getting in the rickshaw with you.
There is no time. I will explain to you.
- Quick, get in the rickshaw now.
- I don't want to listen to your explanation.
If you want to find Old Cai, get in the now.
He doesn't allow me to go but he pulled Wu Cai Hong along.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
- Hello, Mr Zhou.
- Did you see Cai Hong?
Cai Hong? Boss Jiang just took her away.
It seems to be something urgent.
You can leave.
Where did Cai Hong go?
It seems like she got into Boss Jiang's rickshaw.
Do you know where they went?
I don't know anything about this.
Do you know where Jiang Yu and Cai Hong went?
I know. But why should I tell you?
Because you are just like me.
You don't want to see them together, right?
Is anyone there?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
We are a step behind again.
You killed her just to prove your innocence.
What are you saying?
I was at Ling Long the whole day. Everyone, including you,
can be be my alibis. How could I have killed her?
If you wanted to kill anyone, you don't need to do this yourself.
- Wu Cai Hong!
- Let me go.
You need to tell the truth.
Look for yourself. These doors and windows are perfectly intact.
Nobody forced their way in. Also,
this room doesn't have the slightest sign of a fight.
The table also has two cups of tea, which shows that the aggressor
was very familiar with the victim. And I
don't even know this girl.
What you said, couldn't it have been done after the murder?
You schemed to harm my father and to take away Ling Long.
You say a weak woman was killed.
Why did you take me along with you?
You originally planned for me to be beside you.
You are simply awful!
You think that I'm the killer?
In order to clear my name I need to prove my innocence?
That's right. Not only are you a killer, your killer tactics are even scarier.
You are a monster.
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian. Jiang Yu killed someone.
Let's report to the police now.
What's going on?
What brings you here?
Cut the nonsense. Let's go back now.
Let's go now, Brother Shao Tian.
Cai Hong, is what I am hearing the truth?
It's just that I don't have any concrete evidence.
This is the latest results after the death.
You may leave.
Based on this new report, your father's injury
was caused by a small wound from a metal pen.
It left debris (evidence),
that is only found in a rare Parker pen tip.
Cai Hong. Does your father have such a pen?
Jiang Yu has this fountain pen too.
If we can test Jiang Yu's pen in a laboratory,
we may be able to explain it.
Can I tell Jiang Yu to come here
to examine his fountain pen?
Last time, we already confirmed his innocence.
Also, the witness was my superior, Chief Li Ting.
If you think that Jiang Yu used the fountain pen to kill someone,
let's test the pen thoroughly.
Brother Shao Tian. Did I make a mistake?
In case I hadn't insist on checking on her identity,
she wouldn't have died.
You are not at fault.
You are investigating your father's death to take revenge.
As it is something you swore to do.
Blame the cruelty of the murderer who
covered up the murder through silence.
If I hadn't forced the situation,
this matter wouldn't have come to this stage.
Cai Hong. Leave this matter to me now.
First Lao Cai and now his mistress...
I'm worried that if this continues, it won't bring you any benefits.
I am not going to be afraid. The more he threatens me,
the more I'm committed to removing his mask of hypocrisy,
and investigating the reason of my father's death.
Also,
I must get hold of Jiang Yu's fountain pen.
Brother.
So how? Did you meet Old Cai's mistress?
Yes,
- but she is already dead.
- Dead?
When I arrived there, she was already dead.
Who did it?
I don't know who did it.
How each time someone is always one step ahead of me..
it is like someone is being given clues (information) in advance.
Brother. What are you suspicious of?
I suspect this individual wants to stop people from being questioned
(giving out information
around us.
Brother.
Who do you suspect then?
Fei Fei. When I went to find Old Cai's mistress,
did you tell anyone about it?
I... didn't.
You really didn't?
It's that Brother Shao Tian.
When he couldn't find Wu Cai Hong, he was like a maniac.
He forced me to tell him.
I was thinking that place isn't safe.
He may be able to help when he is there.
Thus, I told him.
Could Shao Tian have done something?
Brother. Ever since Wu Cai Hong came to Ling Long,
she keeps bringing troubles.
When do you plan to let her go?
Wait till I have investigated fully
about who stole the money from Ling Long,
she can go whenever and wherever she wants.
Brother, don't overdue it.
Regardless of who stole the money from Ling Long,
I think we should thank him instead.
If it weren't for him, it won't have been that easy for us to acquire Ling Long.
Why are you always grabbing a hold of that man?
(Why do you always suspect him?)
The person who stole the money from Ling Long,
should also be the one who burnt the ledger.
He is also the same person who harmed Old Cai's mistress.
Furthermore, he should be near us.
If we don't get rid of him soon,
one of these days, he'll back us into a corner.
Shao Tian.
Shao Tian. You are here just in time. Think of a solution quickly
- to let my wife, children and I leave here.
- You are the killer.
I... I didn't have a choice.
What you did is suicidal.
Shao Tian. Listen to me.
I did according to your instructions.
I gave her money to leave
but I never would have thought that that person wanted more money,
she even used Ling Long to threaten me.
She said that she will report to the police.
I was in a panic. Thus...
I didn't kill her intentionally.
Shao Tian.
You are the only one who can help me to leave.
We're in the same boat.
Nothing must happen to me.
Are you threatening me?
I... wouldn't dare.
Master Shao.
Master Shao. I'm begging you.
Please save him. If you don't save him today,
he will be doomed.
Get up first.
Let's do this. I will think of a way
but you must listen to me next
time there is a plan.
Yes.
Okay, thanks.
Thanks.
Thank, Master Shao.
What are you doing?
Brother Shao Tian's mother is sick.
Thus, I'm cooking some porridge. He doesn't have time to take care of her.
I will take his mother to the hospital later.
Cai Hong. Have you thought it through
about being with Shao Tian?
Aunt.
Don't say that I talk too much.
When a girl marries someone,
they will be reborn for the second time.
This is an opportunity to turn your life around.
Of course, you must choose well.
Zhou Shao Tian isn't on your level.
A lowly husband and wife will live in misery.
This is not a game.
I think you have misunderstood.
I don't have the mood to be in love now.
Ever since my father passed away,
Brother Shao Tian has helped us a lot.
I'm just expressing my gratitude.
You should show your gratitude in a suitable fashion.
You are so close to him now.
It's inevitable that he'll misunderstand.
He still thinks he has a chance, no?
Come, Aunt.
Miss Wu, thank you.
It's okay, Aunt.
Brother Shao Tian is like a family member to me.
Thus, it's a given that I should take care of you.
Then, in the future,
could I treat you like my family member?
Of course. Just tell me if you want to eat anything.
When I have cooked it, I will have it delivered to you.
You are really a good girl.
Shao Tian, is really a blessing from the heavens.
Have some again.
Come.
Aunt?
It's really you.
Wench. So, it's you.
Why are you here again? Did you disobey the doctor's orders again?
No. My son is just anxious about me.
I'm getting older. I was feeling a bit dizzy and had a fever, but he was getting worried.
He brought me here for a medical check. Look at me.
Okay.
- I'm great.
- Don't overexert yourself.
I think you're still a little weak when walking.
When one is old, how could they not have any illnesses?
What are you doing at the hospital?
I came to visit someone who also didn't take good care of herself
but Aunt, why are you here alone?
No one is with you?
Yes, there is.
My daughter is here with me.
Just now, I had a craving.
I wanted to eat Rose Candy.
I sent him to go buy some for me.
You like to eat Rose Candy as well?
I have been eating this for several years.
I really like this too
but if we eat too many sweet things,
it won't be good for recovering from illnesses.
Consider that you are fated.
I will share it with you when she has bought it.
Are you bribing me?
That's good too.
Wench. I have met you many times.
I still don't know your name.
Aunt. You can call me Cai Hong.
Cai Hong?
This is a nice name.
Sorry to disturb you, Madam.
Could you please verify this hospital form?
I can't read clearly.
Cai Hong, read this to me.
To the patient, Wang Mei Feng.
The address is Xian Hu Street, number 25.
The hospital stay was three months and eight days.
Principal doctor was Zhao Hai Yang. I filled it in correctly, right?
Yes.
Thank you, Nurse.
Don't mention it.
Cai Hong, thank you.
It's okay, Aunt.
After one reaches a certain age,
coming to the hospital is a common occurence.
I can't even read the words clearly on the paper.
My daughter is very busy. I didn't want to impose on them
to tell them to keep me company.
I wanted to read the newspaper
but I realised that I forgot my reading glasses.
Cai Hong. If you could,
could you go to my house to get my reading glasses?
Go to your house?
Well...
Am I making it inconvenient for you?
Of course not.
I will come back here after I have gotten it.
No need. Let's do this.
Bring it for me tomorrow. This way,
you will have time to stay and talk to me.
When the time comes, you'll think I'm annoying.
How could I?
It's okay. I will bring it for you tomorrow.
Okay.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Miss Wu. What's up?
I'm here to get Madam's reading glasses.
Okay, this way, please.
Come.
- Hello Housekeeper Qi.
- Where are you going?
The flowers in Young Master's room are wilting. I'm changing them.
Okay, go to the backyard and change them. Quickly now.
Your Young Master is staying there?
Yes. His room is over there.
It's pretty exquisite.
Housekeeper Ji! The accountant is over there looking for you.
He says there's an urgent matter.
Okay, I will go over now.
Miss, I have to go attend to some urgent matters.
I will bring the reading glasses to you later.
Thank you for the trouble.
Hello, Young Master.
What are you doing here?
I met Madam Jiang at the hospital.
She wanted me to come her to pick up something for her.
I was looking around your house.
What is there to look around?
You are not welcome here. Leave.
Miss Wu. Why are you here?
I brought Madam's reading glasses for you.
Okay, I know.
I'm leaving first.
Miss Wu. This is Madam's reading glasses.
Since Mr Jiang is back, he can deliver them to her.
Thank you.
Miss.
From the looks of it, the wound on his shoulder
was definitely caused by this fountain pen.
It's Jiang Yu.
Cai Hong, don't be rash first.
Even though, the wound was caused by a fountain pen,
we can't determine if it was this pen or not.
Superintendent Chen, you and my dad have been acquainted for more than ten years.
Based on your past friendship,
you must help me to find out the truth.
On the day the incident happened to Boss Wu, that day Jiang Yu came to find me.
Furthermore, Jiang Yu has always been planning to acquire Ling Long.
Thus, Cai Hong and I think that
he killed Boss Wu.
Even though this fountain pen is not strong evidence,
we could probably find more evidence with further investigation.
Don't talk about my friendship with your father first.
(It isn't just about our friendship.)
Even if we didn't have one (relationship), I would still investigate this and find the killer.
I'm very thankful after hearing what you have said.
You don't need to thank me. I'm the police.
I'm only doing what I should do.
Hello. Go to Ling Long and tell Boss Jiang to come here.
Immediately.
Sorry. Who is Jiang Yu?
It's me.
Please come with us to the police bureau.
Wait.
What are you doing? Why are you taking my brother?
Sorry. We are only just following orders.
Let Mister Jiang assist in the investigation of Wu Hong Da's death.
Please understand.
What does Wu Hong Da's death have to do with my brother?
Do you have any evidence? Can the police just take him away like this?
We are only just following orders, Miss.
If you obstruct our duties,
I'm afraid you will have to go to jail with us too.
- You...
- Fei Fei.
No problem. I will go with you.
- Brother...
- Contact Lawyer Zhang and tell him to meet me there.
Mr Jiang. Do you recognise this fountain pen?
Of course, I know that this is a Parker pen
but how does this fountain pen concern me?
On Wu Hong Da's corpse,
we found a gold fragment
that was proven to belong to the Parker fountain pen.
So to say, the owner of this fountain pen,
could be the killer we are looking for.
This fountain pen is Jiang Yu's, you're smiting me!
You are trying to frame my brother.
Mr Jiang, sorry.
I'm just doing my work. I hope that you will cooperate with me.
Superintendent Chen,
let me ask you. Before you called me here,
did you thoroughly check this fountain pen?
You told me just now that you found a
golden piece of the Parker pen on the corpse.
But this fountain pen
doesn't seem to have any wears or tears.
Also, I know that this Parker pen is rare.
How long has it been since Wu Hong Da's case?
- More than a month.
- More than a month?
One month is enough for you,
you and especially you,
or perhaps someone else,
could have ordered the exact fountain pen from overseas.
Isn't this so?
Also,
how can you prove that this fountain pen
belongs to me?
Sorry. This fountain pen is really mine.
I would like to ask you. I just lost this fountain pen in my home.
Where did you pick it up from?
Can I formally file charges against
the person that stole the fountain pen from my home?
Don't make up stories! It's you who killed my dad!
Return my father to me!
- Cai Hong!
- What excuses are you making?!
Forget it. Don't be rash. Mr Jiang, sorry.
Forgive me for wasting your precious time.
Cai Hong is just a little girl, she doesn't know her manners.
Please forgive her.
Superintendent Chen, if you want to find me in the future,
don't waste your efforts.
Just call me and I will be here any time.
Dad, don't worry.
I guarantee that
I will find the killer
and take revenge for you.
Stop making excuses, I know you killed my father!
Return my father to me.
It's you who killed my father.
It's her.
Why is she here? How dare she come here?
She's here again.
This...
Isn't this because of her?
She still dares to come here?
Do you have documents for the boss?
Thank you.
She is really brave.
Wu Cai Hong.
You still dare to come back here?
How could she come back here?
Are you here to be scolded?
I came back just to work.
I think you are crazy.
Boss Jiang didn't sack me. I'm still an employee here.
Give me this.
Before I lose my temper,
get lost.
That Wu Cai Hong is too stubborn.
Hello, this is Ling Long.
Wu Cai Hong. Why are you still there?
Is Miss Fang there? Hand over the phone to her.
Boss Jiang.
If there is anything, just instruct me to do it.
Immediately go and send someone to retrieve the log from the meeting two days ago.
Where are you? I will deliver it to you.
You don't need to bother about this. After going through what happened yesterday,
you are no longer my secretary.
I admit that I was at fault.
If you want to punish me, I will accept it.
However, I didn't break the secretary code.
I would like to continue to be your secretary.
Fine.
If you can bring that meeting log to me,
I will reconsider it.
Where are you now?
I'm next to a tree where the flowers have bloomed.
What? I...
Boss Jiang wants me to deliver this document to him.
Please pick up the documents from the floor.
You!
I wish you good luck and hope that you can find him.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
What did you do?
I already told you so many times and you still don't understand?
Revise this. If you don't get it done by today, don't report back for work.
Yes.
Miss Fang, it's a call for you.
Hello, brother.
Zhou Shao Tian?
Sorry.
I'm late.
If I really want to continue to work at Ling Long?
If you think that by staying,
you can depend on your endless thinking ability
to find
evidence of your father's death...
Then I will fight until the end.
I don't want to fight with you.
- I'm really very tired.
- I'm only stating the facts.
You wanted me to find a tree with flowers that had bloomed.
I can find any street, large or small,
any park, any tree,
as long as Boss Jiang gives the order, anything's fine.
In your eyes,
am I that hateful?
Think whatever you like.
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian.
I heard you were trying to find an absurd place.
I was worried and came over.
It's getting late. I will take you home.
Can I continue to work at Ling Long?
Where are the documents?
It's the same old time at 8 am.
Why do you want to work at Ling Long?
Cai Hong. I know you want to find out the reason for your father's death
but have you thought about what kind of a man Jiang Yu is?
You came over here that late in the night. Do you know how worried I was about you?
I'm fine, Brother Shao Tian.
Go back then.
Wu Cai Hong. You still have the face to sit here?
If you are smart, you should leave Ling Long.
Leave my brother. Or else, I will not let you off.
Miss. I'm really rushing the documents now.
If there is nothing else, please go back.
Stop acting.
What are you trying to do? What are you scheming?!
Boss Jiang has already gave me the consent to come back here.
My brother has been deceived by you, but I haven't!
- Men!
- Miss.
Drag her out of Ling Long.
Miss. Would you like to check with Boss Jiang first?
Why should I ask him? My word counts.
Get lost now.
Fei Fei.
Brother.
Come out with me for a while.
Brother. She caused us harm
and also Ling Long. Why are you retaining her?
Come out.
Brother. What is on your mind?
What do you mean?
Why did you let Wu Cai Hong come back to work?
Aren't you afraid that she will harm you again when she's back?
You don't need to bother about this.
I have my own plans.
What are your plans?
I didn't see you make any plans.
Is she making your mind restless?
Brother, don't forget
about how father died and how mom got sick.