The Cage of Love
Episode 5
I want to tell you,
regardless if whether you are a heiress or a poor man's daughter,
I will always be with you.
My heart will always be with you.
Thus, I will only leave if you leave. If you stay, I will stay too.
Cai Hong.
Why are you here?
Why are you two together at night
meeting in this room together?
Spread out. Don't be close together.
Mrs. Wu, I'm sorry. It was thoughtless of me.
Since it is late, I will leave.
Go. Go. Go.
Do you feel better?
Cai Hong, listen to me.
From now on, don't be so close
to Zhou Shao Tian.
Our family was rich,
your father let him chase you,
that was because he was nice
and could help us.
He could even be our son-in-law but it's different now.
Look at him, he doesn't have money or power.
You'd better not get so close to him.
I see people distancing themselves from me.
In the past, there were lots men who wanted to the Wu family's son-in-law.
But now, only Brother Shao Tian treats me the same as in the past.
Aunt. Brother Shao Tian is my most trusted friend.
You are really silly.
How can a man and a woman
be friends?
I don't believe it, he must want something from you.
Would he really treat you so well unconditionally?
You should marry a rich guy as you
are young and beautiful now.
Your head and face. (are beautiful) Well surprise your aunt
and make the second half of your life better.
Am I right?
What has it got to do with money? Marriage is for life.
Yup.
What you said is true.
It may not be necessarily good if one is rich
but it's definitely not good to be without any money.
Do you know? Think about it.
What we talked about it to you previously, I wonder what are your views.
I'm very sorry. I'm afraid that I have to reject your kind gesture.
Are you not happy with my bringing up the topic of revenge for you?
If so, I can...
No, it's not about money.
Maybe Master Zhou is still reluctant to express his feelings towards the person he loves.
If this is the case, I will offer a leeway for you,
otherwise I would feel sorry for you.
But I cannot bear Master Zhou' talents wasted.
What should I do?
Or let's do it in this way.
I will keep the position for you.
You are welcome to join us any time.
Thank you, Miss Lu, for thinking so highly of me.
I would like to invite you for a meal another day.
Please show me face.
Of course.
I even invited the Mayor of Huzhou so he could personally talk to Mrs Jiang.
She still refused.
Brother, what can I do? Two days have passed.
Whether Ling Long can deliver the goods or not, it will depend on Mrs Jiang.
Can I try?
You?
My brother can't even do it,
how can you manage it?
I don't think you forgot that
It was Marshall Zhang who fought for orders.
Okay.
I want to see how you can manage it.
If I can persuade Mrs Jiang,
could you let Uncle Fu stay?
If you can really do it,
I won't ask Uncle Fu to compensate but he will need to leave.
It's because he definitely did something wrong.
If it were you, you also wouldn't
retain someone who betrayed you.
But on the contrary, if you can't do it,
not only will I demand that Uncle Fu compensate,
as for you, you should get lost with him too.
Okay.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Brother. You are really not going to take me along?
If we want to persuade Mrs Jiang, we may take some time.
If the both of us go,
what if something happens to Mom when she is home and she needs someone to take care of her. What are we going to do?
Okay, come back soon.
I get it, don't worry.
Cai Hong, Cai Hong...
-Shao Tian.
-Are you really going with him?
Yes and don't worry about it.
He did not embarrass you, right?
Of course not.
By the way, Brother Shao Tian,
Mrs Jiang is very protective of her flowers. If we were to pluck them,
she definitely won't be happy. Thus, we need to think of a way
to make her heart feel at ease.
Leave this to me. I will think of a way.
Wu Cai Hong.
It is getting dark and you are still flirting.
I am not flirting!
You will find out later.
Be careful.
Let's go!
Sorry, sorry.
I... I... I... didn't
Boatman, hand me a cloth.
Okay, thank you.
I am sorry.
From now on, sit here
and don't move around.
Is anyone here?
Mrs Jiang.
Hello, Mrs Jiang.
I am Wu Cai Hong from Ling Long.
I want to talk about something with you.
Mrs Jiang, wait for me.
Mrs Jiang, Mrs Jiang...
Mrs Jiang,
I will be waiting for you here.
I will wait even though you won't come out.
You came out, Mrs Jiang.
-Mrs Jiang, where are you going ?
-I don't want to talk to you, I am going to the bathroom .
Then... I will come with you.
How can you come with me? It's only for one person.
-You...Get your hands off.
-Can you please talk to me?
Okay, I will.
Get your hands off me!
Why are you laughing?
I hate him by his look. Let him go!
Let him go. Otherwise I won't talk to you.
Mrs Jiang, that person
has left.
Don't be so mad.
Did you think about it?
See, we...
Okay, let's just ignore him.
Let's go, Mrs Jiang.
Why didn't he come back?
Are you done?
Yup.
-What?
She has agreed.
-How?
-Hey! I am telling you that my garden is so huge.
Go to the village and find help to pluck the flowers.
If not, you won't be able to pluck the roses before it gets dark.
Okay. I got it.
Thank you so much! Mrs Jiang.
Aren't you going to look for people?
Oh yeah.
How did you convince Mrs Jiang?
Mrs Jiang planted the rose garden
for her daughter who, as you saw, passed away.
I promised her that even though she is a hundred years old, I will still help her to look after the rose garden.
Thus, she let me pluck them.
So, this is her weak point.
I'm different from you. What you were looking for was her weak points.
As for me , what I looked for was her needs.
Treat others well and their heart bends.
Thus, she also uses her sincerity to handle me.
Cai Hong!
Brother Shao Tian, over here.
Why is he here?
To help us.
Brother Shao Tian.
-Brother Shao Tian.
-Yes.
This place is not bad.
I knew that you could do it.
Let me explain things to you.
What is this?
Look.
So how? It looks actually like the real rose, right?
Why are you so smart?
But it must have cost a fair bit of money to buy this.
You should be repairing the house.
- Didn't you spend it all?
- What about the money?
I will just put on winter clothes.
This place is so hot and you are still wearing autumn clothes?
Cai Hong. With you by my side, everything is warm.
It's so cold.
Come, let me wipe your perspiration.
Cai Hong.
Mrs Jiang.
Cai Hong. The boatman just came to tell me that all the boats have already left.
I think you won't be able to leave today.
We won't be able to leave? What should we do then?
You will have to suffer tonight
and spend the night at my home.
Don't say that we will suffer.
- We are troubling you.
- None at all.
But I only have two rooms.
Let's do it like this. I will give you the room of my daughter, Cai Hong.
You both can stay at the guest room.
So how? Let's go and take a look.
I think
you should sleep on the ground.
Who gives you the right? You are not my boss now.
It's because I snore when I'm asleep.
When I'm asleep, I'm dead to the world.
Don't talk about snoring. I can't even feel the earthquake.
Your thinking is too simple and immature.
When I snore, I'm not like just anyone.
I rank higher than anyone else.
Just don't regret it.
This is really interesting.
Is there any regret medicine in this world?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Mutant.
It's late. Why aren't you asleep yet?
They say that the stars in the sky
are the eyes of our loved ones.
About my parents,
which pair of eyes are theirs?
Are they watching me?
Regardless of which pair of eyes they are,
you must know that they are looking at you from above
and keeping watch over you.
Cai Hong. You are tired from the long day.
Sleep early.
I still want my parents to watch over me for a while longer.
Okay then.
It is not too late.
I will stay and watch the stars with you.
Hey, Zhou guy.
Why aren't you sleeping?
If you are not going to sleep, I will lock the door.
You have finished talking?
It's good tea.
Take your time drinking it.
Mrs Jiang. Thank you for helping Ling Long.
I'm not helping Ling Long. I'm helping Cai Hong.
Thank you. I will visit you often in the future.
Have a safe journey then.
Bye.
You have so many goods. How are you going to sit?
But we are in a hurry to use the goods.
The boat should be able to take the three of us, right?
Could they bend the rules?
Why is there only one boat?
There is only boat here and that's mine.
Who's getting on board?
We are all getting on board.
This boat can only take two passengers now. You have so much goods.
- I can pay you much. How much do you want?
It's not the problem about money. It's too dangerous.
I think the boss should get on board.
Let's do this instead.
Deliver these goods back for me.
These goods are extremely important to Ling Long.
If Ling Long doesn't have these,
and something happens on the way there,
Cai Hong and I will not take responsibility.
- How will you go back then?
- It's getting late.
Cai Hong and I will wait for the next boat. We may need to stay here for the night.
But we are not in a hurry. Boss, please go first.
I was just short of finding
the whereabouts of the large sums of missing money. Then
I will be able to find evidence of the killer then.
What evidence did you find?
I got this from Jiang Yu.
Mister Zhang placed some orders. He gave good feedback.
He was extremely happy.
He also promised to place future orders and
they will come to us.
Of course, we were able to overcome our obstacle this time to complete the order.
- This is because of the hard work by the staff.
- Boss Jiang.
Cold water, warm water and water. Which kind would you like to drink?
Warm.
It's not hot enough.
I have prepared it so the water can be mixed.
If the temperature is not enough, there is still the cold water.
Boss Jiang. I already wrote this document.
If you still need more, there are still two copies in the office.
Looks like I should be well prepared too.
Continue.
Brother.
- Brother.
- What's wrong?
Look at this.
This is missing information. The file contained Ling Long information about the liquidation.
But with our research...
I already knew about this. Don't panic.
This is just a duplicate.
Brother. Wu Cai Hong definitely stole it.
I already said that she's here for an ulterior motive.
She's only trying to find evidence concerning me about Wu Hong Da's death.
Fei Fei.
I remember that was a big sum of money missing from the previous Ling Long.
Help me to investigate where that money went to.
What has that old accounts got to with us?
Why should we bother about this?
Just investigate when I tell you to do so.
But Cai Hong stole the documents.
Enough. If she do anything wrong, I will punish her.
Forget about it.
Could it be that there is Brother has something to do with Wu Hong Da?
He won't do something like that.
He won't.
Are you trying to help me carry some of this stuff because I'm struggling with it?
You are really thick skinned.
I told you before not to even think about playing tricks.
Otherwise you will get into more troubles than you'd be able to handle.
I think the one who is looking for trouble is you instead.
Don't think that by pretending to be pitiful,
others will take pity on you.
Your pretense may trick others but you can't trick me.
You don't need to come with me.
This is the second code of a Secretary.
The secretary must be close by.
I already told you that regardless of whether the boss is right or wrong,
you must do what you are told.
- But...
- I even said that
if you dare to defy the codes,
I will kick you out immediately.
Dye Material Storage
Cai Hong.
-Quiet
-What are you doing?
Cai Hong. What were you looking for just now?
Nothing.
Brother Shao Tian. Are you looking for me?
After work today I will be eating with friends
so I won't be able to escort you home.
I'm not a baby.
It's no matter.
I'm used to this. Maybe I'll do nothing at all.
If you are really going to quit, that's good then.
I can take care of you every day.
I...
I am hiring you to do the work
and not to let you come here to date.
Brother Shao Tian. I'm leaving first.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Thank you. I will treat you to a meal on another day.
I can treat you to anything.
Where should I find you? Where do you live? What is your name?
I have never seen such a rude, stingly and mannerless man like you!
I find him very good looking.
You see, he has a strikingly handsome face.
He has a Grecian nose, strong brows and bright-eyed, with an uncommon demeanor.
No matter how you look at him, he is smoothing to look at, a handsome man.
I already know your name.
It's Jiang Yu.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I have a dinner party tonight, you do not have to accompany me.
You can knock off work now.
It's after office hours. Let's go.
Let's go and have drinks.
Go home and rest more.
Use mine. I will cut for you.
Thank you very much.
If I didn't have you here now,
I wouldn't be able to eat my steak.
Miss Lu. You are good at joking.
But I'm greedier. Not only do I hope that you will cut my steak for me,
but also that you will help me in getting the dyeing factory.
I know that you are preoccupied with the issues connected to Ling Long.
It may be wishful thinking but I am looking forward to this meal and hopefully you having a change of heart.
Everything is difficult following right after a disaster.
I don't have anyone now and I also don't have many skills.
Even if I don't have someone like you to help me,
even a cloud can be a secret ingredient
in the Huzhou weaving and dying business. Even the earth has a seat.
(Things out of our control can play a part.)
By the way, I heard that Ling Long has a secret recipe.
The recipe was provided for royal use. Even you know it too.
I joined Ling Long when I was nineteen years old. I have been with Ling Long for ten years.
I have never heard of any secret recipe.
It could be that the reporters
have spread ridiculous news.
It's okay. Come.
I raise this cup (toast) to you today.
Being able to dine with Miss Lu
who is a beauty,
not everyone would have this honour.
Talking about beauty,
if one has money, one can get anything.
If Mr Zhou were to prosper,
he may get the beauty that has always gotten away.
There are insects there.
Insects!
There are insects.
Open the door.
Because of a Wu Cai Hong, you are suffering at Ling Long. Is this worth it?
Miss Lu. I think you are mistaken.
I, Zhou Shao Tian, don't need to spend 300won to
to drink a cup with Cai Hong.
But women like men who are strong.
Because a strong man can gives security to a woman.
As you know, Jiang Yu was suppressed.
That is not a good thing.
It's only a matter of time before I leave Ling Long.
It's just not now.
Then, let's celebrate your early departure.
Madam.
Is Cai Hong here?
You scared me. Why are you here so late in the evening?
You reek of alcohol.
Cai Hong is not back yet.
Where did she go?
For a young and beautiful woman,
it's common for her to dine and chat with her friends after work.
Furthermore, Cai Hong is now working and experiencing life.
She knows what kind of friends are good for her.
Brother Shao Tian. It's late. Are you here to look for sister?
She is not back yet.
Brother Shao Tian.
Again and again, I keep telling him.
- Mom.
- He scared me just now.
Two little tigers, two little tigers.
Ran so fast. Ran so fast.
One doesn't have a mouth,
one doesn't have ears.
It's really strange.
Two little tigers.