The Cage of Love
Episode 30
People such as Lu Man are vicious like snakes and scorpions.
Moreover, she is obsessed with the recipe. There is an 80% chance that she killed your father.
But to find a flaw in Lu Man's actions or any criminal evidence,
I'm afraid it won't be that easy.
What should we do then? Are we going to just sit here and wait?
As police, we need evidence in our line of work.
I can't do anything without any evidence.
Why don't we do this?
Let's start from her subordinates first.
I'm know some of her employees. I will check with them to see if there are any leads.
- Let me give you a lift.
-I'm walking back.
After being in jail for some time, I would like to have some fresh air and walk around a bit.
- Brother Shao Tian I...
-It's getting late. Go home now.
Cai Hong. I must get used to not being with you anymore.
I will continue to walk alone.
-Brother Shao Tian.
- Zhang Xuan, I hope you can help me with something,
Brother Shao Tian. Don't say this. It was fortunate that you took care of me when I was with Rong Da.
I heard about what happened to you.
Don't worry. I'm a righteous person.
I know. If this isn't the case, I wouldn't have looked for you.
You have been with Miss Lu for many years. I would like to you find something for me discreetly.
Brother Shao Tian, please tell me.
At that time, if it weren't for you, I would have been living in the ghettos.
Fortunately, your money has helped my mother to cure her illness. I will repay you properly.
I want you to find out for me
about Miss Lu's schedule the day of Wu Hong Da's incident.
This...
- Brother Shao Tian, this is not about money.
- I know that it's about money.
This money can help you get through the critical times.
This is very important to me.
Take it as you are doing me a favour.
Okay?
Brother Shao Tian, I will do my best. Wait for my news.
Whether I'm successful or not, I will contact you.
Thank you, Zhang Xuan.
After this is done,
I will thank you again.
Brother.
Where are you going?
Since when do I need to report to you before I go out?
Every day, you leave the house and come back late.
Do you know that I haven't seen you for a long time?
I haven't recovered from my injuries yet.
I don't want Mom to see me in this condition.
She will worry about me.
That's right. If Mom were to find out that you were beaten into this condition because of Wu Cai Hong,
it won't be that simple as being worried about you.
Brother, the murderer will be caught. Mother does not even need to know Cai Hong's identity.
Stay home and take good care of Mom. Don't bother about other matters.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Jiang Yu. Now what?
Director Li said we have to find hard evidence,
so that we can find an excuse for Lu Man to be investigated at the police station.
If not, it will be hard to explain to the Military Governor.
It's okay. There will definitely be a way.
The investigation has been going on for a long time.
In fact, you have already been cleared of all suspicions.
Thank you for still helping me.
By the way, will you be going to Ling Long?
No. I'm going to the hospital for a check up.
Can I go with you?
I'm not a three year old kid. Why would I need someone to go with me to the hospital?
I let you go with me to investigate the case. Why can't I go with you to the hospital?
Just regard this as I'm paying you back.
Let's go then.
Brother. Can I move back to stay here now? Huzhou
Wait a while more.
Wait until we capture Lu Man, then you can move back.
I asked around. They gave up after looking for me for a few days.
I think they will not give me any problems again.
Lu Man didn't find you to create trouble because she doesn't want you to expose her identity.
This woman is very shady and toxic.
Most likely she is already planning a surprise attack. We better be careful.
This is not the first day I was beaten up and harmed.
Don't worry. I will be careful.
Brother, look at yourself. You look more haggard.
Have a good rest. Don't overwork yourself.
Brother.
Are you thinking about Wu Cao Hong again?
I must manage Rong Da properly because of Cai Hong
and also help her to find her father's killer.
Okay.
This is great wine. Where did you get this great wine from?
Brother, you are Miss Lu's favourite person now.
Since Miss is favouring you, you could do few things for me, right?
There's nothing bad with ripping the benefits. Tell me.
What can I help you with?
What do you mean, brother.
I only want to get closer to you.
Every time Miss Lu goes out to handle some major matter,
she only takes Uncle Lai along.
Not only that.
Now even the warlord's people treat me with respect.
All the big and small dyeing factories in Huzhou. That Ling Long and Hua Mei,
I know them very well.
Yes.
When Miss Lu went to see Wu Da Hong of Ling Long,
that old man died after that.
How do you know about this?
Uncle Lai mentioned this when we came here for a meal.
I'm only just guessing.
This is really a good wine.
Don't talk any nonsense.
If you talk any nonsense,
you will die.
Look. I already told you many times.
Fei Fei. Why don't I see your brother lately?
He is too busy with work.
He leaves the house early every day and comes home late.
It could be that he doesn't have the time to come here.
But no matter how busy he is, he should also find time to visit you.
Don't worry, I will lecture him on your behalf.
This little cotton-padded jacket will suffice for his attention.
Let your brother do what a man is supposed to do.
But you must advise your brother to take care of his health.
I know.
The doctor already said that you shouldn't let water touch your wounds.
It will heal fast, but can be very itchy. It would be good to use a clutch for a while.
Okay, I know.
Yu Er.
Mom.
Yu Er, Cai Hong.
What are you doing here?
I had some injuries and came here for treatments. I'm better now.
Everything is already fine.
How did you get hurt?
You should ask Cai Hong about this.
I'm sorry, Madam Jiang. Master Jiang got injured because of me.
I will personally apologise to you another day.
Cai Hong. Ever since you left, I have been missing you.
Why didn't you visit me?
What do you want to tell me?
Mom.
Do you want me to start from your family name?
Fei Fei. What are you trying to say?
Mom, don't stand here.
I will take you home first. Come.
Come with me. I have something to tell you.
What did you wanted to tell my mom just now?
I wanted to apologise to her for what my father did.
You should keep quiet.
Do you know why my brother didn't want you to say anything just now?
My mom is an ill person which was caused by your father.
Your presence will only agitate her.
If my mom gets sick again,
when that time comes, the first person who won't let you off is my brother.
It was my father's fault. Thus, I wanted to do something for the Jiang family and your brother.
If you really feel a guilty conscious and want to do something for my mom,
please stay far away from her.
Our family is finally enjoying peaceful days. Don't trouble us, please.
I'm not trying to create a mess.
- I only want to...
- I know very well what you are thinking
but you will never get rid of your debt.
If you continues on, the matter will only get worse.
My mom can't take on any more traumas.
She would go crazy when she hears Wu Hong Da's name.
How could she able to accept you?
She'd rather my brother never marry or have children.
She will also never accept Wu Hong Da's daughter.
- Hello.
- Brother Shao Tian. I found out what you wanted.
Let's meet at the usual place later.
Okay.
What did you tell Cai Hong at the hospital just now?
Other than the grudges between our families, what else do you think I would tell her?
Fei Fei. Cai Hong is different from her father.
We shouldn't let our grudges run through the next generation.
You are right
but would you dare to tell Mom this?
Do you think Mom will accept her?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Sister. It's late. What are you looking for?
I'm looking for my slave contract.
I'm going back to the Jiang family.
It wasn't easy for you to leave from the Jiang family. Why are you jumping back in the fire?
There are certain things you wouldn't understand.
Yes, I don't understand.
Dad is already dead and Ling Long has been returned to Jiang Yu. What else do we owe them?
We owe them a healthy mother
and remorse for what happened to deceased Master Jiang.
I'm going back to the Jiang family and will seek forgiveness from Madam Jiang.
If not, I won't have peace for the rest of my life.
Are you really doing this to redeem yourself of the crimes?
Yes.
I'm also doing this for myself.
Don't tell me that this is Zhang Xuan's corpse.
I caused him to die.
What exactly is going on?
Don't be anxious. Take your time to tell me.
He was Lu Man's employee. I met him a few days ago.
I wanted him to find out the schedule of Lu Man on the day of Wu Hong Da's incident.
I didn't imagine that...
It's another victim again.
Lu Man must be behind this.
Let's do this.
I will call Jiang Yu first and then find someone to pick up Cai Hong.
Let's have a meeting to see what we should do next.
I will go and pick up Cai Hong.
Be careful on the way. Lu Man may take action.
- Hello.
- Is that Mr Jiang?
- Yes, I am.
- This is Director Chen.
We found a corpse this morning.
He probably is Lu Man's employee, Zhang Xuan.
He should have something to do with our investigation on Lu Man.
I hope you can come down to the police station and help decide what our next step is.
Okay, no problem.
I will bring Wu Cai Hong along with me.
No need. Zhou Shao Tian has already gone to pick her up.
Also, be careful. Lu Man will find men to take revenge.
Don't worry, we will.
What are you doing here?
I'm a maid with the Jiang family. I came back willingly.
Don't tell me you need to see the slave contract?
Didn't you always want to leave?
Since you have already left, why did you come back?
You know the reason why I'm back.
Do you really need to do this?
Whatever has happened has already happened.
What we can only do
is to remember what we should remember.
You must accept that we wouldn't be able to change anything.
Before we can't change everything, I must work hard.
I want to seek Madam Jiang's forgiveness. If she doesn't forgive me, I won't leave.
What if my mom really won't forgive you?
If I don't work hard, how would we know the result?
If you want to remain here, fine. Do whatever you want.
But you should know that
no one in the Jiang family will welcome you.
I know
but there will always be someone to help me.
- Brother Shao Tian.
- Xiao Yun. Where is your sister?
She went out early this morning.
Where did she go?
She went to find Jiang Yu.
Brother Shao Tian. Is anything the matter? I will relay to the message to her.
No need. Thanks.
Mr Zhou. You are here just in time.
The report of Zhang Xuan's corpse is out.
There are stab wounds on his neck, but also some traces of a nail grip.
Thus, we are sure the river is not the scene of the crime.
Rather a place where body was dumped.
I caused him to die.
Zhang Xuan called me that day.
He said that he found out what happened with Boss Wu that day.
If he looked for you, this clearly proves that he found evidence of my father's killer.
That's why they took action on him. It's a pity we were one step behind.
Lu Man has already gone insane.
I think not before long we will be able to find the evidence and bring her to justice.
What we need to do now is to keep the secret formula in a safe place.
Lu Man's motive is to get the secret formula.
Thus, the three of you must watch your safety.
The police will also protect you.
Cai Hong. You must remember what Director Chen said.
I know Lu Man. She is very cruel.
She will never let it rest. You must watch your safety.
Don't worry. Cai Hong will be staying with my famiiy for the time being.
Why?
Because my slave contract hasn't expired. Thus...
Jiang Yu. Did you forget that I bought the contract and returned it to you personally?
Why did you go back on your words?
It was my own decision to go back to the Jiang family.
Did you forget how the Jiang family treated you?
It's because of how they treated me, that's why I want to seek Madam's forgiveness and apologise to her.
Don't worry about this.
It's the safest place for Cai Hong to stay at my home.
Brother Shao Tian. Don't worry about me. I know what I'm doing.
Since you have already thought it through,
fine then.
If you are not comfortable staying at the Jiang's home,
just come back.
- Young Master.
- Prepare a clean guest room for Miss Wu.
- Yes.
- No need. I can stay at the staff quarters.
Ignore her. Take Miss Wu's suitcase to the guest room first.
Okay.
Brother.
Why did you bring her back again?
Didn't you understand what I told you yesterday?
I thought about it and think that it's still best I come back to seek your mother's forgiveness.
What are you trying to do?
Your family already caused my mom to be in this condition.
Are you going to traumatize her here?
- Fei Fei.
- Don't stop me.
I just don't understand.
You are a refined woman. Why is your skin so thick?
You still insist on coming here even though we beat and scolded you.
I know that you don't like me. No matter how you scold me, I don't care about it.
I wanted to say that Madam Jiang has been sick for so many years, living in the shadow of the past.
If I can really seek her forgiveness and make her let go of everything in the past,
perhaps, this may be of help in her recovery.
Impossible. I will never let you do this.
I have been taking care of my mom for many years.
I know her condition. I will never let anyone traumatize or harm her.
I will slowly talk to her. I can wait for her.
One month, a year or even forever until she forgives me.
Stop dreaming.
As long as I'm here, I will never let you go near my mom
and traumatize her.
Cai Hong?
Cai Hong, it's you.
Did you miss me and came to see me?
Madam. I plan to come back here today to take care of her.
Really?
I heard from my son that you found a boyfriend and will be getting married.
What happened?
We already broke up.
Child. Let bygones be bygones.
Starting from now, regard this as your home and stay here in peace.
Thank you, Madam Jiang.
I only know that you are Cai Hong. I don't know your family name.
- My family name is Wu.
- Wu Cai Hong?
Madam. If you are willing, I will slowly tell you about myself.
I will slowly tell you stories about me and let you get to know the real me.
Okay. I can tell that you must have suffered.
Take time to tell me your stories.
If you have any difficulties, you must tell me. I will help you.
Yu Er will also help you.
Brother. Why did you let Wu Cai Hong into our family again?
What you promised in the past,
did you forget all about it?
This morning a dead body was found in the river.
Director Chen suspects that Lu Man killed him to silence him.
Director Chen hopes that everyone connected to the Wu Da Hong's case
must be extra careful.
I allowed Wu Cai Hong to move in with us. It's all entirely for her safety.
Why are we considering her safety?
No matter what, she is still our enemy.
Even more so when she is just a common stranger.
We don't need to accept her into our family and protect her twenty four hours a day.
Our grudge with the Wu family has already ended.
No matter what you say, you can't change the fact that Wu Cai Hong's father killed our father.
You can forget about this deep grudge
but mom and I will never forget this.
I think you should make Wu Cai Hong leave this house as soon as possible.
Since Lu Man is such a maniac,
you shouldn't let her stay here with us.
You should be concerned for your and the Jiang family's safety.
I dare to guarantee that
at least Lu Man wouldn't dare to kill us here.
You don't have to worry safety.
I'm already involved in the Wu Hong Da's case.
If I were to stop now, I'm afraid Lu Man will never let me off.
Only when we lock her up, we will then be truly safe.
What you mean is that
before Lu Man is caught,
Wu Cai Hong will be staying with us.
I think that even if Lu Man is caught,
Wu Cai Hong will never leave the Jiang family.
Everything that you are doing
is only an excuse for you to keep her with you.
Am I right?
Child. When your brain and heart are in trouble,
you should have sunlight. You won't have any shadows in your face then.
Thank you, Madam.
Are you willing to tell me your stories now?
Are you really willing to hear my stories?
I'm ready.
I actually have a complete and happy family.
Even though my mother died young, I had a father who doted on me.
Under the love, care and protection of my father,
I temporarily forgot the pain of losing my mother.
But not long after that,
my life stopped suddently when I was nineteen years old
and my father was killed.
With the murderer still at large,
my family's business went bankrupt too.
I also have a stepmother and sister.
We were kicked out of the house by the debtors.
Overnight, we became homeless.
No wonder
you are young but on your face,
your age does not match your sorrow.
This wasn't only due to what happened to your family,
you also lost your most beloved one.
Cai Hong. If you are willing,
I can be your mother
and you can regard Jiang Yu as your brother.
Frankly, in my heart, you are just like Fei Fei.
We are different.
I don't deserve you being nice to me.
I...
Actually, I'm...
I am actually...
When my father passed away, I then realised that
he did many things in the past that I wasn't aware of.
In my eyes he was a respected and competent man.
But later, because of a moment of greed, he hurt many people.
He did many unethical things.
I really don't understand
how my kind father could be so ruthless.
I also don't want to believe that he was the same person.
I realised now
your grief must stem from your father's case then.
It's not only this.
I think I am also very sorry towards all victims of that time.
For the past days,
I have been living in pain and felt utmost remorse.
Child, this is your father's fault.
It's not your fault.
Out of my selfishness, I wanted to forgive him
but when I thought about what he did,
I really can't forget about it.
I don't want to forgive him either.
That's because you love your father very much and can't accept that he is corrupted.
You will feel a more guilty conscious to those he had harmed.
But Cai Hong, it was your father that committed the wrong deeds.
Your grief will not change his wrongdoings.
but talking about this, he is just your father.
He only just wanted to be a good father.
You don't have any other reasons to hate him.
As his daughter,
you only need to think about how well he treated you.
Don't hate him again.
Child, we must learn to let it go.
Can I really let it go?
Letting go is easy to say but hard to do.
Don't look at me for an answer to your plight.
For the more than ten years, I find it hard to let it go too.
Hard to?
Wu Cai Hong. I overheard your conversation with my mom.
I haven't told Madam about this yet
but I believe in Madam. She is a very kind person.
- She will definitely forgive me.
- Stop dreaming.
I'm here to tell you not to think that my mom will really forgive you.
My mom is definitely a very kind person
but her kindness
caused her family to go bankrupt. To her enemy,
it will be totally useless.
She said that to you because she sympathises and pities you.
What's even more important is that
she doesn't know that it was your father who ruined our Jiang family.
No matter what,
I will use my sincerity to seek forgiveness from your mom.
Are you being sincere or selfish?
You want my mom to forgive you
so she can support you and my brother through thick and thin.
You want her to accept you because you want to be with my brother. Am I right?
You have misunderstood me.
All this hatred stems from my father's deeds.
Thus, I want to use my sincerity
to end the grudge.
Whether it's a misunderstanding or not,
I still want to tell you that
my mom and the Jiang family will never accept a woman who is tainted with the blood of our enemy.
Whether you believe it or not, or whether you will accept it or not,
my repentance is sincere.
When it was getting dark, Zhang Xuan said that he wanted to go home. After he left, he was never seen again.
I don't know who killed him.
Did you say anything to him before he died?
No.
- Any abnormalities?
- I saw none.
Wasn't he fine?
- Who was he close with?
-How would I know?
How can I answer it when I have no idea?
- I'm really not close to him.
- I really don't know.
Enough, let them go.
Let's go.
Director, this Lu Man employees acted really arrogant toward the society.
We interrogated them for the entire afternoon. They all know nothing.
It's very obvious that they all came prepared.
They are very clear about what they should say and not say.
It's okay. Think of another solution.
Yes.
Brother Shao Tian, Brother Ma Li. My sister is not at home.
I know that Cai Hong is not here. I came to visit you and Madam Wu.
Ma Li, bring the stuff in.
Cai Yun. We have been investigating your father's case lately.
Murderers kill people in order to conceal their crimes.
Thus, for this period of time, don't leave home unnecessarily.
Try not to go to remote places. It might be gangerous for the time being.
Dangerous?
In this world, who else is more dangerous than you?
- Mrs Wu, don't you know that good people...
- I see you are no good person!
- I...
- Ma Li.
Mom.
Madam Wu, Cai Yun. I only hope that you will be careful about your safety.
I understand.
We are taking our leave then.
You are still not leaving?
Yu Er. Cai Hong has suffered a lot.
Try to spend more of your free time with her and cheer her up.
Mom. What did Cai Hong tell you?
Cai Hong told me
that when she was young, her biological mother passed away.
The only family who loved her was her father was killed subsequently.
When her family went bankrupt,
she found out that her father did many unethical things.
On one hand, she cannot accept such brutal facts,
on the other hand, she feels guilty about the victims.
This was her father's fault. What has it to do with Cai Hong?
The way Cai Hong thinks about this, it show that
she is a kind and mature young lady.
But this young lady cannot shoulder all this burden alone.
Yu Er. Be nice to her in the future.
I know.