The Cage of Love
Episode 24
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Ke Ke, slow down.
Be careful.
Slow down. Don't trip.
Slow down.
Ke Ke, slow down.
Come and have your refreshments.
Slow down.
Mom.
Mom. Your dress is very pretty.
Your dress is just like the pretty flowers in the garden.
You are just as beautiful as the flowers.
Xiao Man. You are such a good girl.
In my heart, you are the prettiest flower.
You are the flower which I will use my life to protect.
Wait till I have grown up
and when I look like you,
give this dress to me, okay?
Fine. Since you like it,
I will leave the best for you.
You are the best. I love you the most.
I love you too.
Mom.
I know that you are in pain.
Sorry.
I didn't
protect you.
I couldn't even tailor
your favourite dress.
But don't worry,
now that I have the secret formula,
I can tailor the same dress for you now.
I will be able to do it soon.
Miss.
Miss. Mr Zhou is here.
Please invite him to the guest lounge.
Mr Zhou.
I waited for you for a long time. You are finally here.
I'm afraid that you were not waiting for me.
You are waiting for this secret formula.
Isn't it the same whether I'm waiting for you or the secret formula?
To add further, I'm not the only one who obtained the secret formula.
It's our combined efforts.
You are giving me the secret formula easily.
Shouldn't I be suspicious that you have tampered with it?
It's only just a secret formula.
Even though it will bring lots of money, to me,
it's not worth betraying you for this.
I have already helped Cai Hong find the killer.
As for you, you have gotten the secret formula.
Thus, there is already no value to it.
To add further, whether it's genuine or fake,
try it and you will know.
Yes. Under the eyes of ordinary people like us,
the secret formula is precious.
But in your heart,
Miss Cai is still more valuable.
Of course, you look down on people like us.
You don't need to praise me.
You have already gotten the secret formula.
Jiang Yu was arrested.
We are considered even.
Fine.
Congratulations. You eventually got your wish.
Jiang Yu will be executed.
He is not set to be executed yet.
He is like Sharenchangming, right and proper.
He is a tricky/cruel.
Jiang Yu is too sly and he thinks that the police are too stupid.
Thus, I only borrowed your hands
to push him.
Fine then. Let's not talk about this now.
Let's try the secret formula and see if it's genuine.
If it's genuine, what do you plan to do?
I used a lot of effort to obtain this secret formula.
Of course, I can't let it go to waste.
I am ready for mass production.
After going through this silk contest, I believe that
we could use this recipe to expand.
I want Rong Da to become the nation's biggest dyeing factory.
Miss Lu, you have great ambition.
I still need your help.
Let's go.
Miss Wu.
I... would like to visit Jiang Yu.
Please let me go in.
Of course Miss Wu. Please feel at ease here.
Open the door.
Thank you.
Detention room.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
During the silk contest,
you used the secret formula.
This is a fact
but I still don't believe that
you killed my father.
Jiang Yu. I want to personally hear this from you.
You already obtained so much evidence.
Why don't you still believe that I killed your father?
I remember you said that
if you use evil methods to take revenge on evil people,
you will become like them.
You also said that in a dirty pond,
even clean and pure flowers will grow in it.
For the sake of revenge,
you turn yourself into a killer.
If you let yourself get to that state,
you will allow your family to be in pain too.
This is the most stupid method that only causes suffering.
Thus, you would never do this.
You are full of life. (resuscitation)
How could you still laugh?
- Did you harm my father or not?
- I didn't.
I didn't kill your father.
Even though I hated him, I didn't kill him.
Is there anything else?
If there isn't anything else, go back now.
I... would like to ask you...
My stepmom remembered that
when my father passed away,
he took the secret formula with him before he left the house.
But after the incident, the secret formula went missing.
How are do you explain why the secret formula is with you?
The secret formula that I had
was not your father's secret formula.
There are two sets of the same secret formulas.
What's going on?
That secret formula belongs to the Jiang family.
It was a family heritage
from generations to generations.
Thus, when I was young, I already memorised it
but I didn't know about the last step.
It's because the last step would have to wait for the successor to be eighteen years old
before it can be passed down to him.
But when my father passed away,
I wasn't eighteen years old then.
Sorry.
Even though it's too late
but on behalf of my father,
I would like to apologise to you.
The portion that Fei Fei gave to Zhou Shao Tian
was not the secret formula that was passed down to the Jiang family.
Furthermore, the one which I wrote on it later,
it lacked the last step for the secret formula.
So to say,
you didn't know the last step of the secret formula at all?
That's right.
Then, at the silk contest,
how did you use the missing last step of the secret formula to dye the cloth?
The last step involves
a method of straining.
Just add some water to my cloth and it will discolour.
Really?
If what you are saying is true,
will this prove that you are not guilty?
Try it and you will know.
- Ma Li.
- Miss Wu.
Why are you in such a rush? Are you looking for Brother Shao Tian?
- He is not here.
- I would like to ask you.
Do you still remember the two clothes from the silk contest?
Did you keep them?
Brother Shao Tian told me to keep them. They are in the drawer.
I would like to borrow them for a while. Can you get them for me?
Okay, please wait.
Is this the one?
Miss!
It's really very beautiful.
It's gorgeous.
The dye is really magical.
Enough. Stop looking, go back to work.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
It's exactly the same.
It's really exactly the same.
Thank goodness.
My wish has finally come true.
Miss Lu, the cloth is not dry yet.
Just now, you said that you are familiar with this silk.
You even said that it's exactly the same.
I remember
I was not born as nothing. idiom
In the past, I could have been considered a rich person.
I would feel forced to show of all my nice things.
I finally understand now.
When I helped Cai Hong to buy her family mansion,
you were very supportive of it.
This piece of silk, to you, is just like what the Wu mansion meant to Cai Hong.
They hold your beautiful memories in them.
I just remembered
it was also the most tender moment.
I can now understand why you desired the secret formula.
Sometimes, I really envy Cai Hong.
Because of her, you don't hesitate in the price
to help her keep her memories.
There is also this tender moment.
But I...
only feel pain now
and to want to snatch it.
Don't you already have it?
Zhou Shao Tian.
I have something to ask you.
Can you answer me truthfully?
Speak.
Where am I lacking compared to Wu Cai Hong?
Why can't I meet a man
like you?
Someone who is willing to risk his life for my tender memories.
Don't you have the Military Governor?
In this rotten man's eyes,
I'm not a human being.
I'm just a part of his many women.
Someone to get rid of with as I age.
I wonder how I got through all these years.
In the past,
I was also from a noble family.
You could even say that I held a higher status than Wu Cai Hong.
But I had no choice.
I was forced.
When my parents died,
I could only depend on myself
to slowly
become like who I am today.
Don't say that.
You also used your own capability
to get what you want?
Isn't that so?
Yes.
I have already gotten what I wanted.
I don't care about the others.
Mr Zhou.
Now that I have gotten the secret formula,
congratulations. You should congratulate me too.
Jiang Yu, that rascal, is very sly
but he can't escape this time.
What a beautiful piece of cloth.
Mr Zhou.
Let's try it one more time.
If there is no problem, let's start production in the factory.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Jiang Yu didn't lie to me. What he said was true.
What should we do in the future?
We need to feed our families. I have children and elders to take care of.
Where do you plan to go? I will go with you.
Miss Fang is here.
Miss Fang.
Miss Fang. What should we do? We need to survive.
There is something we need to tell you. We are preparing to resign.
- Resign?
- Yes.
You are doing fine. Why are you resigning?
We heard Mr. Jiang got pulled into a lawsuit.
This is not a small matter.
How long can I last here? Ling Long will fold soon.
That's right.
Miss Fang. We are commoners.
We need to take care of our children and elders.
We can only back out.
Miss Fang, please don't blame us.
My apologies. Let's go.
Wait. Don't leave first.
Listen to me first.
My brother was framed. He didn't kill anyone.
He will be cleared and back soon.
Miss Fang, Mr Jiang has treated us very well.
We know that he is a good person
but being locked up by the law is not a game.
We already heard that many clients want to cancel their orders.
If no one works with us, we will lose our business.
What the point of us staying here?
That's right, Miss Fang.
We are saying our goodbyes to you based on our good relationship.
Please take care of yourself.
Everyone, listen to me. Don't leave.
Wait. Listen to me. My brother was framed.
He really didn't kill anyone.
Listen to me. Don't leave.
Don't leave.
My brother was framed. He didn't kill anyone.
Come back.
My brother didn't kill anyone.
What should I do?
Brother, it's all my fault.
I harmed you and Ling Long.
What should I do now
to protect the Ling Long that you worked so hard to reclaim?
- Brother Shao Tian.
- What's wrong?
Brother Shao Tian. Jiang Yu is not my father's killer. He didn't kill my father.
Cai Hong, don't be anxious. Take your time to tell me.
Let me prove it to you.
What are you doing? What is she doing?
What's wrong?
- Is she crazy?
- That's right. What is Miss Wu doing?
Cai Hong. What are you trying to do?
I only want to prove to you...
What's going on?
What is this for?
I don't know what is going on.
Why is the colour running? What's going on?
The colour in our cloths have never run.
Jiang Yi used his memories to write down the formula
but he didn't have the last step.
With Jiang Yi's final step,
the colour ran
because he didn't know the last step.
The complete secret formula is with my father.
So to say, Jiang Yu didn't get this secret formula.
He didn't kill my father either.
Fang Fei Fei gave me this secret formula
which was written by Jiang Yu himself?
- Yes.
Miss.
Jiang Yu said that he memorised the secret formula when he was young.
It's just that the last step was recorded in the last formula.
It will only to be passed down to him when he turned eighteen years old.
- The secret formula is missing one last step.
- Jiang Yu really doesn't have the secret formula?
Jiang Yu didn't have the secret formula in the first place.
Where is the secret formula?
Brother Shao Tian. Let's find Director Chen
and tell him that Jiang Yu is innocent.
Cai Hong. Let the police investigate this first.
If Jiang Yu is really innocent, they will release him.
We don't need them to investigate. Since we already know the truth,
we just need to explain to them and let them release him first.
- But it's a bit complicated now. We don't know anything yet...
- I don't have time.
I'm going to save him.
Cai Hong!
Zhou Shao Tian!
We have more important task to do.
What do you think of this incident today?
Does Jiang Yu really not have the secret formula
or did he give us a fake secret formula?
What happened today was an accident.
Jiang Yu is very sly.
Let's not talk about this first.
The guard at Jiang Yu's cell is my informant.
He overheard Jiang Yu's conversation with Wu Cai Hong.
Jiang Yu merely told her that he didn't have the secret formula.
Cai Hong still went to see Jiang Yu.
Can't you set aside your feelings for that woman first?
Is this important now?
What's important to me now is to know whether Jiang Yu is telling the truth.
And whether he is holding the secret formula?
Wait a minute.
I'm looking for Director Chen.
Director Chen has gone out. He probably won't be back today.
But I need to see him for something very urgent.
Just wait and tell him tomorrow.
Jiang Yu has been framed. Could you release him?
Whether Jiang Yu has been framed or not, we will investigate it ourselves.
If everyone is like you came here to handle the case,
what would you need the police for?
But I'm telling the truth. He didn't kill my father.
Please release him.
Why are you creating a fuss here. This is the police station.
Go home now. If he is not guilty, we will definitely release him.
He was really framed.
Leave.
This is Miss Lu's instructions
but you must keep watch of security and don't make any mistakes.
Did you hear me?
Okay. Please tell Miss Lu not to worry. We will do as we are told.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Are you really going to punish me?
Let me tell you.
Whatever we ask you now, you better tell us the truth
-otherwise you will feel the pain on your flesh.
-I do not know who gave you the right to hurt me,
Who put you up to this? Who wants to harm me?
It's useless for you to call for help now.
If you don't want to suffer, answer whatever we ask you.
Perhaps, we may even spare your life.
I already told you many times that I didn't kill Wu Hong Da.
We don't care about who killed Wu Hong Da.
We only want to find out where Wu Hong Da's secret formula is.
I don't know. I didn't take the secret formula.
It seems you are trying to play tough guy.
Speak!
Where is the secret formula?
Aren't you going to talk or not? If you don't, I will beat you to death.
Let's see who will last longer.
Talk!
Father, I have wronged the Jiang family.
I have wronged you and mother.
You raised and treated me like your own daughter.
I caused brother to be jailed now.
I caused Ling Long to go bankrupt.
Brother said that he didn't blame me
but the more he tells me this,
I find it harder to accept in my heart.
Mom still doesn't know anything about this.
Someone needs to take care of the family
but
I don't know how to face this.
Father, tell me.
What should I do?
I'm giving you water to let you come to your senses
to think carefully over where you keep the secret formula.
Do you know who I am?
If you have the guts,
just beat me to death.
Only you and us know about this incident tonight.
If you die, we will just report tomorrow that you committed suicide.
You better think about yourself and don't worry about us.
Mr Jiang.
Heroes don't feel immediate loss. We don't want to kill you.
We only want the secret formula. I'm going to ask you one more time.
Where is the secret formula?
Since you are using so much energy to find out where the secret formula is,
you must definitely know about the grudges between the Wu and Jiang families.
Let me tell you this now.
When Wu Hong Da died that day, other than me,
Zhao Shao Tian and Old Cai met him too.
Thus, if the secret formula is not with me,
it's possible that it could be with Zhou Shao Tian or Old Cai.
Did you hear what he said?
You aren't looking in the right spot.
If there was really a secret formula,
why would I keep it secret? Jiang Yu is scheduled to be executed.
If this is the case, wouldn't I be a fool?
Since we do not know it, how can we judge?
I think I heard him say they were going to beat him with a bar.
He is only simply just saying it.
Fine, let's just watch.
Mr Jiang.
If you don't tell the truth, you will really lose your life.
The secret formula is really not with me.
It's useless even if you beat me to death.
Father.
I just realised that Jiang Yu is not the killer.
This is considered good news too. Right?
In any case, the grudges between our families can be resolved.
I have decided to find Director Chen tomorrow
to release Jiang Yu as soon as possible.
Our Wu family already owe the Jiang family a lot.
I misjudged them unjustly.
But father, don't worry.
I will definitely
find the person who harmed you as soon as possible.
You must help me.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Miss Lu.
What are you waiting for? Do it!
Wait.
It's getting late. We should pack up now.
Jiang Yu has already been beaten into this state.
If he really has the secret formula, he would have spilled it out earlier.
If you continue to beat him, he will really lose his life.
What you want is the secret formula, not to kill him.
Miss Lu. You must not beat him to death.
Mr Jiang is also an influential person in the community.
Moreover, he has a very good relationship with Police Chief Ting.
Let him go or things will end badly.
Huzhou has already lost Wu Hong Da.
If Jiang Yu died without any known reasons,
I'm afraid the entire community won't be able to let it go.
Jiang Yu has been beaten into this condition and he's still not talking.
Could it be that the secret formula is really not with him?
I was skeptical before
but now I believe Jiang Yu.
Don't tell me that Jiang Yu really didn't kill Wu Hong Da?
But what we can be sure of is that the secret formula was with Wu Hong Da on the day of the incident.
He was definitely upstairs when he fell.
The secret formula must have been with him.
But it went missing.
Don't tell me that Jiang Yu didn't do it.
The day that Wu Hong Da died, he only saw three people.
Jiang Yu, Old Cai
and you.
I really didn't take the secret formula.
Looking at the other options, there is only one possibility.
The secret formula is with Old Cai.
I'm asking you now. Where is Old Cai?
How would I know where he is?
I say, Shao Tian. Stop pretending.
You and Old Cai first stole the money from Ling Long.
I helped you to launder the money.
You trick others but not me.
Since you have hidden Old Cai that well,
even Director Chen and Jiang Yu can't find him.
But if I want to call Old Cai out,
you only just need to tell me.
That won't work. Old Cai won't show up.
You don't want to find Old Cai?
But if you don't hand over Old Cai,
I may tell Wu Cai Hong that
you are the real owner of Rong Da.
The money that you used to established Rong Da was from Long Ling.
Are you threatening me?
When we first started to be friends, you should have already known that
a day like this would definitely come.
Thus, I will advise you to be smart.
You should also know that
I only care about the secret formula and not about Old Cai.
As long as you are willing to help me, Old Cai's recipe can be yours too.
We both get what we need,
I can give you a deadline.
Go in.
You asked for it.
Stop. What are you doing?
I'm here to see Jiang Yu. Please let me go in.
Who are you? Jiang Yu is our criminal. He is guilty of murder.
You can't just see him whenever you want.
But I went in yesterday.
That was because it was yesterday. You could enter because I wasn't on duty.
Let me tell you, I'm fair and transparent.
Jiang Yu is not a killer.
He was framed.
Nine out of ten people here were framed,
but the truth is that no one was framed.
Don't waste your time talking to me.
Mr Policeman. Will this do?
Please let me go in for a while.
If you had the money, just give it to me. Why waste my time?
Go in.
Jiang Yu! What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Don't you have any laws here? How could you beat him into this state?
Jiang Yu, wake up.
How could he have been injured like this? I'm going to report to my superior.
Go now!
Jiang Yu.
How could you be beaten into this state?
It's my fault. I should have saved you yesterday.
I clearly knew that you were framed.
Jiang Yu. How do you feel now?
- I'm fine.
- You are still saying that you are fine?
You have been beaten up until you became in this condition
Why did the police beat you up?
- It wasn't them.
- Who then?
It's those people who wanted the secret formula.
Brother Shao Tian?
Don't move. Jiang Yu.
Jiang Yu. What you told me yesterday,
I already did the test. You didn't lie to me.
I will definitely find a way to get you out of here.
I'm going to find Superintendent Li. Wait for me.
Okay, get this done.
Superintendent Li. Please save Jiang Yu.
Miss Wu.What's wrong with Jiang Yu?
Jiang Yu was tortured last night.
He has injuries all over his body now. Please save him.
What? I only locked Jiang Yu in the detention cell.
Who had the guts to torture him in my station?
Jiang Yu was framed. He really didn't have the secret formula.
He didn't use it at the silk contest.
Those people who tortured him wanted to force him to hand over the secret formula.
Enough, Miss Wu. Let's go to the detention cell to save him now. You can tell me about the rest on the way there.
Let's go.
- Police Chief.
- Chen Zhi Jie.
What's going on?
It was under my management. The guards on duty for last night went missing
but I will definitely catch them and bring them back.
Enough. Send men to protect Jiang Yu now.
Report to me later about the incident today.
Both of you, keep guard here.
Director Chen.
- Director Chen.
- Miss Fang.
How is my brother?
Miss Fang. Don't panic.
Your brother's life is not in danger. The doctor is administrating medicine now.
Thank you.
Wu Cai Hong.
What wrong did the Jiang family do to you?
Why must you keep harming us?
Aren't you afraid of retribution?
Sorry.
What's the use of apologising?