The Cage of Love
Episode 9
Help me to put it on.
You agree?
Wu Cai Hong!
By the way, Brother Shao Tian,
I just remembered that Cai Yue wanted me to help her with her homework. I'll leave first.
- I will take you there.
- No need.
Cai Hong has decided to leave Ling Long
for Fu Sheng. In the future, don't look for her anymore.
It seems like I didn't allow her to leave Ling Long.
It's not important whether you did or not.
What's important is that she has already decided.
Furthermore, she is my girlfriend now.
She is only just a girlfriend?
So what?
We will get married soon
and manage Fu Sheng together.
What are you afraid of?
What else can you do?
Make a guess.
No matter what you do,
Cai Hong is mine.
Wu Long.
Wu Long. Where are you? Come out now.
Wu Long. Be good. Where are you?
Listen to me carefully.
If you don't find the cat,
no one is allowed to sleep.
Go and look now.
Wu Long.
Wu Long, be good.
I found the cat.
Young Master, I found Wu Long.
Look.
Let's see where you run to.
Aunt.
Are you angry?
I told you to get my reading glasses.
I never thought I wouldn't see you again.
It's clear that
you didn't place me in your heart.
Looks like someone is really angry.
I will only be able to enjoy this alone then.
I went to Luo Tuo Bridge to buy Rose Candy early in the morning.
It wasn't easy to get this.
It smells so good.
Looking at it makes me salivate.
It must be really sweet and delicious.
It's sweet and soft.
I think I can finish this entire box.
No, I must have one now.
If you finish eating everything, what is left for me?
Look.
Wench.
Come, Aunt. Let's eat this together. Okay?
Here. Does it taste good?
Just eat it, Aunt.
That's right, Aunt. You look much better when you smile.
You must smile more. Your mood will improve.
Cai Hong.
Stay with me and talk more.
Look. When no one is with me,
it's so boring.
I know and I want to
but in the future, I will be helping my boyfriend at his factory.
It's not easy for him to run his business.
I would like to do my best to help him.
Cai Hong. You must remember to visit me.
Of course.
Wait until my boyfriend's business is stable, I will visit you often.
You must keep your word.
If you don't believe me, we can cross our fingers.
You really treat me like a kid.
Do you dare to say that you are not?
I wonder whose son is so lucky
who will marry such a good wife like you.
I'm not married yet.
You always joke with me.
It's getting late. I should be going home soon.
Aunt. Remember to go out more
and take in more fresh air. It's good for your health.
I know. Leave now.
I will take good care of myself.
With your concerns, I'm already very happy and satisfied.
Go now.
Take good care of yourself.
I'm leaving.
Wu Cai Hong.
I won't accept your resignation.
Come back to work immediately.
What are you doing?
I have a meeting tomorrow morning.
Make the arrangements for me.
I will no longer accept your insults and let you torment me.
You better find someone else.
I will change my attitude.
I know now.
You want me to stay at Ling Long
because it is a past time of yours (to torment).
If this is the case,
why don't I go to Fu Sheng to do real work
and investigate my father's case.
Why do you think that I killed your father?
Don't worry.
If you really killed my father,
I won't let you off.
Don't you find this strange?
The audit of the five warehouses inside
the ledger was burnt by someone.
Old Cai disappeared and you went to talk to Old Cai's wife.
When you went to find his lover, she was murdered.
It's one coincidence after another.
Don't tell me the third time was also a coincidence?
What exactly is on your mind?
Only those who are close to you
would know your movements.
The person is always one step ahead, destroying evidence.
Don't place too much trust on those near you.
Well said.
Ling Long's ledger, Old Cai's wife and lover, these are not coincidences.
Why would I believe what you said?
I will never trust you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Sis. Since you came back today, you have been unhappy.
Are you not used to being with Brother Shao Tian?
No.
Since you are here, sit down for a while.
Cai Yun. Frankly, I know that
ever since Dad passed away, you and stepmom have suffered.
Who says so? The one who suffered the most was you.
Blame me...
for not having understudied Dad in the past.
If not, it wouldn't have been so easy for Ling Long to fall into other's hands.
Don't place all the burdens on your shoulders.
Arent you getting better now?
Brother Shao Tian also said that you are good with business now.
Our family will definitely get better.
Yes.
Sis.
You have really accepted to be Brother Shao Tian's girlfriend?
In the past, when Dad wanted you to marry Brother Shao Tian,
you said that you wanted to regard him as just a brother.
Do you love him now?
When did you start to understand love?
Now there may only be females in my class, but we read Xu's poems.
Of course, I understand.
Sister, your love for Brother Shao Tianis just like poetry.
In my mind now,
what if the poetry from Xu's poems are wrong.
I only want to think simply. Brother Shao Tian is very good to me.
I would like to be good to him too.
I want to find the killer of Dad as soon as possible now
and then learn all about business
so that you and aunt will live well.
But after such a long time,
will you still be able to find the killer?
As long as I don't give up, there is hope.
Brother.
I overheard your conversation with Cai Hong today at the hospital.
You are still worried about her?
- No wonder, the way you treat her...
-I am not.
I want to advise you.
Don't forget that Dad died a terrible death.
- Don't forget that the Wu family brought us pain...
- I don't need you to remind me every day on how Dad died.
Why are you still not drawing the line between Wu Cai Hong then?
I already said that
I want to investigate who embezzled Ling Long's money.
I think you are worried about Wu Cai Hong instead.
You want to help her to find out the truth.
What I want to find out is who is the killer next to Wu Cai Hong.
Think about it.
If the most trusted and closest person to Wu Cai Hong
is the killer of her father,
to her, this will be
a great irony and conflict.
This would be like God giving the Wu family
an even worse penalty.
Her closest and most trusted person?
Could it be Wu Cai Hong's sister?
Mrs Wu is not Wu Cai Hong's biological mother.
If Wu Hong Da were to leave the family assets to the eldest daughter,
she would have motive to do it.
It's also not Mrs Wu.
The closest person to Wu Cai Hong?
Could it be Zhou Shao Tian?
Without any confirmed evidence,
it is too hard to judge.
Brother.
Are you serious about this?
Everything that you are doing is to make Wu Cai Hong suffer?
If you are feeling bored,
please spend more time with Mom. Okay?
Come and take a look. The buns are hot.
The vegetables are fresh.
Let me tell you. The imported products from this shop are really great.
Once you see them, you won't want to leave.
I'm not going. I don't use make-up.
What's wrong? Didn't you use to like this in the past?
My family now...
you should know that my sister is having a hard time making money.
I don't need this anymore.
Cai Yun. We haven't gone shopping for a long time.
Just go with me.
Ah Xue.
It's not that I don't want to go with you. But...
I understand. Let's just go in and browse.
We are only just browsing. We don't need to buy anything.
Okay?
Let's go.
Sister Fei Fei. What do you think of this colour?
- It's pretty.
- Let me take a look.
It's pretty. This is the one.
But it's too expensive.
Let me think about it.
It's a bit expensive.
It's okay. If you like it, I will pay for it. I will get one for each for us. What do you think?
Really? Sister Fei Fei is not like the rest.
No. It's Mrs Jiang who is not like the rest.
Mrs Jiang. These two words have such a nice ring to them.
Don't talk nonsense. If Brother hears this, we will be in trouble.
Who says we are talking nonsense? You and Boss Jiang...
No, you and your brother are in fact friends since childhood.
The position of Mrs Jiang is definitely yours.
That's right. It's no difference if we call her this.
She will be called this in the future. What's the difference?
- Mrs Jiang.
- Enough.
Mrs Jiang. Our blessed life in the future will depend on you.
In the future, we have to stick close to Madam Jiang.
She will be constantly happy with her joyous welfare.
- Mrs Jiang...
- Shouldn't we look around the shop? I heard the new lipsticks were delivered.
Didn't you always want to go see it?
Really? Just take a look. It's okay if we don't buy any.
Okay.
Miss, which do you like?
We didn't expect you to.
This colour is really pretty!
We are buddies. Why are you saying this?
Isn't that the second daughter of the Wu family?
Her sister was your brother's ex-secretary.
Didn't her family go bankrupt?
How does she still have the money to go shopping?
So, she is Wu Cai Yun.
Just as the old saying,"Enemies are bound to meet on a narrow road".
Isn't this the second daughter of the Wu family?
Which Wu family?
It's that Wu Hong Da who went bankrupt and killed himself.
She is his younger daughter.
Cai Yun. Let's go. Just ignore her.
You are broke and you still have the money to buy luxurious items?
That's really something.
If she doesn't have money, she can just browse around.
I think the products suit her better.
Ah Xue. I have something going on.
Let's leave first.
Miss.
I just saw that girl
steal a lipstick and put it in her bag.
I think you should check whether it's from your shop.
Go after her. I will mind the shop.
Okay, tell the boss now.
Stop there.
Stop there. Someone saw you stealing from the shop.
You can't leave.
Nonsense.
We didn't.
You didn't? Open your bag.
I didn't. You are wrong.
I'm going to report you.
Yes, I'm going to report you for a crime.
You can eat anything but you can't talk nonsense.
Since you said that you didn't steal anything, open your bag and let me check.
Why are you so unreasonable?
Do all customers who go into your shop subject to having their bags checked?
Check everyone then. Why do you insist on only checking me?
Call your boss here.
No need. Our boss is already here.
Boss. She stole from your shop. We caught her but she is still not admitting to it.
Miss.
Boss Ku. You are here in time.
She is making irresponsible accusations. She claims I was stealing.
I didn't.
Miss Wu.
We just took an inventory count
and someone definitely saw you taking the lipstick.
This lipstick is imported from France.
It's a small shop. We can't compensate for it.
Your items are expensive.
Even if I liked it, I wouldn't steal it.
By saying this, you are insulting us.
Miss Wu.
I know that you used high ended products in the past.
Please don't be a hot head. don't get angry.
This must have something to do with... This must be her only solution.
Why don't we do this? Return the lipstick to me
and I will gift you a cheaper one.
This way, we won't make a mountain out of a mole hill.
What do you mean?
You are using slander against me today.
You want to check, right?
Okay. Call the police to come here.
If you can't find anything, I will sue you for framing me.
Miss Wu. If you really don't want to co-operate,
I will call for the police then.
Okay, call them.
- Sister Fei Fei. Will she be captured by the police?
- Do you think I'm afraid?
Look, the police are here.
Move aside.
What's going on?
They are planting lies against me.
Sir. I didn't. It's like this.
Someone saw her taking a lipstick from our shop.
Sir, he wronged me.
(told lies)
- I have not wronged her.
- Alright, Alright. Let me investigate.
Miss. Since you said that you didn't steal it, show me the proof.
He wronged me.
(telling lies)
Open your bag. If it's not there,
I will deal with him for not being fair to you.
See if you are agreeable to this.
Okay then. Let's do this.
If there really isn't anything there, I will apologise to her.
Okay, check then.
- Is this it?
- Yes, this is it.
Sorry, come with us.
I didn't steal anything. I really didn't.
Ah Xue. You know about this. I have been with you all along.
I didn't steal anything.
I don't know anything at all.
I was only shopping. I didn't notice what she was doing.
Miss, you've been caught red-handed.
Come with us to the police station.
I have been framed. I didn't steal anything.
- Take her away.
- I have been framed.
I have been framed.
I didn't steal anything.
I didn't steal anything. I really didn't.
- Where is Wu Cai Yun?
- She is over there.
Cai Yun.
Mom. I really didn't steal anything. They framed me.
Alright. Alright. I will deal with them.
Hey. My daughter would never steal.
You must have gotten it wrong.
She was caught red-handed.
We took out the lipstick from her bag.
There were many witnesses.
I don't know how the lipstick ended up in my bag.
I really don't know.
Yes. It's only just a lipstick.
My daughter would never steal. Someone must be behind it.
Yes. You must have gotten it wrong.
My sister would never steal.
- Stop crying.
- Sir, about this.
I would like to ask.
Since you saw it,
we won't deny that the lipstick was in her bag.
But I would also like to know,
did anyone personally witness her stealing it?
- It seems so... - You should call the witness to stand here then.
That's right.
Sir. Based on your experience,
look at her carefully.
Does she look like a thief who would steal?
Chief, is there legal grounds for this?
Can you see if we can do this?
We will pay for this lipstick and consider that we bought it.
We don't need to make it hard on her anymore.
You have also been troubled enough. This will accommodate everyone.
If the victim is willing to agree, that would be good to resolve the matter privately.
But if he is not agreeable, there is nothing we can do.
Please wait. I will make the call.
We will have to trouble you then.
Everything's fine.
Brother Shao Tian. I really didn't steal it.
Don't panic. We know.
First calm down.
That's right, Cai Yun. Don't panic. There definitely will be a solution.
There definitely will be a solution.
It's okay, if they don't reach a compromise,
- I understand.
- I will go to the shop to talk to the boss.
Everything's fine. Don't cry.
Alright, the seller was quick to resolve the issue.
After some small formalities, you can take her home.
Thank you for your trouble.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Cai Yun. If you want to cry, just cry.
It will make you feel better.
Sis.
Enough, Cai Yun.
I know that you have suffered
but I know that this matter is already over.
Isn't that so?
Sis. I really didn't steal it.
You still don't believe me.
Of course, I believe you.
Stop crying. There is only one thing I have to know. What happened between you.
Stop crying. Crying won't solve anything.
Ah Xue told me to go with her to the shop.
You should know that after what happened to our family,
no one is willing to be my friend anymore.
Except Ah Xue.
She asked me to accompany her to the shop.
I originally thought that if I just browsed, I would't spend any money.
But they said that I stole the lipstick.
I was not so convinced even when the police were called
because I didn't steal anything.
But subsequently, when the police opened my bag, the lipstick was in there.
- Okay, I get it.
- I also don't know how it got in there.
Do you know the people there? How do they look like?
I don't know them. They are all from the rich families.
There was one who kept watching me.
Sis. I swear that I really didn't steal it.
Enough, Cai Yun. I believe you. You are a good girl.
Don't worry. I will investigate this thoroughly
and prove your innocence. Okay, stop crying.
Okay, I know. I don't blame you.
Boss Gu. This is just a small gesture.
You are too polite.
My sister caused you some trouble yesterday.
About the incident, regardless of who is right,
I would also like your store to not get a bad name.
I'm here today to apologise.
Miss.
Frankly, after thinking about this, we feel bad.
In the past, your father helped this shop a lot.
Hence, I...
Don't talk about the past anymore.
It's just that my sister is still young.
She is mature in our family.
I think she would never steal.
What happened yesterday?
Was there a misunderstanding?
Actually, I wasn't here yesterday.
I heard about this from two of my staff.
They said that your sister met some ladies here
and they had an exchange of words.
When your sister wanted to leave, a lady told the shop staff that
she stole something.
Second Miss?
Do you now that lady?
Who is she?
It seems like her family name is Fang. She's Miss Fang.
I'm not very clear about what her name is.
but she was very generous.
A few of her friends were joking with her
and kept calling her Mrs Jiang.
Mrs Jiang?
Miss Fang?
That's right. I have her receipt from yesterday.
Xiao Wu.
Take out all the receipts from yesterday.
Boss. Here it is.
This is it.
She bought these three lipsticks.
Jiang Yu.
To what end will you go with your hatred of my family?
Looks like Zhou Shao Tian didn't take good care of you.
You look haggered
and your temper is flared up even more.
I'm asking you a question.
Do not challenge my limits.
After toying with me,
you find this interesting, right?
If there is anything, you can take it out on me.
I'm not afraid of being accused but you should clarify everything first.
Accused?
You let Fang Fei Fei steal a lipstick and frame my sister for it.
She is only just a young girl. How could you do this to her?
So, you are sure that I did it.
If it's not you, who else would it be?
This only proves that Ling Long bought three lipsticks from Little Paris.
I would advise you to think clearly about this.
If you don't want your sister to be famous,
the best solution is to keep it (the incidence) a low profile.
So,
you are admitting to this.
Fine.
Even if I did it,
so what?
They said that humans were born kind.
I always thought that you weren't that bad
but the truth is the proof. I was wrong.
Moreover, I was gravely mistaken.
Being born as Wu Hong Da's daughter
is your life's biggest mistake.
You took my father's company.
Since you even dare to say this...
Even if my father
offended you in business dealings,
did you ever think that my sister is still young?
If this were to leak out, how would you expect to live?
Jiang Yu. Let me tell you.
If you dare to touch my family again,
I will never let you off.
So, in your heart,
I'm really this kind of person.
Sorry.
You have never been in my heart.
You will never be in future either.
I think what Brother Shao Tian said is right.
Someone who is so cold and selfish like you,
Ling Long will go bankrupt sooner or later.
Just wait and see then.
Let's see whether Ling Long or Fu Sheng will go bankrupt first.
Brother, this Hangzhou White Peony root just arrived today. Try it.
What's wrong, brother? Who made you angry?
Regarding the Wu family issue,
you were the one behind it, right?
That's right.
- Don't do such things in the future again.
- Why?
Wu Hong Da destroyed our home.
Father was framed by him.
An eye for an eye.
I wanted to give them a taste of their own medicine.
You are using such a tactic to take revenge.
What's the difference between you and Wu Hong Da?
"Trying to punish the wicked is like putting yourself on a bad horse."
What right do you have to hate Wu Hong Da? Tell me!
I hate them.
I hate them for causing father to die.
I hate them for causing mom to be sick.
I hate them for causing you to be unhappy for many years.
Why?
Fei Fei. Why did you become like this?
I suddenly remember when you were young.
A little bird in our house was killed by a maid. You cried for a long time.
You cried miserably.
Ever since Dad passed away,
all these years, you have been helping me to take care of my mother.
Because of your existence,
you turned this house into a family.
Fei Fei. I have always hoped that you would be a very kind girl.
I really don't want you to dirty your hands because of revenge.
Thus, all those matters,
let me take the burden alone.
Brother.
When Father took me in when my parents died,
he gave me a family.
At the most difficult time,
you didn't get rid of me.
Without the Jiang family,
and with you, I wouldn't have grown up peacefully.
I will always remember the family's great kindness.
For you,
I could do anything for the Jiang family.
If you still want me to be your brother,
don't get involved.
Thus, regarding everything,
I will make the arrangements.
What is the progress of this matter?
I have already done according to your instructions.
There has been talk with some of the suppliers.
We only need our suppliers not to supply to Fu Sheng.
Thus, starting from today,
Fu Sheng won't be able to obtain any materials for dyeing.
If this continues, it's just a matter of time before Fu Sheng goes bankrupt.
Unless Zhou Shao Tian spends a big sum of money
and imports the materials.
Please come to the boss with anything major.
and let them be enlightened.
The Huzhou weaving and dying sector has become this way.
Moreover, you have already seen Jiang Yu's underhanded tactics.
Jiang Yu buys cheap
This time, he got involved with the suppliers of the dye materials.
Yes. He is sabotaging my family now
but he won't be able to harm your positions.
Thus, I feel that
Ling Long's real ambition is
to occupy the entire area of Huzhou.
Boss Zhou. Your words are logical.
In your opinion, what should we do?
Among all of us, none of us are his match.
But if we were to join forces together,
we will be able to poach his clients.
Even though we can't harm Ling Long, we should at least send him a warning
so that he wouldn't dare to harm such a small shop like us.
Stable prices will inevitably lead to increased pressure to reduce earnings.
Especially when we are doing business to make profits.
Yes. We need to support our families too.
Everyone.
If we join forces together,
we will benefit from the purchase of raw materials.
What do you think?
Join forces together?
The prices of raw materials will be reduced.
Yes, this is a good idea.
Even though our margins will be lower
we will be able to poach even more clients from Ling Long.
Sales will go in a straight line up and our total profits will not be reduced.
It will be even higher.
It's sound logical. It's a good idea.
Dear everyone,
when my father was alive, he helped you a lot.
Now that Fu Sheng is facing difficulties, we hope that you will help us.
We must work as one
and resist the evil.
Okay, Miss. Count me in.
Tell us what we should do. We will listen to you.
If everyone agree, let's sign the consent form.
Okay, I will sign.
Count me in.
- I will sign too.
- Thank you.
Count me in.
Me too.
I will sign too.
Please take a look around.
These are Ling Long's new products.
Regardless of the colours, patterns or textures,
they are made with delicate care.
Please feel free to look around.
It's really not bad.
This is made well. Look at the exquisite work.
You have a good eye.
In terms of color, gray is the hardest
followed by cool colors.
Mr. Jiang does a cool color treatment that is very cathartic. full of emotions
Really makes me open my eyes.
You are over praising me.
I wonder if the colour will run if it gets wet.
It can't be that you don't believe in our products.
No, Boss Jiang. Your products are the best in Huzhou
but your products are the most expensive.
But if we don't do the water test and we buy it,
inevitably something could happen.
Boss Jiang. I know about Ling Long's rules
but it's really hard to do business now.
Our small businesses also want to avoid risk.
Why don't you reconsider?
We will reconsider too.
Let's compromise.
Brother. Why don't we let them try the water test?
Dear everyone.
We don't have a tryout policy in Ling Long.
I know that there are many small and medium shops
who are willing to do the water tests.
That is because they only sell locally.
The process is simple.
Ling Long does business throughout the country.
If I were to break the rule today,
how would I face foreign merchants?
That's right.
The prices at Ling Long are definitely more expensive.
Higher quality.
No one can be compared to ours.
This is the first we have worked with some of you. For the rest we have worked several times.
Those who have worked with us,
I believe, know very well the exquisite high quality fabrics here.
As for those who are working with us for the first time, I will guarantee that after going through this,
you will definitely have no regrets.
Boss Jiang, you also offer a final inspection of the product.
Yes. I heard that
Boss Zhou of Fu Sheng
orders are intended to be made of this.
Let's go to visit the Miss of former Mr. Wu of Ling Long.