The Cage of Love
Episode 23
- Wait for me.
- Okay, Boss Jiang.
I know you don't want to see me here.
I will ask you one last time.
Did you harm my father?
Aren't you already determined to kick me out of Huzhou?
As long as you tell me that you didn't harm my father,
I will talk to the Governor about this contest.
This way, you and Shao Tian don't have to withdraw from the dyeing industry.
You are that worried about him?
He only lost one round of the contest and he wants be to withdraw from the contest?
What did you take the silk contest as?
Was it to make you happy? Was it a game for you?
You wanted me to take part, I took part. You want me to withdraw and I should withdraw?
Miss Wu.
Don't think too highly of yourself.
Are you hoping that you can force me to use my formula by taking part in this contest?
Stop dreaming.
Fine.
Since you are that confident,
let's see how you are going to win the third round.
If you lose, what I want is
is not as simple as your withdrawal.
After putting in such a high stake, the loser will escape?
It's not that easy.
Wu Cai Hong did so many disadvantageous things to you.
Why can't you just forget her?
As for me, I have always been by your side and you have never noticed me.
Young Master, Miss. You are back.
Young Master, Miss. Please have your tea.
We are now even at the silk contest.
The third round must be a victory.
Brother. What should we do next?
What else can we do except to win.
If Zhou Shao Tian loses,
would Wu Cai Hong leave Huzhou with him?
Zhou Shao Tian wants to kick me out of Huzhou so that he can get Wu Cai Hong.
In any case, anyone who goes against me, I will make him pay for it.
What do you mean?
Even if it's Ling Long
or Wu Cai Hong,
Zhou Shao Tian wants them both.
Brother, don't forget that
Wu Cai Hong is Wu Hong Da's...
Don't think too much. I'm only saying that I won't let him have Wu Cai Hong.
I didn't say that I wanted Wu Cai Hong.
I'm very clear that
it's impossible for her and me.
Okay then.
I'm going back.
Why didn't you knock before you came in?
Sorry, Miss. I forgot.
You don't observe the rules at all. Leave now.
Yes, Miss.
She is not even the young mistress of the house or a real lady.
She is only someone who was adopted from the street. What kind of airs is that?
Who knows? She may be the future Young Mistress of this family.
- Our Young Master doesn't have her in his heart.
- How do you know?
I can see that Young Master usually treats her very well.
That's because he is very kind.
I heard the women in the kitchen saying that
our Young Master likes Miss Wu Cai Hong.
Furthermore, Miss Wu Cai Hong can't get along with our Miss.
If she were to join our house as the Young Mistress, she may kick her out.
Even she can't be compared to her.
What are you talking about?
You are getting braver and braver.
You dare to badmouth me?
Who taught you to be more and more disobedient?
Get lost now. Don't let me hear you badmouth me again.
Get lost.
Let's leave now.
Boss Zhou. Did I do it right?
Extremely well.
You did extremely well.
I'm leaving then.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
She is not even the Young Mistress of the house nor is she a true lady.
She is only someone who was adopted from the street. What kind of airs is that?
Our Young Master doesn't have her in his heart.
If she Cai Hongwere to join our house as the Young Mistress, she may kick her out.
She can't be compared to a real lady.
It can't be that I will really lose Brother one day.
I will lose my family.
I already don't have anything in this world.
This is only what I have left.
Isn't Wu Cai Hong back with you now? Why did you call me here again?
I called you out here to ask a favour from you.
Why would I help my brother's rival?
Unless if you want your brother to be together with Cai Hong.
What do you mean?
You should know very well what I meant.
Don't tell me that you can see that your brother has feelings for Cai Hong.
Did you forget about how your brother saved Cai Hong during the Ghost Festival?
If what your brother felt for Cai Hong wasn't love,
why would he risk his life to save someone he has a grudge against?
That's because...
Frankly, I don't really care about the silk contest,
I originally wanted to use this opportunity to defeat your brother.
It won't be that easy.
You are right. It won't be that easy.
Perhaps, this is the only way
for Cai Hong and your brother to never see each other again.
It's also only through this way that Cai Hong will slowly forget your brother.
Even though I had a fair contest with your brother twice
you know very well that I will lose in the last round.
- Why don't you admit defeat then?
- If I lose,
it's fine with me if Rong Da withdraws from Huzhou.
It's just that...
It's just that Cai Hong...
What's wrong with her?
Do you think your brother can give up Cai Hong?
He even resorted to such a tactic as to make Cai Hong his servant.
Do you believe that?
Miss Fang. Does your family lack any servants?
I'm afraid that, this time, he will think of another reason to make Cai Hong stay.
You are wrong.
My brother kept Wu Cai Hong by his side to torment her and let her suffer.
He will never forget the deep grudge between our families.
He has also personally guaranteed that
he will never have any connections with the Wu family again.
Fine. Let's give it a try then.
If I were to win and Ling Long withdraws from the dyeing industry,
this way, you can be with your brother.
But you will wrong your deceased father.
If I lose,
Jiang Yu will definitely take Cai Hong along with him.
I think you don't want these two conclusions.
It's okay if it's Ling Long and Cai Hong too.
Zhou Shao Tian wants both of them.
It won't happen.
Impossible.
I will never let Wu Cai Hong step into the Jiang family again.
Can you be the decision maker?
What do you mean?
Do you think that I'm only just a girl that the Jiang family has adopted and I don't have the right to make decisions?
This is what you mean now. Right?
Miss Fang.
I hope that you can face the reality of the Jiang family.
Yes. What could I do?
As long as it's a fair contest between your brother and I in the final round,
everything will be resolved.
No one needs to leave the dyeing industry in Huzhou.
No one needs to lose any face.
When that time comes, I will take Cai Hong far away from here.
I guarantee that your brother will never see her again.
Really?
Yes.
As long as it's a fair contest between your brother and me in the final round.
How can I help you then?
I know that Jiang Yu wants to win. For the last round,
he will use his secret formula.
Yes, he has plans to do this. He said that as long as he uses the secret formula, he will definitely win.
Give me the secret formula then. Let me have a fair contest with your brother.
I will then sell Rong Da
and use the money to leave for a distant place with Cai Hong.
We will not appear again.
Miss Fang. You are a smart lady.
I won't trick you.
That secret formula is very important
but no matter how important it is, it can only make money for us, it won't bring us happiness.
When Cai Hong and I leave, you will be able to get Jiang Yu.
You will have a family with warmth.
Will you guarantee that after this contest ends, you will never touch Ling Long
and take Cai Hong far away from here, never appearing again?
I guarantee it.
Where is it?
Brother.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's just that...
do you still remember that day when you talked to me about the secret formula?
Why are you suddenly talking about this?
Because I heard those people there talking about it as if it was a legend.
Thus, I would like to take a look at it and see what it's like.
Forget it if I can't take a look. I'm not insisting that I should look at it.
No problem.
Come with me.
This is the Jiang family's secret formula?
Then, with this secret formula, we will win for sure, right?
That's right.
That's great. With this secret formula, we will definitely not lose.
We also won't need to withdraw from Huzhou.
Father.
I don't know if I'm doing the right thing.
You also don't seem to see Wu Hong Da's family entering the Jiang family.
I don't want to see brother in pain again.
I'm not only doing this for myself
but also for brother, for mother and for the security of the Jiang family.
Stop looking, I personally copied it.
Jiang Yu will definitely use the secret formula on the day of the contest.
Of course. My brother will never let you defeat Ling Long.
Don't forget what you promised me.
As long as in the final round,
Jiang Yu uses the secret formula, he will never be able to see Cai Hong again.
Fine.
It is indeed the secret family recipe. I have never seen such a sophisticated process.
Jiang Yu.
Let's see how you are going to overturn this.
Is the secret formula in your hand?
Miss Lu. Why are you here so late in the evening?
You are really amazing. Congratulations. Since you have gotten the secret formula,
what do you plan to do next?
I already told Fang Fei Fei that Jiang Yu must use his secret formula for the final round.
When I first chose to help you, you weren't willing. You are now using this method.
Looks like you have come to your senses.
I'm not like you.
I'm doing this for Cai Hong.
Okay, I know that you are doing this for Cai Hong.
You are forcing Jiang Yu to use his secret formula to prove your innocence and also help Cai Hong find the killer.
Since you have already gotten it, give it to me.
I will let you have it after the contest.
- Why?
- I already talked to Superintendent Chen.
When Jiang Yu uses the secret formula at the contest, the police will arrest him.
Moreover, this secret formula is very important evidence.
You must remember to use the secret formula during the contest.
We can only win with this.
Didn't you use to advise me how to be so anxious?
Because I'm very worried. I'm worried that if we lose,
we will need to leave Huzhou.
All our hard work here would be over.
In any case, don't worry.
I guarantee that we won't lose.
Let's go.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Do you think Jiang Yu will use the secret formula?
Do you hope that he will use the secret formula or do you hope that he won't?
If Jiang Yu uses the secret formula, we will have the evidence of the killer.
Even if he wins the contest, he will go to jail.
If...
if he doesn't use the secret formula, I will definitely win.
Let's set off.
Brother. Let me see what it is.
It's such an important item. Of course, we should leave it to the last.
Brother, I'm your sister and not an outsider. Let me take a look at it.
You will know when the time comes.
Miss Lu. You are here. Why don't I see General Du here today?
He has something going on. He won't be here.
Official matters are more important. Miss Lu, please go upstairs.
- Governor.
- Did you buy it?
Yes. I bought $200 for Ling Long.
Okay, you may leave first.
This time, I must win back everything.
Everyone. The third round of the contest starts now.
We will invite our only judge for today.
President Mr. Zhang.
Let's give him an applause to welcome him.
What is this contest turning into?
How could there only be one judge?
What do you know? Shut up.
President Mr. Zhang, himself was the one who placed and order before. This is perfect.
He will be personally judging today.
Stop worrying and relax.
Everyone. During the first and second rounds of this contest,
Boss Jiang and Boss Zhou came to a draw.
Thus, this third round will be the most crucial.
Whoever wins, will break the tie.
Also, the winner will also gain
this prestigious Presidential plaque as a gift.
Great!
Mom. This is a gold ingot board.
Whoever wins this, won't have to be afraid that they won't have any business in Huzhou.
But of course.
But they will still have to keep to their earlier words.
Whoever loses,
they must admit defeat and according to the agreed upon rule,
they must withdraw from the dyeing industry of Huzhou.
They must never do any dyeing business in Huzhou again.
They should also never show up within Huzhou again.
Here are the bosses to show off their work.
Great.
Victory to Rong Da!
Cai Hong.
Don't worry.
Rong Da!
You must win, Rong Da!
Rong Da! Victory to Rong Da!
Victory to Rong Da!
Rong Da!
This rascal, Zhou Shao Tian,
is really talented.
Mom. This silk piece is really very beautiful.
Of course, I have good taste.
I just know that Shao Tian will definitely win.
Look, I placed my bet on this.
Mom. You gambled again?
It's definitely dyed very well.
No wonder, Wu Hong Da thought that highly of him.
Brother. Will we be able to win?
Let's invite Boss Jiang of Ling Long.
Great.
Victory to Ling Long!
Victory!
Excellent.
It's really great!
So, this is the silk dyed using the secret formula.
Great.
It's really great.
This is the cloth. Mom, I finally found it.
It's this piece of cloth.
I need to pay up.
Let's invite Mr Zhang to judge the most beautiful cloth.
Everyone, let's give him a warm applause.
Great.
The silk of Huzhou
is definitely a legend.
It's definitely a great piece of silk.
Everyone. The result of the silk contest is already very obvious.
Boss Zhou's silk piece has a really good reputation.
It's exquisite technique is centuries old. It is unique to the world.
Right now, with the power given to me,
appoint...
Ling Long's delicate weaving and dyeing Factory as the winner of the silk contest.
Great!
I'm doomed. My money.
Why are the police here?
What happened?
Who are they arresting?
Isn't that Superintendent Zhen?
Stop talking.
What's going on? What has happened?
We have reasons to believe that Jiang Yu is connected to Wu Rong Da's death.
According to gathered evidence,
on the day of Wu Hong Da's incident, he took out his secret formula.
But after the incident, the secret formula went missing.
Thus, the reason for today's silk contest was to force Jiang Yu to take out the secret formula.
That piece of cloth that he just took out was definitely created using the secret formula.
It can't be.
Jiang Yu.
Your sister personally handed this secret formula to me.
This certificate is evidence.
All here.
You can't escape.
Zhou Shao Tian, you are a conman. You are a despicable and small minded person.
Brother. It's not like this. You have been framed.
- Brother, listen to my explanation.
- Take him away now.
Brother! Don't take away my brother.
Let me go.
It's not like this. Let him go. Brother!
It really wasn't like that. Brother!
- Let my brother go.
- We should kick him out of the city.
- He is a killer.
- Let my brother go. Let me explain.
Great.
Today was a great day.
Fortunately, you and Cai Hong thought of a great idea this time.
You forced that rascal Jiang Yu to take out the secret formula.
We also forced the killer out.
I think the police will find him guilty soon.
Thanks for our Old Master's protection, he can finally rest in peace now.
And also, Old Master had good taste.
He chose Shao Tian as his son-in-law.
Not only are you talented, you are good in doing business and are a good person too.
I have nothing bad to say about how you treat Cai Hong.
Aunt. You and Cai Yun can continue to live here.
I will take good care of Cai Hong.
- Don't worry about Cai Hong and me.
- Don't worry.
I definitely won't.
Cai Hong. Did you hear that?
Cai Hong.
- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
I was talking about you and Shao Tian.
Sister, congratulations.
Let's talk about this later.
Cai Hong.
Look. She is so thin-skinned.
As for you, find a good time,
bring flowers,
and talk to her nicely.
Thank you, Aunt.
Is this any business of yours? Let's go back to our rooms.
Let's go.
Brother Shao Tian.
There is something I wanted to tell you for a long time.
You are really a very, very good person
but I don't deserve you being so good to me.
Thus...
Cai Hong.
Do you know why I brought you here?
Why?
There is a legend about this small place.
Once you encounter unhappy events, as long as you circle this once,
all the unhappy things will disappear.
- You believe in this?
- Yes, I do.
When I was young and encountered unhappy events, I would circle here.
After a long time, it became a habit.
After you have made a circle here, things really got better?
Since young until now, I have experienced many unhappy things
that I don't disregard instead overcome them
See? Aren't I standing in front of you safe and sound now?
To feel at ease...
Come, give me your hand.
Let's circle it once.
I believe that this will improve your mood.
Give it a try.
You said that after making a circle, everything would go back to the way it was.
Will my heart go back to the way it was too?
Of course.
With me here, no matter what happens, I will always be with you.
Everything will go back to the way it was. Your heart will too.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Brother. So how?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Sorry. I caused you to be in this state.
Don't worry. I will think of a means to get you out.
I didn't kill anyone. Nothing will happen to me.
I know you didn't kill anyone. You were framed by Zhou Shao Tian.
Blame me for believing in Shao Tian's words. I stole the secret formula
and caused you to be jailed.
Sorry.
I know.
I know you were used by him.
I don't harbour any resentments.
Mr Jiang. Miss Fang told me about your situation.
I carefully studied your case. Although the secret formula was in your hands,
the police can't prove that whoever has the secret formula is the killer.
This is because of the secret formula that you hold in our hands.
That's why, they think you are the suspect.
Boss Jiang, I'll help you apply for bail as soon as possible.
You will have to suffer for the time being.
Let's do this. Don't get involved in this matter first.
- Why?
- Listen carefully to me.
Also, I won't be going back to Ling Long for the next two days.
Help me to take care of the factory. I will be back soon.