The Cage of Love
Episode 13
Madam Jiang
Madam, today I will take care of you.
I'm Cai Hong. In the future, let me manage your tasks.
As you are trying to wake up, I will serve you well.
Madam. The weather is really nice today.
It's every fresh.
It's a pity that you can't feel it. Thus, I opened the door wider.
This way, the air from outside will come into the house.
Wu Long.
What are you doing? Why did you leave the door open?
- I wanted to let the air in.
- Shut up.
What kind of intentions do you have?
You clearly know that Madam is sick and you let the door wide open?
Are you trying to let her catch a cold?
Bad thing. No wonder, Miss wanted me to keep watch over you.
I am washing Madam's legs.
Look at how dirty this towel is.
Don't you know how to work?
The water in the tub is dirty.
You are going to wash Madam's legs with this?
Are you inconsiderate or brainless?
I have never seen anyone so stupid.
Change the water and wash the towel until it's clean.
I just washed this towel.
Rotten wench. You still dare to talk back to me?
I'm telling you. If I say it's dirty, it's dirty then.
People like you are not clean in the first place.
You are dirtying my eyes.
What you are saying is really too ugly.
You still dare to criticise what I said?
If you are someone of substance, don't take advantage of a place.
Get lost and stop harming others.
Fortunately, Miss told me to watch you. If not, I wonder what harm you would have caused Madam.
You are such a bad thing.
Dirty thing.
- You dirty thing.
- What are you doing?
Young Master.
Wu Cai Hong doesn't know how to do her work. I'm teaching her.
In the future, if you want to teach your subordinates, do it outside. Don't disturb Madam.
Yes, Young Master.
What are you still doing here?
I didn't let you in here to freeload on us.
If you don't know the rules, study them well.
I will work hard.
Why are you still standing here? Change the water and wash the towel now.
Remember to wash your hands thoroughly.
Don't argue with others. Did you hear me?
If you don't change your personality, let's see how I will handle you.
What is she doing?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Morning, Madam. How was your sleep last night?
Come. Let me feed you the medicine, okay?
Come.
Wu Cai Hong!
What did you give my mom?
It's a folklore prescription.
Mrs Zhang was right.
Last night, you were secretly making some unclean items.
What did you give my mom?
This is medicine from leeches.
Mom.
Why did you let my mom drink this?
The doctor said that Madam is unconscious because there are blood clots in her brain.
- The leeches can clear blood clots and stasis.
-Nonsense.
You are not a doctor. How could you let my mom take this medicine randomly?
I spent a lot of effort to obtain this folklore medicine.
My mom was in the same condition and confined to a bed.
She had blood clots but after drinking this medicine, it helped her.
In any case, I won't allow my Mom to be placed in any danger.
If there are any mistakes, who's going to be responsible?
I think it's still not enough that I taught you a lesson the last time.
Mrs Zhang.
Take her out and punish her.
Come out now.
I'm going to beat you to death for retorting.
I will beat you to death for disobedience,
for not listening and being argumentative.
I will beat you to death.
Don't talk back. Don't talk back.
Enough.
Brother. She was only given a few beatings.
If you do this, she won't change.
If you beat her until she's injured, I will still need to call for the doctor.
I don't want to waste money this way.
The recipe (for the medine) is useful.
You must trust me.
How should I trust you?
Who was the one who pushed my mom down the stairs?
I'm warning you.
In the future, don't make any decisions on your own.
So be it.
Change your personality in the future.
Brother Shao Tian. Are you doing well?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
- Waiter.
- Mr Zhou.
- Bring another bottle of wine.
- Mr Shao, you have already drank too much. Don't drink anymore.
Why don't I heat up the food for you?
I told you to bring me another bottle of wine.
Go now.
Don't drink anymore. I'm afraid you don't have the money for the wine.
I'm telling you, I have money.
What I have is money.
Being rich is a form of pain.
Bring the wine here.
You already drank enough. You can't drink anymore.
Take the wine away.
What I have is money.
Mr Zhou, you are drunk.
I have money.
Go now.
Cai Hong.
Madam. When my mom was sick and laid in bed, I massaged her too.
Madam. Can you feel the massage I'm giving you?
If you can feel it, move your hands. Okay?
Or you can blink your eyes.
Looks like you can't hear what I'm saying.
Young Master and Miss miss you very much.
You are a good mother.
You must wake up soon. You shouldn't let them worry.
Isn't that so?
Okay, Madam. I will massage you.
Don't be fooled by her.
Mom's current condition
was caused by the Wu family.
What's this? He is drunk.
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Mom.
You must pay for it.
Pay me. Are you crazy?
What are you doing, drunkard?
Cai Hong.
Don't leave.
Who are you? What are you doing?
Cai Hong, it's me.
♫ So long, I have waited for so long... ♫
- You are not Cai Hong.
♫ Waited for your love to bloom. ♫
♫ Desperately, I was desperately struggling to find... ♫
- You are not Cai Hong.
♫ Yet couldn't find the way to your heart. ♫
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
What's wrong?
What did you do to my mom?
I was just stimulating her acupuncture points.
She felt pain just now. Perhaps, she has already regained sensitivity.
Perhaps, she may wake up.
What exactly did you do to my mom?
My mom is laying in bed and can't talk now.
She wouldn't know what you have done to her.
Did you take revenge on my mom because we beat you?
I saw this today. What did you do to my mom when we didn't see anything?
I really didn't do anything. I only wanted Madam to wake up soon.
I don't believe you. I only believe what I see.
Mom.
I think I had you beaten too lightly. That's why you didn't change your personality, right?
Mrs Zhang.
Drag her out and punish her.
Yes. Come out with me.
Kneel down.
Mrs Zhang. Beat her until she admits her fault.
Yes.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Still dare to argue?
I really have no intentions of harming her.
Nonsense. I don't believe you.
My mom is laying in bed and can't see
but I have eyes. I have been watching you.
I really didn't do anything wrong. I'm doing this for Madam's sake.
You are still not admitting your mistake?
Mr Zhang, continue with the beatings.
Beat her until she admits her mistake.
See if you still dare to argue again.
Open the door.
I want to see Cai Hong.
What are you doing?
- Where is Cai Hong?
- Who are you?
- Cai Hong is not here.
- Who's stopping me?
- You are a drunkard.
- Don't stop me.
- Get lost.
- I want to see Cai Hong.
You can't go in. Stop there.
Dare to argue again?
- Enough.
- Stop there.
- Cai Hong!
- Brother Shao Tian.
Let's beat her together.
Brother Shao Tian.
You dare to come here to create a ruckus?
Since before he was like this.
- Brother Shao Tian.
- Beat him to death.
Beat him.
I'm begging you, stop beating him.
Let me go. Brother Shao Tian.
It's all my fault.
Tell them to stop. Don't beat him anymore.
Brother Shao Tian.
Continue with the beatings.
I'm begging you.
Stop beating him.
Leave. You even dare to create a ruckus here?
Get out.
You really don't know what's good for you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I previously made several requests but you rejected them all.
Why are you so free as to visit me today?
Unless you have already thought over my advice.
Miss Lu.
We are understanding people. Let's get to the point.
I will help to start the dye factory that you wanted to set up in Huzhou.
You've finally thought it through?
That's great! I, Lu Man, am also a frank person. Based on our previous arrangement,
if you give me the secret recipe, I will set up the factory. You will be the General Manager and have 30 percent of the shares.
I already told you repeatedly. I don't have the secret recipe.
Make it forty percent then.
Even if you give me the entire factory, I really don't have the secret recipe.
Mr Jiang. My time is very precious.
If you don't have the secret recipe, why are you here to see me?
We can change the methods and set up the factory together.
I will use my management and technical skills to manage the factory.
Mr Zhou. In this community,
there are many people with management and technical skills.
There are many people who want to work with me.
Why should I hire you?
It's because I have been with Wu Cai Hong for many years.
Ling Long is one of Huzhou's best dyeing factories.
This you should know. Ling Long's
capital, technology, and channel are all here.
I think you should know this.
No matter how great Old Wu is,
didn't he lose to the Jiang family too?
Weren't you forced out by the Jiang family too?
If I didn't guess wrongly,
Jiang Yu inflicted the bodily injuries on you, right?
If you have an escape route, you wouldn't be here looking for me.
Miss Lu.
You have dared to try each method.
Do you really think I'm not a match for Jiang Yu?
If you had the solution, you wouldn't be forced into this state now.
By the way, I seem to have forgotten.
I heard that your girlfriend
has already been sold into the Jiang family as a maid.
Since this is the case, let's change the methods.
We set up a factory together. I will provide the financial backing,
technical skills and experience too.
I will give you thirty percent of the shares. What do you think?
Mr Zhou, are you kidding?
- How could there be such a good deal on earth?
- The good deal is in front of you.
I have the money. I would like to borrow your name to start the factory.
Miss Lu. You are a smart person. You can probably catch my drift.
I get it now. You are thinking of borrowing my name to clear your reputation.
Isn't thirty percent of the shares too insincere?
I want forty percent.
As the saying goes "going bigger does not get you more."
Don't miss out on the offer of thirty percent shares.
If you don't take this opportunity, I'm afraid you won't be able to set up a factory here.
I won't ask where you got the money from
but you using this money to clear your name, there is no one else in Huzhou
who can do this except me.
Mr Zhou. You should know who my backer is.
In your condition now, who knows? You may be able to use him.
Fine.
Since you put it this way, make it forty percent then.
I will fund the set up of the factory and provide the technical and management skills. You will be the boss on the front.
I will be the General Manager and hold thirty percent of the shares.
How bold. I'm was still satisfied before
when Wu Hong Da shook things up.
How could he easily have lost to Jiang Yu?
The student surpassed the teacher,
mastering the tricks and mastering life.
He definitely chose a capable son-in-law.
Fine. Congratulations, Mr Zhou, for your comeback in the dye industry.
We have formed an alliance today. I also hope that
you will be able to get ahold of the secret formula.
If you can obtain the secret formula, Huzhou will be our kingdom.
I will remember what you said.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Granny Gu. Let me help you.
No need. Madam only likes the fish soup I cook for her.
I heard that you are Madam's nanny.
You are also Madam's trusted person.
Did you come into the Jiang's family with her?
What do you want?
I'm looking for a solution to help Madam to be conscious.
I heard that you pushed Madam down the stairs.
At that time, the situation was very chaotic.
I'm very apologetic about it too. I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologise to me. I can tell that you are feeling a very guilty conscious.
I heard that you used folklore prescriptions and massages too.
It has been hard on you.
I would also like to do my best
to redeem my past.
Granny Gu. Could you tell me
some stories about Madam?
There are many stories about Madam.
I don't know which stories would be of help to you.
Granny Gu. You can tell me any stories.
For example, what is Madam's happiest moment?
Or her favourite song?
You can tell me about these.
I think Madam's happiest moment is when she met Old Master.
Both of them loved each other very much and married later.
The happiest moment could be when they were together.
Even God was envious.
Old Master passed away at such a young age.
What a pity. Ever since,
Madam has never been happy again.
They were so much in love. There must be a special place.
For example, what was their lovers' keepsakes?
Lovers' keepsakes? I don't really know about this.
There was a song for it though. It's "Ten Glass Boats".
It's because at that time,
when Madam and her husband went on dates,
she would always sing this song.
When she was singing this song and smiling,
do you know how lovely she was?
In my lifetime,
that was the most beautiful that Madam looked.
Wu Cai Hong.
What right do have you to ask about my parents?
Granny Gu.
Did you forget what the prohibitions for the Jiang family are?
Young Master. Miss Cai Hong only wanted to...
What?
Listen carefully.
You gave me your word.
Don't let me find out that you are checking about my parents again.
Do you remember when I was young and joined the Ling Long Dye factory?
Yes.
I heard from them that Ling Long has a secret recipe.
Is there something like this?
The secret recipe was from Jiang Yu's family.
Jiang Yu?
Yes. He...
Shao Tian, what's wrong with you? Did you fight with him?
This doesn't concern you. Tell me about Ling Long first.
Tell me.
Tell me now.
Ling Long originally belonged to the Jiang family.
Later, Old Master Jiang,
that is Jiang Yu's father, committed a crime.
Ling Long then changed hands and became the Wu family's company.
I didn't think that it would fall into Jiang Yu's hands again.
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Are you sure that Ling Long belongs to Old Master Jiang in the past?
Definitely. Jiang family's Young Master is Jiang Yu.
I met him when he played at the factory when he was young.
Shao Tian, it really does not matter.
So to say, Ling Long belonged to Jiang Yu in the first place.
Since it was the Jiang family, why did they change the name to Wu?
What exactly happened then?
Tell me.
It happened a long time in the past. Why are you bringing this up again?
You must tell me. It's extremely important.
Shao Tian.
I know that
you've taken to heart the things in the past and can't get over them.
Frankly, I find it hard to accept
but since this happened a long time ago, just let it be.
You are still young. You can move forward.
Let's not talk about this now. Stick to my questions. Do you know what the crime was that Old Master Jiang committed?
You just said that Ling Long belonged to the Jiang family and later became under the Wu family because of a crime he committed.
I remember Old Master Wu was a government officer then.
He was the one who first announced Old Master Jiang's crime.
At that time, the officials went to the factory to raid for opium.
I was at the scene.
I personally witnessed Old Master Jiang jump to his death.
The government said that he committed suicide.
So to say, Wu Hong Da forced Jiang Yu's father to die.
No wonder, every time when Jiang Yu sees Cai Hong,
there is a kind of hatred.
Old Master Jiang's crime was confirmed?
The government said that he was guilty. What would commoners like us know?
But Old Master Jiang treated his workers very well.
Our family received help and kindness from him too.
"The unjust are doomed for destruction."
Looks like God is still fair.
There is retribution.
Who are you talking about?
Let's not talk about this first. Tell me about the secret formula.
The secret formula is the Jiang family's inheritance. I heard from the ex-workers of the Jiang family that
for Empress Dowager's birthday,
the Jiang family used the secret formula for the textiles
dedicated to the Empress Dowager.
Where is the secret formula now?
I don't know.
After Old Master's factory went bankrupt, would it still be there?
♫ The first glass boat made a whistling sound. ♫
♫Two oars making a pilgrimage. ♫
♫Headed to an ultra-long mountain every year. ♫
♫The smell of incense burning in the ocean. ♫
Madam Jiang. Jiang Yu doesn't allow me to talk
but he didn't say that I couldn't sing.
I believe that they miss you very much and want you to wake up soon.
This song will bring back many beautiful memories of you and your husband.
Madam, wake up soon.
♫The second post ship gathers as a pair♫
♫Gilded railings installed on both side. ♫
♫Beautiful upper pavilion♫
♫Under the noisy drums♫
♫ The third glass boat arrived very fast. ♫
♫Two dragons swim in order♫
♫Water engulfs the white silk♫
♫The waves bring the immortal White Empress♫
Let's see how Brother will handle you.
Brother.
Last night, I heard Wu Cai Hong singing "Ten Glass Boats" in mom's room
but when I walked there, she had already stopped.
Brother. Wu Cai Hong clearly knows that this is a prohibited song for Mom.
If she continues to sing, then she is purposely causing you pain.
Brother.
♫ The third glass boat arrived very fast. ♫
♫Two dragons swim in order♫
What are you doing? You definitely know that you're singing a prohibited song.
You are singing in front of her. What are you scheming?
- I wanted to stimulate...
- Did you forget what I told you yesterday? You are doing this on purpose.
I...
- Madam.
- Mom.
- Did Madam hear me talking?
Young Master. Doctor Zhao is here.
Doctor Zhao. Check my mom now.
Doctor Zhao. What is my mom's condition?
Madam Jiang's recovery is not bad.
Her breathing, blood pressure and heartbeat are not bad now.
Furthermore, she has been laying down for a long time.
Her complexion is ruddy. She doesn't have an inflammation and her joints are fine.
It looks like she has been taken care of very well.
Why did my mom cry then?
Under what condition did she cry?
When she heard that song, it seemed like...
This is a great phenomenon for Madam.
It proves that she can sense what's going out. Perhaps, she will regain her consciousness soon.
If conditions allow, you must stimulate her more.
If the song helps, do it then.
I understand.
Doctor. I still have a question to consult you with. Let's talk in the living room.
Okay.
This is from Mr Zhou.
Thanks.
Doctor Zhao. I would like to consult you regarding folklore prescriptions.
Using leeches as medicines,
will this help my mom's illness?
I studied Western medicine but have also done some research on Oriental medicines.
I recall in Shen Nong's Herbal Classic, there was a written account.
It said that leeches can clear blood clots and stasis.
This medicine with regards to your mother's illness,
from a medicinal perspective, it can help your mother.
I understand.
And also, if my mother's acupuncture points were stimulated and she felt pain,
what's going on?
With regards to Madam Jiang's illness, stimulating the acupuncture points and massages
these will help her.
This is to prevent stiff joints, muscle atrophy
and to keep blood flowing.
If Madam Jiang can feel the pain,
this is a great phenomenon.
Cai Hong. I know that you are not having a hard time at the Jiang's home.
This medicine can help fight infections. I will go to you soon to save you.
Your family and I are well.
The seven rainbow bracelet is not worth much money. This is my lover's keepsake.
Now that it's in Jiang Yu's hands,
I will think of a way to get it back.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I have seen enough stupid people
but I have never seen someone as stupid as you.
Idiot.
- Come up.
-You realise now that leeches are beneficial?
- Let me do it.
- No need.
I'm a maid of the Jiang family. This should be done by me.
When I was young, I handled lobsters and prawns. I know how to do this. Let me do it.
This is not the same fish you are used to.
Thus, let me do it instead.
Why do you know so much?