The Cage of Love
Episode 19
If it wasn't for your help, I wouldn't have been able to leave unscathed.
Am I that great? I'm only just your subordinate who runs around doing errands.
I just act according to you instructions.
But
did you really kill Wu Hong Da?
Of course not.
Why are you so nervous then?
Don't worry. Even if you killed someone,
I wouldn't tell anyone.
I really didn't kill anyone.
I still suspect that Jiang Yu killed Wu Hong Da.
He had the motive to kill, intent to commit the crime, and owns an identical pen.
In order to mask the truth, he has done some dirty deeds against me.
By doing that, he sabotaged my love with Cai Hong.
Forget it. If you are fighting in the business arena,
one can lose their head and commit murder.
This is too scary.
You are too ethical.
How could you let Jiang Yu bully you again?
If this drags on, there will come a day when you will suffer.
I'm waiting for the opportunity now.
When the opportunity is here,
he won't be able to get away.
From what I can see, Jiang Yu and you are playing games with each other.
Can't even help oneself.
Okay.
Don't be too harsh on yourself.
Cai Hong. You haven't eaten anything for the whole day. Eat something.
Mrs Li. I'm really not hungry.
Eat something.
Young Master already said that if you don't eat anything, I'm not doing a good job.
I have to change and redo things until you eat.
Help me please.
I will eat then, Mrs Li.
Frankly, Young Master is doing this for your own good.
I don't know what the others think but I can
see clearly.
You don't need to twist it. Just eat it.
This is right.
Brother.
What do you take Wu Cai Hong as?
What do you mean? Of course, she is a servant.
But your attitude to her, is that of a servant?
I treat all my servants equally.
You are lying.
Would you take a servant to view the lotus pond?
Would you be concerned that your servant is not eating?
Brother, don't forget, she is Wu Hong Da's daughter.
I'm not a three year old kid. I don't need you to tell me what to do.
You know that I didn't say anything wrong.
You are angry because you have a guilty conscious.
What I said was right.
Your feelings towards Wu Cai Hong already surpasses that of an ordinary person.
Leave.
I can leave
but I would still like to advise you.
Don't let your personal feelings get in the way.
Did you see how Young Master treats Wu Cai Hong better than anyone?
Based on what you said, Wu Cai Hong is the young mistress.
We should treat her better in the future then.
If Wu Cai Hong becomes his wife, what will happen to us?
They may be childhood friends
but Miss has feelings for Young Master who is not interested.
But Miss's affections towards Master are unintentional. She lights up every time she see's him.
No wonder Miss hates Wu Cai Hong so much.
Even though they address her as the mistress of the house, her family name is Fang not Jiang.
She is also an outsider.
If she can't be the Young Master's wife, she will have to marry someone and leave the house sooner or later.
If a girl wants to marry, she should marry an authentic Young Master.
Look. Miss has placed so many thoughts on Young Master.
It was really rotten and a waste of time.
That's right.
I will never leave this family.
I will also never leave Mom and Brother.
Wu Cai Hong. I won't let you and Brother be together.
Miss Fang. Are you really inviting me out for tea? It can't be that simple.
I have already thought it through. I can help you.
You are not only helping me but yourself too.
Say whatever you want but let me state this first. I can help you
but you must never harm my brother.
I must not harm your brother?
But you have harmed Cai Hong a couple of times. What does this count?
Looks like you are not sincere in collaborating with me.
Miss Fang, let me advise you. You don't have much time.
If you don't manage it, I'm afraid that when Cai Hong enters the Jiang family
and becomes your sister-in-law,
what I would lose is just Cai Hong.
What you will lose is not only Jiang Yu.
Are you threatening me now?
Why would I collaborate with a menacing person?
Once a friend becomes an enemy, he becomes more dangerous than the enemy.
Yet once an enemy becomes a friend, he will be more reliable than a friend.
By helping me, you are helping yourself too.
Fine. How can I help you then?
Get the slave contract for me as soon as possible.
If I could do this, would I still be here?
I believe you will find the way.
I will wait for your news.
How was the investigation regarding the opium case at Ling Long?
There was a lead but the investigation midway, stopped.
We found the court official who handled this case twelve years ago but when we went to visit him,
he refused to reveal anything about that night.
He refused to talk? This means there was a major problem in the case.
Yes, I find it strange too. This court official is on extremely good terms with Jiang Wen Yuan.
Since Master Jiang's death, the top investigators have all left.
Thus, I feel that he knows some insider's information.
Please.
Please wait.
Old Master. Boss Zhou is here.
Leave.
If you are here to find out about the Ling Long case,
sorry, please go back.
Uncle Gao. I'm here to seek advice regarding the Ling Long case from twelve years ago.
At the same time, I'm also here to visit my mother's foe.
Do you still remember, three years ago, the aunt from the weaving and dyeing factory.
Are you referring to her husband, Zhou Da Liang who had lung disease?
I'm his son, Zhou Shao Tian.
Talking about this, you look exactly like your mother.
Uncle Gao. I visited you without advance notice today.
You definitely must have a request.
I know that you don't want to talk about it but I still would like to find out about the opium case at Ling Long.
Please do me a small favour.
Wasn't the case settled then?
It has been such a long time and that person has already died.
Why do you still want to talk about it?
If it weren't for my mother's wish, I wouldn't want to talk about this either.
Your mother's wish?
When my father got sick and was lying in bed,
Old Master Jiang took care of my mother.
He gave her some of Ling Long's business. Old Master Jiang knew about my family's hardship.
He gave wage advances to try to solve the urgent needs of my family.
If it weren't for Old Master Jiang's kindness,
I'm afraid that my mom wouldn't have been able to support me and her sick husband.
Boss Jiang was really a good person.
When Boss Jiang passed away, my mother has never talked bad about him.
She said that someone like Old Master Jiang would never use opium to frame anyone.
Unfortunately with our family situation the way it was, Jiang was unable to be compensated.
Only during the Winter Solstice Festival, his burning point for money was all for nothing.
Now with mixed effort, Old Jiang can rest in peace.
I couldn't pay him for his kindness to my family.
The only thing I can do is to prove Boss Jiang's innocence.
He will then rest in peace in heaven.
Your mother has such a son who is willing to redeem himself for the family,
that is her good fortune.
But the case happened twelve years ago, it won't be easy to turn around the case.
I have no choice but to seek your help now.
I won't be able to help you
but there are some matters that I can tell you.
Old Master Jiang and I were on very good terms. I know how he was too.
Just like what you said,
he would never do anything like that.
The years following the wrongful death of Boss Jiang, there were a lot of people who could have cried foul.
The strange thing is that he payed for other's grievances but everyone suffered in the end.
I'm ashamed for not speaking sooner but now I can help prove Jiang's innocence.
But I think when he was implicated and everyone was tight-lipped.
I wanted to find a home for windows and orphans and find a solution
but when I heard that they were kicked out by the tribe, they have been hiding in their hometown.
I sent men to find out about their whereabouts but there was no news.
I heard that Jiang Yu is very capable now and he has gotten back Ling Long.
At that time, I was a coward and didn't dare to speak up on his father's behalf.
I don't have the face to see him. Thus, I have never visited him.
If you are sure that Old Master Jiang was duped, where is the evidence?
The incident happened a long time ago. If there are any evidence, it would already have been burnt.
Boss Jiang was wronged and not only be my side of the story.
I think if you could find the case file from that year, perhaps you could read through the documents.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
- Miss Lu.
- You are looking for me?
I'm here to ask for your help to investigate a case.
You are really insincere.
When you look for me, it's either to help you find a fountain pen or to investigate a case.
Can't you treat me to a meal or go to the movies?
As for dinner and movie thing, how could I dare to cross warlord Lu?
We are discussing business and nothing else.
Speak. What help do you need?
During the Xuantong years is when the opium trafficking case took place.
We are a republic country now and you want me to help you investigate an official court case?
On what ground do you think I am able to do that?
If you cannot do it, Miss Lu, no one can.
I would like to see the records of the case. You are the only one who can help me with this.
Fine.
Since you said that we are presently discussing business now and nothing else,
if I can help you with this difficult request,
how are you going to thank me?
Tell me.
I want Ling Long's secret formula.
I think you are mistaken. I was with Ling Long for many years and have never heard about this.
I know that you don't have it. Anyway, it's not that urgent just as long as you will help me.
When doing business, it's for mutual benefits. Please do something for me.
If you think that you can't do it, let's not transact this business then.
I agree.
Don't play me. I know many secrets about you.
I'm leaving.
Cai Hong, be patient. I will come and get you soon.
I will be able to show Jiang Yu's true colour soon and reveal the truth for you.
Is everyone here?
Yes.
Today is the 15th of July, Ghost Festival, and the day for us to remember Old Master.
Mom. I have already prepared everything.
Every year, we have prepared for this festival. There was no other exception.
Especially when Old Master will be back today. Everyone, don't delay it.
Yes.
Go and do whatever you are assigned to do.
Have you heated up the buns?
Yes, it should be ready soon.
Let me take a look.
Let me take a look. Are you okay?
Let me see.
Move aside.
What's wrong?
Did you scald yourself? Are you okay?
Let me take a look.
It's not me.
It's Miss.
Brother, you still don't admit that you treat Wu Cai Hong differently?
I was flustered just now and didn't check who was hurt.
That's because the problem is you didn't see who was hurt.
Your subconscious behavior is being driven by your inner thoughts.
Brother, I'm your sister.
We went through hard times for twelve years.
We got back Ling Long together to take revenge for father.
Other than your mother, I'm your closest relative in this world.
But why was
the first person that you were concerned about today was Wu Cai Hong and not me?
In your heart, Wu Cai Hong is more valuable than me.
You are still not going to admit it?
I have matters to attend to. I'm leaving first.
What you are feeling inside?
Why must you force me to talk about this?
Fei Fei. What exactly do you want?
I want Wu Cai Hong to leave this house.
Since you can't control your own feelings,
don't let your emotions bring you down.
Brother. You won't let me and Mom
and also our father who is in heaven be disappointed with you, right?
I will repeat myself. I will decide my own affairs.
Brother, you are really foolish.
Do you think you can run away from this problem?
Come back, dear.
It has been many years. How are you doing in that world?
Shao Tian has the ability now.
We are doing better than before.
If you need anything there,
just appear in Shao Tian and my dreams.
I know what you are worried about.
Don't worry. I don't have any grudges now.
He will understand me one day.
What you do mean by saying all that?
If there is anything on your mind, just tell me directly.
You don't need to complain in front of dad.
Shao Tian. You have misunderstood me.
I don't have any misunderstandings with you.
Father.
If you didn't pass away early,
you could be enjoying this.
I know that because our family was poor, you didn't have the will to live.
I have my own factor now. I can make big bucks.
Everything that I have done
was for you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
How could you be just like a ghost?
Would be there be such a beautiful female ghost just like me?
Or one that would also be this thoughtful?
Guess what this is.
This is the opium case regarding the Jiang family.
Don't forget what you promised me.
Of course, I will find Ling Long's secret formula as soon as possible.
This is the way.
I already read this report.
According to what is written in the report, Jiang Family should have transported 100 tons of opium before.
Only for this amount,
the owed tax amount and the fine could bankrupt Jiang Family.
But, most of the drug smugglers had an accomplice.
In this report, Jiang Wen Yuan was the only one found guilty.
This point doesn't add up.
Think about it. It's such a big amount. Where did it come from?
How was it transported? Where was it stored?
If it was really stored in Ling Long, 100 ton
they wouldn't be able to hide it. I find this rather amusing.
Perhaps, all these weren't recorded here.
Because it could not be explained clearly, why try to make it worse?
Even more strange, I searched the records of Huzhou regarding the past 12 years,
on it, there is no mention of the opium case 12 years ago.
To put on a show, why was it recorded?
So, twelve years ago, Jiang Wen Yuan's case
was a case of mis-identity.
Exactly. Also the true criminal was the police chief at the time.
And the ultimate victor was Wu Hong Da.
Cai Hong. I can finally get you out from there.
However, according to the predictions,
could it be that the Jiang family in this case is Jiang Yu's family?
Of course.
Wu Cai Hong's father is Wu Hong Da. Jiang Yu's father is Jiang Wen Yuan.
Wu Hong Da, as the Police Chief, killed Jiang Wen Yuan because of money.
He took their family business, Ling Long Fabric Plant.
Tell me what is Jiang Yu's motive for getting close to Cia Hong.
Revenge
but if Jiang Yu really falls in love with Cai Hong now...
Who cares whether it's real love or not.
If Cai Hong were to find out that he got close to her just to take revenge for his father, what do you think she will think?
If I were Wu Cai Hong, I would definitely hate him to death.
The acquisition went well yet I am afraid of hurting Cai Hong.
It is the result of revenge and Wu Hong Da's death.
Then, Ms. Wu will naturally come back into your arms.
You exerted that much effort just to win a woman.
You are really passionate.
Thanks.
Old Master, you can rest in peace now.
The children have already grown up to be adults.
Your son has done well. He has taken revenge for you.
I will never be able to repay the kindness of the Jiang family.
I will always take care of the Jiang family and repay you back for your kindness. Mom is getting old
and brother has grown up.
Don't worry. I will take good care of Mom for you
and I will also take good care of brother too.
It's getting late.
Son. Go with Fei Fei to release the water lantern.
Madam.
Cai Hong, what is it?
Today is the Ghost Festival. Could you let me take time off?
I will like to release a water lantern for my father.
It's rare for someone to be this filial. Go now.
Thank you, Madam.
Quick.
Why are you keeping a close watch on my brother?
I know what you are thinking in your heart but it's just your fantasy.
This is just a dream. The deeper you get involved, you will only get hurt more.
Because my brother will never really like you.
I don't know what you are talking about.
I want to hide it so it is not exposed.
Ask yourself then what exactly you are thinking of.
Cai Hong.
Brother Shao Tian.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to tell a story to Cai Hong about what happened between the Jiang and Wu families twelve years ago.
Cai Hong. Jiang Yu is a consummate liar.
You have been tricked.
Brother Shao Tian. What are you talking about?
You are only just a tool for his revenge. Everything that he has done,
it was because of the opium case at Ling Long twelve years ago.
Your dad's death, Ling Long's confiscation,
it was all part of his plan.
Cai Hong, come over here.
- Stay far away from that liar.
- Zhou Shao Tian, what are you doing?
I want you to see his true colour.
Brother Shao Tian, don't do this.
Cai Hong!
Cai Hong.
Brother, don't you want your life?
Move aside.
Brother.
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
- Move aside.
- Coming.
- Is she okay?
- Get the doctor now.
- Cai Hong.
- Move aside.
- Brother, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Wake up.
- Brother.
- Cai Hong.
- Do you know what you are doing now?
You risked your own life for Wu Hong Da's daughter.
Did you think about Mom and me? Have you gone crazy?
What she and Brother Shao Tian said,
is it true?
Cai Hong.
Take your hands away from her.
Cai Hong. Are you okay?
I'm taking you to the hospital.
Brother, come to your senses.
Don't keep making this mistake.
It's a dead end ahead. Give up.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Doctor, how is she?
I have already done tests on Miss Wu.
Her injury is not grave. She only has some superficial wounds. She was only shocked.
it took a toll on her physical strnght, so she is very weak now.
When she wakes up and feels much better, she can be discharged then.
Thank you.
No.
This can't be true.
This is not true.
Cai Hong.
What's wrong with you?
Brother Shao Tian, what's going on?
Did I have a nightmare last night?
Cai Hong. Everything that happened last night
was real.
Are you saying that
my father
was Jiang family's enemy?
Is this true too?
Twelve years ago, your father was innocent.
Jiang Yu's father, Jiang Wen Yuan, was the owner of Ling Long.
He was charged with possession of opium. Jiang Wen Yuan condemned him
and seized his home. Later Jiang Wen Yuan died
and your father became the new owner of Ling Long.
I found someone to investigate this case.
This is indeed a messed up case.
It was your father, Wu Hong Da.
It can't be.
My father would never do something harmful like this.
Cai Hong. I'm telling you this not for you to keep go after your father's mistake.
That happened in that era.
This incident happened twelve years ago. Your father is no longer here. He's already dead.
I wanted you to learn so that you can see Jiang Yu's true colour.
He is only using revenge to take back what he has lost.
Come to your senses. Don't be tricked by that rascal.