The Cage of Love
Episode 14
I know this. Let me do it.
This is not the same fish you are used to.
So, let me do it.
Why do you know so much?
When my Mom was sick, I took care of her medications.
I didn't feel assured leaving this task to my servants. Thus, I gradually learned how to do it.
♫ The first sailboat has a protruding bow. ♫
♫ Two oars stretch outward, inviting fragrant whiffs. ♫
♫ Overcome the mountains year after year. ♫
♫ Offer incenses amid the joyful ruckus.
♫ The second sailboat makes it a pair. ♫
♫ The railings on both sides are gilded in gold. ♫
♫ How beautiful is the pavilion upstream? ♫
♫ The drums below make lots of noise. ♫
♫ The third sailboat approaches speedily.  ♫
♫ Two water dragons swim through the waters ♫
♫ They push the waters like white wrapping silk. ♫
♫ The rippling waves pray to the White Goddess. ♫
♫ The first sailboat has a protruding bow. ♫
♫Only post ship dressed up. ♫
♫Traveling to Nanyang happily. ♫
♫The first boat sitting with its pole ♫
♫ The fifth boat wearing a white railing on its pole. ♫
♫ Lü Dongbin played White Peony three times. ♫
♫  Song Jiang killed Yan Poxi (his wife). ♫
♫  Later, Xiǎo zhāng sān was captured. ♫
Wen Yuan.
Madam.
Madam, what did you say? Please say it again.
You are awake, Madam.
Cai Hong.
Why is it you?
Madam, you are finally awake.
We missed you very much. I'm going to tell the rest.
Madam is conscious.
- Really?
- Madam is conscious.
Mom. You are awake. Can you recognise us?
Mom.
Yu Er.
You are finally conscious.
Mom. You are finally conscious.
You scared us to death.
Cai Hong.
Thank you.
In my dream,
when I heard you singing,
my dream
became beautiful.
Madam. Thank you for waking up.
What are you doing?
I would like the rainbow bracelet back. It's very important to me. Could you return it to me?
No.
Also,
don't think that just because my Mom is conscious, I will forgive you.
Wu Long, you rascal.
Forget it if you don't want to help me. You scared me.
Come, sit here and be good.
Where does he keep the necklace?
What are you doing?
Wu Cai Hong, what are you doing?
I didn't do anything.
You still deny it? I saw you sneaking into my brother's room.
What are you looking for?
I... was looking for Wu Long.
I just saw Wu Long coming in here and I was afraid that he would mess up the room.
- I was just about to carry him out.
- Nonsense.
I saw you sneaking into my brother's room. You even searched his drawers.
Would Wu Long be in there?
I was really looking for Wu Long.
I'm going out first.
You are not going to tell the truth?
My brother is not here. I will teach you a lesson on his behalf.
My brother really hates his room being intruded into.
Even if I can't come in here, it's even more so for a servant like you.
Wu Cai Hong, I know there is a definite reason why you came to our house.
But in the end I was ignorant
and was just wishful thinking.
If I see you doing this again, it won't be that simple as getting a slap from me.
Get out.
You don't seem very happy.
Madam Jiang, I'm fine.
Your eyes are red and you still say that you are fine?
If you have any problems, I will decide for you.
It's just that I couldn't find a bracelet which is very important to me.
Don't be too anxious. I will tell the servants to look for it together with you.
No need, Madam. Thank you.
You are really too polite.
Brother.
I just saw Wu Cai Hong searching for stuff in your room.
I asked her what she was doing and she told me that she was looking for the cat.
How could the cat hide in the drawers?
I know what she is looking for.
Aren't you angry?
Don't you hate people intruding into your room?
She is looking for her bracelet.
Bracelet?
What bracelet? Brother, Wu Cai Hong is our enemy who killed father.
She certainly has tried her best to take revenge. You must always be cautious of her.
Enough, don't worry. Everything is fine.
Where did you keep that bracelet?
In the drawers.
What is its significance? Why aren't you returning it to her?
Enough, don't bother about it.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Hateful. It's such a worthless thing.
I really don't understand why brother wants to keep this?
Did you go to my brother's room because of this?
This is my bracelet. Return it to me.
It's such a worthless thing. Let's just throw it away.
No. Brother Shao Tian gave this to me.
So, this is the case.
Zhou Shao Tian gave this to you?
So to say, this is a lover's keepsake.
You want it, right?
Brother Shao Tian personally weaved this bracelet.
It represents his heart. Even though it doesn't cost much,
as long as your gift is sincere,
no one can say that it's worthless.
Because you don't know, doesn't mean you can trample on other people's stuff.
So what if I trampled on your bracelet? No matter the reason, it won't change anything,
I'm the mistress now and you are my servant.
I can check on you, your love and your worthless bracelet
and trample it with my feet. So what?
I know that I'm a servant of the Jiang family.
You are also the lady of the family.
In your eyes, my bracelet is nothing to you. Hence, could you please
return my bracelet to me?
It's good that you know your position but I still won't return it to you.
So what?
You are really unreasonable. Return the bracelet to me.
Wu Cai Hong. Your sister pushed my mom down the stairs. Are you going to push me now?
Why would I push you? I only want you to return my bracelet to me.
That day, why did my sister mistakenly pushed your mom down the stairs? Aren't you responsible too?
If your brother didn't instigated you to use the lipstick to frame Cai Yun,
would the both of you have exchanged words on that day?
If you both didn't exchange words that day and you didn't hit Cai Yun first, would Madam have involved herself in the tussle?
If you weren't so brutal,
-my sister would not have grabbed the wrong hands and pushed Madam down the stairs.
- and you took the rap for your sister.
If you feel bitter about this, go and tell my brother that it was your sister who pushed my mom and not you.
I will never talk about what happened regarding Cai Yun.
I only want my bracelet back. I'm reasoning with you.
That day Cai Yun's tussle caused such a great tragedy
It made the innocent Madam Jiang get hurt. I really hope that you can start anew.
Also, this bracelet is really very important to me.
Are you saying that I caused my mom to be injured?
Fine. Go and tell my brother then and see if he believes you.
I won't tell Jiang Yu.
I only hope that you can return my bracelet to me.
Also, I'm very sad too regarding Madam Jiang's injury.
I'm working very hard to redeem for it.
I hope that between us, we won't repeat the same mistakes.
Stop pretending to be a good person.
Redeem yourself?
Let me tell you. You will never be able to redeem yourself for what happened in the past.
Also,
let me remind you. Don't forget your status. You are only just a servant in the Jiang family.
You are being too extreme.
Return my bracelet to me.
What are you doing?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Is this that important to you?
Use the medicine. It will help in the healing,
otherwise you could get an infection.
- I'm leaving first.
- Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you, Doctor.
The bracelet representing Zhou Shao Tian's heart has not disappeared.
Did you overhear my conversation with Fei Fei?
How much did you hear?
Is that something you were afraid that I would overhear?
It's all because of this?
Was it worth it?
Come in.
Brother. You wanted to see me?
What you just said to Wu Cai Hong, was it all true?
Which part?
Everything.
I don't know what you mean.
Fei Fei.
In this house, living as two siblings...
I'm asking you.
It was clearly Wu Cai Yun who accidentally pushed Mom down the stairs.
Why did you say that Wu Cai Hong did it? Also, you were in the wrong first.
Why did you say that they intentionally pushed Mom down the stairs?
Is there any difference whether it was Wu Cai Hong or Wu Cai Yun who pushed Mom down the stairs?
They are both daughters of father's killer.
Of course, there is.
How could you frame her?
Because I hate Wu Cai Hong.
I hate how you protect her.
I hate how you are so careful about her.
Nonsense.
Fei Fei. When did you change?
Last time, you use a lipstick to frame Cai Yun, I already stated that I didn't like you acting like that.
I don't want my sister to do unethical things.
Where did that kind girl go to?
But brother, don't forget.
They are the daughters of the killer of our father.
So what?
We still need to be upright.
If we undertake unethical tactics for revenge, what's the difference between them and us?
I'm afraid that Jiang Yu overheard my conversation with Fei Fei.
He surely knows now that it was Wu Cai Yun who pushed his mom down the stairs.
What if he finds Cai Yun and give her trouble?
When I used the lipstick to frame Wu Cai Yun, why did you tell Wu Cai Hong that you instigated it?
Because you are my sister.
When you do something wrong, of course, I have to be responsible for you.
Fei Fei, tell me the truth. What exactly happened at the hospital the other day?
Let me tell you then.
You bumped into Wu Cai Yun at the hospital that day.
You both argued because of the lipstick. In the end, you took action.
Mom came forward to mediate and in the chaos,
Wu Cai Yun accidentally pushed Mom down the stairs. That's what happened.
Fei Fei.
Why didn't you tell me the truth earlier?
Because Mom was injured
and I couldn't accept it.
I feared you would blame me.
To add further,
Wu Cai Hong was the one who took the fall for her sister.
So, I blamed him wrongly for the issue regarding the lipstick.
I want to be alone.
What should I do?
Should I tell him or not?
Come in.
What is it?
You heard my conversation with Fei Fei just now?
So what if I heard it?
Cai Yun is still young. Thus, the mistake that she committed,
I hope that you will allow me to be responsible for her.
How are you going to do it?
We didn't intentionally push Madam Jiang down the stairs.
Thus, I'm willing to do anything for Madam Jiang.
I heard what you just said to Fei Fei.
I made a mistake about you regarding the incident about the lipstick.
It wasn't you who instigated Fei Fei to frame Cai Yun.
But even if I made a mistake about you, why did you protect your sister?
She is my sister. If she does something wrong, of course, I have to be responsible for her.
Since you can do this, why can't I?
In the past, Fei Fei wasn't like this.
In the past, she was very innocent and naive.
It's my fault. I didn't have the time to watch her grow up.
Ever since my father passed away, Fei Fei and my mom have been with me.
Thus, my mom and Fei Fei
need my protection for life.
I understand.
My stepmom and Cai Yun also need my protection.
♫ Gently, I gently tried to inquire ♫
♫ but did not ask you whether I was your fated love. ♫
♫ Rushing, rushing to capture you. ♫
♫ In the end I did not get your heart. ♫
♫ I'm not willing to give up (the love), but I can't have it either. ♫
♫ I fight a bitter battle between advancing and retreating. ♫
♫ I didn't see through to your eyes or heart ♫
♫ but I've already fallen in love with your tenderness. ♫
Let me go.
Don't!
Miss.
Do you know me? Why do you keep following me?
Who are you? Why did you come here?
I was asked to go to the warehouse to bring this colored silk.
Miss. What gives you the right to question me?
I personally saw your hand
being cut off. You were also bleeding profusely.
It was this hand.
Miss. You are referring to this?
That was only just an act.
The hand was false and the blood was pig's blood.
You are fortunate that you are an employee of the Jiang family.
Why would Mr Jiang do something like this? Who do you take him for?
Looks like you know Mr Jiang very well.
Of course, I understand him. He is a good man. In the past, my name was Hua Zi.
I almost died in the streets. Mr Jiang saw me, fed me and even took me in.
He even gave me a job.
So that's to say, since he helped you, you helped him to do things that are against nature.
How could you say that about Mr Jiang? I have been with him for ten years.
I have never seen him do any harmful deeds.
- Really?
- Of course.
Miss. You are really strange.
Could it be that Jiang Yu is not that bad as I think. Did I make a mistake about him?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Wu Long. You are here?
Seriously.
When I saw you in Jiang Yu's room yesterday, I didn't have time to talk to you.
How did you become so heavy? Looks like Jiang Yu has been treating you well.
Wu Cai Hong.
Young Master Jiang wants to see you.
Why is he looking for me?
I don't know. Go there and you will find out.
Take a look. See which bracelet looks like yours.
Go ahead.
Take a look to see which threads you need for the bracelet.
Take a look.
Each colour is different.
Brother Shao Tian personally dyed the colours for this bracelet.
He also personally weaved it for me.
To me, it's second to none.
But thank you for taking trouble over this.
It was Fei Fei's fault. As her brother,
I should help her to redeem herself.
By the way, I just saw that person.
Who?
The man who had his hand cut off.
Why did you put on a show for Brother Shao Tian? Why did you do that?
I was forced to. (had no choice.)
I'm an innocent person who you accused of killing your father.
Of course, I want to find out the truth.
You are really not my father's killer?
If I'm really the killer, the fountain pen is such an important piece of evidence, would I leave it at home?
Furthermore, it was that easy for you to find it.
Why were you at the scene when something happened to my father then?
I definitely went to see your father that day. I went there to settle scores with him.
I told him that I started the process of acquiring Ling Long.
You have always wanted to defeat Ling Long.
Yes but
I used legal methods to fight. I have never used any underhanded tactics.
Tell me honestly then. The money that was stolen from Ling Long,
Old Cai and you really didn't do it?
I'm very sure that the money is in Zhou Shao Tian's hands. Why do you
think I pursued him?
I only wanted to force out the origin of the money and also to clear my name.
It will also show you clearly the person next to you
and the kind of person he is.
Jiang Yu. I can believe that
you didn't kill my father
but you can't suspect Shao Tian.
He wouldn't do that.
I know that you won't believe what I'm saying now
but I will show you the evidence in future.
Come with me to a place now.
- Where are we going?
- You will know once we are there.
I just don't believe that I will lose to Zhou Shao Tian.
See if there is anything you like. Just choose any one.
If you don't find anything to your liking here,
just tell me and I will personally dye it for you. There won't be a problem.
The colour is quite similar
but it's a bit off.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
I finally found it.
You found it?
Over there.
I will do it myself.
Look at the condition of your hand. How are you going to do it?
I will help you to hold it then.
Pull this.
Show me your bracelet.
So, it's a seven coloured rainbow. (Cai Hong is Mandarin for rainbow)
When Brother Shao Tian gave me this bracelet, he said that it suited my name.
This Zhou Shao Tian really knows how to humour girls.
Unfortunately for him, rainbows only come after the rain.
He is so shady. He will never be able to catch a rainbow in his lifetime.
It doesn't seem to be nice for you to be talking about him this way.
You shouldn't speak ill of others. It is not what a gentleman would do.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Here.
Then, I'm going back to work.
What are you doing?
You indecisive little guy. Now you push me aside.
But animals can't lie. He will be good to whoever is close to him.
Looks like you are treating my Wu Long nicely.
At least, he is better than you and he can differentiate between good and bad people.
So to say, are you saying that you are a good person?
At least, I dare to say that I didn't do anything unethical.
You can tell the truth then.
Right , Wu Long?
I'm going back to work.
It's exactly like the previous one
but it's still not the original bracelet.
Brother.
Fei Fei.
Where did you go? Looks like you are in a good mood today.
Is that so?
You are my brother. Of course, I can see your moods.
But brother, does your good mood have anything to do with Wu Cai Hong?
No.
Where did you take her to last night? You came back very late.
Aren't you a busybody?
Can't I even ask?
There is a new dye factory called Rong Da. They sent you the invitation.
The invitation arrived last night. Do you want to go?
We are in the same industry. Of course, we should go.
Okay, I know.
So how? Does it look nice?
Of course, you look good in this.
I'm asking you if the dress is nice.
You are beautiful and look good in anything.
I just knew it was useless asking you.
Miss. Why are you so happy today?
Because my brother and I are attending a launch ceremony today.
I can't embarrass him.
That is right. Don't give cheek and embarrass him.
You know how to flatter.
But you used to attend such events with Young Master in the past.
Why are you so anxious today?
That's right. I keep thinking that person standing next to my brother
is definitely going to be me.
When did I start to feel so anxious?