The Cage of Love
Episode 33
Mom. Cai Hong is here.
Don't let her come in.
Madam. I only want to visit you.
During the fire,
you risked your life to save me.
I should thank you,
but I really can't face you.
When I look at him, I think of my husband's
miserable death caused by your dad
Thus,
I'm requesting of you,
don't let me see you again.
I know. My dad had done something unforgivable.
I can't do anything about what happened.
Thus, I would like to beg for your forgiveness.
Madam. As long as you are willing to forgive me,
I'm willing to do anything.
I'm willing to pay any price.
Mom. Cai Hong is already kneeling down.
Let her kneel down.
I will never dote on her.
Fei Fei, shut the door.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
It's useless for you to wait here. Looking at the scenery?
Not only will I admit that you treat Cai Hong very well.
When I look at you sometimes, I also think that if I let Cai Hong go, it's for her own good.
Letting you be with her is the best choice.
But sometimes, I also feel that
only I would be able to give up everything in order to protect her.
Regardless of who she is, why don't I let her stay with me?
I will feel assured this way.
I have thought about the same thing as you.
Too bad I am not you.
My companion and care
may not make her happy.
The one is Cai Hong's heart is you.
I could do more for Cai Hong than you.
It was the best for Cai Hong to be with me
but later, I realised that
no matter what I do, it won't be what she wants.
What she wants is you.
If you and Cai Hong get together, the path will be tough
but if you retreat because of these hardships,
that means I would have misjudged you.
I know that you are not that kind of person.
It's because I know that even if I'm not happy with it,
I'm willing to hand Cai Hong over to you.
You must protect her and give her happiness.
Aren't you going to see her now?
Cai Hong, are you okay?
- Stop kneeling. Get up.
- Don't bother about me.
It's my father's mistakes. As his daughter,
I must pay the debts on behalf of my father.
Jiang Yu.
Mom. I'm taking Cai Hong back first.
Have a good rest.
Karma.
Mom, have some tea.
Frankly, Cai Hong is very pitiful.
She hasn't recovered from her injuries and she kneeled down on the cold floor.
Even more so even though she got injured because of others,
she needs to shoulder the consequences of her father's mistakes.
This is not fair either.
It would have been great if the fire would have burned away the grudges between the two families.
The most pitiful one is brother. He's caught in the middle.
Like a saw that
has pierced his heart.
Why are you looking at me?
Do you know that
by doing this, I will misunderstand.
I don't think you will misunderstand.
In any case, it's not a misunderstanding.
Cai Hong. I was wrong in the past.
I didn't treasure you well.
Sorry.
But if
we were together,
your mom will be hurt.
You told me that
hatred can be resolved.
You have always been working hard
and paying for it.
Starting from today, I won't let you fight the battle alone.
I will stay with you. Let's work hard together.
We have the biggest problem between us.
It's the grudge between the Wu and Jiang families.
Cai Hong.
Life is short and life is fragile.
Anything can happen in any day.
Just like two days ago. I almost lost you in the fire.
I don't want to wait till I have lost it before I try to get it back.
We should treasure them when we can enjoy them.
As for the grudge between our families,
let's face it together.
But Madam...
I believe that as long as we work hard together,
we can move her heart.
She will definitely accept us.
Are you willing to face it together with me
and face the trials together?
I'm willing.
Miss.
Uncle Lai.
All these materials don't have the right feel.
When we get the Jiang's secret formula, then Miss will be able to dye the way you want.
I don't want to wait anymore.
When are we going to start to kidnap Madam Jiang?
These few days, our people have been spying at the hospital.
There are many eyes at the hospital. Jiang Yu is always at the hospital too.
We can't take action.
Why don't we wait?
I don't want to wait anymore.
If I continue to wait, I'm afraid that I will go crazy one day.
If they collect evidence against me,
the Military Governor will shoot me.
In the eyes of these men,
I'm not worth anything.
I will send men to take action now.
Uncle Lai.
Once we have gotten the secret formula,
let's leave this place.
I don't want this kind of life anymore.
Doctor, is the medical examination over?
Yes.
Don't worry, Miss Wu.
Your injuries are recovering well.
Will they leave any scars?
Even if there are scars, you will be just as beautiful. Everything's fine.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't worry. As long as she takes her medicines on time,
and she doesn't get injured again in the future,
I guarantee that there won't be any scars.
But there may be a mark on your forehead.
Okay, have a good rest. Call me if there is anything.
Doctor, I will see you out.
- Okay, go back.
- Take care.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
The weather is nice today. Go out for a walk with me.
The doctor already told you to rest well. Don't wander anywhere.
I have some matters to attend to. I'm going out for a while.
Where are you going?
I'm not telling you. I will be back soon.
You are already keeping secrets from me so soon?
Are you regretting now?
It's too late.
Boss Jiang.
Let's go.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
- Hello, Sir.
- Hello.
May I ask what you need?
I would like to customise a necklace.
Please enter.
Hello, Madam Jiang.
We are here to examine you.
Please come with us to the medical room.
I don't have a medical examination today.
To add further. I'm recovering well.
Look. I'm going to be discharged soon.
It's like this, Madam Jiang. This will be the last medical examination
to make sure that you can recover completely and get discharged.
Where is my previous doctor?
I'm very familiar with the doctors here. Why haven't I seen you before?
These few are not bad.
Yes, and this too.
Many rich housewives have seen these.
How about this?
Sir. You have really good taste.
This is our shop's treasure.
This necklace picks people to wear
to be their Miss.
Madam Jiang, are you there?
Who... who is it?
It's Cai Hong. Can I come in to see you?
Get lost. I already told you many times that I don't want to see you.
Make the person outside leave
- I didn't.
- If you try it, I will shoot you.
I'm not feeling very well.
I don't want to see any guests.
Madam. Your voice doesn't sound normal. Where are you unwell?
Don't bother me. Just leave.
Why don't I call the doctor to see you?
No need. Just leave.
Madam. I'm really worried about your health.
I'm coming in now.
Don't bother me. Leave now.
Even if you don't want to see me, I can't just ignore that.
I'm really coming in now.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Don't move.
You better be sensible.
Let's go.
Don't be rash.
I'm telling you, this is the hospital. If there is a gunshot sound, you wont be able to escape.
As long as you listen to me, I won't kill you.
We only want Madam Jiang.
Are you using her to threaten Jiang Yu?
This is none of your business.
If you are smart, don't foil our plan. Don't waste time. Take her away.
Don't capture Madam. Exchange her life for mine.
No. Let her go.
Madam Jiang.
All of you better stay still.
Don't try to play any tricks.
I know. You are trying to stall for time, right?
Believe me or not, I will kill her.
I know who you are.
Lu Man must have sent you here.
Miss Lu doesn't want you to come here and kill anyone.
She wants you to come here
because she knows that Madam Jiang is very important.
She sent to you do her bad things. dirty work.
When the time comes, even if she lets you off,
the police won't let you go.
Rotten wench. Shut up.
If you speak again, I will kill you.
Jiang Yu. He treats me well.
I'm very important to him.
Believe me. Use me to help hand over the secret formula.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
No. She's lying.
Take me away and you will achieve your goal.
Don't do this.
If you make noise again, I will kill you.
Cut the crap. Take them both along.
No It's too dangerous for you to do this.
Many doctors and nurses in the hospital recognise Madam Jiang. I don't know anyone here. I'm the safest.
Trust me. Jiang Yu will use all means to help me.
Okay, just take her along.
- Let's go.
- No, don't take her away.
Madam.
Shut up. Let's go.
Cai Hong.
Mom.
Mom!
Mom. Doctor!
- Is anyone there?
- What's wrong?
Something has happened to my mother.
What's wrong with Mom?
I don't know either.
When I just came in, she was already in this state.
Madam Jiang's head suffered a powerful blow.
Fortunately, it's not serious. She will be when she wakes up.J
She was in her room. How did she get hurt?
Er... this we cannot conclude why either.
- I'm going to prescribe some medicines for Madam Jiang.
- Thanks, Doctor.
Fei Fei, keep watch on Mom. Take good care of her. I'm going out for a while and will be back soon.
Brother!
Cai Hong!
- Did you see Miss Wu?
- No.
- Did you see Miss Wu? - No
Cai Hong!
Mr Jiang. Madam Jiang is awake. She keeps crying.
Go there now.
Fei Fei. What should we do?
Mom.
- Yu Er.
- You are awake. Are you okay?
Cai Hong has been taken away by the bad people.
What should we do?
- You must think of a way to save her?
- Cai Hong has been taken away?
I don't know.
Two fake doctors came in
and wanted to take me away. Cai Hong, that foolish girl,
to save me, she...
Do you know those two doctors?
No.
Cai Hong seemed to know those two bad people.
It seems like they are employees of Miss Lu.
Yu Er.
Save her now.
Yu Er. You must think of a way to save her.
Cai Hong.
- Cai Hong.
- Cai Hong is missing. Where did she go?
- Cai Hong was kidnapped by someone.
- Kidnapped?
Who kidnapped her?
Lu Man's men.
Jiang Yu. It's always you! Every time when something happens to Cai Hong, it's always because of you.
Why weren't you with her? Where did you go?
Do you think I wanted it to be like this? I don't want it either.
Where did she go?
Where did she go? Say something!
I'm going to find Lu Man. I'm going alone.
What's the use of finding Lu Man?
If she took Cai Hong away, why wouldn't she run away? Use your brain!
What you can only do now is to wait. Wait till she states her terms.
Lu Man, I won't let you off.
Miss Lu.
Please.
Miss Wu. We meet again.
So, it's you.
You kidnapped me just for the Jiang family's secret formula, right?
Miss Wu is smart. You are right on the mark.
If I didn't guess wrongly,
I'm guessing that you killed my father too.
Boss Wu. I was here early by a few minutes.
I didn't see anyone on the way here.
I even thought I got the time wrong.
Today is my birthday. I let the staff off.
Old Master Wu, you are hurt.
So how? Do you want to go to the hospital?
I'm fine. It's just a small injury.
Boss Wu. I'm here to help Ling Long get through the hard times.
Okay then. Let's discuss real business.
Okay then. I will get to the point then.
I am aware of Ling Long's situation.
I am willing to help.
but...
But what. As long as I can do it,
I will definitely do my best.
I am someone that doesn't like to force people.
The request that I want, as long as you are willing,
you can definitely do it.
Please speak.
I want the Jiang family's secret formula. The price is negotiable.
I already told you that
I don't have the secret formula.
A straightforward person does not resort to insinuations.
I know that the Jiang family's secret formula is with you.
Moreover, Ling Long and the secret formula don't belong to you either.
Hand over the secret formula in exchange for cash to save Ling Long. Think about it.
This transaction will be worth it.
You are thinking too much.
I will repeat myself. I don't have any secret formulas.
You should think carefully.
This is your last lifeline.
I don't need to think anymore then.
I'm telling you. If you don't hand over the secret formula today, don't think of leaving here alive.
Shoot then.
Fire the gun!
Let me tell you. Even if I have it,
I won't give it to you.
Do you want to fire the gun? Fire then!
Go away.
- Give it to me.
- Let go.
Give me the secret formula now.
I'm telling you. Even if I die,
I will never give it to you.
Give it to me.
Dad!
It was me
who killed him.
ut you don't have the evidence.
Without any evidence, what can you do?
I will have the evidence sooner or later.
By doing this,
you are not afraid that God will punish you?
Don't talk to me about God.
I don't believe in this.
God will never come.
If you are that worried, why didn't God open his eyes
and deliver you to me instead?
By the way, you seems to be Jiang Yu's girlfriend.
Frankly, I planned to kidnap Madam Jiang
and use her to threaten Jiang Yu to trade her for the secret formula.
But little did i know, you would fall into my trap.
I will use you then to trade with Jiang Yu.
You are wrong then. I'm not Jiang Yu's girlfriend.
I lied to you.
Jiang Yu will never come.
My father harmed his father.
Wu's family and Jiang's family have death feud
Consider your plan as a having failed.
Do you know what kind of people I hate the most?
Those who lie to me.
If you are not Jiang Yu's girlfriend, you better pray to God to help you.
If not, you have only one life.
You will not succeed!
Is it? That might not be the case.
I can tell that
Jiang Yu doesn't treat you like anyone else.
He will definitely come to save you.
I almost forgot. Zhou Shao Tian too.
Why don't we do this? Let's play a game and bet on
which of these two men will save your first?
If they are late,
I will kill them for you.
Okay?
You are a lunatic.
Jiang Yu, don't come.
Don't ever come.
Brother Shao Tian.
Don't come either.
You must not come either.
Mr Jiang. Someone delivered a letter for you.
Who?
- I'm not very sure. He gave it and left.
- Thanks.
- Don't mention it.
Jiang Yu, bring the Jiang's family secret formula alone
and meet me at the street tonight.
Don't be late. Don't report this to the police.
Otherwise Cai Hong will die.
Good luck
What do you plan to do?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Is it because you can't bear to part with your family's secret formula?
How could I do that?
I know that the secret formula is priceless to you.
In the past, no matter how I forced you, you wouldn't hand over.
This secret formula is precious to Jiang's house.
Are you willing to take it out in exchange for Cai Hong's life?
Don't even talk about the secret formula. Even if it's my life, I would use it to trade for her.
It is no expense.
I know Lu Man very well.
I'm worried that once you hand over the secret formula to her,
she won't let you and Cai Hong come out alive.
This is what I'm most worried about.
We must think of a flawless plan.
Why don't we do this? It's still better that I go to Lu Man's place alone.
Go and seek Director Chen's help. We will meet again later.
But Lu Man has a spy within the police force. You must be extra careful.
Miss.
Come in.
Miss. Everything has been arranged. We are only just waiting for Jiang Yu.
This is...
the pin that your mom left.
Yes.
This is the only thing my Mom left me.
I'm going to wear this today
and prove to her that I will definitely get the secret formula.
I want to create her favourite gown again.
I want to prove to her that
I will bring back Wang's house glory.
Ke Ke.
I am sure your mom will understand your kindness.
Your wish...
your mom in heaven,
will protect you and make it come true.
Uncle Lai.
All these years,
I have been around those wealthy and powerful men everyday,
drinking with them, serving them.
I had enough.
Starting from today,
I am going to end that kind of dirty life.
Once I get the secret formula,
I want to start a new life.
Then I won't need to waste my energy serving those people.
Those disgusting people.
There will come a day,
I will get those who took advantage of me
and cut off their limbs.
Ke Ke. Don't worry. Even if I sacrifice my life today,
I will help you to fulfill your wish.
Are all the men ready?
Yes.
Don't even talk about Jiang Yu. Even a fly wouldn't be able to escape.
Don't be too complacent.
Jiang Yu is very sly.
Zhou Shao Tian is very toxic.
Tell our people to be on high alert.
Once we get the secret formula, all will get rewarded.
Yes.
Miss. Why are we preparing these?
Jiang Yu is very sly.
I won't know whether he will bring the real or fake secret formula.
Thus, I want to personally see him dye the cloth
and make sure that the secret formula is real.
But this secret formula is from Jiang ancestors,
Would Jiang Yu bring it? th
I can only take a gamble.
I want to see
in Jiang Yu's heart whether the secret formula is important or
if Wu Cai Hong is more important.
What about Zhou Shao Tian?
He will never let this rest.
Zhou Shao Tian.
When you meet Jiang Yu later, don't bring him straight here first.
Take him for a few rounds.
If you find that there are people following him, get rid of them.
Yes.
Wu Cai Hong.
I almost forgot.
You are Wu Hong Da's daughter.
You definitely know about the secret formula.
So what if I do?
Even if I know, I won't tell you.
You have such a tight mouth.
Tell me then.
What should I use to make you talk?
Why don't we try this needle
and see if it will make you talk?
If you hand over the secret formula to me now,
I won't let you die.
Dream on.
If it doesn't belongs to you, it won't.
You will never obtain the secret formula.