The Cage of Love
Episode 26
Quick! Let's leave now.
Catch them.
Quick!
Don't move!
- Mom.
- Don't move.
Don't move!
Go over there.
Catch him.
Don't chase after him anymore. Let him go.
Everything's fine.
Kid, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Fall back.
Be good. Don't be afraid.
Let's go.
Brother!
Something bad has happened. Old Cai's wife and son have been captured by the police.
We have been targeted. Brother, leave now.
Leave Huzhou and hide for a while.
Ah Li.
I'm sorry.
Nurse, did you see my brother?
Mr Jiang?
I just saw him leaving with two policemen.
He was apprehended by the police?
It didn't seem so.
Wu Mansion.
Brother Shao Tian. Why didn't you go in since you are here?
Cai Hong.
I would like to take you to a place.
It's so late. Where are you taking me?
There is something I need to tell you.
I'm afraid that if I don't tell you now, I won't find the opportunity again.
Are you leaving? Will you be in danger?
Brother Shao Tian. It's already very late and you brought me here...
Do you have something to tell me?
Didn't you say that
when you encountered an unhappy event, you would come here?
Cai Hong.
Do you remember what I told you?
This
has magical powers.
If anything bad happens,
as long as I walk around this,
everything will go back to the way it was.
I would like everything to go back to the way it was.
This way, we can start anew.
But I don't understand, Brother Shao Tian.
If you want to go back to the way it was,
which part should we go back to?
That's right. Where should we go back to?
For so many years, I have taken so many paths
and experienced so many matters.
If I hadn't missed that chance...
If everything could really restart,
I would go back to its original state.
Or back to the time when my father passed away.
Or also back to the first time when I joined Ling Long.
Or the first time my father took me to your home
and the first time that I met you.
If my father didn't pass away that early,
I would never had gone to Ling Long. If I didn't go,
I would have never met you.
If I haven't met you...
Cai Hong,
Frankly, I know that
everything can't go back to the way it was.
But I don't have any regrets.
It's because I met you
when I took this path.
Knowing you was not a painful period for me.
It was a most beautiful thing.
Brother Shao Tian.
Can you tell me what has happened?
- I'm really worried about you.
- Cai Hong.
Remember what I said.
Perhaps, I may not get the chance to say this to you again.
Do you know that being with you
was the most beautiful moments in my life.
I did not regret
♫They will wither. ♫
♫Just as people do. ♫
♫Yet, I still have to believe.♫
♫ Who are you to me? ♫
♫ I am so sad ♫
♫when you let go of my clasped hands♫
♫Whether you are in my heart or in my thoughts.♫
♫ Who are you to me ♫
- I love you.
♫Freedom of flying like in a dream♫
♫You give your love out to hastily♫
I really love you
♫ the aftertaste. ♫
Brother Shao Tian. You must be hiding something from me.
Don't tell me that compared to when you went to the battle ground,
it can't be worse than that, right?
I beg you,
can you not leave?
♫You are the sunshine in my heart, the aftertaste,♫
♫ Who are you to me ♫
Don't be afraid.
Many events will become things of the past.
♫To fly over in my heart.The aftertaste.♫
♫ Who are you to me ♫
Everything else will disappear.
♫As you let go of my clasped hand.♫
♫Whether the same feeling is in my heart.♫
♫ Who are you to me ♫
- The night is really beautiful.
How I wish we can be together forever...
to experience the world, for all seasons
and forever be together.
Even if I want to be with you forever,
it's time for me to take you home.
Cai Hong, I will take you home.
You haven't told me yet what happened.
Tomorrow.
I will tell you tomorrow.
Go back and have a good night's sleep now. When you get up tomorrow, you will know the answer.
Okay?
Tomorrow then?
Tomorrow.
Brother Shao Tian, your hands are very cold.
I remember that your hands were very warm in the past.
You were always warming my hands.
I didn't think that today, it would be me doing this instead.
Cai Hong, thank you.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Don't move.
Zhou Shao Tian, come back with us to the police station.
Old Cai. You already admitted that you stole Ling Long's money.
I'm giving you one last chance now.
Do you have an accomplice or not?
I already told you that I did it alone. I didn't have any accomplice.
Fine.
Bring them in.
Why are you here?
- Dear.
- Dad.
Son. Director Chen.
This doesn't concern my wife and son. Why did you bring them here?
Dear, we almost didn't see you again.
Do you know that a lot of scary events happened last night?
Take them away first.
Dear! Son!
- I'm scared, Dad.
-Sit down.
Old Cai.
Your wife and son were in the hands of the bad guys.
We rescued them.
I can guarantee their safety now.
Old Cai.
You stole Ling Long's money. This is not a small crime.
Do you want to spend your entire life in jail?
Why don't you think for yourself and your wife and son too?
I really want to help you.
If you are willing to cooperate, I will personally ask the court to help you.
But first,
you must tell the truth.
It was Zhou Shao Tian.
Zhou Shao Tian forced me to do everything.
If you are sure, lay your bets now.
It was
Zhao Shao Tian that set the trap for me.
He lured me to gamble and I subsequently went into debts.
I couldn't pay my debts and he forced me to work with him
to establish a fake company.
We then used a fake document and forged Old Master Wu's signature.
All of Ling Long's money was transferred to the fake company.
Zhou Shao Tian forced me to do all this.
He slowly planned all this and forced me to take action.
He later controlled my family
and pushed everything on me to take the fall alone.
Director Chen. You must believe me, please.
Let him sign the statement.
Mr Zhou.
Sit.
I asked you here in the hopes that you will cooperate.
We would like to ask you some questions.
I hope you can reply truthfully.
Old Cai has been caught by us.
Furthermore, he has implicated you.
Do you have anything to say before we start?
Jiang Yu. You are really a schemer.
You already can't wait to give me the final verdict.
Zhou Shao Tian. I know that you took Ling Long's money.
Did you kill Wu Hong Da too?
Why did you give me the name of a murderer so quickly?
Whose idea is this?
You only need to answer me by saying yes or no.
It's not that simple as saying yes or no.
Yes or no.
In your eyes,
you already believed Jiang Yu and find me guilty.
Cai Hong, answer me.
Don't waste your time. Old Cai has already confessed.
Do you still have anything to defend yourself?
The police charged those who are guilty based on evidence.
Since you are sure that I killed him, show me your proof then.
Fine. Take him away.
Since he knows that we are here,
by answering him,
is that really that hard to do?
Get in the rickshaw. I will take you home.
No need. I would like to walk alone.
Go back first.
Miss. Old Cai has already confessed and implicated Zhou Shao Tian.
Zhou Shao Tian has now been taken away by the police for investigation.
Did Zhou Shao Tian confess?
No. I heard that he was overbearing, refusing to say anything.
Should we go and save Zhou Shao Tian?
Not yet. Go with me to the cell to see him first.
Miss. What you mean is that...
When Wu Hong Da died that day, he met with three people..
Zhou Shao Tian, Jiang Yu and Old Cai.
I forced Jiang Yu before. He definitely doesn't have the secret formula.
I want to use this opportunity to ask Zhou Shao Tian.
If he does not have the secret formula,
he is abandoned.
I will concentrate on going against him then.
You are really wise. I will go and make the preparations.
Frankly, I know that everything can't go back to the way it was.
But I don't have any regrets.
It's because I met you when I took this path.
Knowing you was not a painful period for me.
It was a most beautiful thing.
Cai Hong, I love you.
I really love you very much. Don't be afraid.
Everything will be in the past.
Everything else will disappear.
Even though I want to be with your forever,
it's time for me to take you home.
What Brother Shao Tian told me is definitely not false.
I don't believe that he killed my father.
I'm going to ask him again.
I really don't have anything to say to you.
Go home.
You are not telling me anything.
Is it because you have nothing to say
and no evidence?
Brother Shao Tian.
Are you really not going to explain
or apologise?
You don't even want to say this to me?
Last night,
I remember that you told me
that you love me.
You would protect me.
Why did you take Ling Long's money then?
Why did you harm my father?
My knowing you is just like a dream.
I have woken up from my dream.
It's time to face reality.
I won't believe it.
It wasn't a dream.
I want to hear you say it.
Did you cause my father to die?
Is it that difficult to tell me the truth?
Please show Miss Wu out.
Miss Wu. Let's go.
Leave this to the police.
Shao Tian.
You did so much for Cai Hong
and what did you get?
You did so much for her and she doesn't even see you.
She only hates you
for stealing Ling Long's money and killing her father.
Miss Lu, in the end, I will find out what you are doing.
We are considered friends.
You are already in this state.
I wanted to come here and see if there is anything I could help you with.
I can also do my part as a friend.
When did you become someone that would miss a friend?
Even more so when we are not friends at all.
Just come and get what you want.
You have never trusted me.
You are really a direct person.
Fine, I like direct people too.
We won't waste any efforts this way.
I will get to the point.
- Do you have the secret formula or not?
- I already told you many times
that I don't have it.
It looks like you will never trust me.
Don't you get it?
The reason they forced you to confess is to make you die.
I'm asking you because I want to save you.
If you have the secret formula, you can tell me.
I can plead to the Military Governor
and tell him to put in a few good words for you and get you out of jail.
Wu Cai Hong will never believe you.
I'm the only one in this world who can help you.
If you give me the secret formula,
I can get you out.
I can let you get far away from here.
What I already told you,
I won't repeat it again.
Fine.
This is your last chance.
Since you have such an attitude, I can't help you then.
Have you really thought it through?
I never thought of
letting you help me.
Fine. Since you don't need my help,
don't blame me for not being righteous.
We already have a witness now.
Why doesn't he defend himself?
Did he really take Ling Long's money?
Sister. I can understand how you feel.
Shao Tian is just like an older brother in our family.
Frankly speaking, I find it hard to accept it too.
Old Cai, Zhou Shao Tian.
The reason I asked both of you here is because this is our first confrontation.
I have already recorded what you said.
It will be used in the court in future.
Director Chen, I understand. I will answer all your questions truthfully.
Okay, Old Cai.
You said that you collaborated with Zhou Shao Tian to steal Ling Long's money.
It was RMB$1 million.
Zhou Shao Tian. Do you have anything to say?
Not answering, right?
I am telling you,
this sum of money is the same as what Ling Long's account showed.
Old Cai. How did you split the money?
Thirty and seventy percent.
I took thirty percent and Zhou Shao Tian took seventy.
Is Old Cai telling the truth?
Both of you took such a big sum of money. What did you do with it?
I used it to settle my debts. I owed a lot of it.
I know that you are telling the truth.
We went to investigate your debtors. They admitted to it.
Zhou Shao Tian. What about you?
What did you do with such a big sum of money?
If you don't talk, we have no choice then.
Invite Miss Lu Man here. You must be polite.
Miss. These are Rong Da's new products.
Compared to the textiles used with the Jiang family's secret formula,
these don't deserve to be looked at.
Uncle Lai.
Looks like the secret formula is with Old Cai.
Regardless of which methods you use,
you must bring Old Cai here.
Miss. I have an informant in the police station.
This is not a difficult task.
It only depends on when there is a suitable time to do it.
Wait for Director Chen to get the evidence first
and find Zhou Shao Tian guilty,
we will do it then.
Miss Lu. There are two policemen outside.
They would like you to go to the police station for a while.
It seems to be connected to Zhou Shao Tian.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Director Chen. Shouldn't we do this in the interrogation room?
Miss Lu's identity is different. It's more comfortable to do it here in my office.
We would also like to thank you for taking time from your busy schedule to cooperate with us.
It's fine.
Director Chen, didn't you say that Zhao Shao Tian could have to pay with his life?
I only just established a factory with him.
I won't be involved right?
Miss Lu, don't be afraid.
We, police won't accuse the good people.
We are only worried about whether he asked you to do things which you shouldn't have been doing.
How could this be possible? But talking about this,
I don't know what I should do or not do.
There wasn't anything suspicious?
Frankly, ever since Zhou Shao Tiao showed up,
I have been hesitating about something.
I wonder whether I should tell the police.
Please speak.
Frankly, Zhou Shao Tian is the real owner of Rong Da.
He funded the company. He only used my name for the company.
I didn't imagine that Zhou Shao Tian was the real owner of Rong Da.
Yes. At that time, he told me that I didn't have to come up with any money or efforts.
He just borrowed my name to start the factory.
He also shared 40% of the profit with me.
I am thinking, it was such a good offer.
In a moment of foolishness, I did not think too much that
about something bad happening to him.
The more I thought about it, it didn't sound right. Could there be such a good thing on earth?
Did he tell you where he got the money from?
He really didn't tell me anything about this.
It's just that...
I did ask him.
I told him that since he has such a big sum of money, why didn't he take the post of the boss
instead of being the subordinate?
He told me that this money can't be made known.
He's was using me to launder it.
Miss Lu. Other than this, do you have anything else to tell me?
Let me think.
There is something else which seemed very strange.
Not long ago, he asked me for help.
He wanted me to help him order a Parker pen.
At that time, I didn't think it was a big deal and helped him with the favour.
I looked for General Lu's people and helped him make a pen.
Cai Hong. In the past, you told me that
you wanted to buy this fountain pen as your father's birthday present.
But because you fought over this with someone, you didn't manage to buy it.
I wanted you to be happy. I ordered the exact same fountain pen for you.
If this fountain pen has harmed anyone,
its tip wouldn't be like this.
You were to the one who got the fountain pen for Zhou Shao Tian?
Yes. This was not so long ago.
It was just a month ago.
At that time, he needed it very urgently.
Why do you find it strange then?
At that time, I didn't think much about it. Could something had happened to him then?
I later asked him why he needed that fountain pen.
Furthermore, he wanted it that urgently. He said that he wanted to use it as gratitude.
As gratitude to help him avoid a murder case.
I thought he was joking with me then.
Who knew that he would be caught?
Record all this.
Miss Lu.
We are almost done with the questions.Thank you.
Don't mention it. I only just told you what I know
in order not to get involved.
Let me get someone to take you back.
No need. My subordinate is waiting for me outside
Okay then.
- Please.
- Bye.
Miss. Did everything go smoothly?
Yes. It went too smoothly.
It actually made me feel nostalgic.
Zhou Shao Tian. What a pity.
Miss. What you meant is...
Uncle Lai.
Bring that contract for Rong Da that I signed with Zhou Shao Tian
and hand it to Director Chen.
Also, go visit General Huang and tell him about the fountain pen.
Let him use it as an evidence.
Yes. This way, not only will we close Wu Hong Da's case,
we will also push Zhou Shao Tian into a dead end.
Don't blame me for being cruel.
If he must blame anyone, he should blame himself for choosing the wrong woman.
He choose the wrong path.
Regarding Old Cai, make the arrangements quickly.
Okay.
This is Old Cai's statement.
This is Lu Man's statement.
Warlord Lu's counselor Huang's statement.
The telegram sent by the overseas manufacturer of the Parker fountain pen.
And also, the Rong Da's contract that you signed with Miss Lu Man.
We will follow the law and hand over this evidence to the court.
If there is anything else you want to say, you can do it now.
But you can choose not to talk and hire a lawyer.
- You can talk again in court.
- I will give up the rights to a lawyer.
Zhou Shao Tian. I have known you for a short while.
You are a smart person. All the evidence is here.
I think you should know what your end result is.
I know.
Headline! Headline!
Soon they will get to the bottom of Wu Hong Da's murder.
Tomorrow's the trial for the suspected murderer.
Since there was still a ledger that wasn't burnt,
before finishing with this exquisite book,
they were not able to drain the warehouse.
Thus, it was not burnt by Zhou Shao Tian.
It was only discovered yesterday.
There should be proof in here that showed Zhou Shao Tian made use of Ling Long's money.
See if it's of any help to you.
It will definitely be useful.
Thanks.
It's getting late. I still need to prepare for court.
See you in court.
I won't be going today. If you have any other matters, you can look for me again.
You are not going? I thought you would definitely go.
That's regarding the Wu family. It doesn't concern us. Why would I go there?
But you have been very helpful.
That's because Zhou Shao Tian made everyone a suspect.
I was aggressive because I was only protecting myself.
Protecting yourself?
Yes.
Okay, it's self protection then.
Wu Cai Hong needs someone by her side now.
I'm afraid that she won't be able to handle the end result.
It's okay. She has her family with her.
Furthermore, she needs to learn how to be independent.
Let her get used to it.
Mr Jiang. On your exterior, you seem very cold
but actually, you are a warm hearted person.
You could even see that I'm warm hearted?
Perhaps so.
Okay, I will be here today.
If there is any other matters, you can always look for me.
I'm leaving first then.
According to witness testimony provided by the police, today
is the court case of Zhao Shao Tian. The public trial.
It begins now.
According to the testimony of the former Finance Manager at Ling Long and Old Cai,
as Wu Hong Da's secretary, you schemed with Old Cai
to use his position to take illegal funds
and embezzle RMB$10 million.
About this allegation, do you have what it takes to refute it?
According to the testimony of Rong Da's Boss Lu Man,
you transferred the money from Ling Long to her to found Rong Da.
Actually, you are the real owner of Rong Da.
Do you have any objections to these allegations?
Zhou Shao Tian. Based on the overseas telegram from the manufacturer of the Parker pen,
you bought a fountain pen.
After the confirmed death of Wu Hong Da, his wound was examined.
According to Lu Man and Jiang Yu's testimony,
you got the very same pen handed over by Huang Junsheng.
Those two statements seal our presumptions.
You bought the fountain pen first to cause the death of Wu Hong Da.
Afterwards you were helped by Huang Junsheng.
The motive was to cover up the evidence of the Parker pen being used as an accessory for murder.
It was to cover up the truth for killing Wu Hong Da.
Do you need to defend your against this?
Why isn't he saying anything?
He's been asked several times. Why doesn't he speak?
Shao Tian. Say something, quick.
Based on the evidence, the court confirmed that
he joined forces with Zhou Shao, Lin Long's former chief financial officer,
and embezzled Ling Long of RMB$10 million.
After being unmasked, Zhou Shao Tian went to Wu Hong Da and had a bitter dispute.
During the dispute, Zhou Shao Tian stabbed Wu Hong Da with a pen.
He committed murder to silence him.
What do you say about this presumption,
Zhou Shao Tian.
Do you have anything to say to defend yourself?
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki