Episode 28
Cai Hong?
You father really gave you a nice name.
After the storm is gone and all clouds disappear,
you are able to see the rainbow.
Are you comforting me?
Can everything dissapear
and the sky clear after the rain?
If this is the case,
once I find Old Cai,
and save Brother Shao Tian,
the grudge between the Jiang and Wu families,
will it
also be lifted?
I will do my best
to find Old Cai.
As long as we can end the grudges between our families,
I will do my best.
Why are you still not sleeping? You are going to die soon and you are still reflecting?
Forget it. He is going to die the day after.
Let him do whatever he wants.
Cai Hong,
from far away you share this moment with me.
I have only two days left.
How could I possibly sleep?
Miss. Zhou, Shao Tian's man, Ma Li is here to see you.
Can he just see her like this? Where is the rule?
Miss. We already taught him a lesson just now,
but he said that he has a very important news to tell you.
Please see him.
Miss.
Aren't you Zhou Shao Tian's confidante?
Why are you looking for me?
Miss Lu.
Ever since my brother was caught,
I haven't been living well.
I would like to follow you.
I would like you to employ me.
You are already beaten in such a state and you still want to follow me?
It's truly touching.
But I don't lack any staff here.
I already have enough staff.
What I lack is someone who can get things done.
Someone who is smart.
Miss Lu. I have a very important news
which I would like to tell you.
After you have heard me out,
you can consider whether you want to take me in or not.
Speak.
Frankly, I know that you are looking for the secret formula.
I know where it is.
Where is it?
It's with Old Cai's wife, Madam Lin.
Why should I believe you?
My brother and I grew up together.
I'm his most trusted person. He doesn't hide anything from me.
When he was caught by the police,
my brother went to visit him in jail.
He had a condition for saving him.
That's how he forced Old Cai to reveal the whereabouts of the secret formula.
The secret formula is with Madam Lin but it was a pity that
before my brother could get it,
he was caught by the police.
Do you know
what will happen to you if you lie to me?
I know.
I wouldn't dare lie to you.
Frankly speaking, if my brother wasn't caught,
I would rather take the knife to my neck,
than ever reveal the whereabouts of the secret formula.
But it's a pity that it's useless for my brother to have the secret formula now.
I want to survive.
Thus, I'm exchanging this news for a way out.
Jiang Yu has been looking for me for the past two days.
He wants to know where the secret formula is.
He promised to give me lots of money
but I didn't tell him about this.
It's because, in the past, I helped my brother to go against him
and did a lot of things.
Even if I were to tell him this,
he would never let me off.
I could only ask you for help.
You are still considered smart.
Miss Lu. You must use this time now.
With Jiang Yu's slyness, it won't be long
before he finds out that the secret formula is with Madam Lin.
Zhang Xun.
Take Ma Li out.
Give him some money as he goe.
Thank you, Miss Lu.
Thank you.
Miss. Did you believe what Ma Li just said?
I don't believe him entirely.
I only believed eighty percent.
We are also not in rush to take any actions. Let's keep watch on Jiang Yu and Wu Cai Hong first.
Miss. Do you really want to retain Ma Li?
Of course not.
This kind of person, he betrayed Zhou Shao Tian today.
He will betray me tomorrow.
What I want is only the information that he's holding.
Uncle Lai.
Find someone to watch Ma Li. Don't let him to see or hear anything.
If not, we might be bitten by him later.
Also, find out the address of Madam Lin as soon as possible.
- Just in case.
(lit. just for a rainy day - when needed)
- Yes.
If you need to order anything, please call me.
Okay.
Would you like to order something?
Our homemade snacks are really good.
We will call you later.
Please have tea first.
Please enjoy.
Miss Lin.
Please sit here.
Waiter.
Please sit.
What would you like to order?
Miss Lin. What would you like to drink?
No need.
- A pot of Longjing (tea) is good.
- Yes.
By the way, why are you looking for me?
Regarding Old Cai,
you must be very sad and worried.
Frankly, me too.
I asked you here because I would like to get back
the secret formula that Old Cai took from my father.
Secret formula?
I didn't know that Old Cai had this secret formula.
I don't know what you are talking about.
Miss Lin.
This secret formula belonged to my father.
Even more so when my father treated him very well.
Regard this as compensation for his crime.
Miss Wu.
I know that Old Cai
stole the money from Ling Long.
He was wrong. He has committed a big crime.
He has wronged the Wu family and Old Master Wu
but I really didn't know that he had the secret formula.
Thus, even if I really want to give it to you,
I don't have it.
Since this is the case, I won't insist on it.
But I would like to advise you.
Even if you don't want to do this for Old Cai, you should think for yourself.
The Zhou Shao Tian, who has been taking care of your family,
has already been betrayed.
Have you thought of what you are going to do in the future?
I guarantee that as long as you return the secret formula to me,
you won't have to worry about you and your son's living expenses.
I know what you mean.
I also would like to thank you for thinking on my behalf
but regarding the secret formula, I really don't have it.
What happened?
I met Miss Lin. She has already gone back
but someone was following me this morning.
Looks like we have hooked Miss Lu.
But Brother Shao Tian will be sentenced to death tomorrow.
What should we do?
It will be my turn to set the stage now.
Watch my performance next.
Your injury...
Is your injury much better?
It's not big deal. It will be fine soon.
Be careful too.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Miss!
Is there any news?
I followed Wu Cai Hong and saw her meeting with Madam Lin.
I found out her address.
What did Wu Cai Hong say to her?
I overheard Wu Cai Hong asking her
to hand over Old Cai's secret formula.
Madam Lin didn't admit that she had the secret formula.
Even Wu Cai Hong has gotten in the scene too.
Could the secret formula really be with Madam Lin?
But...
Madam Lin insisted that she didn't know about the secret formula.
Of course, she wouldn't admit it.
If she were to admit it,
it would mean that Old Cai could be even more implicated.
I'm afraid that in the murder's case
he would not be able to escape anymore.
That's right.
Indeed, there are so many connections in this case.
Uncle Lai. Prepare the rickshaw for me.
I'm going to visit Madam Lin.
We must not let Wu Cai Hong and Jiang Yu
snatch it first.
She is here. Keep this now.
Madam Cai. As long as you hand over the secret formula, you can name the price.
Mr Jiang.
I already said many times that
I really don't have the secret formula.
Think about this carefully.
The secret formula is useless to you.
You can't use it to dye textiles nor would you dare to take it out.
As long as you are willing to hand over the secret formula to me,
I can give you a big sum of money
to let you and your son spend it for the rest of your lives.
You don't have to embarrass me. No matter what you say,
I will still reply the same thing.
I... really don't have the secret formula.
This is not about money. Old Cai already said that
he wouldn't sell it at any cost.
What I meant is that
Old Cai said that we really don't have the secret formula.
Let's do this then, Mrs Cai.
Reconsider carefully what I just told you.
I will come again tomorrow with the cash.
Miss Lu?
What a coincidence.
Madam Cai.
I really hope that you will seriously think about it.
I'm taking my leave.
Miss. You are...
You are Mrs Cai, right? I'm Lu Man.
I also run a dyeing factory.
I'm here for the same thing as that gentleman just now.
I... I really don't have the secret formula. Don't come here anymore.
This is your husband's knotted button, right?
This... You...
Do you get it now?
I'm here not to talk nonsense with you.
I only want to exchange the secret formula with Old Cai.
If you are agreeable, your husband can go home soon.
If you don't,
I guarantee that you will never see him again.
Okay, I will do whatever you want
as long as you don't hurt my husband.
Fine.
How are you going to make me believe that you are holding the secret formula now?
My husband gave me this textile which was dyed according to the secret formula.
So, the secret formula is really with you.
You caused me to waste so much energy on others?
Give me the secret formula.
Give me the secret formula and I will release Old Cai.
The secret formula is already in my head.
I want to ensure my husband's safety first
before I hand it over to you.
You even know how to talk terms.
Fine.
I will send someone to pick you up tonight
to see your husband.
How is my husband now?
He is fine.
Won't you be seeing him this evening?
Uncle Lai.
Once you have gotten the secret formula,
don't let them live.
I'm not going anymore.
Once the task is completed, bring the secret formula to me.
You must not make any mistake. Understand?
Miss, don't worry.
I will complete everything.
I'm taking you to see Old Cai.
Let's go.
Dear.
Madam Lin. You have seen your husband.
You can hand over the secret formula now.
We don't have the secret formula at all.
How could the secret formula of the Jiang family be with us?
Just because of a piece of secret formula,
you beat my husband into such a state.
Are you humans? I'm going to beat you.
If you don't hand over the secret formula today,
I will send you to see the King of Hades.
The secret formula has never been with us.
Jiang Yu gave me this piece of cloth.
This is all part of the plan by Jiang Yu and the police.
Just wait for the police to catch you.
You beat my husband into this state.
- You will get your retribution.
Police!
Don't move!
Men, take cover!
Let's go.
Quick, let's go.
What now, Doctor? Is he awake?
The patient's injuries are very serious. He has many broken bones.
Not only does he has many injuries, they even cut off three of his fingers.
He has excessive bleeding that was full of infection.
Even though we have already tried our best to do a blood transfusion and patch up his wounds
but when he will he conscious,
it will depend on God.
His injuries are very severe. You must be mentally prepared.
Okay, doctor. It has been tough for you. Thank you.
It's okay. This is what I should do.
Cai Hong.
Take a break first.
Old Cai is still unconscious.
If he doesn't regain his consciousness, everything will be too late.
What should we do about Brother Shao Tian? We are running out of time.
We have already tried our best.
We can only depend of Old Cai now.
It's time to eat.
Zhou Shao Tian. This is your last meal.
Director wanted me to prepare some nice food for you.
Once you have eaten, have a good journey.
Do not have any worries.
If you have any last words, I will help you to relay them.
Even more so when you have known Director Chen for a while.
If there is anything, he will help you to do it.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Old Cai. Wake up.
What can be so important that you can't wake up.
Brother Shao Tian is running out of time.
- Cai Hong.
- Old Cai, please wake up.
I'm begging you, Old Cai.
- I'm begging you.
- Old Cai, don't be like this.
Jiang Yu. What should we do? I can't see Brother Shao Tian die this way.
Help me to think of a solution.
If Old Cai doesn't wake up, Brother Shao Tian will really lose his life.
I'm begging you.
I really don't want him to die.
Old Cai. Did you hear what I said?
I'm begging you to save Brother Shao Tian.
Old Cai.
Wake up, Old Cai.
Wake up.
No.
I must save Brother Shao Tian.
Hello, Police Chief Li. It's me, Jiang Yu.
It's like this. Old Cai is still in a coma.
Can you postpone Zhou Shao Tian's execution?
I say, Brother Jiang.
Don't make it difficult for me. How can this be possible?
Many reporters and citizens are watching this.
If there is no evidence, we can't suspend the execution of Zhou Shao Tian.
We have no legal authority.
How are we going to face the people of Huzhou?
No.
Old Cai is the most important witness in this case.
His testimony is extremely important.
It could take weeks (for Old Cai to recover), but Zhou Shao will.
Brother Jiang. Zhou Shao Tian's case has already been closed.
He showed the people with the case that he had no objections.
Do you need to do this?
We really can't just simply reverse the case.
Just because there was a real haste in investigating the case in the past,
there were so many grievances.
This can't carry on.
What the world needs now is fairness.
Okay, Brother Jiang. It's not that I don't want to help you
but I really can't do anything.
Cai Hong.
Don't be sad.
Ever since I was born,
I have been plagued by poverty.
When I was young,
I personally saw my father killed.
When I grew up, because of revenge,
I bit the bullet. made bad choices
There was no light in my life.
Until I met you.
During the darkness in my life,
you were the rainbow.
I have had you long enough.
Sorry.
I'm apologising on behalf of my father.
You don't need to apologise.
You are not in the wrong at all.
Cai Hong.
As long as you are willing to believe me,
even if I die, I won't have any regrets.
You won't die.
Do you know that
there still is a word in this world.
It's called a 'miracle.'
Jiang Yu
has already gone to find other evidence.
Perhaps, Old Cai may regain his consciousness.
No need.
Don't let him waste any more time.
Since I have committed a crime,
I don't need any miracles to happen.
Zhou Shao Tian. It's almost time. We should be on the way.
Cai Hong.
You were willing to visit me
and being able to see you,
I don't have any more requests.
At the final moment,
being able to see you,
I feel very blessed.
Kill him!
You cruel and ungrateful thing.
Zhou Shao Tian, you murderer.
Kill him!
Scum!
God has eyes.
Scum! Kill him!
Zhou Shao Tian. How could Huzhou have such a beast like you?
Old Master Wu was so kind to you and you murdered him.
You are really ungrateful!
Ungrateful!
Where is Miss Wu?
She went out and didn't say when she would be back.
Old Cai.
Your wife died while trying to save you.
We can't let those bad people get away.
Wake up now.
Shao Tian. Mom will see you off.
When I'm gone,
I will look for you and father soon.
Our family will be reunited
and will never separate again.
Shao Tian, don't be afraid.
Mom is here with you.
Sorry, let me through.
Get ready.
- Wait!
- Stop!
Executioner. Chief Police Li has issued an order.
Stop the execution of the death penalty on Zhou Shao Tian.
Wait.
He said to stop the execution of the death penalty on Zhou Shao Tian?
Where is Chief Police Li's order?
He told me to verbally tell you.
Sorry. Without his order, we can't do that.
Even more so, who are you?
To add further, even if there is an urgency,
and Chief Police Li wanted to verbally relay the order,
he would't send you here. He would send his subordinate.
This order is faked and made up. Stop interfering.
Human's life depends on it!
You said that I faked his order? If what I said is true,
once you kill him, you won't be able to revive him.
I can't let you just disregard a human life.
You dare to say that the police disregard a human life?
This is a brave accusation.
Do you know that you are interfering with the police enforcement right now?
I think you must be tired of living. Men!
- Pull her away so her insolent gaze will not disrupt the execution!
- Yes!
- Miss.
- Don't shoot. I'm telling the truth.
- Retreat.
- I'm telling the truth.
Wait!
Zhou Shao Tian was the fiancee of Miss Wu.
What is this? Hidden secrets?
She even doesn't want her father because of this man.
This important witness has something to say.
Wait.
What do you have to say?
I can be the witness.
Zhou Shao Tian didn't kill Wu Hong Da.
Don't worry. Chief Police Li's order will be here soon.
Old Cai. Can you speak?
I know that your injuries are very serious but
you are a very important witness to us.
I hope that you will think carefully first before you answer my questions.
Whatever I know,
I will tell you.
On the day of Wu Hong Da's incident,
Zhou Shao Tian said that you were with him at 12 noon.
Is this true?
Yes.
That day, when Boss wanted to talk to me,
I felt that something was wrong.
I went to find Zhou Shao Tian
and wanted to escape with him.
But I didn't imagine that he wouldn't want to leave.
Because of this,
I quarreled with him.
When it was 12 noon, on the street, I saw
many people running towards Lin Long.
It was very chaotic and they were shouting,
"Someone died."
Based on your testimony, Zhou Shao Tian wasn't at the scene.
Yes.
But on the day of Old Master's incident,
other than me, Zhou Shao Tian and Mr Jiang,
he saw another person.
Who was it?
Who was that person?
I don't know.
It is just that when master answered the phone
he was very polite.
He said that he was waiting for the other party.
I felt that
that person on the phone must be a big shot.
Big shot? So prominent that even Wu Hong Da would treat her politely?
Who would it be?
Old Cai. Do you still remember who kidnapped you?
I didn't see that person clearly.
One of them covered her face.
She even threatened me
to hand over the secret formula.
I only know that she was a young woman.
Young woman?
Director Chen.
I think we should talk to Zhou Shao Tian.
At this time,
Zhou Shao Tian should already be dead.
Don't blame me for being cruel.
Blame yourself for loving the wrong person.
Miss. Someone just came with news that Zhou Shao Tian didn't die.
What? How could this be possible?
Leave first.
I heard that Old Cai regained his consciousness.
Jiang Yu brought him to the execution site. Not long after that,
the orders from Chief Police Li arrived.
It said that there was an important witness and testimony.
Now that Zhou Shao's excution was postponed temporarily
everyone is asking about the real culprit.
Miss.
What should we do now?
Zhou Shao Tian didn't die?
Miss. We should get ready soon.
If the police find out that Zhou Shao Tian didn't kill Wu Hong Da,
they will definitely suspect others.
He said, that on the day of Wu Hong Da's death, he met three people.
They were Jiang Yu, Zhou Shao Tian and Old Cai.
In the past, the police didn't get their testimonies
but it's different now.
If they collect all three testimonies,
- it wouldn't be advantageous to us...
-Enough, don't say anymore!
Uncle Lai. Sorry, I was too anxious just now.
Don't keep this in your heart.
I understand.
Zhou Shao Tian's fate is still undecided.
God is helping him.
Let's not panic.
Even if they suspect us, they can't find any evidence now.
Furthermore, I'm the Military Governor's woman.