The Cage of Love
Episode 18
Miss, you told me to pay more attention to Wu Hong Da's case.
The police have re-opened the case for investigation now.
Wasn't this case already closed? Why are they investigating it again?
Rumor has it that there is new evidence
that can prove that Zhou Shao Tian has the same pen as Wu Hong Da.
I know.
Make a point of keeping an eye on it. Do not go wrong.
By the way,
Zhou Shao Tian should be back today, right?
Call that whatever Ma Li here
and let him bring this news to Zhou Shao Tian.
Ask Zhou Shao Tian what he should do.
Miss. Why are you thinking on his behalf?
Thinking about him is also for our own good.
Miss Lu. Two policemen are here to find Zhao Shao Tian.
Okay, you may leave.
Dear Sirs. Why are you here?
Miss Lu. The Director asked us to invite Zhou Shao Tian to the police station.
It's a grave matter and we have offended you but please cooperate.
Tell us where he went and when he's coming back.
You sirs looking for Zhou Shao Tian, I don't dare interfere.
However, Mister Zhou went out of town.
Regarding when he's returning, I really don't know.
- This...
- Then you should at least know where he went?
Mister Zhou was sick and rested for half a month.
So he has a lot of things to do and hasn't seen a lot of people.
This time, I'm sure he has to go a lot of places
and meet a lot of clients.
As for where he is right now,
I really don't know.
Miss Lu, we are only following orders. Just be honest with us.
If not, others will think that you are an accomplice.
What do you mean? Is Miss Lu someone who would be an accomplice?
Miss Lu, please forgive us.
But if you put it this way,
you are making it hard to do our work.
By saying this,
you are saying that I'm delaying your investigation?
You are implicating me. I'm a weak woman. I really can't handle this.
It's like this. Mr Zhou
will only be back on the following day.
You should also know that there is chaos in the military now.
What if there is no peace?
Of course, I wish for peace too.
Even if everything was peaceful and things were well,
weather can be unpredictable.
Strong winds and rain could delay him two days.
Okay then. We will go back first and report to our Director first.
We can only do this.
Miss Lu, if Mr Zhou returns,
please let us know immediately.
But of course. Take care, I won't be seeing you off.
We are leaving.
Giddy up.
Brother!
Ah Li, why are you here?
- Brother, you can't go into the city now.
- Why? What's going on?
This is a letter from Miss Lu. She insisted that I must stop you.
You must not go into the city.
Ah Li. I won't be going into the city for the time being.
I'll go to the lake for the next two days.
Relay this message to Miss Lu.
- Okay, Brother.
- Thank her on my behalf.
Okay.
Cai Hong.
Wu Cai Hong.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
I... would like to take leave.
I would like to go home for a while.
Even though Brother Shao Tiao bought my famiy home for us
before there is any conclusion in the investigation,
I would like Cai Yun and my stepmom to move out.
I will go with you.
Master, you died wrongly.
Zhou Shao Tian, you ungrateful (person)!
You said you would be promoted and not be poor. You wanted to be betrothed.
You did such a toxic thing and even tricked Cai Hong's feelings.
What is our family to do now?
Stepmom, stop crying. There is no evidence now that Brother Shao Tian is the killer.
Before the conclusion of the investigation, I think we should leave here.
Cai Yu and I are going to pack our stuff.
Stop crying, Stepmom.
This is the Wu's family home. I moved in when I married your father.
I have already been kicked out once and I have to leave again.
I'm not moving out.
If Zhou Shao Tian is really the killer, then the money used to buy the house
will be stained with father's blood. Mom, do you still want to live here?
The money didn't belong to your father.
This is the Wu's family home.
I want to protect this place. I want to help him to safeguard it.
Even if you tell me to die, I won't move out. I want to live here until I die.
Cai Yun, what do you think?
If Mom doesn't want to move out, I won't either. I already don't have a father.
I want to be with Mom.
That's right. Cai Yun will follow me.
We are not moving out.
We will live here till we die.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
It's normal that they can't accept the truth.
It's even hard for me to accept it too. It's hard to accept the result.
It's even more so for my stepmom and sister.
When Zhou Shao Tian returns in two days,
everything will become clear.
But, us three, already moved out of the house once.
If this time, I let Cai Yun
and my stepmom move out again, my stepmom definitely won't be able to take it.
Don't worry about this. I can buy over the house.
I will deduct the money from the sale of the house from your salary.
Miss. Ma Li is back.
Miss Lu.
So what? You met Zhou Shao Tian? What did he say?
My brother would like to thank you for this news.
He is temporarily living in Chang Xing.
Could Miss Lu do another favour for my brother?
Why does he need me to help him with his problems again?
My brother said that you have a wide connection.
He requested that you get him a similar Parker pen as Jiang Yu's as soon as possible.
Otherwise my brother will jump into the Yellow River
instead of being a fugitive.
Don't think that highly of me. Do I have that wide of a connection?
A 18K Parker fountain pen? That is not a toy.
Even more so, he wants me to find the exact same model.
Miss Lu, I'm begging you. You must help my brother.
My brother has been framed. He can't bear the title of murderer.
I can guarantee that he didn't kill Mr. Wu.
Whether your brother has been framed or not, it's the police's job to investigate.
My words don't count.
Miss Lu, please. I'm bowing to you.
Enough. Go back first and wait.
If I have any news, Uncle Lai will contact you.
Thank you, Miss Lu.
Thank you.
Uncle Lai.
I remember that he seemed to have a confidant.
He liked to receive expensive fountain pens.
Go and find him
and see if he can find a solution.
Yes, I will do it now.
This is not an expensive gift
but I personally dyed it and
weaved it.
Also, you two are alike.
Its name is the same as yours.
It's just like a little rainbow.
Cai Hong.
Let's be together.
Let me take care of you.
Instead of working, why are you dreaming early in the morning?
Hey.
I only knocked into you lightly
and you are on the ground and can't get up.
Stop pretending.
Fei Fei, what are you doing?
She was slacking off.
I only said a few words to her.
Are you okay?
Brother, where are you going?
We still have important business to discuss in the afternoon.
I already discussed about that business.
You can just greet Boss He and it will be fine
Why did you take my water bucket? I still need to get water for Granny Gu.
Where is the water?
Don't drag me.
Let go.
Jiang Yu. Where are you taking me?
Slow down. Be careful.
Why did you bring me here?
Boatman.
I want to rent your boat.
-How much?
-One silver dollar.
This is for you
but I only want your boat. You can take a rest.
Okay.
This way, please.
Get on.
Do you know to row the boat?
I don't want to fall into the water.
Get in when I tell you to.
Cut the nonsense.
Don't be afraid.
I have also gone through supporting a family of three
by being a ferry boatman.
I think that after have you found out about Zhou Shao Tian,
you haven't been happy.
My dad is dead.
It's very possible that he was the most trusted person
who killed him.
How could I be happy about this?
I understand.
You won't be able to understand.
That kind of hurt was inflicted by someone whom you regarded as family.
You will never understand it.
By the way,
you said that, in the past, you rowed boats
to support your family of three.
But looking at Madam Jiang,
her decent and generous behavior,
as if she came from a scholarly family.
How could it be possible that you worked
as a boatman?
The Jiang home, at that time, had only a little money.
Before that my father was a supporter of the foreign efforts movement.
He was a rich businessman
but he was sabotaged by someone later
and framed for housing opiates.
This resulted in my father's death.
The reason that the court officials gave us was that
my father committed suicide.
Something like this happened to your family.
No wonder you look this way - a face filled with depression.
Furthermore, you have a cold attitude.
When my father passed away, the factory was confiscated.
My house was occupied.
You could say that we went bankrupt overnight.
My mother couldn't face the situation and attempted suicide.
Fortunately, I was there and discovered it.
Mom!
It was really hard for us at that time.
To feed my family, I took on all kinds of jobs.
I would do them. When I was working as a boatman,
I had other jobs too.
I really didn't imagine that you had gone through such an experience.
Those days were really tough
but I continued to hang on
just to take revenge.
I can't let my father
wrongfully die.
I must punish those bad people severely.
Did you find those people who harmed your father?
Did you seek revenge already?
Before I could take revenge, that person died.
It was too easy for that bad guy then.
I had the same thought too
but I later found out that
perhaps God
- had arranged something else for me.
- What was it?
Perhaps, grudges and revenge should end in grudges and revenge.
Just like in this dirty pond,
such clean and pure flowers would even grow here.
It allows us to forget the unhappy things first.
Can you forget about the grudge towards the person who killed your father?
But thank you for bringing me to such a beautiful place.
After seeing such beautiful things,
I forgot about many unhappy things.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Boss Ke, take a look.
This is the product we created based on your request.
If there is no problem, we will start production at the factory.
-Of course.
-Also, if you have any suggestions, we can cater to that.
Not bad. It totally met my request.
Not even a small amount off.
It's good that you are satisfied.
I'm assured of Ling Long's products.
Why isn't Mr Jiang in the company today?
My brother was actually here waiting for your arrival but
he had an urgent matter and had no choice but to take care of it.
But he told me that
you are our valued client.
that I shouldn't carelessly treat you.
Mr Jiang is too formal. We have been friends for many years.
Don't mind this. To add further,
Miss Fang is Mr Jiang's most trusted person.
Furthermore, you are family.
Isn't it the same that you are here with me to see the product?
Boss Ke. Thank you for your compliment.
Not bad.
Brother. Where has you been for the whole day?
Did you go to the pond to appreciate the flowers?
Brother. You ignored such an important client like Boss Ke.
I represented you today. Can't you just answer me?
You are very smart.
With you taking care of Boss Ke, I don't have to worry.
But, don't you feel that
taking a woman to appreciate the flowers
would invite gossip?
Who would be such a busybody?
- Brother.
- Cai Hong.
Deliver these flowers to my mom.
Okay.
Brother.
Why is it so hard to see you lately?
I couldn't see you the whole day and I wondered what you are busy with.
I had some matters to settle.
Don't bother about what it is.
Does it concern Wu Cai Hong?
Brother. In your heart,
is Wu Cai Hong more important than the rest?
Ridiculous.
Miss, What you wanted is here.
So fast?
The head of the military said that
it's such a difficult task but you could do it so easily.
Uncle Lai.
Prepare a gift for me.
I'm going to visit Zhou Shao Tian's mother.
But the Zhou family has been watching you.
It's okay.
Don't worry. I know.
Miss, we are here.
Here.
Take your time.
Aunt Zhou, how are you? I'm Lu Man.
Did Mr Zhou mention me?
Hello.
Then...
Please come in.
Timing and subtitles brought to You by Gone with the Shirt Team @ Viki
Please have some tea, Miss Lu.
Aunt Zhou. You really don't need to go through all this trouble.
Shao Tian is not at home. You...
I know that he's not home, I came especially to visit you.
Shao Tian went on business because of work.
Thus, I brought you a gift. I hope you like it.
Shao Tian is not at home. If you need anything,
just let me know and I will help you.
You have been taking care of Shao Tian.
Well, for sharing your kind heart with me,
thank you very much, Miss Lu.
Aunt Zhou, you are being too formal.
Just call me Lu Man.
Please have your tea.
- Did you get scalded?
- I'm fine.
Aunt. Could I borrow a place
to clean my clothes?
Please come with me.
Miss Lu. This way, please.
This is Shao Tian's room. No one is here.
It's fairly clean, so please use it to clean yourself up.
I will have to trouble you then.
Please make yourself at home.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Aunt. Frankly, I'm here today
because I have something else to tell you.
Two days ago, the police came to find me.
They suspect Shao Tian of harming the boss of Ling Long.
Aunt, please don't worry.
I was afraid that you would be worried. Thus, I'm telling you in advance.
If the police were to come in a few days time to make inquiries,
please watch what you say.
Aunt, don't panic. I believe Shao Tian is not that kind of person.
There is no conclusion to the investigation now but after it's done, everything will be fine.
Aunt. If there is nothing else, I am leaving first.
Man Mansion.
Miss. You are back. Did it go smoothly?
With me taking care of it, is there anything I can't do?
Uncle Lai.
I came to warn you. Get him out of the city before the gates close.
Tell him to tell Zhou Shao Tian that I have done what he requested.
He can come back without any worries.
Yes, I will do it now.
Giddy up.
Stay here and don't go anywhere else.
- I'm going to tell Director Chen.
- Okay, go now.
I will keep watch here.
Shao Tian, you are back.
It's good that you are here. Your boss came.
It's Miss Lu.
She said that you are being investigated regarding Wu Hong Da's case. What's going on?
Did you kill someone?
Do you really hope to see your son as a killer? You are already finding me guilty.
No, I'm just asking you. Tell me.
Is it because of your father's death that
you blame Master Wu.
Thus, you killed him
to take revenge for your father?
Mom.
Why would I vent my anger on Master Wu when he wasn't the one who killed my father.
The one who killed my father
was you.
Let's not talk about this first. Did you kill Wu Da Hong?
Let me tell you. The killer is you. You are the one who killed that person.
Don't forget.
When I saw you take my dad's last breath,
that many years, have you been sleeping well at night?
When you are having dreams, did you dream that my father came to look for you?
You are the killer.
Don't say anymore. I'm not.
At that time, I didn't have a choice. Your father was very sick.
I couldn't get any money to cure him and raise you.
Who didn't know that it was better for him to die then suffer?
But your dad was tortured by his illness,
he was good as dead.
It was him that begged me to end it for him.
I couldn't do it
but if I didn't do it,
would I have let you do it instead?
I didn't have any choice.
Didn't have any choice?
Talking about it,
we are poor people.
We don't have any money.
I will always remember in my heart
that I will tell you that I hate you.
Thus, I didn't kill Cai Hong's father.
I swear on my dad's name that...
if I wanted to kill someone,
he wouldn't rest in peace even in hell.
Young Master. Zhao Shao Tian is back.
Brother.
Zhou Shao Tian is back.
Come with me.
Mr Zhou. We are here to ask you to help us in the investigation regarding Mr Wu's case.
Has there been progress in Boss Wu's case?
It's convenient for us to talk here. We should go in.
Director Chen Suo, what exactly happened
to cause such a ruckus?
Brother Shao Tian
Cai Hong. Why do you look so bad today?
Tell me.
After my father passed away,
did you buy a Parker fountain pen?
It's exactly the same as Jiang Yu.
Why are you suddenly asking me this?
Tell me if you bought it.
You are all here today just because of this?
Okay.
I did buy the same model of the fountain pen.
Did you kill my father?
You ungrateful thing. Why did you do it?
Why? I was forced by you.
I didn't.
This is the pen.
Brother Shao Tian. What is going on?
Cai Hong.
In the past, you said that you wanted to buy this fountain pen as a gift for your father's birthday.
Subsequently, you fought with someone over this and didn't manage to buy it.
I wanted to make you happy by getting the same pen.
But, in the past,
why didn't you tell me about it?
I ordered this pen from overseas.
It took a bit of time.
Before I could give it to you, your father had that accident.
I was afraid that you would get sad again.
Thus, I didn't use this as the birthday present.
Later, I knew about the report on Boss Wu.
There was a fountain pen on his dead body.
I was afraid that it would cause a misunderstanding.
I didn't take out this fountain pen then.
Cai Hong.
If this is the weapon which killed your father,
why would I still keep this at home?
Think about it. If this fountain pen
injured someone, the tip wouldn't be like this.
Director Chen Suo.
You are in this line.
Take a look. If there is a need,
you can go back and run tests on it.
I took the pen back to run some tests
but it looks new.
It probably didn't injure anyone.
Director Chen Suo.
Cai Hong. I went out of the city to conduct some business.
I came home. Look, I didn't even change my clothes yet.
And I heard about this.
I know that
you said that you would trust me.
I don't blame you. You must been instigated by someone.
Jiang Yu.
I don't want you to lie to Cai Hong again
and sabotage our relationship.
Okay?
Perhaps, Brother Shao Tian is really innocent.
He is so good to us. How could he have killed my father?
I know your heart is contradicting itself right now,
but if you keep everyone out, it will become empty.
There must be an answer.
I'm at odds now to find out who contacted him about this
and allowed him time to make the preparations.
You are only guessing now.
Perhaps, you are thinking too much.
Once a person lies,
he needs countless lies to redeem himself.
It's a pity that
it was simple to do.
Don't talk to me about this.
I don't want to listen.
I'm here today to take Cai Hong away with me.
Name your price.
It can be double, triple or whatever, it's not a problem.
He brought that much money to take you back.
Don't you find it strange?
I'm the General Manager of Rong Da.
Is the salary of the General Manager of Rong Da that high?
I hold thirty percent shares in Rong Da.
You got a bonus already?
I loaned money from a bank.
Ms. Lu
Word has it that today, you, Wu Cai Hong, and Jiang Yu
in front of a bunch of police
had a special encounter.
Well, it's all thanks to Ms. Lu.
If it wasn't for your help, I wouldn't be able to leave unscathed.
Am I that great?