How much?
US$ 7 million
Thank you, you may go now
You'll soon be better than me!
The case of Ronning Holdings
is so difficult that
You still can win that,
let's celebrate!
Cheers!
Mandy, Philip, congratulations!
For merging your business together
They're getting marry!
It's not business
Come to our firm to be our auditor,
OK?
Waise, what do you think?
I appreciate Philip's talent,
but it'll be boring
for couples working together
I'd never be bored!
Don't you regret?
Never!
Be honest! Every morning
I've to wake her up
& prepare her breakfast
Then, do her laundry
And then...
Petty,
please stop disclosing my privacy
Shall we delay our marri...
What're you saying?
Poor me...
Right? What's the good of marriage?
You mean it or not?
Sorry, I've to finish my work
My tie!
Sorry!
Let it go!
I'll call someone to clean it
Go to work
Mr. Chow, I'm sorry!
Never mind
Philip have to live with
the bad habits of Mandy
If you don't want to be married,
just say so
Don't be so serious!
You understand me, right?
Mr. Chow, Mr. Ng's arrived
Let him in
Please
Hi, David
Brother Waise
The money will be deposited
in 5 companies accounts
Next week,
the money will be paid as
buying the US properties of Chiu
Then we'll remit those money back to him
I'd like to deposit the money
as soon as possible
So I can get back to US to report duty
No problem! How is Uncle Chiu?
Healthy!
But the Italian are making
troubles recently
They're ruined some of our business
Need my help?
No, Waise
Uncle Chiu is going to
give them a good lesson
Should you need any help, tell me
OK!
Let's toast for Chiu's health!
Cheers!
Judged by the court, Ann, my client
Is approved divorced to Mr. Yau,
the reason is,
Mr. Yau intentionally & continuously
skipping the responsibility of a husband
Ash tray, Mr. Yau
Thanks!
You've unstable income
& neglect your economic responsibility
You don't like my job of being a cop!
Mr. Yau...
Miss Ann is judged psychologically hurt
She can take half of your property
Including your house & bank savings
Don't be son rude!
Ann, give me a last chance OK?
I've given you many chances
You're still the same
If you find no problem, please sign here
Did you flirt with any girls
in the States?
You're the chairman of Adonis' club.
I've no chance after you've left
How about you?
I've been a good boy
because AIDS!
Smart!
How's then?
He's got the money, chase him!
Come on, wake up!
Don't get in!
Blood! I'm fainting...
Move it now, or I'll kill you!
Move it quickly
Go there & have a look!
That way!
They'll kill you! Hurry up!
I...
Where is the money, where is it?
Hurry up!
Tak!
Hi! Dragon!
I've just left the Law office
Are you OK?
It peanut for me,
but there's hell of a mess
Kent...
Sir, be calm, don't touch the injured
Come on over!
Be careful Miss, it'll be ok!
Hurry up!
Hello boss,
after Kent'd got on Mandy Chang's Car
The money was gone
Maybe that bitch took away our money
Well,
don't let her tell anyone
about this case
No matter how,
I've to talk to her first
Miss Chang,
can you recall the situation?
It's a mess! That thief...
He... He was running with the robbers
Mind what you're saying!
Are you very sure?
He'd just visited my office, I'm sure!
Don't frame me!
Be calm!
She is framing me!
He's nuts! Don't let him come near me!
You bitch!
Don't you want me to beat you?
Let me go...
I don't want to see him!
Don't let me see his face
He is out of your sight!
Be careful! Slowly...
This way
Thanks
Hurry up!
We've got the wrong guy!
You idiot! Throw him out of the car!
Stop any bull shit!
We've been buddies for so many years,
why don't you trust me?
I do trust you!
But the money is robbed
There must be a betrayer!
Are you tailed all the way to HK?
If so,
I'd have been robbed in C. America!
There must be a betrayer here!
Who are you suspecting?
How much does your girlfriend know?
Nonsense! She won't!
I'm just playing her
I won't let her know such things
How about Mandy Chang?
She won't!
Maybe, she's hiding our money
She wants to take it as her own!
Impossible!
Waise Chow, we've the responsibility to
get the money back
I'll inform Uncle Chiu,
you'd better figure our an explanation
You've heard what we said?
Yes,
the triad members of US export
the dirty money secretly to HK
Cause HK is a free port
They'll white wash the money here
& remit it to US lawfully!
Thus, the govt. Can't check it our
You're quite correct
You're the one
who launders the money for them
I've not committed any crime in HK
But to me,
you're no different from
the triad criminals
I do it for our future
You still love me, right?
Are we friends from now on? I doubt it
I wonder if the robbery case
was masterminded by you!
Thanks
Waise, we'd keep the righteousness
for we're the lawyers
But anyway,
we cannot commit crimes!
I always trust you,
but why you cheat me?
I can't forgive you, anyway!
So, sorry...
No! You're the one who'd apology
You'd better think over
how to defend yourself
Inspector Yeung
Speaking!
Hello, I'm Petty Lee
I'm at home, I want to talk to you
Can you come here immediately?
Sure
OK!
May I accompany you home?
No! I'm tired. I want to rest early
Be careful
Sure! Goodbye
You bitch! You frame me again & again!
Do you want me to
teach you a good lesson?
What're you doing? Don't come to me
You've taken 1 /2 of my property
& you framed me too?
I'm telling the truth!
I'll call the police
I don't give a damn!
I'll beat you to death!
Don't come
Petty!
Blood...
Police! Don't move!
Freeze!
Call the ambulance
Yes Madam
Search!
PC 26891 calling centre,
please send an ambulance
Petty!
Getn up!
You're suspected of murder,
go to police station with me
I didn't kill nobody! I didn't
You won't believe me
except I admit murder
Come on, shut up! Go!
Don't touch my head
Go!
Jump!
It's so high! I can't jump!
It hurts, leave me alone!
But you'd run for your life!
Hurry up!
Don't shoot!
No... Don't shoot! Don't...
I'm not going!
Move!
Why you take me here?
I want to see Petty
Bull shit!
Bullets were flying up there!
I don't want to be killed!
I'll be a suspect of homicide
if I run away
You don't? I'll help you!
Put me down!
What're you doing? Damn!
Don't
Stop pulling me!
I'm scared
Don't hold me!
Hands off!
Don't pull me!
Why did you beat me?
Are you ok? Get up at once!
Help him! He is falling down
Mind yourself!
Why don't you save him? He is falling!
My feet are killing me! I can't walk!
Let me go! Where do you take me to?
Let me down! Damn you!
Are you crazy!
Are you happy?
Let me down!
Don't pull my hair!
I'll make you blind!
I can't see! You'll be easily hurt!
You wanna get killed?
I almost run you over!
Bastard, go to hell!
Don't play on the road
Don't block my way...
I am sorry!
My foot! It's painful!
Don't move, cops
He kidnaps me!
I didn't
Arrest him...
You've assaulted a police officer!
Help! He kidnaps me!
Don't shout...
Are you ok?
Breathe deeply
Don't die,
I don't want to
be charged of another homicide
Are you ok?
Let's go!
Where is it?
This is my home
Where are you going?
Hurry up!
What do you want?
Pissing!
I won't go in there!
I won't let you in too!
Don't pull!
It's painful!
Stop!
What're you doing!
Let me down!
Get up!
Don't come over! Don't!
You think I want you to stick around?
If not the cuff, who'll care about you?
Who do you think you are?
Why did you follow me home?
You've framed me of robbery
So I came for you
I did see you rushing out
together with the robbers
If I were a thief, you'd have been killed
After raped! Don't cry!
Was the dead
your friend?
Don't move!
You're smart in the solicitor's office
But now, you look shit!
We can no longer stay here
The police will find us here
There was a murdering case
in Happy Valley last night
An experienced lawyer Petty lee
was killed in her apartment
Shootouts occurs between
the police & the suspects
2 police officers were seriously injured
3 suspects are wanted now
They are: Dragon Yau,
nick named Mad Dragon
Around 30 years old,
is a retired police officer
Mandy Chang, lawyer
And a suspect
who dressed in motor cyclist suits
Any body finds them, please...
See, we're being wanted!
What's your idea? Solicitor Chang!
What happened? Petty was killed,
I become a murdered!
Hey!
Let's eat first, come on
Your noodle will get cold!
You don't like me, anyway
Change my ex-wife's clothes after eating
Then, do what you like
After the death of Petty,
David following us
I think, he must know the secret
Let's go for him, ok?
Are you begging me?
Let's eat first
It's hot!
Sorry, I didn't intend to!
Did the cops treat you badly?
No, I've informed Uncle Chiu,
he'll in charge of the case
I'm leaving
Follow him, see what's he doing!
Yes!
I'm looking for you
Me too
Hit him!
What's the use of at stick?
Find a big one!
I've never hit any body!
Get bigger one!
Left side... left side!
Don't scare me!
Wake up please! I don't intend to...
Wake up!
Mandy Chang!
It's Mandy!
Dragon, try your best to stop the car!
Dragon, they're after me,
come up & help me!
You'd better come down!
It's high! How can I?
There are stairs! Idiot!
Go!
Where?
Over there!
I can't walk...
Run!
They're close! You trouble maker!
Did you kill Petty?
Why you killed her?
I didn't
Give the money back to me
If the money is taken by me,
why should I stay here?
Why should I come to you?
What sort of money is it?
Speak up! Or I'll lose my temper?
Chase them!
Release me!
How are you? Are you ok?
Stop!
Give me back the money,
it is important to me!
Is it dirty money?
It's not your concern,
you can't take it!
Give it back to me
I don't want to tell, how's it?
In my home
He means his home!
We don't know!
Sorry!
If I killed Petty,
I could have killed you too
Who are they?
I do want to know.
I suspect that
there is a betrayer in your office
This is my phone no.
Call me if you're in need
I'll call you
I'm back to investigate
Who's the guts to steal from Uncle Chiu
Kent was dead on the car of Mandy Chang
I've asked my boys to catch them back
But I don't know why David let them go!
Is it true?
If it's true,
I won't ask you here
to be in charge of this case
I'll find the money back & find out
who's the head of this case
This is my territory,
may I send someone to help you?
No!
The one who killed Kent would pay for it
Hello, I'm Mandy, may I speak to Philip?
Philip is busy,
he told you not to call him again
A table for...
Two
That way please
Please sit
Let's eat!
The beer's come
Alcohol makes me happy
See! You're stupid, your clothes' wet!
Thank!
Let's eat
OK!
You're rude!
Let's try!
It's hot
In the past,
I think you're a rude person,
but you're not
Why do you make yourself disgusting?
When I was a cop, if you are not fierce
The rascals won't to scared
"Hey bastard who you are?"
You'd ask like this!
Why did your wife leave you?
If you were her, would you leave me?
I don't know, cause I'm not your wife
I help her cause she is my client!
I'll help you
when you divorce again, ok?
Next?
If I were Philip, I'd have helped you
Don't talk about that bastard
Ok... Sorry
The bill please
Coming!
$1 80
$1 80, what'll we do?
Sorry, we do want some more dish
I think you've
never committed any crime
What?
I don't have enough cash with me
You bastard, get lost at once
Your girl stays with me tonight
What's the matter?
Sorry!
What's that on? Crazy!
Help!
Shut up! Knee down!
Open the door!
That way!
Go!
Hurry up!
Dragon!
Don't! Stop!
Stop!
If you want to leave safely
Give back the money
I won't mistreat you two!
I treat you as my role model,
I can't imagine
you're doing this dirty job!
I don't need
your comment of my personality
But I need to know where's the money
I know it!
The US dollars put
in a black brief-case, right?
You can't take away the money,
give it back to me
I'll make you a share!
Ok, why don't you let us go,
then I'll give you half of it
What a proud idiot!
Dragon!
I feel so good! It's like massage!
Faster please!
Boss!
The men from US have come
Watch them carefully
I'll return soon
It's so nice
It's of 1 st class
Right!
Good!
But Mr. Luciano
is not satisfied with the deal
Anything makes him dissatisfied?
Even he does,
who do you think you're?
I've agreed with him that
We'll share the business of
Uncle Chiu after Chiu's death
50/50
By Luciano and me, is that clear?
Just wait until we see Chiu's death body
Bull shit, if you can kill Chiu
You won't be in my office,
begging for my help
Sit, sit...
I've got it!
My boss agreed with the terms
We're straight forward people
I'll present the body of Chiu on time
Will your buddy arrest us?
He's loyal to friends,
he's not like Philip
Don't even mention that bastard!
Ok...
Tak!
Tak, I'm Dragon!
I don't see you! You'd better leave
You're invisible to him, let's go
What's that mean?
I'm not your buddy if I arrest you,
I'm not a cop if I don't do my job
I'm innocent! Why you treat me so cool?
Why do you come to me so secretly?
You must be the criminal
I didn't do it,
that's why I come to you
Let it be! He doesn't take
a glance at you, leave now
We're no thieves! Why should we leave?
Ok, I'm now arresting you
We're good buddies,
how come you treat me like that?
Don't stop me,
I'll give him a good lesson
Who do you think you are?
I've to arrest of
you've offended the law
Stop!
Get lost, bitch!
Help!
Help! I can't swim...
Hold on, I'll save you!
Go & save her now!
You know I can't swim, go & help!
Hurry up!
You always add me trouble
when I ask for help!
You've always made me down graded!
I'm benefiting you cause we're buddies
If you do this for me,
you'll surely be appreciated
You'll make me in deep shit!
You always bring troubles to me!
You've really a strong fist
Thanks!
Welcome, it's nothing
Let me do it
No, I've almost finished
Are you ok?
Ok!
Let me use Tse-ku to heal you
You know it?
Sure, but lack of practice
Take your clothes off!
You're great!
Comfortable!
Yes, but a bit painful
I've just called David,
he is on his way to here
What?
He gave me his name card
He asked us to call him for help
Why you trust him?
Tak, come on
What's the matter?
Come on!
Can I borrow it?
You're putting me in trouble again?
When did I put you in trouble?
Other than those incidents!
Go to buy something to eat, I'm hungry!
I pay for it again?
Sure, cause we're buddy?
You...
Are we buddy?
You always make your buddy miserable!
Stop!
Dragon, what are you doing?
What're you doing?
You damn ABC, you play tricks on me?
Kill me then!
I don't want to do it!
You'd deserve it
What are you doing
Cruel interrogation
Hold the bowl
Don't
Don't move!
If you want your face ruined, move
What's the relationship
between you & Waise Chow?
Do you want to murder him?
Put it back!
Hands off!
Oh my face hurts!
Damn! Oh! My face...
Help! It's painful...
Will water hurt you face?
It's only water!
Look into the mirror!
I'm scared! You nuts!
You deserve it
You want to know it? Ok!
Those are the dirty money
I brought from US
Waise Chow's responsible to
white wash it
I'm suspecting that
he arranged the robbery & murder!
You idiot! He is on our side!
See, no bullet!
Give me the keys, hurry up!
Be quick!
Thanks!
I'm sorry!
I know where Mandy & Dragon are
Really?
Yours dirty money is taken away
by them
I give you the people,
you give me 30% of the money, ok?
What dirty money?
Stop acting,
I can arrest them anything, so that
They'll disclose your crime
Sergeant,
I'm a lawyer as well as a merchant
What secret do you mean?
You're black-mailing me
It's a trade only,
deal or no deal, it's up to you
You want to black mail me?
You're not wise enough!
Mr. Chow, what do you want to show me?
Your fellow wants to blackmail me,
he hides the criminals too
You can search him.
He taped the conversation
Search!
Don't drive mad...
Don't push him!
I've a tape too
Sergeant Ho,
if you beg me to defend you
You may be spared
You asshole!
Tak, give a report to me
During the investigation,
you are temporarily suspended
Are you ok?
I'm ok!
You're so careless
Inspector Yeung,
although such thing happened
I'm still willing to co-operate with you
Thanks
Miss Leung, may I come in?
Sure
What can I help you?
I'm suspecting you are linked with
the murder of Petty Lee
You're under arrest!
Don't go, or I'll shoot
It's illegal!
How can we arrest Waise without a car?
You've being suspected of murder,
which is more serious crime than this
Hurry up!
It'll be ok soon!
Get on the car!
Come on!
You're great,
you're faster in stealing car!
It's on hire, idiot!
Why'd we steal? Idiot!
Sit the back seat, I'll drive
Why?
I'm familiar with the traffic of HK
But you're wanted by the police!
Sit at the back
Shut up!
You 2 sit at the back, I'll drive
There is Waise's home,
I'll give you signal
Then you go & stop his car
How about you?
We'll catch a fainted Waise
for questioning
How you drive?
David, what are you doing?
He's Uncle Chiu!
What shall we do then?
Boss is being attacked!
We'd fight back!
Take the knife!
Watch out!
Go after them!
Don't go!
You dare to run?
Mandy
Don't go!
Kill him!
Where is here?
Hotel!
Where are my clothes?
Yours are dirty & worn,
I've got rid of it
Did you... touch me?
Sure
Otherwise, how can I put you in bed
You are over weight!
Any more?
Any?
Good figure
You've seen my body?
No! Except the important part!
Those clothes are wet,
it'll make you sick
What else did you do?
I did want to do something,
but you awaked early
Next time I'll do it
How dare you?
Sorry, I don't intend to!
You've seen me, we break even
I didn't!
Ok, I'll let you see once more!
You...
Ok, don't you think I'm scared!
Take if off you've guts,
I'll tease you!
Take if off! Why not?
Don't be serious!
I've brought you a suit, try it
I think you'll look pretty, try it
How is Dragon?
Who's the litter bug?
I'll call the police?
Who did it! Come out! Bastard!
What's the matter?
What're you doing here?
Don't go!
Freeze!
Go over there!
Ok!
No.6767 reply
What? They're in motel now?
Open the door!
Sorry, I'm off!
You're committing an ordinance!
I'll sue you
You're stink
Don't come in!
My friends live here
You're stink, you can't come in
I can't smell it
You're stink!
Where's Mandy?
Bathing
While I was risking my life,
you took her here?
What's that mean?
What did you do to her?
This is my privacy,
none of your business!
You want to court her,
that's my business
Is she your wife?
No
Sister?
Your mom?
You crazy!
That mean,
it's none of your business, right?
Damn you!
What are you arguing?
Dragon, why you look like this?
I'm worrying about you
I'm fine
Are you staying here for long?
Half the night, I've just waked up
You look pretty
Isn't it? Dragon
Yes
He gives it to me
Turn a round
What're you doing?
Stomach-ache...
I'm going to get the jacket
You won't believe in me,
you'd better ask her
Don't you think I'm scared?
What's the matter?
He's something to ask you
What? Go ahead
You look ugly for
lacking of enough sleep
You're even worse
What I concern most is
how to find the money back
I won't care anything else
This is your own business
I'll give you bonus
if you get the money back tome
US$300,000
It's such a small amount!
I've seen the case, it's filled with money
You saw the case?
Your partner with
the case has pumped info me
before entering the lift
Hold it, I saw Kent running out
without holding anything
I know where the money put
Come down!
Sometimes, violence works
Mandy, lady first
We'd do such dangerous thing
You'd better watch out
Get up
Watch out!
Dragon, watch out too!
Ok?
Did you sleep with Mandy?
If I say no, you won't believe
If I say yes, you'll totally believe
You'd better ask her
Find it?
What is it?
We're rich!
Mandy, cheers
You'll deserve it
Another one here,
I've burned a 50 note only
Come on ABC, let's cheers
Thanks for your help
I do it for myself only
Who is going to beat Waise Chow for me?
I'll do it
What've you planned?
1 st, I'll go back to US,
2nd, to find a girl friend here
Girl friend? How's she look?
Have a look of this photo,
you'll know it
Have a look, come on...
It's me!
I always think of getting rich
But I've never think of
the life after rich
Now, I've got it!
I'll go to Caribbean Sea for sun bath
I've heard that the girls
there are easily hooked
Do you know where's Caribbean Sea?
I don't know
You're jealous only
I'm not qualified to jealous,
but I can drink...
I know who I am!
Best wishes to you two
My regards to you two!
To us? That means we're gays?
I'll take this money
to Uncle Chiu tomorrow
Don't you afraid of Waise Chow?
He can do nothing cause Chiu's here
Give me the bonus
Take it yourself
Dragon, which is more important?
Money or friend?
Both are important to me
I'll go with you tomorrow
Thanks, this is my family business
Do you treat us as friends?
Ok, let's go together
But now,
let's enjoy ourselves first
Sure!
Let's play the guessing game,
drink a glass of wine if you loss
If I loss, I'll drink double
No. Let's make it equal!
Be fair!
Ready, go!
6, 1 0, 8, 6
You loss!
Why the glass shakes?
Hold it tight for me please
Ok... Come again!
Six... Six... Ten
You loss again, drink it
Ok, I'll drink it
Again?
Sorry? Buddy, take this first
Later on, I'll pay you the rest
You'd not make him drunk
if you treat us friends
Sorry, I didn't mean it
Can you stop going?
Are we better than yesterday we are?
That's why we'd have a better tomorrow
See you
Goodbye
Wake up!
Is it snowing?
Wake up! Hey
Uncle Chiu, I've found the money back
I've enough evidence that
Waise is the one
who masterminded the case
Uncle Chiu,
the money is here please judge it
He said that he'd enough evidence,
then judge it
Oh! He can't talk!
He can't judge it!
See, they're fighting!
Let them be! Let's watch
Go to hell!
What're you doing?
You'd sneeze to the wall
Sorry
Hurry up, he is coming
David...
Don't move...
Don't come over, or I'll shoot!
I mean it...
Let's go, Mandy
How are you, you should not die
We've agreed to go together,
why you go alone?
You deserve it
Shut up!
I don't want to put you into trouble
You'll be ok, David!
You can't die! You'd pay me the bonus
You cannot die
We're good friends, let's pay it later, ok?
If you don't pay we,
you'd not die!
Mandy
I think we can earn money together!
We will be partners
Our business will be so busy.
We'll work happy together
David!
The goods will be loaded today
in Kong Tai Godown, Yau Tong
Let's leave HK together
with the money ok?
No, we've not committed any crime
If we leave now,
we'll be wanted criminals forever
We can't let Waise Chow go!
Are you crazy? He is powerful here
The police are wanting us,
we can't do anything!
You can leave alone
I want to be proved innocent
even I'm killed!
You'll deserve it!
Don't block my way,
I'm not like you!
You've money in mind only!
I don't want to be a chicken!
It's none of your business
Stay where you are!
What is this?
If I were a money lover, I'd have left
who will help you?
If I am a chicken,
who's staying here safely? Lawyer Chang!
Hands off me!
Boss...
Tak!
Don't hide up! Get out now!
Or, I'll shoot him! Come out!
Ok, I'll shoot!
Leave me alone!
If I die, kill him for me!
Come out, or I'll shoot more!
You bastard!
I'm here! Come on... Shoot!