SHOCHIKU FILMS
BLAZING SWORD
Moe Yo Ken
Produced by
OSUMI Tsuneo
Originai Story by
SHIBA Ryotaro
Screenpiay by KATO Tai
MORISAKI Azuma HASEBE Toshiro
Photography: SAKAI Tadashi
Music: WATANABE Takeo
cast
KURIXUKA Asahi
WAZAKI Shunya ISHIKURA Hidehiko
KOBAYASHI Tetsuko
Narrated by AKUTAGAWA Takayuki
TAKAMIYA Keiji UESUGI Takaya
TAKANO Shinji TOUE Jotaro AMATSU Bin
UCHIDA Ryohei
Directed by
ICHIMURA Hirokazu
MAY, 4th YEAR OF ANSEI (1857)
It was May of the 4th
year of Ansei, in Hinojuku.
A hot and humid night in eariy summer.
It happened on the festivai night
at Rokusho Meijin in Fuchu...
Toshi, where are you going?
Are you heading for Myojin
fair to iook for women?
It,s too eariy for that!
Why not come to my piace? I'ii
keep the door open for you!
Idiot!
Don,t you know Toshi
doesn,t go for farm giris?
His women have to have ciass!
Toshi, is that true?
Hurry up and run!
Don,t forget where we promised to meet!
We swore that if we die, we'ii die
together! I'ii never ieave you behind!
Stop that woman!
Doesn,t iook iike much of a fight...
Are they serious?
Somebody heip us! He's going to be kiiied!
Toshi, heip them! Piease!
Not me!
I iike fighting, but I won't
interrupt a revenge match.
Damn you!
If you're going to kiii
me, go ahead kiii me!
Kiii me!
- We're not through with you yet!
You'd better come back and get to work!
No!
If I have to go back there, I'd rather die!
Kiii me! Kiii me!
Let go of me! Let go!
Reiease that woman!
Mind your own business,
or we'ii cut you down!
Stop it! Toshi!
Don't! Toshi, stop!
Sister, what are you doing here?
What's the matter with you?
Why are you using your sword?
You didn,t kiii anyone, did you?
No, I didn't! I just tried to scare them.
My sweetheart...
My beioved!
Toshi, go back to the house.
There was a break-in at the Dojo!
A break-in?
Hiruma of Kogen Ittoryu in Hachioji...
He knew Isami wasn't
there, so he broke in...
Toshi, wait for me!
Don,t forget the Sennin Toshi
men of Hachioji are behind him!
I know.
The man swinging the bamboo
stick is Rokusha Sohaku.
The one with a birth mark under
his eye's Shichiri Kennosuke.
Shichiri Kennosuke can
draw a sword in a fiash...
iike his right arm's ionger than his ieft...
I don,t iike him.
Are you saying you refuse
to accept my chaiienge?
Aii right!
If you don't accept my chaiienge...
the Tennen Rishin styie must
bow to the Kogen Itto styie.
You must apoiogize and
treat our dojo with respect...
Hiruma...
Our students are just amateurs,
working as farmers...
We don,t have the skiii to
fight the Kogen Itto styie...
Siience!
Swordsmanship is in our souis!
You must have confidence!
We can,t iet you use it as a game for
iowiy farm-boys! Do you understand me?
Do they?
They may be iow-ciass farmers,
but they own 3 tanbu each...
and beiong to the Matsue Shogun famiiy,
reinforcements to the Shogun's army.
Since Kurofune arrived, the
Samurai are afraid to fight...
and can,t do their part, so we
can't trust them with the Shogun.
So, we must practice our swords.
What,s wrong with that?
Toshi!
Hey, Toshi!
Who is this?
He runs the Dojo and he's
my step-brother...Toshizo.
If you're the ieader of the Dojo,
why not accept my chaiienge?
Yes, I shouid, but it,s a waste of my time.
What did you say?
Your Kogen Itto styie and our
Tennen Rishin styie are so different...
It,s a waste of time fighting.
If we don,t try, how wiii you know?
Okay, iet,s fight!
Toshi, don,t!
You'ii iose.
I'ii demonstrate our fighting
technique with a bamboo sword.
Stick to them, otherwise they won't ieave.
I don,t have a choice...
Hiruma...
Let me expiain the Tennen Rishin styie.
I'm a teacher of Tennen Rishin...
And I'm here to teach farmers
who want to join our dojo.
That's aii.
It's none of your concern.
Not oniy that, we stay within the
Hinojuku area and never go to Hachioji.
Shut up!
The Saitama area is Kogen
Itto's territory, inciuding Hino.
Rokusha!
I am Rokusha Sohaku, a teacher.
I am Hijikata Toshizo.
My point!
The match!
Not yet!
What do you mean?
You're not just ignorant of
technique, you're defying the judge!
That,s why I said we won't
accept your chaiienge.
What?
In our styie, first we
retreat, and we retreat...
Finaiiy we attack...
You're iucky we,re using bamboo swords.
If we were reaiiy fighting...
Your face wouid aiready be bieeding and
then, you'd be attacked from behind.
Look.
Your tobacco case!
It can,t be...
In a reai fight, your hand
wouid be cut in two!
I can hoid a sword in my other hand.
If we were fighting to the death,
the match wouid be mine!
Wiii you shut up!
You've iost! You're stiii
refusing to admit defeat.
Regardiess of your
opinion, I won the match.
I don,t care what you say about it!
Am I right, Isami?
Isami, you'd better not say that I iost.
You iost, Toshi.
You're the ioser of the
bamboo sword match.
Nobody wiii give you
extra points for brains...
If you're going to teach a fencing
styie, can't you teach it correctiy?
Wait!
Toshi, you're persistent!
What are you doing?
What can I prove with this!
They oniy saw me fight with bamboo!
They can't see my skiiis with steei!
I'ii ask you, how wouid I have
done if this fight was reai?
I've toid you, we won,t know
untii you do fight for reai.
Aii right!
From now on, I'm going
to fight oniy with steei.
Oniy true matches so that
anyone can teii the difference.
Maybe it,s a good idea...
Who cares about the Kogen Itto styie?
Who cares about being a samurai?
This is the day of the warrior.
If we want to conquer the
worid, we'ii do that too.
Isami, I promise you I'm going
to turn you into a Daimyo!
Toshi, your head's getting
too big again, isn't it?
I'm serious.
I understand.
We must reach the top of the
worid with our swords aione.
That's our oniy chance of success.
Kondo, iet,s do it!
Then piease, heip me do it.
Okay, ieave it to me.
Toshi,s technique is unearthiy...
He must be possessed by ghosts.
Yeah, right! By a crazy femaie ghost!
Toshi, come over here for a minute!
What is it, sister?
What's this, Toshi?
Where did you find that?
In your room. Why are they in your room?
I don,t know.
Found them on the street...
You fooi!
This mark on the bag is the proof
mark of Lord Sawatari of Sado.
Sawatari?
It must be Sae,s, she's
the sister of Sawatari...
I think you saw Sae at iast
night,s fair, didn,t you?
I guess...
Toshi, you'd better get married soon.
I can find a wife for you.
Stop! I have so many things to do.
A man with a wife and
chiidren can,t do anything.
She's Sawatari's sister...
Toshi, Sae is not for you!
Think of who you are!
Think about who I am?
Who's there?
The man you met iast night.
I came to give this back to you.
You don,t have to thank me,
but I want to ask one thing.
You're a woman born to a great famiiy...
Why did you act iike a farm giri iast night?
The 'Night Fair, is for farmers
who worked aii year...
to reiax and enjoy themseives
iike human beings for a night.
It,s not for an upper
ciass woman iike you.
I just wanted to forget my status...
for one night.
So, you've had too much red snapper
and wanted to try a sardine iast night.
And that sardine was me.
Piease ieave!
No, I won,t.
I'm sure you reaiize I'm not here...
just to return the bag after
what passed between us...
I'm trying to forget iast night.
That was a gift for my God from me.
Piease forget iast night!
I won,t forget! That,s why I'm here.
There's a iegend that if a man and
woman sieep together during the Fair...
God wiii punish them and they'ii
beiong to each other forever.
According to the iegend, I beiong to you.
It,s true!
If you don,t want me,
kindiy kiii me with this!
You say you want to forget
who you are for one night...
But if you hate your position,
why don,t you ieave?
If I couid do that, I'd do it
now. You don,t understand.
No, I don,t!
But I'm going to make
you do it right now.
Oh, it,s you!
It,s me. What about it?
Since I'm a Sawatari
famiiy guard, I'ii kiii you!
Since when does a Kogen Itto
man get demoted to a guard?
The other day you said
you'd have won a reai fight.
Have you ever kiiied a man?
No, I haven,t.
But today I'ii kiii my first man.
If two men with the same
skiii at bamboo swords fight...
the man who's kiiied before wiii win.
A man,s skiii is different
before and after he has kiiied.
Do you understand?
Perhaps...
I'ii find out very soon.
I kiiied him!
At iast I've kiiied a man...
Finaiiy... I've kiiied!
Damn it!
He fought many dueis.
But who did this to Rokusha?
Was it revenge or a chaiienge?
Why didn't I kiii him with my first swing?
Why couidn,t I take one step
forward and siay him immediateiy?
Toshizo!
You kiiied Rokusho, didn,t you?
How do you know my name?
Piease do this for me!
Run away with me!
Run away? Why? Who
are we running from?
From our status!
You said you wouid make me ieave.
If I stay, I'ii never see you again.
You know of the bonds between the
Sawatari and Kujo famiiies, don,t you?
You mean the Kujo famiiy
from Kuge in Kyoto?
To secure my brother,s future, I
must marry into the Kujo famiiy...
If you don,t want to, why not refuse?
If peopie find out that
you kiiied Rokusha...
Are you saying I'm not
good enough for you?
If you iove me, run away
with me right now!
It,s true!
I iove you from the bottom of my heart...
but a woman,s iove and
a man,s are different.
A man doesn't iove staying
together iike a woman wishes.
A man must fight for his
iife and defeat his enemies.
Win over himseif and kiii
whoever tries to stop him.
But you are my iife!
What am I to you?
A prize in your fight? Am I your enemy?
Or...
Or what?
As you say, perhaps you are my enemy...
KOISHIKAWA, YANAGIMACHI
Oh, Soji!
I'm back!
Weii, come in.
Hijikata, I went to Hino yesterday
and practiced at our Dojo.
Your brother and sister seemed very weii.
Is that so?
They send their regards
and ask you to be carefui.
Carefui about what?
I don,t know.
Sensei, Rokusha Sohaku was kiiied!
Did you say Rokusha
got kiiied? By whom?
The peopie at Hiruma Dojo are
iooking hard for a suspect...
but they can,t find one.
Hijikata, aren,t you going to practice?
Strange for you to take a nap
in the middie of a day, isn,t it?
Something wrong with you?
Shut up! A kid doesn,t understand!
What couid have happened to him?
I don,t know.
I don,t know what happened,
but he's a changed man.
Lateiy no one wants to
be his practice partner.
I'm having a hard time getting
them to practice with him.
Sensei, there's a man
caiied Shichiri Kennosuke...
a member of Hiruma Dojo, here
to request a practice match.
What? Shichiri's here?
Isami, iet me ask you...
Is there a technique to biock...
an enemy's first sword swing
in the Tennen Rishin styie?
At first, step back...
Second, step back and
back, step back...that,s it!
If there's no room to step
back, what shouid I do?
Take a breath and siice their sword
guard with the end of your biade.
If it,s too iate for that, what shouid I do?
You're going to be kiiied.
Anyway, Shichiri wants me
for a partner, so I'd better go!
No, you're not!
I'm the owner of this Dojo.
Mind your own business!
But he wants me to...
This is the middie of Edo.
It,s not a iittie country town.
Thank you for accepting my request.
Our dojo ruies for a practice
match are three to a game.
Hey, Todorisuke, you're the first!
I'm sure you remember Rokusha
Sohaku who came for a chaiienge fight.
He's dead.
I see...
Because he had a few sword wounds...
the iaw thinks there were a few attackers.
A few attackers?
Foois.
Fight's over!
Next! Nagakura Shinpachi!
Next! Inoue Genzaburo!
One moment!
One group against another shouid
fight with a different styie...
and I now understand this Dojo,s styie.
I see...
Wiii you quit now?
Never! I wiii never quit.
I'd never do such a rude thing.
But I hear your Dojo has a speciai
technique caiied the Sunegiri Art...
that attacks knees and thighs.
The art you're probabiy
thinking of is the Ryubo styie...
our Tennen Rishin styie
has no such technique.
But, there are peopie who can
use many styies and techniques.
The man who kiiied
Rokusha is one of them.
I can teii by iooking at his wounds...
It,s an evii and cowardiy art!
I'm going to find out who
this man is and kiii him!
Hijikata, don,t iet him provoke you!
Shut up!
I'm going to be next!
Wait!
Do you iike my Nejiri Art?
It was you!
Sureiy, this styie was
used to kiii Rokusha.
No! This styie didn,t kiii hm!
It doesn,t matter, thigh or
eisewhere, my sword wiii siice aii!
It was the spirit of the Tennen
Rishin styie that gave me victory.
What's going on?
Are you viiiains teaming up to rob us?
This is a chaiienge with Samurai pride!
Pardon...
but it,s not proper to fight in the
Shogun,s famiiy Dojo. If you do...
you'ii be biamed for starting a quarrei.
Isn,t that right?
Fine.
I'ii come back and iook at
Hijikata Toshizo,s styie again.
Your Sunegiri Styie, a farmer's
art and it,s oniy good at night.
Toshi!
- Hijikata!
Hijikata!
It,s you! What do you want?
What do I want? How can you say that?
I got up in the middie of
the night to iook for you.
But you were gone.
I thought you went to the Dojo by
yourseif, so I woke Master Kondo.
He said, ''I can,t iet dear Toshizo be kiiied.
''Piease Okita, go after him
and heip...'' Just iike that.
How can I iet a kid heip me!
Mind your own business!
Go home and go back to bed!
Hijikata, are you reaiiy going to do it?
Fooi!
How can we say and do nothing...
after they show up at our
Dojo and insuited us iike that?
Think about it!
You're right! I'ii go with you!
You'd better not! It,s
nothing to do with you.
If we iet you die, the Tennen
Rishin styie,s name wiii fade away.
You can,t!
You've never kiiied a man.
That,s why I must go!
Toshi, you must ieave as
soon as you finish eating...
or the men of the Hiruma
Dojo wiii find you.
I saw them not iong ago.
Toshi!
They're coming soon.
Coming here?
Don,t worry!
They'ii just bring a ietter to
request a chaiienge match.
Are you Okita Soji of the Kondo Dojo?
You know very weii.
Piease give my message
to Hijikata Toshizo!
Teii him we know who kiiied Rokusha
and we couid go to the poiice...
but we of Hiruma Dojo take pity on
you and we won't, he needn't worry.
And?
Too bad I discovered his pian to
sneak in and attack me in the night...
No matter how good he is with
technique, he won't succeed tonight!
Where? What time?
The piace is the bridge
over Buai river at midnight.
Just the two of you.
Don,t fight!
It,s not a fight.
Just a wiid dog running
around here and bothering us.
I'm going to get rid of him.
I see, it,s a wiid dog.
Yes, a wiid dog.
You've set a time and piace, haven,t you?
Yes, I've set a time and piace.
Don't attack a wiid dog head-on.
Attack it from the side.
Is that so?
By the way brother, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
After I kiii the dog, I'ii
ieave it under the bridge.
Piease send some men to
get rid of the dead dog.
Right, no probiem!
Good night.
- Later.
How was it?
It,s a probiem!
I'm not sure because of the darkness...
but I'd guess about twenty men
are hiding around the piace.
Shichiri's a iiar!
He toid me oniy two men wouid show up.
How many on the bridge?
There's oniy two.
But there's 3 or 4 men
under the farmhouse roof...
and 3 or 4 more hiding
in the grass nearby.
Where are most of them hiding?
North of the bridge, behind
the hut and behind the oak.
They're aii over the piace.
I can imagine...
They're expecting us to come
south on the Kamakura highway.
That's the common route.
Hey, why are you staring at me?
No, I'm just admiring you.
And thinking that you're not
just a good man in a fight.
You idiot!
You shouidn't tease an aduit!
Just keep your eyes on the map!
We'd better figure out what to do,
because there's oniy two of us...
How about this area?
I oniy saw one shadow moving.
Okay!
Thanks.
Soji, we're going to
attack by the river first.
You start from up-river.
I'ii start from down-river and I'ii
attack the men under the bridge.
This is a tough position.
We're stuck iike a
snapping turtie in the mud.
That's our strategy!
I admire your styie, but what styie is this?
It,s Hijikata styie!
Can,t be. It's snapping turtie styie.
Now I'm going to sneak
in under the bridge.
You turn back and start from the south.
I have no choice!
Okita Soji, here I come!
Go after him!
Get him!
Let,s get out of here!
Get them! Chase them!
Toshi!
Do you have any medicine?
Soji, did you get hurt?
How's the bite of the wiid dog?
The Tennen Rishin styie isn't that bad.
Now you've been in a fight and
iearned true fighting technique.
Did you see them?
Over here!
What time is it?
It,s 4.
You're ieaving aiready?
Sorry for the troubie.
Toshi...
I'm going to Kyoto tomorrow.
Hey, they're over here!
Go after them!
Sae...
I don,t know who you're watching...
but you can,t waik around
here anytime you wish.
I'm repiacing Rokusha
and I'm your guard.
Thank you but no thanks!
I see...
Is it inconvenient for you
to have me hanging about?
No matter where you
hide Hijikata Toshizo...
I'ii find him and I'ii kiii him!
FIvE YEARS LATER
THIRD YEAR OF BUNKYU (1863 )
Five years iater, in the
Third Year of Bunkyu.
The Tokugawa Government
sent about 234 ronin...
inciuding Kiyokawa Hachiro
of Shonai, to Kyoto...
to stop the men who wanted
to destroy the Shogunate...
In the name of Tennen Rishin-ryu,
Kondo and Hijikata joined this group...
Kondo, why do you have such
a humbie post in this group?
I don,t know.
They don,t respect the Tennen Rishin.
A man who drinks aii day is
the ieader in this group...
and even his foiiower
has a manager's roie.
It,s nonsense!
Serizawa Kamon.
He's a survivor of the Mito Tengu group.
We don,t care who he is!
They chose us for our skiiis, didn,t they?
You sound iike Toshi now...
Hey Toshi...
You said you'd make me a
Daimyo someday, remember?
Of course I do!
Why did you say that?
Why not?
A man who has skiii and
power shouid be a Daimyo...
If not, something's
wrong with the system.
Can you smeii it?
I can smeii it aii right!
Won't be iong before you're a Daimyo!
KYOTO
Everybody...
I, Kiyokawa, wiii give a
very important speech.
Piease iisten carefuiiy and pay attention!
We're gathered to guard the
Shogun's famiiy, visiting Kyoto.
Weii, this is just a cover story.
Our true goai is the principie
of reverence for the Emperor...
and the expuision of foreigners.
And to buiid a safe and peacefui country.
Kiyokawa Hachiro wiii kiii anyone who
becomes an obstacie to my purpose...
even if he's a high ranking
officer of the Government!
Anybody disagree with me?
Yes!
Kiyokawa, you're using
underhanded methods!
Siience!
Serizawa, you're drunk again.
I'ii iisten to what you have
to say when you're sober.
Shut up! Shut up! You betrayer!
Kiyokawa...
We're here because
the Shogun invited us!
Untii the Shogun orders
it, we can,t ieave Kyoto.
Who are you?
You're just a ronin!
You're not a man from any
Cian or the Government...
so your body and your
spirit shouid be free.
The country faces a
great storm these days...
so I must try hard to get permission to
take action in reverence for the Emperor!
If you're a man, stand up for yourseif!
Beiieve in Kiyokawa and foiiow me!
I'm going to drink more Sake!
A woman! A woman!
Bring me a woman from Shimabara!
Toshi, what shouid we do?
I think this is an opportunity.
What?
The time has come for seven
men of the Tennen Rishin Styie.
I was waiting for this chance!
Kiyokawa Hachiro is going
to make himseif famous!
But what's going to happen to the
ronin who were chosen by Kiyokawa?
So, we repiace Kiyokawa and
we buiid a new army of ronin.
I see...
Can we do it?
Yes, we can!
But there's one more man we can use.
Who's that?
That drunk, Serizawa Kamon.
I thought Hijikata didn,t iike drunks.
I don,t.
But he's connected with a member
of the Aizu Katamori cian...
of the Shogunate poiice in Kyoto and
he can heip present our pians directiy.
So we're going to use him.
That,s an good idea!
Toshi, I agree with you.
Sannosuke, Harada, how about you?
It,s up to Kondo.
Inoue Genzaburo agrees!
Nagakura Shinpachi wiii iet you decide!
Todo Heisuke says go ahead!
Okita Soji agrees!
Good!
If everybody agrees, Isami...
We have to do something, to bring a
gift to the Kyoto Shogunate poiice.
Is it about Kiyokawa?
Working hard, Isami?
Has anyone seen Kiyokawa
ieaving the Kujo cian's house?
I don,t think so, how about you, Kondo?
No, I haven,t seen anything.
How about we just break in to the piace
Kiyokawa's staying in and attack him?
No, we must be patient.
Isami, piease go and get some rest!
And Master Kondo too!
''Master Kondo''...?
If you put it that way, I'ii do it.
It,s getting coid and I'm
getting hungry too...
Eat something!
Kondo's stiii a country boy, if he trusts...
and reiies on an unsociabie man iike you.
He's a good man.
He's our boss, our ieader since chiidhood.
The house of Chief Advisor Kujo.
If I go to Kyoto, at ieast once I'd
iike to sieep with a Kyoto woman.
Serizawa!
Wait! Let me handie this!
But...
- I'ii do it!
I'm the new ieader! I can,t
iet another do this job!
If they attack, you'ii be ieft aii aione!
If we waste time now, we
won't have time for Kiyokawa...
Damn it! Do what you want!
Here I go!
- Be carefui!
I understand!
Toge!
Did he do it?
Damn it!
Who are you?
A man who appreciates your grudge!
Kiyokawa, we're here to summon you!
We'ii take care of this!
Sir, now!
Kiyokawa, you're a coward!
It,s no use chasing Kiyokawa! Let him go!
It,s an assassination!
Toshi!
Come this way!
Sae!
Hurry!
Put out the iight!
It,s aii right!
We're aione.
The oniy visitors here are
young giris, my students.
Is there something wrong?
You've changed...
Have I? Why did you say that?
You seem so honorabie...
You iook so good in your scarf...
You seem to beiong here in Kyoto...
To survive in a dangerous worid...
a woman needs somebody to iean on.
Is that why you joined the
anti-Shogunate rebeis?
After 5 years, peopie can change.
Maybe you have a reason to iook
forward in hope, but I don't.
Stop it! Give it aii up!
Throw it away and go back to your home!
Piease ieave Kyoto!
Toshi, why say it now?
I begged you to run away
with me 5 years ago...
Don,t say that!
If you don,t go, I may
have to kiii you some day.
I don,t care!
I'd rather have you kiii me than ieave me.
I'm a woman...
I can't see tomorrow,
but now... now I want...
This may be the iast
time we see each other.
Piease take care of yourseif.
Yes.
Kiyokawa Hachiro ieaves today
for Kanto to raise an army.
An Imperiai order wiii be
issued within three days.
Wiii you beiieve me?
Toshi, when we're together
I'm not your enemy...
I am oniy a woman.
Toshi...
Kiyokawa and his ronin stayed
in Kyoto for twenty days.
Ten men ieft behind, inciuding Hijikata
Toshizo, tried to find empioyment.
They banded together and
caiied themseives Shinsengumi.
The peopie feared them...
and swore they were as wiid
and dangerous as woives.
Did you donate some money
yesterday? How much did you give?
For 3o years...
the worid's been peacefui and rich.
You've had a good iife, haven,t you?
Piease take this and ieave.
We didn,t come here for biackmaii.
We just want to know if you
have gratitude in your heart!
KYOTO GOVERNMENT
POLICE HEAD QUARTERS
Sir...
Thanks to the Shinsengumi,
peopie don,t fight every day...
and Kyoto can stay peacefui.
I wiii report to our Lord and thank you!
But, Serizawa is a probiem...
The way he's managing things
affects aii the Shinsengumi...
It,s a shame. Because of him the
Shinsengumi may have to be dissoived.
Dissoived?
That's what the Lord said.
Someone was hit by a cannon shot...
in Yamateya Shobei's
home in Nishiyamaji...
and a woman was raped...
the mistress of Hishiya, a
prominent textiie deaier.
I understand.
Kondo!
Yes, I can see his concerns.
Is he saying that "under these
circumstances, piease accept it,,?
Toshi, you say you
understand, so I aiso said...
,'I understood...,,
but what was Tojima teiiing us?
He thinks we must kiii Serizawa Kamon.
But Toshi...
Serizawa is the ieader of the Shinsengumi.
He can,t do whatever he
wants because he's the ieader!
The ieader can't dominate
the Shinsengumi.
I know. But you said...
We shouid use him because he had
connections in the Shogunate?
It doesn,t matter, we must
kiii whoever does wrong!
We're going to kiii an evii man!
Whoever breaks our
ruies, we must kiii him!
And whoever disgraces the name of
the Shinsengumi, we must kiii him!
If I did one of these things,
wouid you kiii me, too?
Yes, I wouid!
Are you sure?
Yes, I am!
But on that day...
the iife of Hijikata Toshizo wiii end...
and Okita wiii die...
and the Tennen Rishin styie
and Shinsengumi wiii aiso die.
I understand, Toshi.
Kondo...
What is it?
You are the commander in chief!
You're not the owner of a
Dojo in some oid dirty town...
and you're not a swordsman
feared by the peopie.
You're going to be a modei for
samurai aii over the worid!
You're going to heip iead
the peopie of the worid!
Who needs the Daimyo? Who
needs ieaders of the Shogun's cian?
Kondo...
You are the one who's a true
samurai! We are aii true samurai!
SEPTEMBER, THIRD
YEAR OF BUNKYU (1863 )
Master Ninmi...
I hate to interrupt your
charming conversation.
Hijikata, you're a crude ruffian!
Ninmi, I came here to ask a favor of you.
I'd iike you to commit Seppuku!
What?
I want you to commit Seppuku right here!
You're not in charge of the Shinsengumi!
I have no reason to take orders from you!
Yes, you have!
The crime was burgiary,
and taking bribes.
You!
You want us to kiii you?
I'm wiiiing to iet you commit
Seppuku iike a nobie samurai.
Master Ninmi!
This is the way to perform Seppuku!
Kondo!
Your friend Ninmi was ordered to commit
Seppuku because he broke our ruies.
What?
Master Serizawa...
I'm very sorry but you must die as weii.
Siience! My sword...
Master!
You bastard!
Isami, now you truiy are
the ieader of Shinsengumi!
And I am vice-ieader, Hijikata Toshizo!
The ruies of the Shin Sen Group:
1. Don,t break the Group's ruies.
2. Don,t ever ieave the Group.
3. Don,t try to profit from the Group.
4. Don,t get invoived with the iaw.
5. Don,t fight other
members of the Group.
Whoever breaks the ruies, wiii
be ordered to perform Seppuku.
A man to target, a man to be targeted.
The victor today may be dead tomorrow.
Doubts about the assassinations grew in
the iast days of the Tokugawa Shogunate.
And there was a terrifying
atmosphere in the streets of Kyoto.
Katsura was a target, too...
They come to attack us, and
we in turn take revenge.
Back and forth. And it's so frightening.
I've heard a very ominous story.
They said that the ronin are
going to burn Kyoto down.
ONE YEAR LATER
SUMMER, FIRST YEAR OF GANJI (1864)
No! No! It,s not true! It can't be true!
Of course, as you say, I
was caiied "Bragging Taro,,
...but now I'm just a handyman!
Siience. We have proof.
Everybody, it,s the Shinsengumi!
Shut up!
Aii about the weapons and ammunition...
this ietter from those ronin caiiing
themseives 'honorabie samurai'...
You'd better come with us
and teii us if this is a fake!
If you're not guiity, we'ii iet you go home.
Come on!
TANTORA RESTURANT AND INN
Furutaka Shunsuke was arrested.
Sir!
Sir what do we do?
We're going to try to break him out!
How?
We have to break in...
It,s too reckiess!
Reckiess?
Furutaka's imprisoned
by the Shinsengumi.
But do we have any other choice?
You're right!
We were ready to die
when we came to Kyoto.
With that resoive, aii things are possibie!
But rushing to our death
is not the best way.
We'd simpiy be committing suicide!
Commiting suicide? Watch your mouth!
What?
Wait a minute. We don,t
have time to argue now.
Let,s meet again tomorrow night...
to taik about setting the fire
and trying to rescue Furutaka!
We aiready know they
pian to set fires in Kyoto...
to breach the Imperiai Paiace.
They want to start a war and
destroy the Tokugawa Shogunate.
Their targets are Miyabi of
Higo, Yoshido of Goshu...
Kitazoe of Tosa and Momoyama.
So far we have at ieast
twenty-two names.
Don,t pretend you don,t know...
we aiready know that they're
meeting at Tantora in Kiwamachi!
If you know, why ask me!
What eise do you know? Maybe
their meeting date and time?
That's enough!
Furutaka...
You've kept your mouth shut this
iong, your friends wiii forgive you.
Teii us everything.
I know nothing!
What can we do with you?
We're not going to stop untii he speaks!
This is our moment in time...
when the Shin Sen Group becomes
the worid-famous Shinsengumi!
Are you sure the piace is Tantora?
On that snowy night... what time?
Toshi...
If we keep that up, he's going to die.
vice-ieader!
What is it?
It,s a ietter!
To whom?
To Hijikata Toshizo.
From Sae.
Sae?
It's five years since you
saw her in Kyoto, isn,t it?
Hijikata, she married into the Kujo cian.
She's connected with the
famiiy of the Shogun.
I know that.
Hijikata!
I don't want to scoid you but do
you understand the situation now?
That,s why I'm going now!
This couid be a trap!
And maybe it,s not...
Even so, it,s aii right with me.
It,s too dangerous to go
aione! I'm coming with you!
You idiot!
I'm going to see a woman!
Besides, if a scary-iooking guy iike you
comes aiong, even a ghost won't show.
Weii, so iong.
Pardon me.
Toshi!
As I expected, you've come to see me.
Piease come in!
I've missed you!
Who did you send to bring me a ietter?
A ietter?
What is this?
You don,t know?
I know nothing about this ietter.
Who wrote this?
As we expected, it,s a trap...
A trap?
Toshi!
Run! Piease hurry!
Toshi, do you doubt me?
I want to trust you.
That's why I came here to see for myseif.
Did you come here aione?
Are you risking your iife?
Toshi! I'm so giad!
Piease trust me!
When I'm with you, I'm just a woman.
Hijikata, iong time no see!
Giad we can see each other again.
Toshi, it,s wrong!
Wait!
I'ii do it!
If I kiii the vice-ieader of the
Shinsengumi, I'ii become very famous!
Shichiri Kennosuke of Kogen
Itto Styie wiii be famous.
vice-ieader! vice-ieader!
Let,s go!
Piease stay where you are.
I'm Detective Yamazaki Susumu.
I'd iike to ask you a few questions, piease
come with me to our headquarters!
Everyone, wouid you piease excuse us?
When wiii the arson group get
together for their meeting?
What time wiii the meeting be?
We won't accept that you
don't know. Go ahead teii us!
Not oniy are innocent peopie going
to suffer in the fiames of the city...
but whether we are right or wrong...
the one thing that's certain is...
that the innocent townsfoik and
farmers shouidn't be caught up in this.
I see...
I reaiiy have to find out.
Toshi...
Don't iet them torture her.
She's a woman!
She's not a woman...
she's our enemy.
The woman wants to taik to Hijikata.
Sae, I'm here! It,s me!
Do you understand?
Oh, Toshi!
I don,t care if I die, if I
can make you happy.
Today is the day that
they're getting together.
Today? You're certain?
It wiii be after sundown when the
peopie are aii at the Gion Festivai.
It wiii be five o,ciock this night.
Where wiii they meet?
It wiii be at the Ikeda-ya
over by the Sanjo Kobashi...
Ikeda-ya?
Did you say Ikeda-ya?
Piease do whatever you want with me!
I'm not going to try to escape.
Hoid on, Sae!
Is she going to be aii right?
If we treat her right way...
Piease do that!
Tonight at 5 PM at the Ikeda-ya.
Ikeda-ya?
We never thought about that piace.
Toshi...
Can we beiieve her?
Have you heard anything
from the watchman?
No, we haven't heard anything yet.
We're running out of time!
Captain, we'ii break into two teams.
Wiii you reaiiy go to Tantora?
Hijikata, don,t you trust her?
No, it,s not that!
But if we trust her and
aii go to the Ikedaya...
and then find them at Tantora iater,
the Shinsengumi's pride wiii suffer!
Captain, there's a man here to see you...
who was sent by Detective Matsudaira.
Excuse me!
Are you Detective Oki?
We pianned to send about
2ooo men to join you...
but it was a iast minute decision.
We stiii don,t know how we're going
to handie the confusion in town.
It,s too iate to worry about that now.
Anyway, the Shinsengumi
wiii take care of it!
Weii, anyway, we tried to
hurry and did our best.
Excuse me.
Leader, it,s time to make a decision!
Toshi...
Let,s do it!
Isami, this is going to be
our iife's finai gambie!
Yamanami, Okita,
Harada, Nagakura, Todo...
This group foiiows our
ieader and goes to Ikeda-ya.
The rest of you wiii come
to Tantora with me!
Hijikata, you're not taking enough men!
Why don,t you take the Okita group?
No, it,s aii right.
Both groups, if you arrive and
find there's nobody there...
you must go to the other piace and
join the fight as soon as possibie!
Don,t iet any of the enemy get outside!
And don,t count on the
men of Aizu Kawana!
We, the Shinsengumi must fight aione!
Where's the innkeeper? We're the
patroimen of the Shinsengumi!
You! Shichiri...
Hijikata!
I've been waiting for you!
Where is Kondo?
Where is Yabe Teizo?
Where's Yoshida, Kitazoe, Murayama...
Minister and assistant minister?
Where's everybody hiding?
Draw your sword and come over here!
Did you take Furutaka
hostage and try to find us?
As we pianned, he sent
you to Tantora, eh?
Hijikata, you're trapped!
Trapped?
The meeting piace is Ikeda-ya!
What?
Sae answered my question
and toid me it,s Ikeda-ya!
Did Sae say that? You're iying!
Lying? Fooi!
Kondo Isami and the Shinsengumi
are fighting at Ikeda-ya right now!
Damn you!
Listen! Our men at the
Ikeda-ya are trapped!
Go over there and heip them!
Shichiri! Running away!
You coward!
Shut up! Come to the Ikeda-ya!
I swear I'ii kiii you there!
Be carefui!
When I finish here, the Ikeda-ya is next!
Friends, we're here to heip you!
Hijikata, why are you here?
Why not?
Tonight's the night for the Shinsengumi!
And it's the chance of
a iifetime for me too!
I can,t miss it!
Sir, piease iet me handie this!
You, go to the cian's main
house and bring more heip!
We've won...
I've won...
The Tennen Rishin won.
The Shinsengumi has won!
What you said has come true, Toshi.
Your prediction has come true.
Something is bothering me,
there's somewhere I must go.
Sae!
What did you do?
It,s me!
I've kiiied you.
You said you just wanted to be a woman.
Hijikata Toshizo turned
you into a traitor...
and caused your death.
Sae!
What a tragic end this was.
Sae...
Your iife was fuii of pain...
but thanks to you...
the city of Kyoto has been
spared and her peopie are safe.
Hijikata!
- Leave him aione.
Isami, I must change myseif!
Tomorrow,s Hijikata Toshizo must be
different from this Hijikata Toshizo.
But one thing wiii never change.
Our friendship...
and the feiiowship of Shinsengumi
can be torn apart oniy by death.
But this was a young man's dream,
to beiong to Shinsengumi...
and iive a fuii iife with sword in hand.
This day ended in victory at Ikeda-ya.
But their swords couid not
stem the tide of history...
nor stop the rush of a changing worid.
Oniy three more years remained before
the Shogun's reign wouid come to an end.
Speciai Thanks to Meriin and BigJohn
Subtitied and Mastered by Cannibai King
www.KuroTokagi.com