Brought to you by
LesKing.com.vn | Best place for Les and Trans Guys
DESERT HEARTS
Excuse me.
Passengers of the super speed
service to Sacramento and Oakland.
can now be on board.
-Can I help you, miss?
-Please.
-I'll bring this for you.
-Thank you.
-Professor Bell!
- You can call me Vivian.
- Welcome to Reno.
-I am down the street.
- Hi Francie.
- Hello, Burnett.
- I have space in my car.
- No, not such luck.
Well, you are looking forward
to some desert living?
I'am looking forward to get
these shoes of.
It's terrible when
your legs hurts.
It's a kindest thing
I've heard in three days.
- How long have you been married?
- 12 years.
No,no. We handle that.
Quint, that's a lucky one.
I could have used that last night.
See you in six weeks, madam.
Soon as we are out of here you
can tell me all about youself.
I was the special dancer
in casino over there, 100 years ago.
Do you have children??
We were a couple of
professionals.
My husband was a prominent lawyer,
here in town.
- He died of a heart attack at 41.
- Sorry.
How long have you been alone?
I'm not alone, I have my boy.
My girlworks there
in the Golden Ring.
Has the unbridled
Glen force!
I have always lived
in the city.
Do not know what to do
with all this space.
I think of it as a God's backyard.
Just sit back and let
it clean out the impurities.
-And the heat?
-Lot of ice tea and not deep thinking.
I agree
Oh, Jesus!
-What are you doing at this hour?
- I have things to do.
-Professor Bell, Cay Rivers.
-How do you do.
-Shall I call you the professor?
-No, Vivian Bell.
Put that damned car forward!
Jesus!
You'll never guess who that was.
- Do you mind if I smoke?
- Of course not.
Never would have guessed
you smoked.
May I be honest, Frances?
That is an endangered art.
Forward.
My things are a little bit shaky
for me at the moment.
-Thank you for open up ...
-I can not be a part of group right now.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
Walter, we are here!
Walter, shake hands
with professor Vivian.
-Hello.
-You are younger than I thought.
-I'll take that as a compliment.
Bring bags, Walter.
You gona love it here.
Well, here it is.
Nice, isn't it?.
Lovely.
-He will take you to your room.
-Thank you.
-The bathroom is over there.
What do you teach?
Literature at the University
Columbia.
116th Street, Broadway,
New York, New York.
I know you want me to hang around and
tell you history of the ranch.
How did you guess, Walter?
Why I did not stay in a hotel?
I felt burned and start to yearn
Hold you tight
- Guess what baby girl.
- What?
I am engaged.
-Hello
-Hello, love.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Careful not to stay blind.
and...
I'm pregnant.
Joe and I are settling down.
Darrel and you should follow.
-We would go on vacation together.
-I feel nothing for Darrel.
I never get tired
to defend your reputations.
I got used people
talking behind my back.
but if you did not accept
who I am
that would really be tought.
Hey, you're the best.
And all the best people
know it.
Thank you
Good luck. Thank you.
- Would you like to play that, sir?
- Sherman.
Sherman, would you like to play?
I prefer to play with you,
my love.
Apologize to the lady, buddy.
-Apologize, man.
-Sorry.
It makes two of us.
-Thank you.
-You are right?
Yes.
- A cup of tea?
- Frances!
-Do you have any burbon?
-Sure.
In fact, I'll joing you.
Will not do any harm.
It's the weather.
I was reading a lot.
You sound like Cay.
She locks herself in that college
and works until she drops.
-What does she work?
-She is a sculptor.
Oh, don't look at that stuff
It is sentimental junk.
I have no taste.
That is Glen, Cay's father.
I had Walter with him.
I'm not the mother of Cay.
I'm her ...
I do not know what I am.
Not anything really.
Only one pair of hands
and a familiar face.
Thank you
God, look at him.
As handsome as day is long.
And married.
I lived with him 10 years.
Maybe I didn't get my wedding
bouquet in my collection.
But I got what I wanted.
I had a love of my own.
That song is beautiful.
You had more than
most people dare hope for.
Do not pay attention.
I'm just babbling.
I am a silly woman.
I don't think you are, Frances.
Hi.
You and me should make
a raisins pie.
-I'm too depressed.
-In this air?.
Will you well be fine when you
leave that creep.
Larry is not a creep
Any man who leaves a woman
for a model is a creep in my book.
I do not know which is worse.
A cheeter or a hobby man.
At least you can share
a hobby, Lucille.
We would all like to
have a different past.
Good morning!
Good morning.
-I come down to stretch my legs.
-It's was about time.
What did you do in that room
for last five days?
Whatever it is, it is too deep
for us to understand.
Come, sit down.
Join the girl talk.
We talked about sex
vs. marriage.
I'm not an expert on these issues
so I apologize.
I heard that your culture types
go out like a bench sheet.
- Lucille!
- Is that true?
A bench sheet is a woman
weeping for the dead.
Perhaps you wanted
to say "monkeys".
Hey!
Well, I'll start with my pie.
Lucille, would you drop Cays' mail?
I'll take it.
Just going for a walk, anyway.
Just slip it under her door.
You do not have to knock!
- Morning!
I was just passing by.
Thanks.
Do you want to come in?
-I'd love to but you're busy.
-Come in anyway.
To see if I can see it all
in one glance.
Look around.
I can't do it if you are watching me.
- Hello!
- Hey....!
Hello
-Where is Cay?
-I am here. Go back to sleep.
Sorry. I was not alone.
Fine. Socialization
was not what I had in mind, anyway.
You get all that traffic
without any equipment?
I can not understand.
-Where are you going?
-To an appointment with the lawyer.
No sense in taking two cars?
-I do not want to intrude.
-Will you bring her back?
Oh, don't worry about that.
Give space, Gwen.
You have a car for today
and I save the trip.
Cay, drive like a lady.
Someone used it as an ashtray.
Come in front.
Long time without seeing you, Mrs. Parker.
Doesn't bother me.
-This is my friend, Gwen.
-We met.
Yes, nice to see you again.
-Are you serious?
-Why?
That music is for a funeral.
Do you know that piece, Vivian?
Yes, it is a piece of Prokofiev.
Lovely, isn't it?
I better get to the record
store before they sell it out.
Oh, come on, Gwen.
We all have sensitive side.
I do not remember that
you said that last night.
-Thank you.
-Do you want me to wait?
I am sure you have better things
to do than wait for me.
Oh look, I am sorry about Gwen.
You know why I am here for.
I don't need to understand your friends?
I'll leave the key here.
I have more important things to
think than how I'll go back.
Thanks anyway!
You're welcome.
From what I see in this agreement,
Dr. Bell walks out with everything.
I've always supported myself.
All I want are my books.
-Is there a third party?
-No.
Rare women, walks out with
no strings.
What is your ground?
It is not that I have practiced
this.
It is not easy to talk
with an attorney.
-Do you like ranch?
-It's different.
There are many crazy people there.
Mr. Warner, I have 35 years.
I want an honest life.
I am leaving a decent marriage
to see if I can find one.
Not having children helps.
Although our careers served very
much that purpose all these years.
To bond us togehter.
We were very big on form.
Right friends, a prince
on the wall.
I urge for something we can not
analyze or rationalize.
Sure he refused to
visit in-laws, sometimes.
I want to break free
from what I've been.
And your husband?
Martin wants to have me
no matter how I feel.
-He will not contest?
-No, no.
Well...
-We'll go with mental cruelty.
-We've never treated each other that way.
It's just a formal term.
It is better for law.
A headacke or two.
Maybe I'll be alone
the rest of my life.
I made a very difficult decision and
it was not based on a headache or two.
Time for a martini.
Would you like to take one with me?
Please, go on.
Well, the first thing I
advise my clients
is not to leave the state
once the residence is established.
Many leave to San Francisco
for a break.
Don't misunderstand me,
Mr. Warner.
But that does not happen
in this case.
No. I trust we can leave the
keys with you any time.
Thank you.
Ok, put your stuff in here.
Lock it up. The changing room
is over there.
-Hello everybody. -This is Joyce.
-Hello, Joyce!
I leave you with the girls.
See you on the floor.
All right.
Cay, I'll like to see you in my office?
Please.
Darrel, where shall I put the key?
-Oh, God!
-I'll tell you where.
Thank you, Silver.
That was not very clever.
Cay.
Do you know how much I love you?
I started to express myself
and ruined everything?
There's nothing to ruin, Darrel
And I've been honest with you
about why.
I know everything.
I can look the other way
if I had to.
Oh, hi.
-Sorry.
-Frances is awake.
I just thought about ...
having a cup of tea.
Let me get it for you.
Don't bother. I could
use a practice.
Would you, please, go and
sit down?
If she hear us, I wont
get out in less than hour.
I'll come back when it is less
complicated.
Shit!
What are you doing?
Shut up!
I'll clean.
Look at my boots.
Please, don't
turn on the light.
What's matter?
You are having a rough night?
You could say that.
Listen, I'm always awake.
Next time you can't sleep,
come to my cottage.
Some company will help.
You'll make me cry.
No.
I'm going to make you some tea.
Is it you, Cay?
- Yeah
Bring me a coke, please?
I have a glass.
-Who is in the kitchen?
-Vivian is making tea.
She is so nice.
This all place has risen
category since she came.
I spend all night
struggling with migrene.
You are wearing that one
out, Frances.
No, everything is falling apart.
It is middle of the night.
It will be together by morning.
Ok...
What is falling apart?
The ranch, for example.
Business is bad. I don't think
it will hold much longer.
Remember the good old days?
Can not drink for the good old days.
If I do sell, I want you
to come with me.
We do not picture us living
in two rooms togehter.
Oh, It will be bigger than that.
If you come with me
You can leave the casino
and go to study art.
Botton yourself up.
Professor does not need
to see your business popping out.
-Where are your pants?
-I have to go.
I will not stay so do not
squeeze me.
You and Walter are all
I have left from Glen!
Glen is dead.
No, if I still have you.
Someday I will meet someone
who counts.
Counts?
But look at who your friends are.
Do not ask your support. But
if you stand in my way ...
Now, go to sleep.
I empty out my ice box.
Good night, Frances.
Good morning!
Good morning.
When was the last time you
ride a horse?
I don't even remember.
Then, take off your reading
glasses and come over here.
I did not know you were
painting, Frances?
The last supper.
Oh, looks like someone did not pack
riding cloths.
I thought my riding days are
behind me.
Here. Try this to see the size.
- Oh.
Reserve me place in the mental
for me.
Good times are hard in the end.
Sorry about your friend
the other day.
I temporary lost my sense
of humor.
It is awful to forget
how to laugh.
I'm always get-by by laughing.
That what you are going through
takes real courage.
You're the first person to say so.
Everyone else ...
Well, maybe, I am up
to the risk.
Here you go. Maybe some of your
gambling spirit rob off on me.
I am sure that nobody accuses
you of playing safe.
No, but that is because they
don't really know me.
There are so many things
I want to do but I am affraid to try.
-You're ambitious?
- I do all right here.
But there's always another story
under the surface.
- You know what I mean?
- I am about to. My surface drowned.
-Did you realise all your ambitions?
-No. Only my plans.
What do you say when they ask
about your marriage?
-I tell you that it sank in still waters.
-Say no more.
Hot ass, Joe.
Congratulations.
What? With a ring costing $ 100.
I need condolences.
-But her eyes are sparkling.
-Not sparkling. It is panic.
Kiss me in a way to
last me the entire shift.
Pervert.
-Do you have a date, Cay?
-No.
Pick up an extra steak, lover?
Hey!
I can not keep my hands off him.
And you invite me to your house
to watch the show?
I want to find out
why are you so mysterious.
Joe is in the kitchen,
you in the bathtub. I am happy.
Ok, now start talking.
-You'll gonna laugh.
-It must be serious.
I think I've found somebody
who counts.
From the beginning
and do not miss the good parts.
Well, she is professor of English
and is 10 years older than me.
Well, rock'n'roll!
It sounds a lot funnier than it is.
She is at the ranch?
You promised not to mess around.
Vivian Bell.
I just say her name
when I want to smile.
Did you sleep with her?
No. And probably will not.
-She does not want?
-It's not that, Sil.
Just remember that she will pick
up her decree and leave.
Maybe by then I will figure out
something in this screwed life of mine.
Oh, I love your life, babe.
I don't want to be here without you.
You look like two desserts.
Thank you for that.
Sometimes I'd like to know what
is like to be a beautiful woman.
-You want the ring back, honey?
-No.
Maybe I'll be reincarnated.
I'm going to check steaks.
Joe.
I'm afraid that if it will stay...
... this good...
I'll find a way to fuck it up.
Babe, don't we always
stick with good times?
-Did Cay behave herself the other day?
-She was absolutely charming.
-I would not be too won over by her.
-I do not understand.
The thing is ...
She has nothing in common with...
a person of your caliber.
I've seen this movie.
Good night.
We could stay here all day.
I'll bring lunch.
See you.
Bye.
Will you give me one?
No,no!
It's too big.
Take it on.
He did nothing as a singer.
So I started to work in casino.
In a hope of being discovered.
-Who named you "Silver"?
-I did.
But she still answers to Silvia
when she is wiery.
I'll ignore that...
Catherine Anne.
Oh, oh here comes snake guy.
It's hard to track you down.
I heard you spent night...
after Joyce.
you got it backwards for
a change.
This is our friend, Vivian.
-Whose friend?
-My friend.
-I am Darrel.
-How do you do.
You are probably doing better.
So, when we are going to see
you in that new outfit you just bought?
Uh, I barely had the nerve to
buy it...
But Cay convinced me
to throw caution through the window.
That is what she is best at.
I think I am going to try
my luck.
Whatever was your intention,
you accomplished quite the opposite.
I say, Cay steped way out of
her range with that woman.
Do you want a tip?
Change your seat.
-Thank you for really lovely day.
-You are welcome.
Good luck.
Ah, my back is killing me.
Yeah, I was on 6 tranquilisers
before I got here.
The house, the kids,
Gale...all of it.
Really? I am surprised. Your seam
so self assured.
Thank to Buck...
It's amasing what a little "understanding"
will do.
I do. Me and Cay are
becoming friends and that does help.
Not that it is any of mine concern,
but you should think twice before
hanging out with her.
You are right, it's not your concern.
Did you know that she was kicked
out of College
for "unnatural acts" they say?
Shall I rise up my
eyebrows in gasp?
Well, I am definitely out to lunch
when it comes to queers. You?
I don't think any of us would be
so limited, Lucille.
Nobody said that it did not
take all kinds, Vivian.
And your are certanly making
a unique contribution.
Hey Buck! Over here!
Are you winning?
Go away.
Yeah.
If you don't play,
you can't win.
Hey, Buck!
Come on.
Good luck.
Enough here. Put your bet.
Come on.
Down the way. Get your bet.
Your time is my time.
Come here, darling.
Change my luck.
No,no. Really,
I don't know how to play this game.
Well, I know how to play it.
And I am down $200.
You just give them a nice shake,
and roll them down.
Put them in the air now.
Let them go.
And get 7.
Roll 7. Lets go.
That a winner!
That was beautiful, thank you!
Come again.
same lucky lady.
Let's go. Come on.
Winner, winner!
Yeah, yeah again!
Winner. Lucky day.
This time blow.
Like this. And roll.
Roll 7.
2, and 2.
Not good. Sorry.
I am sorry.
You did fine. Take it.
I can't take it.
Sure you can.
Use it to get married.
Oh. Cash it in!
Cash it in ot not.
What's she gonna do?
Put bet down.
Here we go.
Well...
Pat is having an engagement
party tomorrow night.
I can't say I blame her.
Oh, we shall miss her with all
this volgars going on.
I made your favorite, pancakes.
You are not going to like it.
In the middle of that circus.
I am not going.
-Sensible.
-Why not?
I have lectures to prepare. I have only
week and half left.
Come on. Have some fun.
Did Darrel put you off?
Beg your pardon.
Don't fuss. Eat your breakfast and leave
the woman alone.
It doesn't concern you,
Frances! Honest.
You are skating on thin ice, girl.
I wont you to come.
How can you resist such a
passionate request?
Vivian, are you Ok?
Walk with me.
I apologize for not stepping
in and taking your side.
I surely wanted to.
-Would you do something for me now?
-Name it and it's yours.
You are a wise observer.
Why does your mother dislike
Cay and I being friends?
She wants Cay all to herself.
Does she mind you and I
spend time together?
I dont' believe but
I'll find put.
We are fated to be friends, Walter.
I felt that way since we met.
Care for chicklick?
I'd love one.
Based on what we just said,
would you reconsider going tomorrow night?
No. I don't think I'll be comfortable
celebrating with strangers.
Well, I am pretty sure Cay
can get me invited.
Are you asking me to be your
date, Walter?
Not exactly my date.
I know planty of girls.
I just ask would you? That is all.
How did you become
such a gentleman?
The movies.
We'll make an odd couple.
I guarantee you that.
I don't care about
stupid oppinions.
Folks, may I have your attention,
please?
Quiet!
I would like to welcome you
to this party of Joe Lorenzo.
Special applause for our
star attraction. Miss Silver Dale.
Please stop applauding
because I would like to sing.
I wrote this song last week and
I've been singing it everywere.
I wrote it ...  For everybody
that I love in this room.
Joe!
I am holding you of the gorund
all the time I sing this song.
Ok boys, let's hit it.
I need to find someone
that is mine.
I've been so lonely.
I've tried a few, wouldn't do.
I am so lonely.
Now I hope these days end...
and better days begin...
I am looking...
for someone to love.
I'll let the spark in my heart.
to flame so bright...
As I feel it burn I start to...
to hold you tight..
I know I gave no sign...
you must have read my mind.
I am looking for
someone to love.
someone
to love.
I love you, Joe!
What are you dreaming about,
old lady?
Glen and me used to go
dancing here.
I swear that if I was to turn
right now it's like
he would be standing right behind.
Why him and nobody else?
Beacause he reached in and
put a sting of lights right
around my heart.
These days are good and gone.
But you are still the best
dancer in town.
You better believe it.
Thank you
Mrs. Parker, I am cutting in.
Why? You go right ahead.
So, why do you live at the ranch?
It is my hide out.
I know all about hide outs.
What are you hiding from?
Anything I can't handle.
Well, I am relieved to hear that.
You know that I am not alowed
to go over State line?
I tell you what... What?
If any rules get broken, I'll
take the blame, ok?
Ok.
Now, I'll tell you what...
I...would prefer that
none did.
-Vivian.
-What?
I believe that you are loaded.
I could not imagine doing this
if I was not.
And what are you doing? Haa..
-So, how long you've been with Darrel?
-Not long.
What did hapen?
I alowed to myself to get attracted to
what is attraction to me.
-For him, that has been love.
-And for you?
Let's put it this way. I didn't
exactly get a ring.
-How do you get it?
-With the woman.
You are trying to shock me?
No. I was only telling you
the truth.
Did I missled you in any way?
Not for the minute.
Because...you know I
care a lot for you Cat, but...
Roll it all the way down.
You don't have to stop.
I do.
Where did you learn to kiss like that?
I don't know where they came from...
It belongs ... and I
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Take me back.
-I can't seea thing.
-I'll take my chances.
Just drive.
-Are you ok?
-I guess.
Well...Looks like you two
got caught.
We went for a ride to the
lake after the party.
Must have been quite a sight
to keep you up till now.
No, somebody is checking out.
Somebody is checking in?
I made a reservation at
The Riverside.
Your bags are packed.
I didn't know that leaving the
party would cause concerns.
It also caused talk.
Here is your refund check.
-That was uncalled for.
-Oh, for God sake Francis!
Don't you talk about God, girl!
You made your point, Frances
Just as well. I would leave anyway.
I'll never forgive you for this.
I'll never forgive myself.
Let her come here with her books,
and her influence over my family.
Shut up, Frances!
I can't claim angel wings,
but I am normal.
And when I think... I was
proud to call you my friend.
May I tell you - betrayal is
mutual.
- I want to do that!
- Walter, bring them here!
Can't you find something
better to do?
Not since you came on the scene.
Get in the house.
Now!
Can I go with you?
I can't.
I'll be at Silver's.
Will you call?
Let's go.
I guess the only was to
save my plants from
this damm disease is to buy a new one.
I am moving out, Frances.
- Why?
- To get your hands off of my life!
You sound like your father.
Using my place to hang your rat.
You want things without loving them!
That is greed!
Wasn't greed that took you in
when your mother left you.
It was not greed, it was
his soul comfort for 10 years!
It is fancy word for what
you really were!
It will be cold day in August
when I take in another educated tart!
She meant something to me.
And you knew it.
She'd broke your heart,
the one I ever...
There is no reason to stay.
Put your sweet lips
Little closer to the phone...
Let's pretend that we are together...
All alone
I'll tell the man to turn
the jukebox way down low...
Hello
-It's not complete.
-How is that possible?
Sorry.
-Over for tonight?
-Yes, sure.
Good night.
...mine, I got to know.
Should I hand up
or you'll tell him he
has to go?
You can't say the words I want
to hear while.
you are with other man...
Do you want me?
Answer yes or no...
Darling, I will understand...
Put your sweet lips
A little closer to the phone
Let's pretend that we are togehter
all alone.
I'll tell the man to turn
the jukebox way down low...
And you can tell your friend
there with you:
"You have to go"
Halo
No, Mr. Warner, it was
misunderstanding.
No, thank you.
Accomodations are just fine here.
That will not be necessary, mr. Warner,
although I appreciate it.
If you need to get in touch with
me, I'll be her.
Thank you. Good bye.
Are you ok?
I've been better.
Yes, I know what you mean.
Why did you come?
I guess I am scared to death
of not seeing you again.
Cay, you have to let it go.
You know that.
Stop it!
I want you to open the door!
- And I want you to leave me alone.
- I can't!
Honestly.
You look wonderful.
Are you kidding?
All right, Cay.
We'll talk.
You start.
You kissed me.
And you kissed me.
And I kissed you, I know...
I don't believe what I am saying.
You see...
I enyoj order.
What happened between us...
was innocent more than anything else.
And friendly. Don't forget that one.
I was really hoping that we can have
mature conversation about this.
So far we talked about order and
disorder and who kissed whom...
What the hell is it about anyway,
since it was all innocent and friendly.
Than I'll get to damm point.
I am a respected scholar.
I've been married many years to
respected scholar.
And for moment of indiscretion,
fleeding lap of judgement, I...
stood in the rain and allowed
Frances Parker...
figure without any resemblance
to anyone in my entire life experience,
to humiliate us as we were pair
of deliquents.
You should have told her off.
I don't have a habit of rising
my voice.
or false issues.
When I retire
I will simply write short stories
for my revenge
about this town, these
people, these gamblers...
My only clear memory is
arriving.
The rest is a blur...
Absolute blur.
Oh, God!
What do you think you
are doing?
Waiting for you.
I want you tu put your cloths on
and leave.
-No you don't.
-Yes I do.
No you don't.
I...
I wouldn't know what to do.
You can start by putting
"Do Not disturb" sign on the door.
Well...
That part went smoothly.
So, take your hands out of your
pockets and come here.
I am not...taking off my robe.
Well, everybody draws the line
somewhere.
I don't usually...
feel this way...
it's blocking me.
I don't know if I felt
this way ever before.
I am sorry.
That goes the hot water.
Vivian...
We have to get out of here,
you know?
Stand up...
-Take a walk.
-I don't...
Have a coke?
We go shopping?
You feel sorry?
-No, I feel exposed.
-Because of me?
And me.
Do you know how beautiful you
are right now?
I don't have any references for this.
-I am not great at it either.
-You had the experiences before.
Not this one.
My life has always been so
contolled.
-And it will be again.
-Sure, of course.
An affair, a divorce.
Nothing to break stripe on.
-I love you.
-And affair with 25 years old woman on my head.
I really do.
I am sure that students and the
faculty will appreciate that.
"These things happen".
I love you, too.
Compliments of the boys.
-Let's leave.
-Oh, just relax.
-Check, please!
-We haven't had desert yet.
We'll get desert from
room service.
Keep it, boys.
The night is still young.
Bye, honey.
Oh, come on, I am used to this.
Well, I am not.
Listen, you are just visiting
the way I live.
It suites you fine to hide in that
hotel room till your train leaves.
By all means, let's hide.
You are so insisting that
everyone see the things you do.
Oh, yeah, made it really
like that in your apartment.
No fear, no confusion.
So selfasured.
I don't act that way to change the world,
but to goddamm world not change me!
-Low your voice!
-Why? is this a false issue?
Is there some way to make
this easier?
Da
You take the car and I'll walk.
That is easiest as it gets.
Does it have to turn
around this quickly?
Comes with the territory.
-I'll walk!
-Its 18 km, Vivian.
Good!
Maybe it will wake me up!
Do you need me the way I need
you?
Yes. You know I do.
Hello. Sorry I am late.
Walter couldn't find parking place.
Oh, Silver, you are gorgious.
-Come on.
-How long will it last?
5 minutes
-I am glad to see you, Walter.
-I am glad to see you.
-Thank you.
-My pleasure.
Good morning.
Its Joe and Silvia.
Silver!
Well, Joe and Silver,
where are you, nice people, from?
-Brooklyn.
-Charlottesville, Texas.
All pretty girl
are from there.
Now I will call upon gentleman upstairs
for a very special blessing for you.
-See me faint?
-I cried all the way through.
It was really best.
Cay is the best.
Don't say I've never
gave you anything.
- Have a good trip.
-I see you in New York.
Yes you will.
Too bad that things didn't
work out different.
Truth is that you don't
own me one damm thing!
I have nothnig to hang on to
you any more.
I love you, Frances.
I'll never accept what you do.
I know.
I just don't understand.
Two women together!
She just reached in
and laid a string of
light in my heart.
Don't keep her waiting.
Oh, Frances, be happy for someone
in your life.
Oh, God!
Look at us!
Standing in the middle of the street.
Next thing you know they be
talking about me.
Is that it, then?
I know you longer than
anybody in my life.
What does that mean?
That will never be it.
Well, congratulations, Vivian.
You return to New York
as a free woman.
Unless, of course, some
fellow here have stolen your heart.
-How about a drink, to celebrate?
-I'd love to. But I have other plans.
Ok, I am sorry. I think I
understand.
You look different.
I see, you have found yourself
a new pin pal.
No, I have much more than
that, Mr. Warner.
Thank you.
Good luck to you.
Can I talk you in to stay one
more day?
-Yes.
-Do you want me to?
No.
-I'll come back.
-When?
Christmas.
Christmas?
-I don't know what you want.
-It's you I want.
Cay?
You are not coming?
I'll see you at the station.
Can we have dinner?
No.
Why?
Because being with you is
starting to hurt.
I want...
I want to say goodbye alone.
We have been saying goodbye
from the begining.
I gotta go.
-I put sugar...
-I won't start.
-I got another postcard from Silver today.
-How are they?
Aren't all honeymoon cards
the same?
"Incredible divine. Just like
a movie set. We'll never come back".
-Come with me.
-oh, sure thing.
Can you really picture me with
you?
If you want a sure thing,
stay in Reno.
As for my friends
I endured an hour with them...
Gwen.
It's a nice offer, Vivian.
but there are still...a few
losse ends...
-At least.
-Than, why did you make it?
Because I care about you.
Because I think that you
diserve to live somwhere with...
or near someone who sees how
wonderful you are.
Know exactly who you are.
"All on board!"
That is why I'll never
finish this conversation.
If it didn't please you, you
wouldn't have to stay.
Well, we'll talk about that
one of these days.
Come with me to the next station.
-What can we settle in 40 minutes?
-I'll talk fast.
Send me a postcard when you get there.
-What is it that you want?
-Another 40 minutes with you.