Subtitle By : Hossein
www.SubtitleVideo.blogsky.com
www.Bia2RapFAA2.Sub.iR
Sometimes
These Wall Seems To Cave In On Me
When I Look In Your Eyes
I Feel Alive
Some Days
We Say Words That Don't Mean A Thing
But When You Holding Me Tight
I Feel Alive
Make It Last Forever
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
You And I Together
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
Ooh...
Each Day
I Feel So Blessed To Be Looking At You
Cause When You Open Your Eyes
I Feel Alive
My Heart
Beats So Damn Quick When You Say My Name
When I'm Holding You Tight
I'm So Alive
Now Let's Live It Up
Make It Last Forever
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
You And I Together
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
Oohh..
Baby Last Forever
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
You And I Together
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
We Gotta Hold On
I Gotta Hold On
You've Got To Hold On
Oh Hold On To Me
We Gotta Hold On
I Gotta Hold On
You've Got To Hold On
Oh Hold On To Me
Make It Last Forever
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
You And I Together
Come One Baby Won't You Hold On To Me
Hold On To Me
BLUE...
[Blue Ivy]
Hold On To Me, Hold On
Been-Sy-Ay
Mami, Mami, Mami
Missus Carter!
Sync by dhifofierce
www.SubtitleVideo.blogsky.com
www.Bia2RapFAA2.Sub.iR