TΗE RED DESERT
Romeo Salvati,
why have you gone into the factory?
You're not a director
you're an ordinary worker
Come out here.
Strike with us
Your wife is ashamed of you
- Where did you buy that?
- At the shop on the corner
- Will you sell it to me?
- l've eaten some
Never mind
- The steam temperature is high.
- Reduce the burners
You'll find that
nobody wants to work abroad
They had trouble finding specialists
to send to. . .
Can't you spare
some of your men?
l'll ask Beltrami;
l need to talk to him anyway
Get me someone at Phillips
Beltrami speaking
l haven't enough men as it is
Ugo? Are you crazy?
We don't fire anyone
We're nationalised
Nothing doing' even at ANlC .
l told you
These are skilled workers
who should have come to us' but. . .
Boni' for instance.
Ηe's a foreman now
Ηe lives at Ferrara?
But that's far away
We pick them up even from Sicily
if we have to
- l've been looking for you.
- Meet a friend of mine
Corrado Zeller' my wife
l'll wait for you in the office
lt was raining' the road was slippery.
She must have braked
She hadn't long passed her driving test
and her mind is always elsewhere
Luckily the truck stopped quickly
- Was she badly hurt?
- No' not badly
A few bruises.
Terribly shocked' though
She was more than
a month in hospital
and she still can't. . . mesh
She wants to open a shop
of some sort
ln Via Alighieri.
lt doesn't quite seem the thing' really
Why?
Take your eyes off them.
This is a game reserve
Did you know
my father put up those silos?
Your new job seems out of character.
Weren't you in mining?
l began with the idea of going down'
now l'm going up
What else could l do?
Since my father died'
l've had to take on
all responsibilities
Just above normal
lt's very high
l dreamt l was in bed
and the bed moved
l looked'
and it was quicksand
lt sank further and further. . .
Looking for me?
l was passing
and l saw you go in
That's untrue.
l don't want to start with a lie
Start what?
Talking.
l'm sorry that. . .
Light blue would be best
- What for?
- The walls
And a green ceiling
Cold' non-disturbing colours
They shouldn't clash
with the merchandise
What should l sell?
Ηaven't you decided?
Yes' l like ceramics'
but l don't know anything about them
Faenza isn't far away;
it's famous for ceramics
l must note that
- Note what?
- Faenza. l must go there
So many phone calls
to be made
Ηas Ugo talked about me?
Well' he told me
you have a child
l knew he was married' of course'
but that's all
Nothing else?
Yes' about the shop
- When did you arrive here?
- This morning
My bags are still in the car
- Ηave you got a hotel?
- Not yet. Why are you concerned?
- What do you do?
- What do you mean?
Do you live in Bologna?
l live in Milan,
but l'm from Trieste really
l was born there,
then my parents moved to Bologna
Then l went to Milan
l've been back in Bologna
for a few years
Now l must move again.
lt's rather complicated
Why complicated?
The truth is. . .
l don't like to stay in one place
So l've decided to leave
Where are you going?
- Leaving that light on?
- Yes' it's best
lt's today's
Are you tired?
Giuliana, are you tired?
l'm always tired
No' not always.
Sometimes
- Where are we going?
- l don't know. l thought you. . .
Can l give you a lift?
- Where are you going now?
- To Ferrara
At once?
l must go home now,
but this afternoon, perhaps. . .
On the sea bed,
in the depths,
there are transparent fish
Please don't tell me such things,
they frighten me
You can't imagine
the fears l have
So to eat an animal
you must love it?
Yes, perhaps
- Give me an example.
- l don't know
Ηow about chicks?
Or kittens,
so small, soft and sleek
Could you eat me?
lf l loved you
ls Mario at home?
When will he be back?
Soon' but some days
he's later than others
May we wait?
- Would you like some wine?
- Please don't bother
l'd like some
Tell me the truth.
Did Ugo talk about the accident?
Yes, but it wasn't serious, was it?
Ηe told me you were in hospital
because of the shock
- l met a girl.
- Where?
- There.
- ln the hospital?
She was very ill
She wanted everything
ln what way?
The doctor told her,
"You should learn how to love
"Love a person or a thing
"Love your husband,
your son,
"a job, even a dog
"But not husband-son-
job-dog-trees-river. . ."
Did she ever tell you
about her feelings?
There was no floor beneath her
The sensation
of sliding down a slope
Down
Of being on the verge of drowning
With nothing
Not even her husband?
No, and he wasn't there,
he was away
Not even her son?
Yes, him
But that girl had no children
When she left hospital,
she had to ask herself:
"Who am l?"
She had to have it
explained to her,
by me
She's cured now
Where does your husband work now?
At a radio installation
in Medicina
Ηave you come
to offer him a job?
Yes, it's a very good,
well-paid job
Where?
lf it means him going away,
l'd rather he didn't take it
lt may not be for long
Once he went away to a family funeral.
l thought l'd go crazy. l was afraid
You could join him
Will your wife go with you?
Know what we'll do?
We'll talk to him at Medicina;
he won't refuse
Are you well?
l'm very well, too
This man wants a word with you
Can l ask you something?
- Who owns this lot?
- Bologna University
Aren't you afraid?
No' l'm used to it
What's it all for?
lt's a radio-telescope,
to listen to the stars
- So you know that man.
- No, l've just met him now
l meant him
Ηe used to live near me
- Did he take the job?
- No
Ηe said l would have to
offer him a fortune
What a shame
Well, factory effluent
must end up somewhere
Anyway, you've all stopped
fishing here now
When we were in Medicina
the other day,
we heard a man in a restaurant
complaining
Ηe said his eel
tasted of petroleum
l've not been here for two years.
l just let it fall apart
Sometimes l feel
l have no right to be where l am
Perhaps that's why
l always want to go away
- Take my gloves.
- No, l'm quite warm
You shouldn't wear such shoes
in this weather
We'll wait for them in the car,
where it's warmer
Where were you
when Giuliana had the accident?
ln London. Why?
Did you come back?
No. l was told
it wasn't necessary
Ηas Giuliana
complained about that?
Not at all
So why ask?
ls the strike over?
The ANlC chimneys are smoking
Perhaps. l don't know
Are you Left or Right?
What a question.
Are you interested in politics?
Good Lord, no.
l just wondered
lt's like asking,
"What do you believe in?"
Big words, Giuliana,
that call for precise answers
After all, one doesn't quite know
what one believes in
One believes in humanity,
in a sense
ln justice, a little less
ln progress' a little more
ln socialism, perhaps
What matters is to act
as one thinks right -
right for oneself
and for others
A clear conscience,
in other words
Mine is clear
Does that answer your question?
You've strung together
a nice bunch of words
Ηere they are
This is Corrado Zeller
- German?
- No, it's a long pedigree
My name's half German, too; l'm Max
My wife
lt was a mistake to come here
My fault, l'm afraid
l knew it, so l've had some fish
cooked at my place,
in my hut by the sea.
lt's sea fish
- What about Mili?
- She'll join us there
What are you looking at?
l know all about such things
They're quail's eggs
They have an ingredient
that arouses you
They're aphrodisiac
- More than fertile eggs.
- What?
- What about fertile eggs?
- Surely you've heard of them?
Fertilised hen's eggs. There's a
treatment you do from autumn to spring
You drink them on the ninth day, when
the yolk is about to become a chick
l've had them.
l used to get them from the monks
The yolk has two black dots.
l asked what they were
"The eyes, my son.
Swallow without looking"
And did you?
l haven't tried your eggs
You don't need to, Mili
- Why didn't you bring Augusto?
- l dropped him
l can't go to bed with a man
who makes less money than me
Do you know this game?
What do you feel?
Not much
Do it to me.
You'll get a better reaction
What have you got?
- Does it work quickly?
- Eat the other
Bring me one
You keep quiet,
you're well away as it is
- Well?
- Nothing yet
lt's too early,
you must allow a little time
Boys, l'm not joking
l really believe. . .
l want to make love
Let's drink
Look who's here
Sorry, Signor Max.
l didn't know. . .
Never mind, Orlando.
Come in
Who's the girl?
Ηot stuff
Ηave a drink.
lt's on the table
Ηe's one of my workers
Ηe has a different girl every day;
he's fantastic
- What's this pretty lady's name?
- lole
The same name as my boat
You'll be interested in
our conversation
Wasn't it you who told me
about that grease, Orlando?
The stuff the negroes use
so as to last longer
Well, it's made from crocodile fat
and some spicy herbs
They spread it on before. . .
On what?
Mili, don't be stupid
The effect lasts several hours
Several hours, Mili
l don't believe it
lt's true. You've no idea
what men do in some countries
ln Jordan, l saw them eat
rams, fat and honey for breakfast
The Chinese
eat crushed rhinoceros horn
Dried sharks' fins, too
l've even tried royal jelly.
Effective, isn't it, Linda?
- What's royal jelly?
- Queen bee food
lt's rejuvenating;
note that for your old age
lf she still wants to
make love then
Ηow about that?
l'd rather do certain things
than talk about them
l like to talk about them,
failing all else
Because you're a sow
lt's cold in here
- Aren't you cold?
- Yes, l am
Where's the wood?
- This isn't much use.
- l'll find you some
Look
That's unusual
lt's because of the fog
Do boats from South America call here?
Yes, but they're big.
They tie up at the SAROM offshore rig
Our supplies could be loaded here
instead of Naples or Genoa
lt would be quicker,
and probably cheaper
The ships go back empty,
don't they?
Look, Mili,
he hasn't seen a woman in two months
- Do you know other nice games?
- Lots
- Where did you learn them?
- Now where do you think?
- l hate him.
- Who?
Your husband.
Ηe's always ready to pounce -
on a bankrupt factory
or a woman in difficulties
You'll see, he'll end up
getting his way with me, too
Do tankers
take any general cargo?
They usually have a dry hold
lt's true what l said.
l do want to make love
Ηow can we?
Don't chase after business.
Let it come to you
l'm not chasing after anything
l'm going because l want to
Because. . .
l think one should
change direction sometimes
Travelling makes sense
if one changes. . .
one's historical setting, as it were.
Otherwise it's pointless
l haven't got much faith in that
ln the last two years. . .
l've traded two bits of land,
even sold this hut to the worker you saw
l'm freezing to death
Ηelp me
lt never keeps still. Never
l can't look at the sea for long
otherwise l lose interest
in what happens on land
l sometimes wonder
if it's worth it -
the effort one puts into a job l mean
Don't you think
it's ridiculous?
l feel as if my eyes are wet
But what do people
expect me to do with my eyes?
What should l look at?
You say
"What should l look at?"
l say, "Ηow should l live?"
lt's the same thing
A doctor
So they've come for that person
who cried out a little while ago
Ηow could someone have cried out?
The boat's only just come
lt's been there
for half an hour
- Did you hear a cry?
- l wasn't listening
- Are you joking?
- You read it in your novel
Do you think so?
Maybe
l heard it
What's it matter
if there was a cry or not?
lt's important.
Linda didn't imagine that cry
All right, so there was
You shouldn't just agree with me
as if l were a. . .
Who could have cried out?
We're almost in mid-ocean
Why did you say "maybe"?
Did l?
Smallpox, cholera or leprosy
ls it one or two flags
for infectious diseases?
Let's go away from here at once
- lt may just be a precaution.
- Perhaps someone with colic
- Let's have a word with the doctor.
- We know him anyway
We won't wait for that.
Where are my gloves?
Ηave you got my bag?
lt's on the step
Don't go.
lt doesn't matter
l'm inoculated against everything
Giuliana, don't be silly.
Wait in the car
Wait, Corrado. l'll go
l'm sorry, Ugo.
l made a mistake
First you were afraid
and now. . .
l didn't see
it was the wrong way
l made a mistake.
l wanted to go home
lt was because the fog mixed me up.
l swear it
Why are you crying?
- Ηow many days are you away?
- Five or six
What's one and one?
- Two, of course.
- Wrong. Look at this
Ηow many?
One so it is
lmagine that
Why not ask Linda to stay here
while l'm away?
- Why?
- Well, if you can't sleep. . .
l could ask her
Better not, perhaps
Do you know why it doesn't fall?
Because of the gyroscope
Gyroscopes help keep ships steady
in rough sea
lt costs me half
in materials and labour -
they unload in Buenos Aires
What are you taking?
Generators, cranes, pipes -
everything for the plant
l mean what personal possessions
are you taking?
Just a few suitcases of things
lf l left
l'd take everything
Everything in sight
All my everyday things
even the ashtrays
Then you might as well stay
as you'd miss everything -
the street where you live
your city
You see in small ads
"Ηouse for sale. Owner gone away"
As if it were an excuse
to abandon everything,
or a part
Why? lt shouldn't be like that
Ηow can you predict
what will be useful?
And when you return, will you find
the same things and people?
Will they be the same?
Maybe you don't return
lf l left for ever,
l would take you, too
Because now you are part of me
One of my everyday things
lf Ugo had looked at me as you do,
he'd have understood
many things
About the accident?
And your friend
at the hospital?
She was you
l didn't want to tell you;
l was ashamed
Not even Ugo knows about it
l had an agreement
with the doctors
l had tried to commit suicide
Remember that man
at Medicina?
Ηe was at the hospital with me
Ηe was very ill
Did he try to die, too?
No, not he
Ηe seems to be fully recovered
- And how are you?
- Fine
As you see
Patagonia is near the South Pole
You'll fly from Buenos Aires
to Comodoro Rivadavia
From there, we'll drive you
to Caleta Olivia in the interior
Ηow about accommodation?
- Ηow about accommodation?
- Comfortable prefabricated buildings
What about payment?
Couldn't our pay
be deposited in a bank here?
We'll talk about that in a moment;
one thing at a time
ls there a hospital?
Yes, very well equipped.
The doctor is ltalian, from Turin
When can wives
join their husbands?
After about a year
but you can phone home every month
Who pays?
The company. You can phone
more often at your own expense
- Is La Gazzetta dello Sport there?
- All ltalian papers are sold there
ls it true the women
are bare-breasted?
Ηe says he can't stand up
What game is this?
Does it hurt? Tell me
Does this hurt?
l can't feel it
Can't you feel anything at all?
You're just trying to
get out of going to school
Ηow lovely
Come and look at
this beautiful boat
lt's so big
and all white
Love, if you don't tell me
what sort of pain it is. . .
Tell me
what do you feel?
l'll try to pick him up
Love, do try to tell me
Or else how can l make you better?
Ηow can it be?
Tell me how it started
Was it when you woke up?
Or during the night?
Polio immunisation
Ηe's been immunised;
the doctor knows he has
So why does he need 24 hours
for a diagnosis?
l can't wait for that.
l'm going to call another doctor
l'm tired of this game
Make another drawing
Tell me a story
l've told you all l know
What about the one
you told me yesterday?
The one about the kite
Now why don't you
rest for a while?
l'll tell you a story later
There was a IittIe girI
who lived on an island
She got bored with grown-ups,
and they frightened her, too
She didn't Iike chiIdren her own age
because they pIayed at grown-ups,
so she was aIways aIone
among the cormorants
and sea guIIs
and wiId rabbits
She had found a IittIe beach
far away from the viIIage
where the sea was transparent
and the sand was pink
She Ioved that pIace
Nature had such beautiful colours,
and there was no noise
She left only when the sun left
One morning,
a sailing boat appeared
It was different from other boats
A real sailing boat
It could brave the tempests
and oceans of the world
Maybe even beyond,
who knows?
Seen from afar,
it looked splendid
But near to,
it was mysterious
It seemed to be unmanned
After a few minutes,
it began to turn
and it went away
as silently as it had come
She wasn't surprised; she was
used to the strangeness of men
One mystery is all right,
two is too many. Who was singing?
The beach was deserted,
yet the voice was there,
sometimes near,
sometimes far
At one point.
she thought it came from the sea
A little cove among the rocks
So many rocks
She had never realised
they were like flesh
And the Voice. . .
In that place,
the voice was so sweet
Who was singing?
Everyone was singing
The papers
Why did you do it?
- What's his room number?
- Whose, madam?
Ηave you forgotten the name?
Corrado Zeller?
Room 309
Your son?
Ηe's all right
Ηe doesn't need me
lt's l who need him
My hair hurts, my eyes hurt,
my throat, my mouth
Am l trembling?
A little;
because of the cold, perhaps
You don't love me, do you?
Why do you ask?
l don't know why.
l never get enough affection
Why should l need others always?
l must be an idiot
That's why
l can't look after myself
You know what l'd like?
Everyone who's ever cared for me
l'd like them all around me
like a wall
Tell me what happened
Nothing
lmagine that -
nothing
l've not been cured
l never shall be
You brood on your illness,
but it's just an illness like any other
We all suffer it a little
More or less
we all need to be cured
ls there a place in the world
where one goes to feel better?
Probably not
l expect you're right. One travels
but ends up the same as before
That's what happened to me
yet l feel just as l did
six years ago
l don't know whether that urges me
to leave or to stay
- When are you leaving?
- l don't know
What are you looking at?
Sometimes l want to
attack somebody
ls that a symptom?
Because l do, too, at times
Ηelp me
Ηelp me, please
l'm afraid l won't cope
What are you afraid of?
The streets, factories,
colours, people - everything
Giuliana,
what is it you want to do?
- Nothing.
- But that's ridiculous
You needn't worry about me.
Everyone does that
Doctors talk to me about me
lt's when l'm alone that l'm ill
l can't take it any more
l've tried everything. . .
to reintegrate myself with reality. . .
as they say at the hospital
Now it seems
l may have succeeded
l've even succeeded
in becoming an unfaithful wife
Don't think of such things
That's right
don't think of such things
The perfect solution
There's something terrible in reality
and l don't know what it is
Nobody tells me
Even you haven't helped me
Please
could you tell me. . .
l didn't want. . .
Does this boat
take passengers?
lt's not that
l've made up my mind
l can't decide
because l'm not a single woman
Although, sometimes,
sort of separated
Not from my husband, no
The bodies are separated
lf you prick me,
you don't suffer
What was l saying?
l've been ill, yes
l mustn't think about it. . .
l mean, l have to think. . .
that everything that happens
to me is my life
l'm sorry
Excuse me
Why does it do that?
Why is the smoke yellow?
Because it's poisonous
Then if a little bird flies through it,
it will die
The birds have learnt that
and they don't fly through it