Steve Bauers, Interpol
Hi there. Marsh... we already met
So, guys- what have you found?
Doctor, you must take a look
inside the Cave.
OK, we better take a look then.
What a fucking smell!
This is the Killer's Cave.
Go and tell the Men...
OK, but there is no trace of George!
OK, you better have a look around then.
" I was a big shot Businessman; "
my Family was the most influential
on the lsland.
A a matter of fact, you could
say we owned it.
Let's see...well...
You want to have a look how the
Baby is doing?
Everything is just fine, tonight we will
reach our Destination.
But on this Trip we got caught in the
middle of a bad Thunderstorm.
Damned!
The Mast!
Vicky!
Come on, help her.
Time has no meaning anymore.
Here it begins and ends...
...the story of the Karamanlis family.
Mary, you are so wonderful.
Stuart, are you coming with me?
I will look for some wood.
Oh no. You go ahead. I will rest a little bit.
Stuart, I am back.
Hey, hey, hey!
How are you?
Look at that hat!
Vince, how are you?
Cool.
What's happening? Where are
Mary and Stuart?
They just went to the beach,
but they will meet us at the house,
you'll see, I didn't promise you too much.
So, what's up now?
It's very pretty here.
Let's take a look around.
We'll be gone for three hours at least.
I'll better let them know.
" Don't bother; they will have a "
good time without us.
Stan? Yeah, we're fine...
Well, there is nothing you can do about it.
OK, here she is.
Hello Darling?
Hello, yes it's me. I've got another
operation an emergency.
" And no one else is available; "
I will join you as soon as I'm finished here.
OK, bye, yeah bye.
Silly bastard.
Turn right here.
Are you feeling ok?
If we don't stop right now I will
puke all over the car.
You better stop here.
Just a second.
Food, Food
We are looking for directions to
Borgo San Lorenzo.
Borgo San Lorenzo? Don't go there.
Food Food.
What did you eat today?
You know what, Hank? They nicked
"the Campsite; "
take a look at the map.
According to the map we should be here,
or here, but we could also be here.
You know what. I haven't got a clue.
Let's camp right here.
Maybe we ran out of gas or whatever.
I don't know, it's not my fault.
Fucking weather.
" Listen; let's just go into the village."
It's raining cats and dogs.
OK
Shit, my Leg.
Carol, is it bad? Or can you walk?
You all just go ahead, I will take
care of Carol.
Vince, take good care of these two.
Anybody there?
Seems deserted...
"Come on; let's take a look inside."
Miss...excuse me...Miss
Hey Vince, can you get me some lce?
I could bring you a Handful of Sand,
there is nothing else here.
You know what, Carol? I take a look
at the engine.
Vince where the Hell are you?
Hello, where are you two?
Come over here!
You won't believe this, but...
" Let's get out of here; yeah let's "
get out of here.
I think I'm done here.
I just saw a little take out there.
Maybe we'll meet some chicks...
...out there and get lucky.
You go ahead, I want to read a little bit,
and we have got a...
...Iot to do tomorrow.
I'm getting a little worried about you, man.
Back home you are
Mr. Loverboy and out here.
You just go and do whatever you want.
Damned, where is the car?
Maybe they found some gas somewhere.
I can't walk any longer.
You know what? I'll just go and look
around for Mary and Stuart.
Let's go that way.
Come on let's go.
Help, help.
Hey you shit. Where are you?
Alan, where are you?...Alan?
You know what? I am fucking scared.
Mary and Stuart are still not here.
Come on, let's go to bed.
Did you also...?
Are you nuts to scare me like that?
Auriet, my god, Auriet. It is me - Rita!
What's happening, who is she?
It's Auriet, Mary's sister.
Take her upstairs, come on.
She is scared to death.
I think she recognized me.
I think this has to be treated.
I'll go into the village.
Be careful.
Auriet, can you hear me? Where is Mary?
I don't know.
Do you know who he is?
It's him, Mary, Stuart, where are you?
Nobody will come! He is here.
How does he smell?
He smells like blood.
Everything is going to be just fine,
got to sleep now.
I hope there is something that will be
of any help to you.
It's useless, Carol is bound to be...
Let's please move on, we will
find them somehow.
Hey Mark, don't quit on me now.
I need you.
He's no god, he's human.
We can hurt him.
We have to stick together or he will
get us one after another.
Come on let's go.
I know that house. It belonged to the
Karamanlis family. They are all dead.
Is there nobody left?
Only his sister, but she went mad.
I can't stand it any longer.
" " "Go away" ". Is this his sister? "
Yes, yes.
It makes me sick, let's get out of here.
Carol, Mary, Stuart, anybody there?
Put her down there. Look at these photos.
" " " My wife, my daughter and the "
unborn child are dead.
Since then I need meat, lot's of
meat from animals but that doesn't stop
my craving for blood, red like blood,
red - the colour of love.
It's hard to describe the pain that's
tearing me apart.
It's like I am a burning flame
"...an eternal hellfire..." " "
Stan! I am so glad you are here.
What the hell is going on?
Vince and Carol are gone but
I know where they are.
Hello, can anybody hear me?
Don't worry about me. Vince, Carol!
Try to control your breathing and relax.
Hello, can anybody hear me?
Mark, no!
Carol, are you here? Carol, are you here?
Stan, is it you?
Carol, there you are. Let's get out of here.
What do you want? Leave us alone,
you monster. Is it the child?
I know exactly who you are. But this sacrifice
won't bring back your Wife and Child.
Child, I once also had a child.
A Storm once took us far away from
the coast and the hot sun cooked our Flesh
You better don't do that or the salt
will destroy your skin.
I know, but it is still better than being boiled
by the sun.
You will burn your skin.
I know.
When would we be saved? A ship could
save us, just a ship.
The days went by and I thought I was losing
my mind. I wanted to live, we all should live.
My god, you know what
we have to do now.
You don't touch her.
It's the only thing left to do.
Leave her alone or I will kill you.
But she is dead. And it's dead meat,
meat we need to survive.
Don't touch him!
Come on.
What do we do now?
Where is the car? Think!
I don't know.
Where is the car?
I don't know!!!!!
Come on.
Where are you?
Shit!. Help!
Hurry up!
Help me, George!!!
Do you think you can bring us back to life
with your cruelty?
We love you, Nicos. Come to us.
Release me, release me.
Strange, very strange. There is something
fishy about this.
The ending, when could he have
written this.
I have to get out of here.