♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Any
discussion of Anne Frank
must occur on multiple levels.
There's Anne Frank the person.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
There is Anne Frank the icon.
There's Anne Frank as one of
six million Jewish victims
of the Holocaust.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
There is Anne Frank the
child onto which we project
an awful lot of our feelings
with regard to the Holocaust.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The world will never know what
was lost and who was lost
when these children
were murdered.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The future was
shut down for them.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And if we imagine what we lost,
we might weep along with those
who directly
experienced this event
more deeply and more humbly.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: Look, Anne
was a little bit I would say
in American a spicy little girl.
She was very clever.
A little like a cat.
It was very nice to
be friends with her.
She was really a
clever little girl.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
We went together to school.
We did the vacations
very often together.
At Sunday we went to the beach.
She would come with
us with the train.
And everything we did together.
So it just developed
quite normal.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(German newsreel).
MARTIN MORGAN: Otto Frank
did everything right.
As soon as Adolf
Hitler rose to power,
he got the family
out of Germany.
He built a new business
in the Netherlands,
they made Dutch friends.
The one thing that he
didn't plan for though was
the fact that Adolf Hitler
would ultimately
invade Holland as well.
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: I saw that
the thunders and lights because
of us bombing and I went
to the bed with my parents.
And the next morning on
the radio then we heard
what was happening.
(MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS)
(Newsreel).
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG:
The Jews in Holland were,
on the one hand,
totally integrated.
But on the other hand they
also were somewhat separate.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The Dutch didn't like the Nazis
except for a small group of
Dutch Nazis.
But they didn't like the Nazis.
But by the same token, it
wasn't a society that said,
we must do everything on,
on behalf of these Jews
to try to hide them.
It's a, it's more of a mixed
bag than the myth would, uh,
lead us to believe.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Anna and me, we had to
leave our school and now
that there were opened Jewish
schools only for Jewish children
and for Jewish teachers.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: We couldn't
use public transportation.
We weren't allowed to go to
sports clubs, cinemas, parks.
We're not allowed to
visit Christian families
and they were not
allowed to help us.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
I met Anne in October
1941 in the Jewish Lyceum.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Anne was very vivacious.
She loved to talk.
She liked to be seen and heard
and in actual fact
the whole class were friends.
I think we were well aware
of the circumstances.
We were perhaps more mature
than normally would be,
so we were all friends.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: It's a sad fact
that throughout Nazi Europe,
people collaborated
with their conquerors.
Holland was no different.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHANNES HOUWINK TEN CATE:
The total number of German
personnel in the Netherlands
was lower than 1,000.
And they commanded far over
100,000 Dutch civil servants.
And they obeyed with
very slight exceptions.
DR. DAVID BARNOUW: The
Netherlands, you pay your taxes.
You do what, what the
police is telling you.
You do what civil
servants are telling you.
You don't realize what's coming.
(German newsreel).
NANETTE KONIG: The strategy
of deportation was the same
in all the occupied countries.
First of all it was
identification,
then it was isolation,
then you had deportation
and extermination.
NANETTE KONIG: This is a card
which shows that I registered
in March 1941 declaring that I
had 4 Jewish grandparents.
It was a death warrant really.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(TRAIN SOUND)
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR:
People started to think
what will happen and
started to go into hiding.
But not everybody
can go into hiding.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG: 25,000
Jews went into hiding in Holland
many of them with the help of
the Dutch resistance.
But one-third of the Jews
who went into hiding
were also turned in,
including, of course,
Anne Frank and her family.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Concentration camps had
different functions.
Some concentration camps
were penal colonies,
prison camps in essence.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Other concentration camps
were slave labor camps.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
There then was one genre of
concentration camps that had one
and only one function and
that was a death camp.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: We all know that
Anne Frank and her family
and friends went to hiding.
Well Sobibor is what
they were hiding from.
In their wildest
paranoid imaginations,
they could not have imagined
the extermination machine
that was that ghastly place.
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG: The death
camps that the Nazis built
in which they planned
to kill the Jews,
when we talk about what
was the chance of survival,
the answer is: there
was no survivability.
The fact that here and there
there are a tiny number of Jews
that survive from Belzec
to Sobibor is luck.
MARTIN MORGAN: It's hard to
believe that if you were sent
to Auschwitz instead of Sobibor,
you were actually lucky.
But at Auschwitz, thousands
of people managed to survive
because there were
chances to stay alive.
At Sobibor, though,
survival was not an option.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Mark Twain said
there are truth,
lies, and statistics.
The statistic is that Sobibor
was opened in, um, May of 1942.
It was closed in
October of 1943.
During that period of time
250,000 Jews were
murdered at Sobibor.
So, the death ratio at
Sobibor was about 99 percent
of those who arrived.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
So, had the Frank's been
deported in 1942, '43,
they would have
ended up at Sobibor,
and they would have been killed
within an hour or two
of arrival.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: Imagine a
death camp so horrific
that even the Nazis sought
to blast it out of existence
during the war that they
still thought they might win.
That's why this new
archaeology is so important,
because it denies the Nazis
their victory over history.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: There's a
new field of study in which is
the archaeology of genocide.
What can you find under the
ground and what does that
tell us about what
happened there?
WOJCIECH MAZUREK: We have
found a lot of artifacts here.
And this pit is a
garbage place of course.
Archaeologists always think a
garbage place is very important.
You can find a lot.
The first remains we have
discovered of the gas chambers.
The first time is the proof.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
YORAM HAIMI: We were surprised
that we find the gas chamber
in this situation because
what you are seeing is only
the base of the walls.
The gas chamber is gone.
The German explode everything
and remove all the remains
of the gas chamber.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
We have a big building here,
this is the gas chamber
of the camp.
It's 8 rooms of gas chamber.
And we have the old gas chamber
and the new gas chamber.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
We have evidence of exploding.
You can see it here.
This is one of the places.
And always in the uh, corner
between 2 walls they put
dynamite to explode
the building.
And they succeed.
They destroyed all the building.
They remove everything.
But what was under the ground,
the base of the wall still,
you can see it still here.
And this is giving us the
opportunity to reconstruct
the gas chamber.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Beneath the ground at Sobibor
there is a story to be found.
There is physical evidence of
the magnitude of the crime.
There are human remains that
are to be found and then
there are objects to be found.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
You find the types of things
that don't deteriorate.
You find human teeth.
You find false teeth because
teeth deteriorate far less
rapidly than other
parts of the human body.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
WOJCIECH MAZUREK: Every moment
we are thinking
about the victims.
And this way that they didn't
want to come here to die.
They wanted to be
alive, still alive.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Human
beings are curious about
the past and the Holocaust
was such a horrendous event
that we have a moral
obligation to confront it
and to understand it and to face
up to what really happened.
MARTIN MORGAN: Anne Frank's
diaries have sold in excess
of 30 million copies since they
were first published in 1947.
And they tell the story of
her life, and her dreams.
But the story of her death
is important as well,
because it reveals the full
terrible dimensions
of the Holocaust, and it's a
story that must be told.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: The people
living in the annex were:
Otto Frank.
His wife, Edith Frank Hollander.
Their daughters,
Margot and Anne Frank.
There was the family
of Herman van Pels.
With his wife Auguste
van Pels Roten.
And their son Peter van Pels.
And the eighth one was the
dentist, Fritz Pfeffer.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The annex where they were
hiding were altogether
I think around 100
square meters,
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
including the attic.
They had 4 rooms.
One of the rooms was also
a kitchen, facilities.
It was very confined
for 8 people.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: By
the fall of 1944,
the war was in effect over.
There was no way that the
Nazis could hold off massive
Soviet army in the East, and
the Allies in the West.
The conflict was
drawing to an end,
and yet the Nazis refused
to acknowledge it.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(Nazi newsreel).
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: The general
attitude in the late summer
of 1944 with the German
authorities,
I think was we'll find
whoever we can find.
We'll just mop up what's left
and try and find out everyone
they could find.
TERESIEN DA SILVA: People
in hiding were, of course,
not aware of any danger.
Well, they were aware
of danger all the time.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
But at that specific moment they
were not suspecting anything
of this kind.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHANNES HOUWINK TEN CATE:
There were material rewards
if you would arrest a Jew.
That premium so to say
started out by being
seven 7 guilders 50.
And it evolves later on
in the war to 50 guilders.
Which was say the equivalent
of a bottle of Dutch gin.
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE SOUND)
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
TERESIEN DA SILVA: Today it's
August 4th and it's exactly
70 years ago that on a
Friday, August 4th, 1944,
at 10:30 in the morning
some Dutch policemen
and an S.S. officer came
inside into this building.
(Pounding on door).
We don't know if they knew
that there were eight people
in hiding here.
But when they interrogated
the director of the company,
they knew exactly what
was going on here.
And they put on guns on him
and he had to take them
to the hiding place.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And that's what happens.
DR. DAVID BARNOUW: Karl
Silberbauer just an ordinary
police officer.
Born in Vienna in 1911.
Became member of Gestapo uh in
1939 when Austria was uh German.
And part of his job
was rounding up Jews.
In 1944 he was 33.
He was one who rounded up uh who
got I think from his boss
oh you have to go there.
And there are Jews hiding.
Ok and pick them up.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: The arrest of
Anne Frank and the other annex
dwellers was all
in a day's work,
just another routine
mundane Jewish roundup.
It's telling that only one
Nazi officer was there,
and that the rest
were Dutch policemen.
I'm sure they all went home
that night and they never gave
any of it another thought.
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: When
the arresting officer,
Silberbauer and his
men entered the annex,
they moved around sort of cover
the premises as policemen do,
I suppose, when
they raid a place,
and they found Otto Frank and
Peter and Peter's parents
on the top floor.
And Edith Frank and the
girls and Fritz Pfeffer
on the lower floor.
TERESIEN DA SILVA: Because of
the fact that Otto did serve
in the first World War,
they were a little bit,
they changed their behavior and
they let them have more time
to gather their belongings.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
After they were taken away,
the helpers came inside
of the hiding place and
they recognized the diary
of Anne Frank.
So, she, they grabbed everything
and took it with them
to the office and Miep
Gies, one of the helpers,
kept it all the
time in her desk.
And of course, it's, yeah, how
you say it, it's a miracle.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Imagine
for a moment that Miep Gies
had left the diary where it was.
What would have been
lost to world literature?
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And it's an iconic diary by an
iconic figure who represents
what could have been and
what was not, what was lost.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(CHATTERING VOICES)
DR. JOHANNES HOUWINK TEN CATE:
Originally Westerbork
in the east of the Netherlands
was set up as a camp
for young unmarried German
Jews who had entered
the Netherlands illegally.
In July 1942 the control of
the camp was taken over
by the Germans security police.
And they reorganized
it as a transit camp
for the deportations
to the east.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: We went
by tram, which was an event
because we hadn't used public
transportation for a long time,
and were taken to
a railway station,
but we didn't know where
these trains were going.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The train took us to Westerbork.
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: When
we arrived in Westerbork
my father was brought
to one barrack.
And my sister and me were
brought to an orphanage.
My little sister was only
2 weeks in this orphanage
and the whole time we were
8 months in Westerbork
she was in a hospital
and very, very sick.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: It's frightening
to think that in a bizarre way
some Nazi's were actually
proud of what they were doing
to the Jews, and they
wanted to show off.
That's why a handful of
scrapbooks have managed
to survive and they provide
a backstage glimpse
into the Holocaust, where the
victims are being used as props.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: There
are two sorts of pictures
of Westerbork.
First of all there
are lots of pictures
of the exterior grounds.
The exterior grounds look like
a, a summer bungalow colony.
Reasonably well kept.
The houses and the housing
facilities look the way in which
housing facilities might look.
And little do you understand by
seeing these the horrific nature
of what's happening
in Westerbork.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
You then see people trying
to have ordinary lives
under extraordinary conditions.
It didn't look that
extraordinary.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And they're part of a
massive program of deception
in which what appears
is very different
than what's really happening.
And what's really happening is
this is a way station to death.
NANETTE KONIG: And the whole
impression that I had
that it was really,
it was awful.
It was terrible.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And of course the people were
very depressed because
they realized that they, it
was a short stay in Westerbork.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
It was all very neurotic,
very depressive.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID BARNOUW: We
hardly know anything about
their life in Westerbork.
But you can imagine that
in her diary she often writes
that she's looking outside.
And it was good weather.
It's August.
And I think that's being there
in a camp that's completely
different from this cramped
rooms where you don't have
real life.
So I can imagine that,
that would be a, a relief.
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: In 1944,
it was a daily practice
that Allied airplanes
were shot down
and the wreckage was
taken to Westerbork
to be taken apart and anything
usable would be recycled.
What we know from later
statements is that Anne Frank
and her group were working
in the battery detail.
They take out lead and carbon
and all sort of materials
that could be reused.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID BARNOUW: If you look
at Westerbork documentary
made by proud S.S. commander
because he was doing
such a great job.
There are famous scene
when a train is leaving.
You see Jews coming there.
Having uh suitcase with them.
They don't know they will be
killed on the other end
of the line.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: Once a week on
Monday when the lists were read
with the names of those people
who had to go on transport.
They were desperate, they no
longer believe they were going
to go for forced labor.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: The train
from September 3, 1944
turned out to be the last
train to, to Auschwitz.
Our eight people were on
that train because they were
punishment cases.
So, it was common practice for
them to be on the next train
to Auschwitz and that's
what they were.
(RAILROAD SOUND)
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. ALFRED GOTTWALDT: They would
ring the railway administration
and say, now can we have a train
from Westerbork to Auschwitz
or from Westerbork to Sobibor.
Those places like
Auschwitz and Sobibor,
they were not a secret
for the railway men.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Then the next step was
how much would it cost?
The Reichsbahn gave a special
rate for transports with more
than 400 people and instead
of the ordinary third class,
rate of four pfennig, they
only charged two pfennig.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The cattle car that you see here
was some sort of a standardized,
type of car.
They were made mostly to
transport goods that were,
suffering from rain.
So you had a roof on them like
furniture or grain or so.
But they were also designed
potentially to transport
soldiers.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Well, the car has an, an
ordinary size of say
three meters in width.
If you had, wooden seats
or stools in the inside,
then 40 people would sit there.
Some of the survivors describe
there were 50 or 70 of them
in a car.
(RAILROAD SOUND)
MARTIN MORGAN:
People always ask,
why didn't they bomb Auschwitz
and stop the trains from
running?
Well, rails can be rebuilt,
and the Allies felt that the
best way to stop the killing
was to win the war as
fast as possible.
It was a race against time
and a vast killing machine.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
George Rodgers was a kind
of zelig character who was,
just so happened to be
in the center of things
during the Second World War.
He documented combat all
the way up to the gates
of Bergen-Belsen,
and his images are what
people remember
when they recall the
horror of the Holocaust.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHANNES HOUWINK TEN CATE:
At the moment in time
that the Anne Frank family
was arrested,
it seemed logical to
hope for a speedy end
to the war on the
Western Front.
They liberated Paris at
the end of August 1944.
They marched through Belgium
without any problems
and then there was a
decisive attack,
an airborne British attack.
(Nazi newsreel).
MARTIN MORGAN: Operation Market
Garden was supposed to end
the war before Christmas,
by leapfrogging
across German defenses.
And when it failed, it condemned
the city of Amsterdam to another
5 months of Nazi occupation.
In fact, the Nazis were there in
the city until the very end
of the war.
Meanwhile, the
Holocaust kept going.
(Nazi newsreel).
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Think of it.
We all know the date: June 6,
1944, the Normandy invasions.
What is Germany doing on the war
against the Jews at that moment?
Between May 15th
and the 8th of July,
four hundred and thirty seven
thousand, four hundred and two
Jews are deported primarily
to Auschwitz from Hungary.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The moment at which they are
facing collapsing fronts
they are using that opportunity
to stretch their resources
to the most extreme to deport
more Jews to their death.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: Instead of
looking for the soldiers
to bring them to the
front or something.
Look it is all so without,
without sense that I cannot
tell you why they couldn't stop.
NANETTE KONIG: Yes, the Germans
kept the Holocaust going
because they had in mind
the Final Solution,
which they wanted to
accomplish no matter what.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Why
would they use such resources
when they were so scarce
and so desperately needed
for the war effort to fight
the war against the Jews?
And the answer is because they
thought they could win that war
even if they had to lose the
world war in the process.
(AIRPLANE SOUND)
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DANIEL UZIEL: We see
here an early blueprint
of the Auschwitz Birkenau Camp,
which was the central part
of the Auschwitz camp complex.
What's interesting about this
specific blueprint is its title.
It says a blueprint of
the Auschwitz POW camp.
The main purpose of the S.S.
was to bring around 100,000 POWs
from the Eastern Front into this
huge camp and to use them as
forced labor in the construction
of a nearby IG Farben and
Petro chemical factory.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
This camp eh, eh, was actually
never used as a POW camp.
It was turned in to a
concentration camp
in late 1941, early 42.
And uh, within matter of a few
months it was turned into
an extermination camp.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
TERESA WONTOR-CICHY:
Auschwitz became the biggest,
the largest Nazi
concentration camp.
And in fact Auschwitz
was a complex of camps.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Auschwitz
1 was a penal colony primarily
for Polish prisoners.
Who were part of
the culture elite.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Auschwitz 3 was a
slave labor camp.
Birkenau or Auschwitz 2 was
the death camp at Auschwitz.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: Remember,
the men who ran these camps
ran them like any
other business,
efficiently as they could,
with a clear
management structure
of who reported to whom.
At Auschwitz there
was a camp library,
there was a camp newspaper,
they had vacation options,
all in all, it was pretty good
duty compared to serving
on the front lines.
DR. JOHN CRAMER: Josef Kramer
was a commandant of a sub-camp.
So his superior was Rudolf Höss,
who was in charge of sort
of the overall extermination
and forced labor,
camp system at Auschwitz.
Kramer was the
extermination expert.
Kramer was also responsible for
sending camp doctors to the ramp
to carry out the
selection process.
Um, and as Mengele was one of
the camp doctors at that time,
he had to answer Kramer; he was
under his responsibility
and I think, they had a good
cooperation as far as I know.
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG:
Josef Kramer was
like other S.S. people.
And for them, getting rid of
the Jews or getting rid of
whoever's defined as an enemy,
if there's some other kind
of enemy that was defined,
then we must get rid of
these because otherwise
Germany and humanity
can't go on.
Then getting rid of those
people is a moral act,
it's not a separation.
It is the moral act.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Hannah
Arendt had a theory called
the banality of evil.
She was wrong.
The reason she was wrong in
the most basic sense is that
evil was not banal.
The evil was demonic.
The evil was horrific.
The evil was of such
extraordinary proportions
that it was hardly in any which
way manner or form ordinary.
What she should have written
and what she probably meant was
that the perpetrators
were often banal.
They were ordinary men who faced
extraordinary circumstances
and who came with both the
mindset and a tendency
to operate in those
circumstances.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The prisoners who arrived in the
camp had survived sometimes days
and sometimes many days, on a
train in which they had been
living in their own
feces and urine.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
There was a stink.
There was a smell.
There was a hunger.
There was a darkness and there
was the fear of the unknown.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And when the train doors opened,
they thought they had
survived the worst.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(RAILROAD SOUND)
(BARKING DOGS)
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: They arrived
in Auschwitz on the night 5-6,
September, in the early morning.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
On the platform the men were
separated from the women,
which was common
practice as well.
So, that's where Otto Frank saw
his family for the last time.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
They were from there marched
to the so called sauna
where sort of intake
process was conducted.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Now the
language appears as a nice place
to go.
We go to saunas for cleansing.
We got to saunas
to sweat, to bathe.
The sauna there was a place
in which essentially branding
and shearing took place.
All this is designed to
eliminate any individuality
and to make you a blob of flesh.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: This selection
process is what makes Auschwitz
different from Sobibor.
Because Auschwitz
was a labor camp,
they needed able
bodied workers,
so, there was a chance you
could walk off the ramp alive.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: The
women stayed in Birkenau
the place where they arrived.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And the men were marched to the
so called Stumlager Auschwitz 1,
which was a few miles
away from there.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
TERESA WONTOR-CICHY: Well the,
the female camp uh was here
in Birkenau.
And the conditions
there were catastrophe.
Were just horrible.
So this is what most of
the survivors remember.
Birkenau as muddy, swampy area.
Terribly smelling with loads
of insects and the epidemics
non-stop.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Most probably Anna Frank was
kept in this type of building
as we are in.
We can see beds here
with the 3 level bunks.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: We know
that the men were on duties.
They had to work on roads,
on the riversides, gravel.
Just like Otto Frank, Hermann
van Pels had to work in
the gravel pits and on
road construction
and what we know of postwar,
statements is that he hurt
his hand at one point
and couldn't work anymore.
So he was left behind
in the barracks.
As common practice in Auschwitz
was from time to time,
all these barracks were swept
and whoever was left there
unable to work would be sent
to the gas chambers and
that is apparently what happened
to Hermann van Pels as well.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
After working with Hermann
van Pels and Otto Frank
on the gravel pits and on the,
on the roads around the camps,
Fritz Pfeffer left
for Neuengamme.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And in December '44
already he died there.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
The accounts of the death of
Mrs. van Pels are contradicting
each other a bit, but there's
one statement that she was
thrown before the wheels of a
train for some reason during
a stop and the other idea is
that she died on the train and
was thrown off the train during
a stop because obviously,
the survivors would
dispose of the dead bodies
on the carriages.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
TERESA WONTOR-CICHY: Typhus
was horrible disease.
Caused basically by, by dirt.
Spread immediately in the camp.
And the administration, the camp
administration at the beginning
seems to ignore this fact.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
So to combine all the diseases
and the work every single day
from morning to night.
To survive was hardly possible.
The sisters were most probably
kept all the time together.
Anna and Margot.
So they were not separated.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
So there was something
what was just uniting them.
And they, they were trying
to as much as they could
to help each other.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MATTHIAS HEYL: If Anne
would have stayed in Auschwitz,
I think she would have
had a chance to survive.
But the Nazis were not
interested to let her survive.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. ALFRED GOTTWALDT: In the
final months of 1944
when the um, gas chambers in,
in Auschwitz were destroyed.
Then the S.S. had the,
the task to, what shall we
do with the people,
with the Jewish
inhabitants of the camp?
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
They simply could not come to
the conclusion, the war is lost;
we finished.
They would go on until
the last bullet was used.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
(Newsreel).
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG: The Red
Army was advancing rapidly,
even in winter.
And the decision that was taken,
based upon earlier orders
from Himmler, wherever possible,
bring prisoners westward
and we'll keep using them
uh, for our own purposes.
So, she's sent, Anne Frank, like
other people, from Birkenau,
while Birkenau's still
functioning, to another camp,
perhaps to work.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. INSA ESCHEBACH: Two sisters
being together have a big chance
to survive usually because it is
a family tradition of helping
each other, of being together
'cause you're much stronger
being together than
being alone and separate.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
So, when Anne and,
and Margot left Auschwitz, they
thought they had survived
the worst.
They went to Bergen-Belsen, they
probably looked at Bergen-Belsen
and said here there
are no gas chambers.
We're safer.
Life's got to be easier.
DR. DAVID BARNOUW: Bergen-Belsen
was seen as a better camp
than the other camps.
Because it was also used by the
Germans to keep people there
they could maybe exchange for
Germans who were somewhere in
uh, Allied captivity.
DR. MATTHIAS HEYL: So there was
a better chance to survive
for a while up to the end of the
camp system when more and more
transports were sent from
the east to the west
and then a lot of transports
ended up in Bergen-Belsen.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: We were sent to
Bergen-Belsen on the 15th
of February 1944.
We belonged to the Palestine
list mainly because my father
have worked for
the Amsterdam bank.
Once we were on the Palestine
list you did not go into
an extermination camp.
It was considered
to be a privilege.
Joseph Kramer was called the
beast of Bergen-Belsen who said
the more dead Jews you bring
me, the best I like it.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHN CRAMER: In Auschwitz,
it was Kramer's job
to kill as many people
as quickly as possible.
In Bergen-Belsen, it was not.
He had problems to adapt to this
different situation and then,
this overcrowding starts.
And he doesn't really
know what to do.
I mean, he was rather
concerned with, oh, dear,
what's the picture that
everybody will get
when he sees this untidy camp?
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: And
now every camp in Germany
got every day new people
from the camps in Poland.
And one day everything was full.
There was less and less food.
People didn't die quick enough.
And we hear they are coming a
whole group of 7,000 women,
women from Auschwitz.
First time that I heard
the name of Auschwitz.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: What are the
odds that in her most desperate
moments, Anne Frank runs into
two old friends from Amsterdam?
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And what are the odds that both
of those friends would survive
the war, and therefore
be able to tell us about
Anne's last days?
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
C] ♪
(German newsreel).
MARTIN MORGAN: The Nazis just
weren't going to let it go.
There were going to keep
going with the Final Solution
until it was indeed final.
There's absolutely no reason for
them to do this, but then again,
absolutely nothing about
this story makes any sense.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: All
Germany was in disarray.
And the war industry that they
were supposed to work in
was in desarray.
So, they were more or less with
all the other inhabitants of the
camp left to themselves,
and as we know now, left,
left to die because there
was no sanitation, no water,
the food was very scarce and
pestilence was all around.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: It is certainly
incredible that I could have
this relationship because it was
sheer coincidence that we were
both in the same place and
next to one another and it was
incredible that we could meet.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: When I
heard Anna is there
I couldn't believe it.
Because the rumor was going on
that they were in Switzerland
with grandmother.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: The first
time I saw her was,
was across the barbed wire, but
one couldn't go anywhere close
to the barbed wire because you
might be tortured, or shot,
or whatever.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: And suddenly
somebody told me Anna Frank
and then I went to the fence.
Everybody told me not to go.
It's of not for allowed
and it's dangerous.
But I couldn't not
go, you understand?
And so I stood there not
so long, five minutes,
seven minutes.
Very cold.
Raining and I was afraid
the German will hear us.
But really after seven
minutes or so a very,
very weak voice is calling
for me and it was Anna.
First thing when we
met we were crying,
because it was really miracle
that we met each other
in million of people.
NANETTE KONIG: Our first me,
meeting was, is unforgettable.
We were both skeletons.
She was trembling with cold.
She was wrapped in a blanket
because she could no longer
stand her own
clothes full of lice.
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: It
was not the same Anna
I knew from Holland, the
nice little spicy girl.
She was frightened and
she was uh, without hope.
It was awful.
So she asked if I could
help with some food.
And so I told her, look we don't
have much more than you have.
But we got for the first
time in the whole ah period
two very little packages.
Like a book from the Red Cross
and I had left something.
So I said Anna come in two
or three days we will see
what I can do.
Everybody gave me some
of the dried prunes.
We put a sock and we put ah,
them some um, um, loaves.
And some food of the package.
A little bit of pieces of sugar
and so very small package.
Like a little football.
After two or three days
I came to the fence.
And when I hear Anna at the
other side it was dark
and we could speak.
I said Anna careful.
I throw it over the fence.
But what happened was
I couldn't see her.
The fence was high.
The night was dark.
Another hungry woman
caught the package.
And she was angry and she
was shouting and crying.
And what happened?
That another woman
took the package.
So I promised her we will try
again come once more in two
or three days.
We could do it once more.
We had three meetings at all.
And this time she got it.
Ah, she caught the package.
But it was the last time
that we could speak.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG:
We never lost hope
that we would actually survive.
Although the circumstances,
the conditions were very much
against us, none of
us ever lost hope.
Life is something which
is very dear to anyone,
and we didn't want
to lose our life.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG: When the
Red Army marched in to Auschwitz
on January 27th of 1945,
they found some 7- or
8,000 prisoners there,
most of them Jews,
quite a few in the infirmaries,
others just wandering around.
Some of them were children.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And Otto Frank is one of the
people that was left behind,
and he was liberated.
And here it's ironic.
He survived because
he was left behind
because he was not
well enough to march.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: Anna didn't
know that her father is alive.
So if she would have known maybe
she had a little more strength.
But she didn't know.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: To
survive you had to have
a balance between
hope and realism.
If you're fully realistic
you could have fallen apart.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. INSA ESCHEBACH: These last
years in concentration camps
were devastating usually because
the epidemics were raging
through the camp and different
kinds of terrible illnesses
were dominating the camp.
And women were dying every
day in dirt and filth.
They couldn't, get up anymore.
They were lying down and
losing interest in life.
Not being able to
eat or drink anymore.
And every morning they were
carrying out hundreds
of dead bodies here
from the camp and uh,
it's definitely this is the most
tragic chapter of the history
of concentration camps.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHN CRAMER: Josef Kramer
was really annoyed by the fact
that he was unable to run this
camp as efficient as he had run
Auschwitz-Birkenau before.
He wasn't concerned about so
many corpses on the campground.
It was the fact that these
corpses were sort of were lying
all over the place.
If they had arranged themselves
decently, in columns of five,
as prisoners had to do
during the roll call,
I think he would've been
completely satisfied
with the situation.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. GERTJAN BROEK: Typhus was
the main cause of death
at that time.
Anne and Margot were
in a barrack together
with a lot of others of course.
And they had typhus as well.
And they more or less withered
away and first Margot died and
the same day or the next day or
two days later Anna as well.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: Anne Frank came
so close to surviving the war,
and being reunited
with her father.
Although we don't know
exactly when she died,
we do know that it was just
a few weeks before
the British arrived.
It's yet another tragedy on top
of everything else that she
and her family and
friends had to endure.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Imagine you survived
the whole damn thing
and you lost your life
four weeks before the end,
three weeks before the end.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: Well, actually
Bergen-Belsen was never
liberated in the
sense of liberation.
On the 13th of April, 1945,
the guards left the camp
and the British Medical Corps
entered the camps.
Can you imagine the stench
of endless heaps of bodies
deteriorating?
There's not, there's no way that
anybody can actually imagine
or describe it.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHN CRAMER: When the
British arrived there was
thousands of, of, of bodies
lying around; corpses.
What the British did was sort
of tried to separate the living
from the dead, bring
those who were still,
whom they could still save
away to a military barracks
in the vicinity of Belsen Camp.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
And I think the very next day
there were the first British
newspaper reports, photographs
taken at Bergen-Belsen,
headlines like ah, this
is what we fight for,
this is why we fight.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: I don't think
any mind can imagine
what it was like.
It was so awful that the British
decided that within three weeks
they'd burn the whole camp down.
ANNOUNCER: Fire helps to
purify the horror of Belsen.
But what can ever cleanse
the guilt of Germany?
Shriveled bodies like old
bones picked over by dogs.
Piles and heaps like the
litter of a bone yard.
These are the foul, wretched
remnants of human beings.
Human beings, like you and me.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Susan Sontag,
who was then a 12-year-old
girl, she said,
I entered the theater
a happy, young woman.
I came out in tears.
I was shattered.
Something in me has
been crying ever since.
ANNOUNCER: At Belsen, we
caught the camp commander,
Josef Kramer, the
Beast of Belsen.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: Who knows
what went up in the flames
of the crematoria?
Great poetry, brilliant
music, world-class artistry?
Maybe the cure for cancer.
The loss of a child is the
loss of infinite possibility.
The loss, the murder of one
and a half million children
murdered the possibility
of possibility.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: Anne Frank
most likely never even saw
Joseph Kramer, either at
Auschwitz, or Bergen-Belsen,
and yet he was
instrumental in her death.
It remains one of the many
tragedies of this story
that Anne Frank did not survive
to bear witness to Kramer's
atrocities.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. JOHN CRAMER: Well, Josef
Kramer was obviously quite
surprised when he was taken
prisoner because he had expected
to be transferred
to the German lines.
Um, he never really, understood
why he was put to trial.
ANNOUNCER: The Belsen war
criminals arrive at Lüneburg
for trial.
Their faces give little clue
to what they are thinking.
DR. JOHN CRAMER: He
had done nothing wrong.
I mean, he had
simply obeyed orders.
Um, he had carried them out
to the best of his abilities.
Until the end, he
never really understood
why he was treated as
a criminal.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: So,
it involved killing
women and children.
What the hell difference
did that make?
They were Jews.
Their life was a cancer
on German society.
And all he was doing was
eliminating that cancer.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID BARNOUW:
Karl Silberbauer,
just like all the other Germans
just went back to his old uh,
job in this case.
The, uh the police in Vienna.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. DAVID SILBERKLANG:
And the, uh, Nazi hunter,
Simon Wiesenthal, found him.
And Silberbauer says,
what do you want from me after
all these years? You know?
And he lost his job briefly,
as a result of Wiesenthal
finding him.
And what he had to say about
that, Silberbauer was, you know,
I just bought new furniture
and now I can't afford
to pay for it.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: Silberbauer
was quoted as saying,
if I knew what was
in those diaries,
I would have taken them.
He experienced no remorse
for what he had done,
and apparently later went
on to work with West German
intelligence, who then went on
to work closely with the CIA.
All in a day's work.
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM: And the
fact that the man who betrayed
Anne Frank could die in his bed
violates our sense of justice.
We become angry at God,
we become angry at
the court system,
we become angry at the world,
because such a man should be
forced to pay the price
for his deeds.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: When I was
taken to the first hospitals,
it was the first sheets and beds
I had seen for a long time.
It was an amazing sensation to
lie in a real bed and to have
bed sheets and in a
way to be cared for,
which hadn't
happened until then.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
This photograph
was also in here.
And this photograph survived.
It was a class photo,
a school photo.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
This is the star.
The original star.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
HANNAH PICK-GOSLAR: We
were 10 days at away.
And really without food.
I only remember
we passed Berlin.
We didn't know but
it was a big city.
So people said, this is Berlin!
And it was really, you could
look through the city.
We were so happy they
also suffered something.
And then the 10th day the S.S.
left the train and the
Russians liberated us.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
We suffered a lot.
And that was enough.
But I didn't know that it could
still be much, much worse.
And even today I
still read things I,
I never would have believed
if it wasn't written down.
It is unbelievable what
these people did to us.
Unbelievable.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
NANETTE KONIG: The
way I knew Anne,
she would have been overjoyed
that she became famous.
She wanted to be known.
She was full of life, full
of zim, zip, and vigor.
And I think this would
have given her tremendous
satisfaction, and she would have
very probably achieved it
had she been alive because she
was a very gifted writer
and a wonderful person.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
YVES KUGELMANN: Yeah, so,
when it comes to the question
what do you have to do when
you have such an archive?
Ah, we have about 1,500
objects of the family,
2000 photograph is original.
About 100,000 and
more documents.
At the end of the day it's
not about home bringing,
but about showing
where they came from.
DR. RAPHAEL GROSS: I think
it's a unique, a very um,
moving moment for a museum when
it gets a wealth of objects,
archival material.
From a family that lived in
Frankfurt for maybe about
400 years until the early 30s.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
We do not have so many important
objects from a Jewish family
of such significance.
It's of course a legacy that we
have to be very careful with.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Because what we do not want to
present is a sweet, happy end.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
YVES KUGELMANN: This is a legacy
which belongs in a way Europe
and it's part of
European history.
And I don't know if he
would have been happy to go
in the family Frank
archive here in Frankfurt,
but in a way I think
he would have liked it.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
MARTIN MORGAN: Evil
can be found anywhere.
In the face of a bureaucratic
butcher like Joseph Kramer,
or tragically, in the face
of George Rodger's grandson.
But it's how we measure
and respond to evil
that is important.
And for that reason, the
heroic story of Anne Frank
and her family and
friends must be told.
DR. JOHN CRAMER: When I come to
Bergen-Belsen and I walk across
the camp grounds, there's a
feeling of sadness somehow,
a feeling of loss.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
Will people come
to Bergen-Belsen,
look for the Anne
Frank memorial?
Will they want to remember
what happened there
during the Second World War?
That's an interesting
question for me, as a German.
As a German historian,
as a father of three.
Um, and I have no answer.
NANETTE KONIG: My children,
my grandchildren and,
and probably my
great grandchildren,
will all know and will all
wonder how come it could ever
happen and that is the
importance of speaking, talking,
and telling the world.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪
DR. MICHAEL BERENBAUM:
Yehuda Bauer,
who is the greatest Israeli
scholar of the Holocaust,
has said three
commandments have emerged
from the shadow of the
Holocaust:
Thou shalt not be a perpetrator,
thou shalt not be a victim,
and thou shall not
be a bystander.
♪ [MUSIC] ♪