Hello, guys.
-Hello, captain.
-Yo, cappy.
Jacques, I hope everything's
in order?. You do a good job?.
Sure thing, captain.
When do we leave?.
In the morning. Our passengers
arrived on the noon plane.
What's wrong, Jacques?.
Well, sir, you know that bringing
civilians aboard brings bad luck.
Plus I just
don't like all this mystery.
I know how you feel.
Give the men a couple
of days leave, and remember....
no strangers are allowed on board.
And especially no reporters!.
Don't worry, sir.
I'm gonna go see those people.
I don't know how the five
of them are gonna fit into one tent.
-Three of them are women.
-Woman!
We must be crazy! You know what
they say about women.
They really bring bad luck!
It's worse than that,
Jacques. They're scientists.
Can you imagine what
kinda monsters they are?.
-Goodbye, Captain.
-I'll see ya tomorrow.
Excuse me. I'm looking for the
members of the scientific expedition.
They're up there by the pool.
Good morning.
Captain Hardee?.
Yes.
I'm Annie Darmona.
My pleasure. And you must be.
Let me guess, the biologist?.
My field is nuclear physics.
I'm Professor Lemuan's assistant.
Disappointed?.
No, on the contrary.
Neither physics nor
biology are my strong points.
Do you want a drink?.
No, thanks, I'm on duty.
I thought that
only applied to policemen.
And sailors, too.
Bravo!
Come here, I want you
to meet a real clean-cut sailor.
A pleasure, captain.
The pleasure is all mine.
I never thought
Science was so interesting.
Are you the biologist?.
She's the zoologist,
Dr. Dorcin de San Jack.
Oh excuse me
Countess de San Jack!
Thank you, my dear. Even the
Navy has its good points, captain.
Are you the one who's
going to take us to the island?.
Yes, the Minister has placed
me entirely at your disposal.
Magnificent! Perhaps you can
take me on a tour of the islands?.
Naturally, if you'd like.
Pardon me for a moment.
You again, Benoit?. You want
me to call the military police?.
You can't do
anything to me, Captain.
Fortunately, we still
have freedom of the press here.
Oh come on,
I just need a good story.
Sorry, Benoit,
but there's nothing here to see.
Besides, I don't even
know what's going on myself.
Lies!! I'm sure
something big is going on here,
and the public's
got a right to know.
Well, you won't
get anything from me.
Goodbye, Benoit.
Captain, this isn't
over yet! Captain, wait!!
Forgive me.
He's the press correspondent here.
It's very hard to get rid of him.
Now what were we talking about?.
I must confess I really don't know
why you're going to that island.
My orders are to bring you there, and
give you whatever help you'll need.
I'm just the
taxi driver, nothing more.
Maybe we can explain
it to you, would you like that?.
I will admit I'm very curious.
But not without
Professor Lemuan's permission!
Please, Countess,
don't be so mysterious.
This whole thing
is becoming ridiculous.
Up to now, we've had no
scientific facts, only a theory.
We have those photos, Annie.
They're not just a theory.
Those photos were
taken from a naval plane.
Are you sure you
don't know anything about this?.
No, that's basically it. The Minister
gave me explicit instructions
not to talk to anyone.
But for awhile now,
we've been hearing of strange
things happening on that island.
For a while now?. But
they only notified us a month ago!
The Minister thought
if we reacted to the rumors,
we'd risk making fools of ourselves.
It might just be a
tall tale told by the fishermen.
You know the people around here,
with their rituals and black magic,
tend to lose sight of reality.
Look! What could
have done this to him?.
No sea animal can do something like
this. Oh God, may he rest in peace.
We told him not to
go near that cursed island.
He went there to kill the
monster, to avenge his son's death.
Come, let us bury him at sea.
The sea can keep many dark secrets.
Do you want to take
a shower?. I'm finished.
Thank you.
Hmmm, I've never seen that
underwear before. It's very sexy.
Simone, you know I hate
it when you make stupid remarks.
Wait, I've got
something here. It hurts.
I don't see anything.
And you don't feel anything here?.
Simone, I'm in a hurry.
The Minister is waiting.
Simone! Calm down!
Come on...
No more!
I came...
According to this evidence, the
problem appears to be very serious.
Crabs, turtles and
rodents, all of enormous size!
This would seem
to verify the rumors about
biological mutations
to the animals there.
That's what we have to investigate.
Minister, Professor Keller
is too much of a perfectionist,
Iike all biologists.
We physicists are not so rigid.
You physicists are also responsible
for those horrible mutations.
Minister, your report
says you sent a plane up
to take photographs
after a long series of...
shall we call them, incidents?. Excuse
me, but why did you wait so long?.
Frankly, Professor Lemuan, I don't
believe what those fishermen say.
They use dynamite to catch fish,
sometimes a fatal accident occurs.
They blame the deaths on a demon,
to avoid responsibility themselves.
But one of them, a man named Keno,
has told of a monstrous creature
on that cursed island
a monster that murdered his son.
That is all fantasy Professor.
But we have photos and the
examanation on the dead child.
The island's
been deserted since 1 958,
when we evacuated
the tiny native population
after the island was chosen as a
test site for nuclear experiments.
Since then, we haven't
allowed anyone to live there.
Is it possible that a few of the
original inhabitants were left behind?.
Perhaps someone living
in a remote area of the island?.
Strange that you would
believe such an absurd theory!
No one could have lived
through those atomic explosions.
Minister, I was one of the physicists
who worked on that experiment,
and ever since
that day, I've asked myself
if we had the right to do what
we did in the name of Progress.
We unleashed a terrible force, the
extent of which we do not even know.
I'm not seeking exoneration, I'm just
trying to rid myself of a nightmare
the possibility that these mutations
may have affected a human being!
Pardon me, Professor,
perhaps I seem a bit brusque,
but they keep bothering
me from Paris. The truth is,
I don't enjoy finding myself
involved with a bunch of scientists
and all these security measures.
I understand.
We'll try to keep out of your way.
On the contrary, I want to help.
I'm assigning you to Captain Hardee,
and if necessary, I'll send a second
boat out to the island to help you.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Come in.
Hello.
Why don't you lock your door?.
What for?. I've no fear that
someone might come in and fuck me.
In fact, I wish they would.
I see your lover has disappointed
you again. But he always tries.
That's enough.
Where's Annie gone?.
She's busy. Would you believe
she went out with that captain?.
She beat you to him, eh?.
If you want another,
just keep acting like a bitch.
What a whore you are!
Such language?. I'm shocked.
Come on,
don't play stupid.
Let's not fight, eh?. Let's fuck!
For you, captain. Eat hearty!
You're wondering why
this place is so peaceful.
I've been wondering about
that myself. I think it's because
there are so few tourists
here, and so little noise.
It'd be the perfect place
for a couple looking for privacy.
The people around here
don't go to a restaurant like this,
that offers the home-made
cooking they can get at home.
This is home-cooking?. It makes
me want to move here permanently.
It's fabulous!
The lobster's not half bad. Tastes
like it came straight from Japan.
What if the tourist people hear you?.
You surprise me, Captain Hardee ---
in a good way. I didn't
expect you to be so friendly.
You're just
getting to know me better.
Have you noticed I'm as
nervous as an Olympic athlete?.
Sure. And I've been wondering why.
Y'know, the big lie about sailors is
that they have a girl in every port.
I never thought you'd
be such an interesting woman.
That's ridiculous. Do you think
I'm different when I'm in Paris?.
Do you think just
because I'm a scientist,
that I've forgotten
how to be a woman, too?.
I don't mean it that way.
But as impossible as it may seem,
at this moment I feel we
could be in a restaurant in Paris.
Of course, some
things would be dif ferent.
Instead of this lobster,
we'd be having hamburgers.
Hamburgers?. What kind of place
would you take me to in Paris?.
Hey! You think I could afford to
eat lobster in Paris on my salary?.
Calm down. Let's
not talk about hamburgers.
That's what I eat every
day at the hospital commissary.
But let's talk about us. Do you have
anything planned for after dinner?.
Sure. We're going to go see a great
show. I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Do we have time?.
I don't like to eat in a hurry.
Don't worry.
We'll have all the time we need.
OK
What a beautiful city!
Isn't it interesting?.
Yes, very.
But not nearly as interesting
as a place I've discovered.
Is sex all you think about?.
Ah, we're here.
I think this is the place.
Have fun then.
This kind of thing's not for me.
Come with me.
It'll be an exciting experience.
It better be, for what
I spent to find out about this place.
Sorry, but I don't have the courage.
Or maybe I'm just too pure.
Well, do as you like. But
I'm not missing out on this chance.
Last week I got
lucky with one of the tourists.
Come in, miss. You have to pay
in advance here. House rules.
Wait'll you see
how you will be satisfied.
I have two fine specimens here.
Here.
Well, here we are.
It's about time.
Oh, those potholes!
That road is pretty bad,
but you'll really enjoy the show.
Give me the champagne?.
Come on, I've reserved
two seats in the front row.
I'm glad you got
a day off before the trip.
I didn't want to leave
without seeing these islands.
It's very slippery. There
are a lot of sharp rocks here.
I've never seen so many.
Be careful.
Oh, my shoe!
Here.
Forget it, leave it like that.
Let's stop here.
No one will bother us.
You were right. It is a spectacular
sight. What a beautiful sea!
I'm going for a swim.
Will you join me?.
No, I'd prefer
to sit here and watch.
But I'm not part of the show.
I think you are. Let's just
say you complete the picture.
The water's incredible.
Why don't you go in?.
You are so amazing.
I want you so bad.
Pierre and Jacques aren't very
disciplined, but they're fine sailors.
And above all,
they're very trustworthy.
Captain, did Professor
Keller introduce you to his wife?.
Not really, but
I know everything about her.
She is Dr. Simone Keller, biologist.
Bravo, captain!
I've heard so much about you.
For example, that you
made a big impact on my colleague.
When will we arrive
on the island, captain?.
Just before dawn.
Is it that far?.
No, but we will change our course a
few times to avoid being followed.
You never know.
Do you think there will be
any danger from radioactivity?.
I don't think so,
not after all this time.
We'll take a reading,
though, as soon as we get there.
How long
will we be staying there?.
A couple of days.
I really don't know
what we can do there,
other than take a
few readings and samples.
I'm sorry...
But is that how you scientists spend
the taxpayer's money?.
You sound like
a politician on a campaign.
Let's consider the evidence here,
the photos and the
testimony of those fishermen.
The aerial photos suggest the
possibility of biological mutations.
If we accept the
fishermen's stories as truth,
that possibility is doubled.
Or maybe it's
all just a wild story,
in which case
we're all having a little vacation
at the taxpayer's expense.
But this island could
hold an unknown danger
that we are
not prepared to confront.
I say we turn around and go back.
You may be right, Professor.
But did we need to hear a speech?.
You should have discussed
your fears with the Minister.
I did! God knows
I did! But no one would listen.
And now, here
we are in this little boat,
preparing to
grab the Devil by the horns.
Keller, you're so boring.
Would you rather go to the
island on a cruise liner?.
We're only going to take samples.
We're not going of f to war.
It may not be a war,
but it's something abnormal.
I'm sure the Minister
wouldn't react this way
to a bunch of fishermen's tales.
All this security...
passing us off as tourists...
changes in the route.
I'm convinced there's
something strange going on here.
Oh come on, Keller,
why are you so grim?.
Simone, what's worrying your
husband?. Doesn't he ever relax?.
We'd better get some sun
now, before we get to the island.
Have fun! We're on vacation!
A beautiful trip on a tropical sea!
Pity it will all end tomorrow.
Lemuan is right.
You really are boring.
Tomorrow we
start working seriously.
From that point on,
we won't have time to go swimming.
That's for sure.
Listen to me,
I know what I'm talking about.
-Don't argue any more.
-Enjoy the trip, like I'm doing.
Oh, shut up. That's the way
I am. Please just leave me alone.
You don't know how
to take a joke. Aw, just forget it.
Are you enjoying yourself?.
Yes, very much.
When we go back,
I'm going to spend a couple of
days relaxing and seeing the sights.
Simone,
will you be staying awhile?.
I'd like to, but we have
to return to Paris immediately.
Look! There's your island.
You mad at me?.
Do you think I am?.
I haven't talked to you all day.
You're talking to me now.
I hate having that stupid
Countess thinking I'm an easy lay!
I'm not an easy lay.
I'm just a guy who likes you a lot.
If I didn't ----
There's hardly
any radiation at all.
A lot less than we'd predicted.
We can all relax.
Great!
The island is so peaceful.
Stop for a minute?.
I want to take a photo.
Nothing at all.
The island looks dead.
You look nervous?.
What's wrong?.
Nothing, really.
I just have a feeling
that we're being watched.
Is your conscience bothering
you?. It's your own sense of guilt.
How about you, Annie?.
Have you noticed anything?.
Nothing at all.
Not even a single insect.
No signs of birds or rodents.....
Yes. Let's go on.
They haven't returned yet?.
No.
Why are you staying by yourself?.
Your pussy still hurt?.
More than you know.
Those black bastards
really busted my hole.
But what a magnificent fuck!
You'll have to be strong now.
How will you survive on this island
for a whole week, without any sex?.
There are always new experiences.
What are you doing?.
I have a surefire
way to keep us both happy.
The boat's on
the other side of that mountain.
We've explored about
two thirds of the island now.
Well, I think
we should return to camp.
Me too.
Maybe we'll come back this afternoon
to get a few samples to analyze.
It'll be cooler then.
Hey, why don't we eat some crabs
tonight?. There are plenty around.
I hope I'm wrong about this.
What do you think, professor?.
No, you're not
wrong. It's incredible!
What a surprise
the Countess will have!
Captain, would you pick
up a few of those for us?.
I'm finished.
Now it's your turn.
I still can't explain
this scientifically.
All I can do right now is classify
and preserve the specimens,
because we don't have the
necessary instruments here.
My husband and I will have
to get back to the lnstitute lab
before we can formulate a theory.
Pardon me. I may not understand
this zoology and biology stuf f,
but I've seen thousands
of crabs around here.
And they all look
perfectly ordinary to me.
This "ordinary" crab is
a cretinos enano, a midget species
that usually grows to a maximum
length of 2 and a half centimeters.
But this one's more than twenty!
22, to be exact.
The radiation, I assume?.
You assume correctly, captain.
If you want to know more,
I suggest you go talk to Lemuan.
It's men like him,
playing games with the atom,
who are sending this
whole world straight to Hell.
-Let's stop here and fuck.
-Hmmm, I like that.
Our tests detect radiation in the
water, but at extremely low levels.
Are you saying that someday
life may return to this island?.
Yes.
We've looked everywhere and we
haven't found a trace of animal life.
Only these strange
looking crabs....
It's possible that
after the atomic explosions,
some species died of f altogether,
while others may have mutated.
And that bothers you?.
It's our only hope, really.
Some of the animals on this
island may have become nocturnal.
And maybe we can
find some specimens.
Pardon me,
I don't mean to be rude.
But how much longer will
we have to stay on this island?.
However long
it takes. If you don't mind,
my wife and I would like
to leave the camp for a while,
to go off and
study some things on our own.
Will you assume
personal responsibility
for your safety if
you don't stay with the group?.
Of course.
Find anything?.
Only a few small fresh
water plants.
I think the life forms
here have started to mutate.
Do you see the strange
coloration of this plant?.
Yes, it looks carnivorous. The
Countess will be able to confirm that.
I'm so tired. Let's go to bed.
We'll finish up tomorrow.
We're going to be
awfully cramped in there.
So?. Does that bother you?.
Simone,
what are you up to now?.
You know this place
gives me a strange sensation.
Are you afraid?.
It makes me feel something else.
Give me a little kiss, professor?.
Simone Please!
What's wrong?. Are you afraid
that someone might see us?.
Then tell me where
you would like to fuck?.
Oh, God, professor. That
was marvelous! It's about time!
Yes, it certainly
was marvelous......
You see, we may
not like this island,
but we've turned this
trip into a honeymoon!
That was the first real
fuck you've ever given me!!
Our first fuck, eh?. God, I'm all
sweaty. And I'm so thirsty.
We need some ice cold
champagne to celebrate!!
I'm going to take a
dip in the water. Wait a minute?.
Hurry back. I'll be waiting.
I won't be long.
Hey, professor.
Is that you?. Where are you?.
Jacques, come over here.
Why're you laughin'
like a fuckin' idiot?.
Those two guys got two women
like that, and look what they're doing.
Playing poker instead'a fuckin'.
My grandpappy was right.
What can I say?.
They're very studious people.
Yeah, the Captain's
been studyin' too.
When he come back with that lady
doctor, you should see his face.
Well, it's none of our business.
Let's go pick some
fruit before it gets dark.
Yes, sir.
I'll see ya back at camp.
O. K.
You go that way,
and I'll go this way.
OK boss.
What the hell was that?.
Quick! Let's go see.
Let's split up.
Captain, I'll go this way.
Alright.
I can't go on.
Here, lean on me.
To whomever finds this notebook;
My name is Antoine Demaduro.
I had no time to leave the
island before the first explosion.
I'm going to live in this cave...
...with my wife and child.
May God have mercy on us,
Monday, the 1 9th of Sept.,1 958.
I just came
from the dock. The boat is gone!
The ropes were broken.
The currents swept it out to sea.
We're trapped here.
What do you
think happened last night?.
I don't know, but I'm
sure it was something terrible.
My men don't lose
their heads so easily.
And what about the others?.
No sign of them. They all seem to
have disappeared, including Annie.
My God, that's strange....
Look! There's Keller.
He's dead.
We have to look for Simone.
Their camp must
be up there. Let's go.
Who could've done this killing?.
I don't know,
but I'm sure it was no animal.
How can you be so sure?.
I don't know of
any animal, except for a man,
that would fuck
a woman before killing her.
No, it's not possible!
I can't believe...
a human being was
responsible for these murders.
Captain, we're in great danger.
What do we do now?.
First,
we have to bury these bodies.
Then we'll go back to the
camp. Annie may still be alive.
In a couple of days, there'll be
another boat coming by to look for us.
We have to make a plan.
Yes, we have to stay alive
until the other boat arrives.
Meanwhile,
help me dig these graves.
I found my men. I just finished
burying them, or should I say,
what was left of them.
I can't understand it.
Who is attacking us?.
Oh, I found a small
boat hidden under some bushes.
Well, that's good news at least.
No, it isn't.
Why not?. Now
we can get off the island!
It's too small
to carry the three of us.
One big wave,
and we'd be shark food.
Wait, Captain. Maybe that
boat came here from a larger ship,
to get water and provisions.
No, that's impossible. Fishing is not
alowed within 50 miles of this place.
Then how did that boat get here?.
It's just one more mystery
we can add to the others.
Maybe we should eat some of these?.
That's not a
good idea. I'm no botanist,
but the fruit
here has an unusual look.
The radiation?.
Yes.
Do you agree, doctor?.
It's better not to risk it,
although eating meat in this
heat isn't a good idea, either.
Yeah.
We don't have
the utensils, anyway.
I think we should keep moving.
When it gets cooler,
I'm heading south.
Still hoping to find Annie?.
We have to
wait for the ship anyway.
Shouldn't we set up a defense?.
I just can't figure out
who that mystery man is,
if he exists.
The captain is right. I agree with
him. We have to try to stay alive.
Yeah, we're not gonna just
sit here and wait to be killed.
Lemuan, there's some
whiskey left. W ant a drink?.
No, thank you.
You know I don't drink.
My God, what a barbaric situation!
Look what's become of us.
We're like wild
animals trying to survive.
You're losing
your dignity too, eh?.
I suppose that's
easy for you to do.
Depends on the
circumstances, Lemuan.
Find any good ones?.
Up to now,
I've just destroyed my hands.
Want some?.
I'm sweating already.
Your loss.....
Be careful,
you could get drunk.
Afraid I'll
lose my respect for you?.
Wait, I'll take care of it.
Hey,
where'd you learn to do that?.
Where do you think?.
Sorry I asked.
Come on. Fuck me?.
No, thank you.
Why, you afraid?.
Drink and you'll feel better.
Wouldn't you like to fuck a countess?.
It might be your last chance.
Tomorrow we might all be dead...
dead! Understand?.
Benoit!! Now I understand.
That was your boat I found.
Who did this to you?.
A cross between monster and a
man. He was dressed in rags.
C'mon, I'll take you to our camp.
No, Captain.
That bastard broke
every bone in my body.
Let me die in peace.
You'd better go rescue the woman.
Woman?.
What woman are you talking about?.
The dark-skinned girl.
She was a member of the expedition.
Where is she?.?.
Up there, in a cave. Listen to me,
Captain. Don't go up there alone!!
Where is it?.
I don't know.
We'd better hurry.
Let's go.
Get behind me!
No, Demaduro, no!!
Let's go!
We're out of gas, water and food.
I'm afraid the current
is taking us to God knows where
far from the shipping lanes.
It's so unfair. We escape from that
monster, only to end up like this.
You know what
you do in a case like this?.
Just make believe
that everything is OK.
Oh, really?.
Sure, my love. How would you
like a nice continental breakfast?.
Scrambled eggs with
2 big slices of bacon.
You're so silly. God, what l
wouldn't give for a meal like that!
Then God bless
the captain of that ship.
Hey! We're over here!!
-We're here!
-Help us!!
Over here! Help us!