Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
A SHORT FILM ABOUT KILLING
Screenplay
Directed by Krzysztof Kieslowski
Throwing away Floor cloths?
They can be useful.
Someone flung it at me.
It hit you?
No.
Haven't you seen anyone
carrying this?
I don't like cats.
They're as unreliable as men.
Is it a good film?
No, it's boring.
What's it about?
It's about love,
but it's boring.
Besides, it's only showing
in the afternoon.
What are you doing?
Removing my white hair.
Where can I find a taxi?
Royal Castle Square.
Hello.
Mr Balicki?
Come in, please.
Would you like a portrait?
How much do you charge?
Two thousand.
Is it long to make one?
What do you mean?
It's not my time you pay for.
You pay
For my talent.
Do you have a talent?
No.
Can you make shoes?
Raise a tree?
A tree?
Yes, I can.
No need to worry then.
Royal Castle Square?
Straight ahead.
I'm trying to think about
how I should answer that.
I've been asked
that question twice.
When I was at college,
the answer was easy.
Then four years ago, right here,
I wasn't so sure anymore.
And now...
it's a good question.
Why do I want to become a lawyer?
Shall I give an honest answer
or shall I say
what I'm supposed to?
We want to know you.
To put it briefly, I don't know.
I'm attracted to...
In the past 4 years, I've seen...
It's a job
which we could say
has a social function.
It's important
that it should be useful.
But what I think
I like the most about this job
is that...
If I succeed in this exam,
I'll be able to meet
and to understand people
I'd never meet
if I'd chosen a different job.
That's my motivation.
I think that as we grow older,
the answer becomes
all the more elusive.
Every man wonders
about the meaning of his job.
I think the further we go,
the more we doubt.
The goods, Chief.
Hurry up, Beata.
Hello.
Go away,
you're scaring the pigeons!
Will you go away?
Are you free?
I'm washing it, see?
We'll wait, it's cold.
In your words, can you explain
the principle
of overall prevention?
Basically,
it concerns not so much a convict
as the other people
so that they don't end up
like that convict.
- Shall I be more specific?
- Yes.
It's about how
the acts of a Convict,
or rather of convicts,
affect other people.
It simply involves instilling fear
into people.
That's what we read
in the Penal Code.
I don't appreciate
your ironic tone.
It's a questionable argument
used to justify
a cruel punishment,
often unfair.
Could you support your thesis
with a classical quotation?
"Since Cain, no punishment
"has been capable
"of improving the world."
- Shall I name the author?
- It won't be needed.
Chief made a mistake
with your account.
Do you fancy a ride, Miss?
My wife made it.
You want it?
Eat up!
Hello.
I have...
You're the plumber?
No.
I thought you were.
I have a photo.
Could you
blow it up?
The crease mark will stay.
That's okay.
All right.
Excuse me.
Can we really tell
From someone's photo
if they're dead or not?
Someone tried to fool you.
- How's things?
- Couldn't be better.
The last number?
Seventeen.
I have that one.
Sixteen.
Sixteen? That close?
fifteen then.
You always fill them out carefully.
Personally, I like order.
Your luck is in.
How much did you get last month?
412.
And 1 200 in the autumn.
Last week, you got 46.
- Adding all that up...
- I'm getting by.
But I wish I could...
Well...
You wish...
Ours is the best club!
We support the best club!
Mr Balicki.
I am very pleased to tell you
you've passed.
After your four-year apprenticeship,
you will be a fellow lawyer.
Congratulations.
All you have to do
is take oath.
I passed my exam!
I'm a lawyer!
Stop fooling around.
Get on!
German?
from Bulgaria?
I can tell your fortune.
Spare me some change,
For my child.
You'll leave the country.
No!
I'm not afraid of anything.
Let me read your hands.
I'll tell the truth.
All right, do it.
- A tea.
- We've none left.
- What do you have?
- Coffee, pastries.
A coffee and a pastry, then.
- Which one?
- A choux pastry.
Not that one, that other one.
Your line of fortune
is long and strong.
Two children.
When?
There are moments in life
when anything seems possible.
Your route is clearly
laid down before you.
That's how I felt
when I finished school.
That's how I feel today.
When you cross a certain threshold,
there's a moment
when you feel
it all depends on you.
Exactly.
You know what I think?
No, I never do.
People will love you.
Just like I love you now.
Are you by any chance going
to Mokotow?
No, to Wola.
We're in a hurry.
To Mokotow.
Where were they going?
To Wola.
Calm down.
He's a bit nervous.
What is it?
Nothing.
It may not be that easy.
Wind up the window, please.
It's cold.
Turn left here.
I could go straight ahead.
I prefer this way.
As you wish.
Stop, it's over there.
- You can't drive on.
- I wasn't going any further.
Jesus!
Please, I beg you...
I beg you.
I'll tell you
about a brave little lion
Whose courage grew bigger every day
All the other lions
Said to his face
That a lion must always have
the heart of a lion
I understand very well
and I like to be brave,
But sometimes I get so scared,,.
Is it still open?
Jacek? Come in!
Hi, Beata!
Are you going to bed?
Yes, very soon.
Come out a second,
I have something to show you.
Do I have to change?
No, you don't have to.
- Is it far?
- It's right here.
I told you. Get in.
You wanted to go somewhere.
Now we can.
You said you had a customer
who went to the mountains.
Her husband...
We can go to the mountains.
We'll put down the seats.
I have some blankets.
The weather will warm up.
Where did you get that car?
This session is closed.
Is this the end, Mr Balicki?
The end.
It's me.
I lost it.
Through and through.
I don't know.
Perhaps I'll go for walk.
No, don't come.
How are you?
Have you slept?
Good.
Yes. Bye.
Excuse me.
Jacek!
I know this is not usual practice...
Indeed... it's not usual practice.
I wanted to ask you,
now that it's over.
Would things have been different
if he'd been defended
by a famous lawyer
instead of me?
Absolutely not.
My summation didn't...
Perhaps if I had...
Your summation
was a wonderful indictment
of the death penalty.
The sentence
couldn't have been different.
You didn't make any mistakes,
not as a lawyer
Of as a Man.
Despite the awful
present circumstances,
it was a pleasure to meet you.
In this case,
I could have imagined
a better judge.
That sentence...
it's my responsibility.
- Does that console you?
- No.
You know, when that lad explained
how he'd rolled the rope
around his hand in that bar,
- I was there.
- Where?
In that bar,
at the same time.
I had just taken my law exam.
Also...
I could have done something.
You're too sensitive to do this jab.
Too late to change that.
Yes, you've become
a bit older today.
Goodbye.
The governor will see you.
- How are you?
- It's hot.
Hello.
The curtain's stuck.
Clean the floor a bit.
Come in.
Everything's ready, sir.
Call number 24.
He's coming.
Thank you.
I knew it.
So did I.
Yes, I know.
You'll have half an hour.
Half an hour.
Okay.
Take the lawyer there.
Can I leave my briefcase here?
Hello, Mr Balicki.
I'm going to see him.
He wants to talk to me.
Quite a hard duty.
Hard indeed.
It's my first time.
I hope it'll be your last one.
Mr Balicki.
It may not be the best time
for this,
but I hear you've had a son.
Congratulations.
Yes.
Not very long ago.
Thank you.
Did you want to see me?
Yes.
Have you seen my mother?
I have.
Was she crying?
Yes, she was.
Did she ask... far anything?
Did she say anything?
No.
All she did was cry.
Sit down.
Could you...
see my mother once again?
When it's all over?
Of course I can.
I thought I'd ask you because...
at the court you called me...
You called me : "Jacek".
I called you...
I wanted to...
I don't know what I wanted.
I'm almost twenty-one,
but when you called me,
I nearly cried.
I'd spoken,
in court...
I don't know.
I wasn't listening.
It was when you called me.
They were all
againSt me,
just like everybody here.
They're against what you did.
That's the same thing.
So you want me
to see your mother.
Yes, to tell her
to bury me next to my father.
Can I be buried in a cemetery?
Yes.
The priest they sent said I could.
Naturally.
Okay, next to My father
there's still
a burial plot,
it was supposed to be my mother's.
Ask her to give it to me.
Yes?
Yes, sir.
The governor asks
if you're through.
Not yet.
You were saying?
I can't remember.
You were saying
there are three burial plots.
Yes, three.
My father rests there, then Marysia,
and there's a third one.
Marysia was buried there
Five years ago.
She was run over by a tractor.
At home, in the country.
She was about
to finish primary school.
She was twelve years old.
finishing primary school.
I was with a friend of mine
who was a tractor driver.
He was a friend.
We'd been drinking.
Wine and vodka.
Then he went and ran her over.
On a field, in undergrowth.
Sometimes I wonder...
if she hadn't died,
perhaps...
I wouldn't have left.
She was my sister.
I had three brothers and a sister.
Only one sister.
She was...
She was my favourite one.
She liked me a lot too.
Everything could have been
different.
But then, I had to go.
I had to leave the village.
I didn't want to leave.
If I'd stayed, perhaps...
You wouldn't be here now.
Things could have
turned out different.
The governor and the deputy
want to know if you're finished.
Tell them I'll never say
I'm finished.
You'll never say that!
Never.
We bought the land
because Marysia liked trees.
She liked trees and green.
That evening,
she was going to walk in the forest.
Do you have the sentence?
It's all there.
Let's go.
You can leave your briefcase here.
Bring out the convict.
The deputy tells you to finish it.
In my stuff,
there's a receipt
From a photo store.
I had a photo blown up,
but I had no time to pick it up.
Could you take the blow-up
to my mother?
What's in it?
It's her first Communion.
I took it with me.
I creased it.
Let's go.
Mr Balicki.
I don't want to go.
Last and first names.
Lazar Jacek.
Date of birth?
March 17th, 1967.
Parents' first names?
Jan and...
Lucia.
I'll read the sentence.
"In the name of
the People's Republic of Poland,
on the 27th of April 1987,
"the court, after the hearing of
Jacek Lazar's case,
"accused of having
"on the 10th of March 1986,
in Warsaw,
"murdered Waldemar Rekowski,
"found him guilty
"and by virtue of article 148
paragraph 1
"and of article 44,
paragraph 2 of the Penal Code
"sentenced him to death
"and stripped him
of his civic rights.
"The Supreme Court upheld
the sentence.
"The State Council refused a pardon.
"Therefore,
the sentence shall be executed."
Cigarette?
No filter, please.
His hands!
Execute the sentence.
Pull it! Keep going.
Enough.
Subtitles by Evaldo de Medeiros
Processed by C.M.C. - Paris
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player