All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
- What is this?- It's a list of 28
incumbent Gookmin Party assemblymen.
-So?-Most are too old, or with
bad legislative track records,
or with previous corruption records.
By looking at
the list, I am pretty sure
that it's a "hit list".
A hit list?
It's a list of people who won't be
getting the nomination next election.
Probably due to someone's mistake,
I think the list was leaked.
But your name is also on it.
D Group List... Jin Sang Pil.
Timing and Subtitles brought to
you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd
Next year, I will be running
in Gyeongjae City District.
I am going to get
the nomination.
Absolutely.
Aide Choi, what are you
doing there by yourself?
Come out here and look!
Yes, Assemblyman.
What Aide Seo said about
this, is it for real?
Is it really a hit list?
It's too early to
make that conclusion.
It could be a document that idle
aides or reporters made for fun.
Right? Huh? This
isn't it, right?
This... this is a fake.
If this is really the hit list, then
it was made by Secretary General Baek.
Right?
But my name shouldn't be here.
My name being here doesn't
make any sense, right?
Ah, yes.
That makes sense too.
That is what I'm saying, right?
Where did you pick this up to disturb
me at the beginning of the day?
Why are you doing this? Huh?
Everyone, don't worry about
this and work, okay?
Where did you pick
up this trash...
Aigoo, really...
Assembly~Episode 7~
No matter how I look at it,
it seems for real.Episode 7
With the exception of our
old man, everyone is
just the perfect candidate
for replacement.
Aide Seo, why do you keep
saying that and worrying us?
I am a person who has
experienced no less than
5 general elections
in the Assembly Hall.
Do you think I've seen a hit list just
once or twice?Who are you glaring at?
When I first saw it, I just
got that feeling right away.
- Aide Choi.- Yes.
Can't you find out if the
list is for real or not?
Whether it is in the
Blue House or in the
Party, there is no one
that you do not know.
I don't think it's a matter that even you,
Secretary Oh, should be concerned about.
Please just do your job well.
How can I work when I
can't focus on it?
Why do you worry
yourself needlessly?
If Aide Choi is that relaxed about it, this
is a fake, fake.Don't concern yourself.
That is because Aide
Choi is out of it.
Hello, Assemblyman Park.
I really enjoyed looking at the
hit list with Jin Sang Pil on it.
Our Secretary General Baek, you
were a very decisive person!
I didn't know you would answer
me in such a firm manner.
I am sure I don't know what
you are talking about.
You can speak to me
honestly.I'm not one
who secretively records
conversations.
At any rate, I trust that you will
gladly join the creation of a
new special committee to improve
the party nomination system.
Yes, of course. Print the
committee member appointment
certificates right now
and hand them out!
Yes!
You have a meeting request from the
party members on the hit list.
If it's about that, there is
no reason I should see them.
Yes, I understand.
He's coming!
Secretary General, have you seen the member
list spreading in the Assembly Hall?
Yes, I have heard about it.
Some are suspecting
it to be a hit list.
Well, that doesn't
sound like the kind of
question I should be answering.
Yes, then...
- Secretary General!-
Just one word, please!
The party's official briefing
will be given soon.Please wait.
As stated thus far...
the mysterious list with the names of
28 incumbent Gookmin Party assemblymen
is nothing more than a mysterious
document with no known source or purpose.
Korean citizens, there is no such thing
as a hit list in our Gookmin Party.
A death note where the moment
one's name is written, the
person comes to an end --
this only exists in movies.
... the moment one's name
is written, the person
comes to an end -- this
only exists in movies.
What do you think about
my ad-lib, death note?
Good.
You're a genius when it comes to
paying perfunctory compliments.
Since I have done
the damage control,
please come clean with me.
About what?
That list... is the
hit list, right?
Assemblywoman Hong, there is a
saying that ignorance is bliss.
It's just that I'm curious...
How about...
each knowing just enough
to do their given job?
Secretary General, why such a
stern face at a mere joke?
Making me feel awkward...
Yes, In Kyung.
I would like to see you
briefly about that hit list.
But the party's official
comment about that has been
released already. That it is
just a mysterious document.
I know that list is
the real hit list.
I also know that you leaked it.
Why are you claiming
that list is a hit list?
Because the list of 28
circulating in the Assembly
Hall, with the exception
of Assemblyman Jin,
exactly coincides
with the document
of 27 party members unfit
for subsequent nominations
that you presented to the
Blue House late last year.
Right before leaving the Blue
House, my duties included working
for the (BH'S) secret network
regarding the legislature.
I even had access to some
classified documents
going directly to the
VIP (PRESIDENT).
The Elder has cared about you a lot since
the days of his presidential candidacy.
I forgot.
If Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's name had not been
there, I would have thought
that the BH leaked it.
But, as long as Assemblyman
Jin's name is added there,
it was you who
deliberately leaked it.
Assemblyman Park Choon Seob
came demanding omission of
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil from
the next nomination round.
I couldn't give him
a written promise.
So I answered with the
hit list instead.
Answer, did you say?
The reason Assemblyman Jin
became the Anti-BH faction's
target was that he had
followed your instructions.
Casting away a person like
an old shoe after all his
purposes have been served... was
that your kind of politics?
In Kyung!
Jin Sang Pil... the moment
he was chosen by me,
he was doomed to be cast away.
You've known that too.
Never even in my dream, did
I think that he would be
thrown away in this kind of
mean, underhanded manner!
Did you ask me to become
Assemblyman Jin's aide
so you could show me
this side of yourself?
Because at that time,
I didn't know that Assemblyman
Jin would so quickly
aim for a nomination for
the next general election.
The reason Assemblyman
Jin is overly obedient
to me... is probably
the party nomination.
If Assemblyman Jin really
wanted to do something
at least somewhat meaningful
as an assemblyman
he should not have had his
heart set on a nomination.
I heard you well.
I know it's very hard on you.
If it's too hard, it's
okay for you to quit now.
You did as much as you could.
Do you know what is
really hard for me?
That my admiration for you
is fading with each passing day.
At least the Baek Do
Hyeon whom I know...
ought not be this
kind of person.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Why do you keep looking at it?
It just bothers me a little bit.
Aide Seo's words sound
right at times.
Aide Choi said it wasn't.
Don't pay attention to it.
Oh, right, Assemblyman!
A group called Gyeongjae City
Youth Volunteer Soldiers...
It's time for their field trip
to the National Assembly.
Youth Volunteer Soldiers?
Secretaries Kim and
Park are out there.
- Why don't you go and
say hello?- Okay.
Oh, right, you know those balloons
we got last Children's Day?
The kids would love them
if we give those out.
The place where you are standing
right now is the Rotunda Hall.
The yellow in the middle of
the floor represents the sun.
And the 24 lines signify
sunrays and at the same time
that the lines
converge to be one.
Namely, they symbolize
the citizens' unity.
When assemblymen
only keep fighting,
how can the citizens unite?
You said they were youth
volunteer soldiers?
During the Korean War (OCCURRED
1950-1953), they were youth soldiers
who participated in the battle
to defend Gyeongjae City.
Why are you wearing
glasses, all of a sudden?
Oh, I wear them once in a while.
Hmm, you wear them
once in a while?
Now, we will go to see
the main assembly floor.
Shall we?
Look here, this balloon is
deflated.Give me another one!
Me, too!
Line up, line up please!
Bon appétit!
Please move. It's hot.
It's good.
- Thank you!- One
more egg for you.
Thank you!
- Have a lot.- Don't
leave any food.
Yes.
Eat a lot.
Elders, this is not
much, but please enjoy.
Yes.
I've tried the Assembly Hall food, and
it was a lot better than I expected.
It looks delicious.
Actually, my heart is full
of the wish to treat you to
a swanky meal even if I have
to borrow money to do it.
But for an assemblyman to buy
his constituents something...
they say that is not acceptable,
that it is illegal.
You don't have to buy us meals.
No matter what, just try
hard to do good politics.
Yes, I will keep that in mind.
Don't get involved in fights.
Yes, I will bear that in
mind.I will work hard.
By the way, in the newspaper,
I saw your name on the hit list.
Oh! That is... I should
have worked hard.
But I didn't do very well,
so my name made the list.
Since my school days,
I was a troublemaker and my name often
made lists. I'm an expert at it.
No! No! A national assemblyman should
not be too hung up on a nomination.
Don't get too timid
and just work hard.
Okay, I will never get timid.
I'll work hard. I won't
get timid, really.
Yes, fighting!
- Did you come with
your grandfather?- Yes.
Eat a lot.
By the way, Ahjussi, are
you an assemblyman, too?
No.
This ahjussi is that ahjussi
over there's secretary.
Goodbye.
It's over.
Oh, our pretty Da
Jeong worked hard.
Everyone worked hard.
Let's go inside.
Oh, Assemblyman!
That granddaughter of the
general affairs manager
grandfather asked me earlier
to give this to you.
That little kid?
Yes.
When it rains, my grandfather cannot
go to the Senior Citizens' Center.
Please help.
- We are back.-
You are back?
Did Aide Choi go somewhere?
- She went home early just
now.- Went home early?
Yes, she seemed a bit
under the weather.
Why under the weather,
all of a sudden?
- Please look
into this.- Yes.
Please look into this properly.
Do not worry.
And don't pick up trash.
But is Aide Choi very sick?
But, Assemblyman, this... I think
you gave me this by mistake.
Assemblyman...
Resignation
Who is it?
It's me, So Min!
Why did you come?
Just one look and I can
tell you're playing hooky.
Assemblyman... what
brings you here?
We came to comfort you in your sickness,
not knowing it was a sham illness.
Come in.
You have all kinds of things.
Drink this a bit.
You shouldn't have...
Are you feeling better?
I'm not sick. I was just
a little bit tired...
A working person goes home early just
because she feels a little tired...
Where is that? The
comptroller's office?
I should tell them to
dock your pay for today.
It's not a workplace that pays you
for overtime, either, you know?
But why have you tagged
along, Secretary Kim?
Just because...
Oh! Isn't this Secretary
General Baek's photo, this?
This is Secretary
General Baek, right?
Oh, right, it is
Secretary General Baek.
Oh, you two went out together.
Aide Choi liked
Secretary General Baek.
Stop joking around, please.
And in an unmarried
maiden's house,
there being a married
man's photo... How
does this work?Is it
okay, legally speaking?
She says it's because she admires
him, not because she likes him.
Hey, Song So Min!
What admiration?
She wants to become a
politician like Secretary
General Baek in the
future or whatever.
You want to die?
Secretary Kim.
Yes?
So Min fancies you.
No, that's not true.
- I will bring some
snacks.- I said no!
- Assemblyman!- Yes?
About Aide Choi...
She's a returned single (DIVORCEE)
but pretends to be a maiden.
Hey!!!
I should've known...
I am telling you clearly so
that you won't misunderstand.
My taste runs
towards idol types.
So don't be concerned and such.
That's a relief. Let's be
on easy terms from now on.
What? Ah...
Really, Aide Choi, I'm not
going to leave you alone...
What did you say?
What? I'm just washing
the dishes...
But, why did Aide
Choi get a divorce?
A long time ago, when she got sloshed
and during her drunken snivelling,
I kind of heard, but
if I divulge that,
I will really die.
Please bring the
dishes from the table.
Resignation (IN CHINESE)
Resignation
With Secretary General Baek...
How did you get to know him?
I joined a circle at college
thinking it was a study group.
But it turned out to be a
bunch of demonstrators.
He was a senior sunbae
in that circle.
Oh, so you go back a long way...
What each of you are thinking,
you must both know at a glance.
That's right... since it's
been over 20 years...
I did think that I
knew in my own way...
That hit list... Is that,
by any chance, for real?
So you got upset and you went home
early.Is it something like that?
No.
It looks about right.
It's for real, right?
Well, I'm telling you no,
so why do you keep asking?
If it's not, then just forget it.
Why get mad?
Do you have a steaming liver (ORGAN
THOUGHT TO BE CONNECTED TO ANGER)?
If my liver is steaming,
yours must be on fire.
I will pay a visit
to Gyeongjae City.
It's not even the weekend. During the term,
why are you visiting your constituency?
There is a little business.
At one time, more than ten
households lived here.
But now, everyone has left
and only that elder and his
granddaughter live here.
Every rainy season, the elder
cannot go to the Senior
Citizens' Center because
of the swollen stream.
And the little kid cannot
go to kindergarten.
He had petitioned the
City Hall a few times,
but it didn't work so he
brought the matter to me.
Yes, we will try and
review this positively.
Really?
Aigo, our mayor is
really decisive!
Is the mayor so decisive,
to begin with?
Yes.
Then I will rely
on you and leave.
Aigo, our Mr. Mayor
is really firm.
You don't have to see me out.
Be healthy.
Yes.
Oh, really? People from the
City Hall have been there?
Yes, Aigo, you must be busy.
Why bother yourself with
something like this?
Aigo, I should bother. I'm
a national assemblyman.
Somehow...
do you think a bridge
will be laid there?
Of course, just count on me. I
will lay one there no matter what.
Thank you for sure.
Yes, Elder, goodbye.
Have you seen me scoring one?
The City Hall...
could have been there just to show
their face.You spoke too hastily.
Let's live a trusting life, huh?
That mayor is such a
big-hearted person.
And if the City Hall
was just putting on a
show, do you think I will
sit still and watch?
If you don't sit still, then do you plan
to demonstrate in front of the City Hall?
Why would I demonstrate
when I can just ask
Secretary General Baek
to put in a word for me?
Do you know how much I helped
Secretary General Baek with things?
You don't know, Aide Choi.
But we are on such terms
that I can easily ask him
for this kind of favor.
I guess the hit list
is scary, after all.
Lately, I can't see even
one of your party members'
faces.
Everyone is holed up in their constituency
and not thinking of coming out to Yeouido.
Assemblymen who are unsure of getting a
party nomination... All they can do is
build their recognition
with their constituents.
Some assemblymen daily deliver a score of
congratulatory messages at local events.
Seen from that light, I
think you are amazing.
What do you mean?
Not just a hit list, but you are
about to encounter the Grim Reaper.
But you are so laid back.
You mean Oh Sae Chang, the former
governor of Gyeonggi Province?
He is supposed to return home soon after
a 2-month research program in England.
I know.
I guess at least you did
some secret investigation.
If you are aware, then be on your
toes a bit more.Oh Sae Chang...
will throw down his gauntlet in your
constituency as soon as he returns.
I'm saying this because I've
heard things from our big boss.
As I've said before, I'm confident no
matter whom I go against next year.
This kid is saying this
because he has never lost.
What?
You are a second-termer
in a row.
But I'm a skip-skip-second-termer
with a loss in between.
An assemblyman who has
lost an election?
Aish, I think I'm
going to cry...
Don't regret later and
come up with a plan.
Current Status of D-Class Elected
Gookmin Party Assemblymen
How on earth...
could the names of the people mentioned
in this document have been leaked?
With the exception of Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, everyone is in here!
I'm investigating how
it came to be revealed.
It's an intolerably
heavy weight to bear.
Let's do away with
this document now.
Is that the Elder's will?
It's my will.
Then, that is rather
insulting to me.
What?
That document, when I took
the office of the secretary
general overseeing the
party's nomination matters,
I prepared and submitted
it to the VIP
with the determination to
replace all the outdated
and corrupt members within
the party no matter what.
- Secretary General Baek!- If
that document is revealed,
my political career may well be threatened.
Fully knowing that,
I made it and submitted it for the
party and the administration!
But, let's do away with it...
Never!
Never will I stand for it!
That person...
What are you going to do about our
Anti-BH members on the hit list?
Right now, there are not only one
or two people who have keeled over
from the high pressure and it's not
like they can gripe to someone.
Let's ask the investigating
authorities to investigate right away
who leaked the list.
Let it be. There are a lot of
Pro-BH members on there too.
You are so laid back.
Not just assemblymen
need to undergo changes.
Factions should undergo changes,
too, to secure new talents.
Those people, now,
are our family who have
shared the same bottom
of the pecking order
for the last 4 years.
We should keep the keepers,
and use up losers
to up the ante.
Look at Baek Do Hyeon. He unhesitatingly
bets on the likes of Jin Sang Pil.
It was like a 3-year old
indigestion going away.
Jin Sang Pil, that
mannerless son of a bi*ch.
Jin Sang Pil is just
spit in the sea.
Even though we were left off the
hit list, neither I nor you
can be sure of next
year's election.
If we can't drag
down Baek Do Hyeon,
we may end up, hand in hand,
looking for appropriate
nursing homes.
Ai, that...
Just a minute.
FROM AIDE: Assemblyman, I have an
urgent matter to report to you.
Why were you in such a flutter?
What information came in?
This is it.
To Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho
Current Status of D-Class Elected
Gookmin Party Assemblymen
D-class?
Without the sender's information,
just naming you as the recipient,
this was sticking out from
the incoming mail box.
A report to the BH
(BLUE HOUSE)...
REFERENCE: DH...
Baek Do Hyeon...
Now, you're dead meat.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Yes, Assemblywoman Hong.
Secretary General, a big disaster.
Can you search news right now?
What is it?
Kang Sang Ho has just
revealed a strange document.
If there is no dissent,
we will retain this item
in the subcommittee
and address it in the next term.
Assemblyman! Assemblyman, this...
here...
Kang Sang Ho, 'Gookmin
Party's Hit List Is the
Work of Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon!'
Assemblyman Jin,
Assemblyman Jin!
We are in the middle of the subcommittee
review right now.Please concentrate.
In connection with the alleged hit list
of 28 current Gookmin Party assemblymen,
Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho has
come forward with a claim that
Secretary General Baek Do
Hyeon personally created it.
You see on this document
IT SAYS 'REFERENCE: DH'?
In other words, DH means
that Secretary General
Baek Do Hyeon personally
created it...
- and submitted it to
the Blue House.- See?
I told you it was
the real hit list!
- Be quiet, please!- According to the
document revealed by Assemblyman Kang,
each of the 28 assemblymen
on the hit list
was not only classified
under being too old,
unfit for legislative
activities, or against
the constituents' popular
opinion categories,
but also was evaluated on
their legislative activities.
In particular, Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil,
who entered the Assembly after
the recent by-election,
was evaluated as unfit for legislative
activities due to the incidence of
his disappearance and opposition
to the supplementary budget bill.
Meanwhile, Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon, who
has been accused of
creating the hit list,
is not making any statement.
But Assemblywoman Hong Chan
Mi, one of his closest
associates, is strongly
denying the allegation.
If it is not his own handiwork,
he must disclose very
clearly from whom, how, and
through which channels
he came to receive
this document...
The Gookmin Party, due
to the hit list scandal,
is getting mired in a confusion where even
its immediate future is unforeseeable.
Where is the Secretary
General, right now?
He is resting at
a certain place.
He has asked you to respond
to the media until
he makes his own
special communication.
Never mind the media. The
assemblymen on the hit
list are about to tear up
the Secretary General.
Assemblyman Jin!
Where is Secretary General Baek?
Where is he, Secretary
General Baek?!
The hit list... in the
end, it was for real.
At this rate, our Aide Choi will
be put in a very difficult spot.
-Hello?-Aide, there
is big trouble.
Aide!
What happened? What
about the Assemblyman?
Over there.
Assemblyman.
In Kyung, it's good that you are here.
Take the Assemblyman and leave.
I am going to meet with Secretary General
Baek, so take your employees and leave.
Didn't I tell you Secretary
General left the office?
He's going to come
to work tomorrow!
I can stay the night here and see him
tomorrow morning.You go home, too.
Assemblyman Jin!
How many times have I told you that the
document from Kang Sang Ho was fabricated?
The one in deeper trouble than you
right now is the Secretary General.
Ah, I'm sure he is.
Assemblyman, I will try to get you an
appointment with the Secretary General,
so please come back to the
office with us for now.
What are you doing?
Assemblyman, let's go.
Let go of this.
Let me go!
Nothing is going to happen,
so all of you leave work.
Assemblyman.
I don't care, so do as you wish.
All staff members on
duty, please come in!
Escort him out as
courteously as possible.
Yes. Assemblyman, excuse us.
What are you, staff members,
doing to the assemblyman?
Aide Choi! If he does not leave right
away, he may get criminally prosecuted.
Let this go!
Tell him that I will
be back for sure.
Okay?
It seems like the assemblymen
on the hit list will form an
emergency measures committee
and start acting collectively.
Assemblyman, you should join the emergency
measures committee, too, for now.
I don't know what you
think, Aide Choi,
but I think that document
Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho
disclosed... was made by
Secretary General Baek.
Assemblyman, this is not the
time to be hung up on that.
Why is Secretary General
Baek doing this to me?
After giving me a party
nomination and having
a very hard time himself
because of that...
why, this late in the game,
why is he doing this to me?
Huh? Can't you guess the reason?
I will run, next year,
from Gyeongjae District.
No, I can't.
Wow, really, politics... this...
is really icky. Wow, it
is horrible, isn't it?
This is why... This is where that
word "political" originates.
Aide Choi, what is it that you like about
this so much that you work so hard?
Huh?
I will be outside.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
I am in front of the Gookmin
Party headquarters where an
emergency supreme council
meeting is about to be held.
In the lobby of
the headquarters,
the staff members of the
assemblymen on the hit list
are holding a sit-down
demonstration.
Those assemblymen issued an emergency
joint statement this morning
and, while calling for Secretary
General Baek's resignation,
also made a demand to
the party leadership to
expel Secretary General
Baek from the party.
In the event their
demands are not met,
some of them are taking a hard line
that they will even defect as a group.
Thus, all eyes are on the decision the
Gookmin Party leadership will make.
Meanwhile, Secretary General
Baek Do Hyeon, who has
been implicated as the
author of the document,
is still not making any
public appearances.
The Anti-BH assemblymen held a meeting
at the National Assembly Hall
and are discussing whether
they would report Secretary
General Baek for an
election law violation.
Secretary General Baek
Do Hyeon, who has been
on a roll, as President Seo
Dae Han's Crown Prince,
is facing the biggest
political crisis since
his entry into the
world of politics.
This has been, from the
Gookmin Party Headquarters
shrouded in a perilous
sense of crisis,
Reporter Park Gwan Jo
of KBC News reporting.
Gookmin Party
Assemblymen, are you really going
to disrupt the meeting like this?
Have your meeting!
Who is stopping you?
How dare you talk down
to the Party Leader!
Shut up and just
start the meeting!
I won't leave you alone if you don't
kick out Baek Do Hyeon from the party!
Why does Secretary General Baek have
to get expelled from the party?
That guy made the hit list!
Don't give me your nonsense.
Secretary General Baek is innocent.
Hong Chan Mi! You stay quiet!
Where do you think you
are, butting in as the
little girl that you are...
Ah, please, just, let's
be quiet, really!
We came to observe the meeting, not
to disrupt it, now, didn't we?
That hit list or something,
that is a bad thing.
But everyone here, frankly speaking,
what have you done so well? Huh?
Including myself. How is this
situation different from
getting your name reported
on the blackboard
by the class representative
for being noisy
during a self-study period and
begging to get it erased, huh?
Then, let's just shut up and
stay quiet for a bit, okay?
Let's observe the meeting, okay?
We are here to
watch the meeting.
Why are you assemblymen
acting like this?
We have no intention of disrupting the
meeting at all. So take it easy and go on.
You do not have to erase my name,
so I'm just going to leave!
Assemblyman Jin!
You do all sorts of
things, really...
Wet blanket, that bastard!
- What?- Hey, Baek Do
Hyeon has appeared!
Secretary General Baek.
Before the meeting, may I
address a personal matter?
Oh? Go ahead.
Respected citizens of Korea and my
dear fellow Gookmin Party members,
I will blame everything on
my general shortcomings, and
will bury all I want to say,
all my grievances in my chest.
Instead, I have made one
grave determination.
For the sake of solidarity
and peace within the Party,
I am about to relinquish what
is, to a national assemblyman,
like a lifeline or rather,
even more precious than life.
I will...
My beloved constituency
and constituents,
who have raised me up and loved
me, a lacking person that I am...
and who have even elected me twice
to the Assembly...I will leave them.
- Secretary General! Are
you saying you will
give up your
constituency?- That is so.
Then, is there a possibility
that you will not
run for the next year's
general election?
I will take time and deliberate
on my next move that may even include
not running in the next election.
But in the short run, as the
party's secretary general,
I plan to faithfully discharge my duties,
such as improving the nomination system.
To the people and party members,
and to my constituents who have
supported me all this time...
I offer you a bow
of deep contrition.
Baek Do Hyeon Declares Relinquishment
of His Constituency...
I leaked that information
to him to fend off Oh
Sae Chang, so why are you
running away and stuff?
Assemblyman Park, the Blue
House has issued a statement
saying it supports Secretary
General Baek's decision.
Secretary General Baek must have
communicated with the
Blue House beforehand.
Since he is a prudent person...
We've taken a step back on
the spur of the moment.
But the more you think about this, doesn't
it leave a bad taste in your mouth somehow?
Secretary General Baek said he
would give up his constituency,
not that he would never run
in the next general election.
Once he makes up his mind, he will
run from anywhere in the 9 provinces
of the nation.
That's his intent.
Right? Then, comparing it to
the world of pro baseball,
this is like a major league
pitcher at the level of
Park Chan Ho coming out
on the free-agent market!
It seems we've been taken for
a ride by Baek Do Hyeon.
What do you mean, a ride?
Assemblyman Kang, you...
have only played the
part of Baek Do Hyeon's
puppet.
What?
The poll shows that your
recognition has increased 17%
and favorable opinion
about you increased 8%.
Chief Lim... Yes.
About your delivering that
document to Assemblyman
Kang Sang Ho's office...
Keep your mouth closed
and take it to your grave, okay?
I understand.
From Choi In Kyung
From disclosure of the document to
relinquishment of your constituency,
I have enjoyed your
well-scripted play.
I beg you to return to
the you of former days
who always played
fair and square.
Secretary General Baek,
let's talk for a bit.
Secretary General
must get going.
Don't butt in, when assemblymen
are talking between themselves.
I guess you are very angry.
And you don't know why?
- Well...- Wow, seriously!
Our Secretary General
Baek is incredible.
I'll just ask one question.
Why did you do such a
dastardly thing to me?
This, your words are too harsh.
Then, I will ask you
again not too harshly.
Why was I on that list?
I think you can ask
yourself about that.
Whether you are a person who
deserves to be on there or not...
So you will play off the question again
with difficult words like that...
If you feel sure of yourself, then
that list must be just trash,
but if even in your eyes, you don't
have the capacity to be an assemblyman,
then you should be
on the hit list
that I, Baek Do Hyeon, drew up.
Just a minute.
Because you spoke so reasonably
my noggin was in danger
of getting confused.
But my body commands
me to do this.
Why don't you just eat this up?
Yes, Elder.
Assemblyman Jin, the City Hall says they
won't be able to build a bridge there...
What?
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Just a minute. The
city hall people,
before they are public
servants, they are super
voters with strong influence
over the constituency.
No matter how angered you are, it's
better to deal with them with kid gloves.
Ahew, don't you trust me? Don't worry.
Let's go in.
But why are you saying you can't
build a bridge there, huh? Why?!
Well, before, you big-heartedly
went "heh heh heh"
as if you were going to
build one there right away!
What is the reason you are
saying no this late in the game?
Assemblyman, calm down first.
Did I ask you to build a Namhae Bridge (BIG
MAJOR CIVIL ENGINEERING PROJECT), huh?
So that the elder can go to the
Senior Citizens' Center, I asked
for a small stone bridge
and that is not doable?
You are saying that because you do not
know much about administrative work.
When setting aside a budget, we
have to do a cost-benefit analysis.
It has a low project feasibility score
but a high risk of getting audited.
In budget planning, projects
requiring benefit-cost analyses,
or BC analyses for short,
their eligibility and monetary
requirements are set by law.
This sort of minuscule work
is outside that frame.
See?!
What is important is the will.
We have reviewed it numerous times
after hearing from you, Assemblyman,
but we don't have the
budget to build a bridge.
Does this make any sense now,
huh?You don't have the budget?
You keep replacing the fine sidewalk
tiles season in and season out.
- And you don't have any
budget?- Assemblyman!
When you have so little
money, then this city hall
building... Why did you erect
this new city hall building?
Just look at the view! I thought
I was at a resort, you know!
But is this an office
building, this?
And I heard that the provincial assemblymen
recently went on an overseas field trip.
With what money did they go on that trip?
Did they go dutch on that trip, huh?
Well, you have the money to build
a building and go on trips!
But that, that little
stone bridge on the
elder's way to the Senior
Citizens' Center...
You won't build that one little bridge.
Does that make any sense now?!
You are just being
too much, really.
Please think a little,
think, think, huh?
Don't you think you're too much?
This evening, the assemblymen on the
hit list will have a gathering.
You'd better attend the gathering because
they will discuss the counter-plan.
Please explain the situation to Senior Kim
and try to proceed with it next year.
Who knows what will
happen to the assemblymen
listed on the hit list tomorrow?
I will still do it.
Assemblyman. Do you mean
you would make a bad
relationship with the city
because of a mere two persons?
A mere two persons? A
"mere" two persons?
Wow! Really? Aide Choi, seriously?
I am disappointed.
- Pardon?- These "mere" two
persons are not our people?
Assemblyman! Don't get
too sentimental, please.
That senior went to the war with a
gun before his mustache was growing.
He risked his life to
protect our country.
If such a man can't go to
the senior center freely,
what kind of country
does he live in?
And, how about me, who
can't make it happen?
Am I an assemblyman?
I understand your
words, Assemblyman.
But this is reality.
Byeon Seong Gi, please come
here with Secretary Kim.
What are you going to do?
For me, the reality
that you said,
I will not acknowledge it.
Here.
What kind of urgent
matter makes Assemblyman
Jin unable to
attend the meeting?
He has a very important
matter in his constituency.
He wants me to
deliver his apology.
Where is a more important
matter than this?
He probably found out
the way to get out.
N-No... It is not like that.
Anyhow, we are apologizing.
We are sorry. We are very sorry.
We are sorry.
Try once to prop it.
Hold here.
Ahh... T-That...
- What happened?
- What do you mean what
happened? I was
very badly reviled.
At this rate, the
hit-listed assemblymen will
put our Assemblyman Jin on
their hit list, won't they?
If this happens, it will
really be a big screw-up.
Aide Seo. Right now, Aide Choi is not here.
How about one game?
- Triggered (GAME
NAME)?- Call.
- Okay. Let's go.- Jacket?
Where is my jacket?
- Let's go without it.- Yes.
Give it ― Oh!!
Excuse me. Are you okay?
I almost fell down! Asshi!
Hey! Be careful!
I am sorry.
I almost fell down! Asshi!
Assemblyman Jin!
Elder, you haven't
gone to sleep yet?
- Aigoo. Now,
stop it.- Pardon?
This is not a job that you
can do in a few days.
That's right. We have no way
to do it within a few days.
What are you saying? Since we
started, we have to finish it.
Senior! Don't worry much. I
am good at this kind of work.
If you keep doing it, I will feel sorry.
So please stop it.
No. It's okay. My aide said that
an assemblyman is a
servant of the people.
Please enter the
house and go to bed.
You didn't forget it proudly.
Have you not gone to Seoul?
I am not the sort of woman who
doesn't have any loyalty.
Well...After goofing off
at some place else,
and bringing just the water,
then you are saying "loyalty".
- I have been to see
Mayor.- Pardon?
I offered him the chance to play co-leading
parts in this heartwarming story.
What is she talking about?
Assemblyman Jin!
What happened?
I told them I am working on
your story to be broadcast.
And I asked Mayor whether he will take
a villain's part or co-leading part?
Wow! As expected! Really!
You are great for the tricks.
Here! Pass them.
Give me that.
Here.
Put it here.
Here, again.
They connect them up to there?
Give me. Here.
Here you go.
Good morning!
Hi!
- Secretary Oh, please give me the schedule
after you have updated it.  - I will.
Soo Min! Is there any
news this morning?
Oh Sae Chang... he declared to
run for the National Assembly.
He will run in the constituency which
Secretary General Baek gave up.
The media deride him as a
burglarizer of empty houses.
Oh Sae Chang is said to be a
presidential-level candidate
from the opposite party.
Does he look cunning?
Don't mind someone else but
concentrate on your area.
What is this?
Project of Managing
JSP Constituency.
What is JSP?
Ahh... JSP. It's me.
Ahh. The title sounds great.
At this time, Aide
Choi looks very cool.
- By the way,
Aide Choi!- Yes.
Is it okay for you to help
me out this actively?
I am red-lined by
Secretary General Baek.
At this rate, you may
be stigmatized like me!
Secretary General Baek
is not so narrow-minded.
So turn off your worries.
You are protecting him...
Assemblyman Jin, Secretary General
is on the morning broadcast.
- Right now?-Yes.
Secretary General Baek, who became
a man in the news after overcoming
the ripple of the hit-list scandal
by giving up his constituency,
is conversing with me.
Secretary General! A lot of people are
curious about your personal life history.
Well... I... have not much to say
about my personal life history.
I am a very common person.
Is past Minister of Home Affairs Baek Seung
Ro, famous for uprightness, your father?
Yes. When my father worked as an
appointed Mayor of Gyeongjae City,
I was born in his old age.
- Was his father the mayor of Gyeongjae
City?- Is your place of birth Seoul?
Ah... A month later after I was born,
my father had to transfer to Seoul―
During the process of
transferring, my place of
birth was wrongly recorded
in the family register.
The exact place
where I was born was
Gyeongjae City, Hae Won
Myeon, Sang Won Ri.
Did you hear that,
Gyeongjae City citizens?
Why all of sudden does he
seek for his birth place?
I will be honored
if you include me.
When Secretary General said you
would do politics in generations,
I am curious as to your father's
reaction.[BAEK DO HYEON SUNBAE]
I have something to tell you,
so please come to the office.
In the interview, you
mentioned your birth place.
I have to roast the meat
when the stones are hot.
I heard the reaction of people
in Gyeongjae City was very good.
Why do you want to see me?
In a short time, a position
at the second level in
the Secretary General's
office will be available.
Transfer to that position.
If you and I are
estranged further,
we will never be able to
meet each other again.
I don't want to lose you.
No matter what, you are my
closest and oldest comrade.
I truly appreciate your words.
While going through this
time, I made a decision.
- Decision?- Until the next
election, not as your aide,
but as Assemblyman Jin's
aide, I will remain.
Hello! Please don't say
always to examine.
Every time you only examine, then
when can you listen to the people?
When are you going to listen?
Tell me.
Respectable Assemblyman
Jin's words―
Don't say respectable
as well, please!
Do you know the meaning
of respectable?
I researched that word's meaning all
night because you seem not to know it.
Respect! RES means "high" and
PECT means "admiration"!
Respect means "highly admiring."
Do you highly admire me?
When did you see
me to admire me?
You honestly don't
admire me, right?
Take this paper and look at it!
Take it! Please look at it!
I... want to make
him properly...
the next trustworthy assemblyman
from Gyeongjae City!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd
AssemblyPreview
The polls show Assemblyman Jin's support
increased from only 10% to 20%.
Gyeongjae City! Let's start.
Secretary General Baek, you will regret
your choice of this time, someday.
Did you nominate me
because of Oh Sae Chang?
Father, this time,
you have to help me.
Have you ever received a watch
from a man called Lee Taek Jo?
Yes. I then gave it
to Secretary Kim.
Inauguration of Baek Do
Hyeon Fan Club at Gyeongjae
City.- I have to fight
face-to-face with Baek Do Hyeon.
The game between you and
me was already over.
Secretary General Baek is eyeing
Gyeongjae City now isn't he?