All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Assemblywoman Hong
Chan Mi was pissed.
How are other members reacting to
Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu's enrollment?
The response was not good.
They will like it when they see the
things happening in the future.
What?
We've transferred
in the new student.
Now we have to take care
of the troublemaker.
Jin Sang Pil... I will
expel him from the party.
For sure.
Episode 15.
Gisong Island is our country's
iconic migratory bird sanctuary.
Every year, tens of thousands of
birds flock to the wintering grounds
and more than 30 of the world's
rarest species can be observed there.
What do you mean you want to
build a massive resort there?
Not there but next to it...
Vice Minister of Ministry
of Environment.- Yes.
This is an issue that is
directly related to the
raison d'être of the
Ministry of Environment.
You can never endorse the
Environmental Impact Assessment.
Man cannot be the only species
populating the earth.
Animals have to live too and plants too.
We all have to co-exist.
That way, we can achieve that
sustainable development or whatever.
As Assemblywomen Cheon said, the
Ministry of Environment should
firmly intervene.
Yes, after a careful review...
Point of order.
"Don't endorse the Environmental
Impact Assessment."
"Intervene."
These are obviously and
explicitly pejorative words.
At this rate, how can the Ministry of
Environment work in a principled way
and conduct an unbiased review?
I request your retraction
of the statements.
Assemblyman Jo, since when did you belong
to the ruling party to side with it?
Be ashamed of yourself.
Please also retract your ad hominem
statement toward a fellow assemblyman.
I too raise a point of order.
Vice Minister, please come to our Gookmin
Party to do an environmental assessment.
Excuse me?- Our party is supposedly a
newly rising migratory bird habitat.
And supposedly we have a strange bird, too,
which thinks of itself as an assemblyman.
You know ornithologists? Please
bring them on your visit.
Please come without fail.
Please I beg you.
How can you spit out whatever
comes to your mind like that?
Did you see the meeting?
Assemblyman Jo is holding it in because
he has a twinge of conscience.
What do you think would have
happened with another assemblyman?
They would have raised a
ruckus about taking you
to a disciplinary action
or suing you for slander.
Would I have said such a
thing to another fellah?
It was because Jo Woong Bird
spoke too brashly like that.
Don't even mouth the words of Gookmin
Party being a migratory bird habitat.
You must refrain from all statements
provoking the party for the time being.
Why?- With Assemblyman Jo's
enrollment, the ratio of the
ruling and opposition party
seats changed to 152:148.
The swing vote, the Indifferent-to-BH
faction's sole weapon, is gone!
So you are saying even if I'm
kicked out of the party, the
majority government by the
ruling party will be maintained.
That is right.
Even though we look very
serene on the outside, the.
Indifferent-to-BH faction is
facing a very serious crisis.
Aide Choi, it seems like you
don't know much now.- What?
Why is the swing vote the
Indifferent-to-BH faction's sole weapon?
When we have secret weapons?
Flame Man, JSP.
And Aide Choi and Kids.
The only solution
is to recruit a new
assemblyman into the
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
Unless that person is out
of his mind, who would
want to join the
Indifferent-to-BH faction?
That is right, though. If they
come, it's not like some special
benefit will be waiting... was
what you were going to say, right?
But lately, there is a
person in the Gookmin.
Party who has lost her
grasp on reality.
Who?- Who do you think it is?
Madam Hong?
Stop shoddy construction, waste of
budget, and environmental destruction!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop shoddy construction!- Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop shoddy construction, waste of
budget, and environmental destruction!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop shoddy construction, waste of budget
and environmental destruction! Stop it!
Madam Hong?
Party Leader Yoon Jeong Soo
is said to have taken umbrage
at Assemblyman Jin's migratory
bird habitat comment.
But we can't sanction him for that alone.
We may get a media whiplash that way.
Secretary General, how about
using the method I proposed...
No, that is too risky.
I'd like to hear your explanation
about the election of the
party chapter head in Seogyeong
City Gap Voting District.
Secretary Lim, you may leave.
Please have a seat.
Answer me first.-
Assemblywoman Hong.
If only you had given
me some support,
I would not have
lost so shamefully.
What is the reason
you didn't help me?
Tell Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi to schedule
meetings with Assembly news desk chairs.
But... I can't get in touch
with Assemblywoman Hong.
I think an order has been handed
down from the Blue House.
The secretary general is a
position that cannot and
must not interfere with any
election within the party.
Secretary General Baek!
Humbly accept the outcome.
The reason for your defeat
was not lack of my help.
But would it not be because you failed
to capture the party members' hearts?
I will cut to the chase. The
possibility of my getting next
year's nomination for the Seogyeong
City Gap Voting District,
is there any remaining?
No, I will revise my question.
Inside you, is there any intent
to give me a nomination?
That is enough for today.
I have done my best for you
for the last four years.
Is this how you repay me?
Assemblywoman Hong.
When you were getting pressured
by the Blue House to resign,
who appeared in this room
first and shielded you...
Have you already
forgotten about it?
You came to visit me in this room
that day in order to shield me?
Yes.
Assemblywoman Hong, you
merely got in my line.
What?- Rather than
from Jin Sang Pil,
it would be far easier to get
a nomination from the Baek Do.
Hyeon Secretariat. Such a
thoroughly political calculation.
The subject toward whom you did
your best for the last four years
was not Baek Do Hyeon, but a nomination.
Can you deny that?
For whatever term that remains, have
some faith in the voting district
and faithfully carry out your duties
as a proportional representative.
Just do it while I'm
telling you nicely.
I don't want to.- Let's do it.
I said I don't want to.- Why
don't we listen and be obedient?
You'll have to talk sense
before I will listen.
Why is this nonsense?
Go outside and ask
the secretaries...
whether seducing Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi to join
the Indifferent-to-BH
faction makes any sense.
But the only recruitable person right
now is Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi.
Still, you have to
look before you leap.
Just leap anywhere, when a viper is there?
You'll get snapped at, bitten!
Even though Assemblywoman
Hong has become too
puffed up after sudden
success at a young age,
originally she was a
rather sensible woman.
Don't just say no but
rise to the challenge.
Challenge what? I hate the idea.
Seriously!
Let's do it already.- If you are so
desperate, you can just go and do it!
Go and do it! Valiantly!
I can't do it because I'm scared. Of
getting bitten. I will never do it!
If you keep doing this, I will
disregard our ranks again.
You just try disregarding
ranks, really.
The last time, I overlooked it because you
were drunk, not because you were a girl.
And do you even know
how heavy you are...
Where are you going in the
middle of the conversation!
I have to go self-wash the car.
It's really dirty.
So why did you send Secretary Byeon on a
vacation, when we are dying from overwork!
Civil Service Exam
Prep School Signs.
Aish, really...
How can there be so many
civil servant schools?
At this rate, everyone will
become a civil servant...
Work hard.
Hyung, why does it takes days
for you to find one person?
Hyung, are you perhaps
screwing around somewhere?
Are you going to keep saying
those things that get to me?
Hey. Do you really think
Secretary Kim is around here?
To me, I don't think he's here.
He told Aide Choi by email that
he was with his buddies who studied
together for the police exam.
So, hurry up and find him. Don't
contact me until you find him. Jeez.
Hey, Sang Pil. Hey. Hey.
Why is it so hard
to find one person?
Hong Chan MiAssemblywoman.
The only person we can recruit
now is Assemblywoman Hong.
Why are you loitering around
another assemblyman's office?
I wasn't loitering. Since
you are just across from
me, I was wondering how
you were doing and such.
Step aside.
Assemblywoman Hong.
I... about the committee
chairperson election,
I know about it.
So? You came to congratulate
someone when they're mourning?
No. That's nonsense.
If you are inclined,
in Indifferent-to-BH faction,
there is this one good position.
Maybe you can come
into our faction...
What did you say?-It's not that
I am trying to belittle you.
As for me, with sincerity...
If I go in, what are you
going to do for me?
What?
Are you able to give
me a nomination?
Come on, that would
be hard for me.
What about political funds?
What about an executive party
position or an organization?
All of that I can't...
Then, shut that mouth of yours.
But honestly, if you come into
the Indifferent-to-BH faction,
guaranteed monthly income, room and board,
things like that are impossible, but...
You will suffer like
a dog but...-Stop!
But since both of us are
in the same situation...
Stop. Stop and shut your mouth!
Shut it!
If you ever start talking
about frivolous things again,
then, you'll end up dying
and I'll end up dying.
Did you see that just now?
Did you see the venomous
snake ripping me to shreds?
You knew you couldn't get her
to join, so you made me do it.
I was so scared, my smile
muscles atrophied.
Welcome, Assemblyman Kang.
So, what brings you here?
A while ago, during the
Secretary General upheaval,
I heard that there was something promised
between you and our Assemblyman Park.
Are you talking about
increasing the Anti-BH
share to 40% in next
year's general election?
Yes, as it's an
important matter,
either a memorandum
or written promise
would put him at ease, he said.
His personality is not by
nature that meticulous.
But Secretary General Baek, you've
been doing a lot of backstabbing.
That's why he's being this way. So
you'll understand and write one, right?
Assemblyman Park, Baek Do Hyeon
asks for a little more time.
I guess he's afraid that he
might fall into our trap.
Don't worry.
I will punch in at his office
every day to badger him.
And if things don't work
out, I will just punch him.
Hello.
To what do I owe this
honor, Assemblywoman Hong?
I have something important
to tell you face to face.
Oh, yes, I understand.
Then I will see you there.
By Assemblywoman Hong, do
you mean Hong Chan Mi?
She says she has something
important to say.
Important my butt.
She got used and ditched
by Baek Do Hyeon.
It's obvious that she
will ask us take her in.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Secretary General.
Why are you here?
Assemblyman Park Choon Seop asked
me to relay this message to you.
He is having a hard time as it is to
take care of current family members.
He's not in a position to
accept a new family member.
I will overlook this
for old times' sake.
But you'd better be more
judicious in the future.
Since you brought up old times,
let me just ask
you one question.
During the last 4 years, what was
I to you, Secretary General?
A butler or a trainbearer?
If neither, a dog that
barks on command?
If I have to put it into
words, probably a partner.
Who can always be contractually terminated
if she fails to meet the profit goals.
So it was like that, after all.
When I considered you a comrade.
Assemblywoman Hong, a
comrade refers to a person
who will gladly accompany you any
time through thick and thin.
If it's Choi In
Kyung, then maybe.
So till the end, you are
talking about Choi In Kyung.
That word "comrade" does not
fit you, Assemblywoman Hong.
Secretary Baek! No, you! You
underestimated me.  (The
(form of "you" rather than
his name is an insult.)
You will end up regretting this.
So it is a word that describes the
relationship between an act and the law.
Commonly, legality means...
Maybe it's because I know now.
He's a spitting
image of his father
when he was young.
They say becoming a civil servant is
like plucking a star out of the sky.
Will he do well?
Let's go now.
And not see Secretary Kim?
It's enough that I've
seen him doing well.
How can you make me work
like a dog for several
days just so that you
can see his face, huh?
I am sorry, Hyung.
Could you give me some time?
Hong Chan Mi.
Why, is Aide Choi giving
you a hard time again?
I was rude to you earlier.
I am sorry.
Aigo, well, I didn't do
anything commendable
either. Just ended
up rubbing it in...
I am sorry, too.
The reason I asked to see you
is to add to the Indifferent-to-BH
faction's track record.
Track record? What track record?
Just promise me one thing.
The information I am
about to give you now,
not to tell anyone that
you got it from me.
But at least to our Aide Choi...
I have to say it.
Then consider this
never happened.
You can turn back.
What is it, so you're like this?
Promise me first.
But I'll get into big trouble.
Okay, I will promise.
You mean it?
Have you been tricked all your life?
Yes, I will promise.
What is it?
An allegation about
cutting up the nomination
pie along the faction
lines in Gookmin Party...
You should not have done as you wished.
You should have consulted with me first!
I can no longer
do it.- Aide Choi!
I can't do it!No way!
Good morning!
Did you have a good vacation?
What vacation? I've come
back from studying to death.
Study?- You must have studied
oriental paintings (GO-STOP GAME).
Right, right.
The Assemblyman didn't
come up with you?
Assemblyman Jin is holding a press
conference in the Media Hall now.
What press conference?- How would
I know what even you don't know?
Pro-BH faction's Assemblyman
Baek Do Hyeon and.
Anti-BH faction's
Assemblyman Park Choon Seop
had a closed-door meeting during the
Secretary General's resignation scandal
and, in return for their
support of Assemblyman Baek.
Do Hyeon keeping the
secretary general position,
agreed to cut up the
nomination pie along
faction lines for the
next general election.
The gist was
to enlarge the Anti-BH's share,
which currently makes up
35% of the incumbent party
assemblymen, to 40%.
Has Assemblyman Jin
scored another one again?
That is not just one score, but
it's a mega-ton nuclear bomb.
At this juncture when a
special committee to reform
the party nomination system
is actively working,
the leaders of these two
factions were meeting
behind closed doors and
colluding this way.
In a nutshell, this was a textbook case
of the old-school, anti-democratic,
backward-looking politics
that undermines democracy.
Wake up. The people
are watching.
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon
and Assemblyman Park Choon Seop,
explain yourselves before
the people right away.
That is all.
Yes?
By this, what are you
trying to pull now?
I am in the middle
of investigating the
circumstances under which
this came to pass myself.
The circumstances or whatever, I am
telling you in no uncertain terms.
If this agreement was all for
naught, you won't be safe yourself.
Assemblyman Park, don't you think Baek
Do Hyeon passed on the information
to Jin Sang Pil so as not to
give us a written promise?
Do Hyeon, was Jin Sang
Pil's disclosure true?
Whether it's true or not,
put out urgent fires first.
Don't give reporters time to exercise
their powers of imagination.
Make an immediate announcement
that it is baseless.
How come it's quiet... Is it a situation
where she's praising him for a good job?
Don't you know Aide Choi's personality?
Wait. For an explosion in no time.
You should have consulted
with me first!- See?
So I am apologizing to you
right now because of that.
Would an apology
solve this problem?
Don't you know what a huge
mess you created just now?
I know. Wouldn't I know it?
If I don't know that, then I
am a real psycho, a real jerk.
I know, but my situation was...
Here, Aide Choi. When
you're angry, chocolate...
But who ate all of this?!
Really people, without
telling me, seriously...
Please stop being angry now.
Okay.
I will stop being angry and
ask you a different question.
This... comes from
an informant, right?
Yes.- Who is it?
It has quieted down quickly.
Today's ending is boring.
What a pity.
Why don't we all
go back to work?
You can't tell me? Does that make any
sense?- They are going at it again!
But I told you I promised that
informant not to divulge the identity.
Not to other people, but
you must at least tell me.
Don't you trust me?- I do!
I trust you so much. If not
you, whom would I trust, huh?
But that is really... A
promise is a promise.
Hurry and tell me. I have to
know who the informant is
so that I can figure out if
that is reliable information,
and if it's reliable, the
reason behind the tip-off.
I'm really sorry.
Assemblyman!
I am really truly
sorry, but a promise...
Why don't you just hit me instead?
I'm okay, just hit me!
Slap me, I'm fine with it!
Do you want to give me an ass whooping?
Do it, whoop me!
Assemblyman Park, Baek Do Hyeon
held a press conference.
The contents?- Jin Sang Pil's
statement was a total fabrication
and an epitome of mudslinging
politics that abuses his
parliamentary privilege. (I.E.
CANNOT BE SUED FOR SLANDER)
Assemblyman Park, if it
plays out like this,
our share of 40% is completely
out of the question now.
Is it Secretary General Baek?
Ah, Baek—.
Assemblyman Park, is Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil's disclosure true?
Have you agreed to a faction share
with Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon?
But reporters, Assemblyman Park
is not running away or anything.
So calm down and sit
down to drink some tea
and share some
cookies as well...
Secretary General Baek officially denied
it. What is the Anti-BH position?
Assemblyman Park, please answer.
This should be, in
a calm manner...
Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's claim is made up.
Without fail, I will ask him to bear
responsibility for this fabrication.
Joint Announcement of Baek Do
Hyeon and Park Choon Seop:
"Agreement about Gookmin Party
Nominee Shares Is Fabrication!"
Yes.- How does it feel
to get beaten up by a
partner who had been
contractually terminated?
I should rather thank you for stopping
the Anti-BH's share from getting bigger.
Is Assemblyman Park Choon Seop the
kind of person who'd tolerate a loss?
Even though not much
time remains in my term,
I will be able to watch
you losing the election,
while exchanging blows
with the Anti-BH faction.
Good luck.
Secretary General Baek, what
on earth happened here!
Explain yourself!
Are you stabbing us in
the back so as to not
to give us the written
promise, or what!
It was Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi.- What?
Hong Chan Mi?- She holds
a grudge because of
yesterday's event and she
tipped off Assemblyman Jin.
We don't have any interest
in that sort of thing.
What I want is.
Secretary General Baek's promise
to carry out the agreement.
Yes, a written promise!
Until you write us that promise, I won't
take even one step from here ever!
Aren't you two somehow
mistaken about the priorities?
What?- Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil who has
dishonored the party by
spreading a false rumor
and Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi
who fed him that false rumor!
I think taking appropriate measures
against those two comes first.
Do you intend to
drag this out again?
I'm just saying we should get rid of
weeds first to harvest better fruit.
What do you think?
Exposé politics,
obnoxious politics.
Out, Jin Sang Pil!
I, Park Choon Seop,
during the last 30 years
of my political career,
acted with rationality,
and I'm proud to say
that I've always kept my
dignity and stayed only
on the right path.
However, because of Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's irresponsible exposé,
the pride and honor that I have
built through all these years
collapsed completely.
All this time, our party
has done its part with patience
and efforts at persuasion
in dealing with Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's perpetuation of exposé politics.
But we can't approve it anymore.
We have decided to file a
complaint with our party's.
Ethics Committee against
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil shall,
before the Ethics Committee hearing,
prove to the party and citizens that what
he exposed today was not false information.
If he ignores our demand,
the Ethics Committee shall remove his
name and expel him from the party.
Exposé politics, obnoxious politics.
Out, Jin Sang Pil!
To avoid being removed
from the party,
you have to prove the
credibility of your claim.
You'll have to tell us who the
informant was in the end.
That's right. Stop
being stubborn.
You'll get kicked
out at this rate.
If they want to kick
me out, let them.
Assemblyman.
The Ethics Committee disciplinary
hearing has been scheduled.
What discipline?
Notice of the Party's
Ethics Committee.
Hearing.Expulsion of
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Wow. These people are
surely moving fast.
Are you still not going to
tell us who the informant is?
I can't help it.
Do you know what it means
to be expelled from the party?
It means the Indifferent-to-BH
faction, which has been
gaining much support from the
citizens, will cease to exist.
I still can't help it.
The informant definitely
belongs to Gookmin Party.
From this point on, log
onto the websites of
every single assemblyman
as well as the party,
and find out if anyone used
the same format as this one
for a press conference
statement.- Yes.
Even if the format's
different, if the statements
have similar text or
expressions, print them out
and bring them to me.
Understood?- Yes.
To stop Assemblyman from being expelled
from the party, we must find the informant.
Yes.
Assemblyman Jin, you
must keep your promise.
Why aren't you answering?
You promised you would never tell people
that I was the one who gave you the tip.
It's just that you asked
about the obvious.
Don't worry. Bye.
Assemblyman Jin. Assemblyman!
Who was that?
It's nothing.
What is it?
A notice from the Ethics
Committee was transmitted.
Ethics Committee?
What is it?
LIST OF MEMBERS OF THE COMMITTEE:
Hong Chan Mi, Kang Sang Ho...
Whose idea was it to put me
on the disciplinary committee
to judge Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil?
I'm not sure. Why don't you
ask the Ethics Committee?
I asked who!
It's Park Choon Seop.
Why did you include me in
the disciplinary committee?
Obviously, because what
you did was despicable.
Aren't you being too hasty
to decide it was me?
If it ever turns out
that you were Assemblyman
Jin's informant,
Secretary General and I will
issue a joint statement
I'm listening.
Assemblywoman Hong
Chan Mi, who lost the
election for the chairman
of the member council,
became upset at Secretary
General for not helping her,
and was denied after attempting
to join the Anti-BH faction.
She then began to bear
a grudge, and in order
to create conflict between
the two factions,
on the condition that he
wouldn't reveal the informant,
she supplied Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil with false information.
Do you think I'll just let
you do that and do nothing?
I'm an attorney.
Look, Assemblywoman Hong.
The place we live in is not
a law court but Yeouido.
Turning a spokeswoman who gained popularity
with her looks alone into an idiot
is a piece of cake here.
Hello.
Assemblyman Park's green
tea's quite aromatic.
It truly is.
Attend the disciplinary
hearing and demand.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
expulsion from the party.
Why do I have to do that?
If Jin Sang Pil says your name aloud, isn't
it better for you to deny it right then?
It would be extremely
troublesome for you if
things get out of hand
and you're not there.
Assemblyman Jin will never
disclose the informant.
Don't forget. Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil must be expelled.
Look, Assemblywoman Hong.
Will Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
disclose the informant or not?
He won't.
Although he's incompetent,
he's a man of principle.
It might seem people
are different,
but if you look inside,
they're all the same.
If you like something,
others like it too, and
if you hate something,
others hate it too.
If you think you might tell on
someone, others will do the same.
Aide Choi.
We looked everywhere but can't
find anything similar to this.
Secretary Sim.- Yes.
Did you check everything
from the Spokeswoman's
office and Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi's office?
Yes, I compared them all.
Why Assemblywoman Hong
Chan Mi all of a sudden?
No matter how much
I think about it,
Assemblywoman Hong Chan
Mi is the informant.
To have access to such
classified information,
the person must be one
of the assemblymen.
Because Assemblywoman Hong
had a falling out with.
Secretary General Baek, that
gives her motivation too.
What's up with him?
Aide.
About Assemblywoman Hong.- Yes.
I just received an
electronic notice.
She's one of the disciplinary committee
members for our Assemblyman.
Disciplinary committee member?
Then it's not her.
Unless she's gone crazy, would
she strike him with disciplinary
action when she was the one
feeding him information?
Attend the disciplinary hearing and
demand Assemblyman Jin's removal.
What are you doing?
I'm here because I
have something to say.
If it's Choi In
Kyung, then maybe.
That word "comrade" does not
fit you, Assemblywoman Hong.
I have nothing to hear from you.
Would you vote
against expelling
my Assemblyman?
What did you say?
Disciplinary committee member.
You probably became one by
Secretary General Baek's order.
But instead of Secretary General
Baek who has hit rock bottom,
I'm asking you to
choose my Assemblyman.
You seem to be relapsing into the symptom
of not knowing your place again.
Do I look like a person who will work
with someone like Assemblyman Jin?
About 6 years ago,
at a gathering of attorneys
who loved the environment,
when you were demonstrating for
amending the environmental acts,
I accompanied Secretary
General Baek there.
What?
At the place where the
demonstration took place,
there was a young lawyer who wrote
something on the big poster.
Even though she had magic marker pen
marks all over her hands and face,
she asked to shake our
hands without hesitation.
She was brave and passionate.
What are you talking
about right now?
I am telling you that you were
like that in the old times.
So?
You want to tell me I
have changed, huh?
"After a promising person
got the gold badge,
"she became trash." That's what
you want to ridicule me about.
Assemblywoman, you have not
changed nor became trash. But...
What about But?
Like many of the
proportional assemblymen,
I think you are weighed down
by the badge worn suddenly
without much preparation.
Ally yourself with
our Assemblyman.
Our Assemblyman is the person who
can bear the weight with you.
Get out.
- Assemblywoman.
- Didn't you hear? Get out!
Still, I...
did my best. Do you know that?
If anybody among the proportional
assemblymen worked harder
than I did on Assembly activities,
ask him to step forward.
I admit that you worked hard
on Assembly activities.
But as a proportional
assemblywoman,
whom you represented, indeed...
- Can you say that with confidence?
- What?
Please check with whom you ate lunch
and dinner for the last four years.
It shows there whom
you represented.
This bravado...
In Kyung, what are you going
to do if you started a fire?
Aide Choi.
What?
I found... What?
The informant.
The informant has
to be this person.
Your reasoning?
There was a fact
that went unnoticed.
Madam Hong is the incarnate
fiend of ad lib.
Ad lib? - Yes.
Hence, from the statements
on the home page
we couldn't figure out
who was the informant.
Because those statements
were written by the aides.
Right? Look at this.
The people watch us.
Here.
The Assemblyman's statement
written by the informant herself.
Wake up! The people
are watching!
The people are watching.
She is properly caught.
M.a.d.a.m. Hong.
Did I do well?
Yeah.
Praise me.
That was praise, wasn't it?
Do you understand the meaning
of getting expelled?
It means the Indifferent-to-BH
faction, which has been
gaining much support from the
citizens, will cease to exist.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Aide Choi.
Assemblywoman Hong, who gave
the information to you,
became a member of the very disciplinary
committee that will sanction you.
Tell the press now. Even though
Hong Chan Mi will deny it.
First, break the news.
It's okay.- Pardon?
In order not to get
expelled from the party,
revealing the informant
seems so low.
Assemblyman.
Assemblywoman is going to expel
you from the party right now.
Is it a big deal that you don't
look low in this situation?
Go home now.
If you are not able
to do it, I will.
Aide Choi. Wait for a moment.
Wait.
It is no use even
if you stop me.
I can't watch Indifferent-to-BH
to disappear
like this. If
Indifferent-to-BH disappears,
my goal, that I will get you
re-elected, will vanish.
Aide Choi.
I, too, do this to save
Indifferent-to-BH.
What are you saying?
You said I can't act by
myself for Indifferent-to-BH.
Then, you are doing this because
of recruiting Assemblywoman Hong?
Assemblywoman Hong asked me what I can do
for her if she joins Indifferent-to-BH.
Nomination? I can't
offer it to her.
Political funds, a party position,
or an Assembly position...
I can't get her any of them.
But, when I thought about it,
there is one thing
I can do for her.
What is that?
Keeping the promise.
Not betraying her.
I can be trustworthy to the person
who always deceives or is deceived.
Assemblywoman Hong
almost lost her reason.
Do you think she would
know your intention?
Whether she knows or
not, if I am the leader
of Indifferent-to-BH, I
have to act this way.
Assemblyman. -That's why you
just pretend not to know it.
I beg of you.
Gookmin Party
20153rd Ethics Committee.
AGENDA: Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's Disciplinary.
Punishment of Expulsion from
the Assembly and the Party.
Ahh, really crazy.
Because Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil circulated
the fabricated false information,
the image of the party has
fallen to the ground, right now.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, do you admit
your conduct is subject to discipline?
No, I don't admit it.
I told the truth. How is it that
conduct subject to discipline?
Playing pat-a-cake with
the shares of nominees
between the Pro-BH
and Anti-BH factions
is the conduct for which
discipline should be applied.
Are you saying pat-a-cake? Give
proof we played pat-a-cake!
Huh? From whom on earth did
you receive this information?
What are you doing without answering?-
Confess quickly who that person was.
I can't answer.
What does it matter who
the informant was?
I made a promise to the
source to keep it secret.
Do you know you will be expelled from the
party? Do you still want not to tell?
No. I will not.
Assemblyman Jin, don't
make it too complicated.
How about resigning on your own?
You don't love our Gookmin
Party much, do you?
Yes. I love it very much.
Sometimes, it looks like
Balsam Institute; I feel right
at home.  (A SCHOOL IN
COMEDY SHOW GAG CONCERT ).
Its environment is so pleasant that
even a migratory bird flies in.
Assemblyman, your words are
subject to discipline.
Assemblyman Jin, what
is your true color?
What do you mean what?
He is a leftist.
I am an onion (YANG PA) that
belongs to leftist (JOI PA) and
to rightist (WU PA). The more you
peel it, newer ones show up.
Stop playing with words. Where is
that kind of ideology in the world?
Yes.
If you want to hear
my ideology, I am...
only a human. A human.
Assemblyman Kang!
A human, like truly
being a human:
To believe one another;
To get along well;
Not to stab someone
else's back, please;
Not to fight each other;
Not to make someone cry;
To join hands
and to walk together...
that's my political idea.
Humanism.
Aide Choi who had worked in BH
sent a text to me just now.
That it is called Humanism.
Will this be the answer
to your question?
Excuse us during the meeting.
I came to watch here as a representative
of the assemblymen who filed a complaint.
This Committee thinks that we
have to take the action of.
Assemblyman Jin's expulsion
from the party right away.
I agree.- I agree.
Assemblyman Jin has to be
expelled from the party.
Assemblywoman Hong
Chan Mi Schedule.
Please check with whom you ate lunch
and dinner for the last four years.
It shows there whom
you represented.
Assemblywoman Hong, what have you
been looking at continuously?
State your opinion of the
disciplinary punishment quickly.
If I have to put it into
words, probably a partner.
Who can always be contractually terminated
if she fails to meet the profit goals.
The place we live in is not
a law court but Yeouido.
Turning a spokeswoman who gained popularity
with her looks alone into an idiot
is a piece of cake here.
Assemblywoman Hong?
I will tell my opinion of the
disciplinary punishment.
I want to take the
action of expulsion.
But the target of the action
is not Assemblyman Jin.
It must be to me, Assemblywoman
Hong, who told the truth to him.
Assemblywoman Hong?
Assemblywoman Hong!
Assemblyman Jin only
trusted the informant.
He had no intention to
drive the party into a
difficult position by
circulating false information.
Therefore, there is no cause for
discipline in Assemblyman Jin's action.
If you want to bring
disciplinary action against me,
please form a disciplinary
committee at your convenience.
Whether the information I
supplied is true or not,
let's call that into question there,
again, Secretary General Baek.
Assemblyman Park,
well... shall we
proceed properly?
Avatar of Anti-BH, will you announce
the result of today's meeting?
From this moment
I resign from the position of
spokesperson of the Gookmin Party.
Oh, no... Assemblywoman Hong...
Assemblywoman Hong!
Please. Assemblywoman Hong.
Assemblywoman Hong.
You are... a fool.
Hello.
Assemblyman Jin!
I know. I know. So creepy!
It's okay. Okay.
Well done, Assemblyman.
I am sorry. I always
make you edgy.
I will consider it as
my fate from now on.
Meet Assemblywoman Hong soon.
Ah... Really. Where is
Assemblywoman Hong?
How... on earth...
Why on earth...
Long time no see.
Have you been well?
You are studying well?
Yes. Aide Choi, you've been well, right?
Don't even mention it. You
don't know how hard I have to
work to raise a kid who is
not supposed to be my fate.
I saw the news. He was almost
expelled from the party.
He had a close call.
Assemblyman might have saved the
country in his previous life.
It's because you are by his side.
When you two team up, no one can match you.
By the way, how is it going
with the bill you were making?
I stopped making it. It looks like I
don't yet have the ability to make it.
Try to send it to me although it's not
finished. I will check it for you.
That's okay. If you read it,
it will only hurt your eyes.
Next time, just call me
with your cellphone.
I won't tell Assemblyman. What
is this, like a criminal?
Yes.
Anyhow, Aide Choi, cheer up.
Okay. Thank you.
Aide Choi.
What are you doing?
It seems Assemblywoman Hong
hasn't come to work today either.
Did you think she would
come to work in the middle
of a rumor about her
resignation from the Assembly?
She doesn't answer the phone.
Will she really resign?
Hello?-Kim Gyu Hwan?
Yes. Who is calling?
I am Section Chief Kim Sang Jin from
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
Central District Prosecutors' Office?
What is the question you want to ask?
Yes.
There is a case that we are
investigating secretly.
Secret investigation?
Do you know Hanmin Bank?
Hanmin Bank?
You received a shopping bag with money in
it from the bank presiden't secretary.
And delivered it to Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, right?
If... I mean if...
If you have not received the
money back from Assemblyman Jin,
there seems no chance
to hand over to the
prosecutor your loan
irregularities we discovered.
6th day of the Parliamentary Inspection.
Of course, Bank President, you
will get a punishment, but
compared to the punishment
for the illegal loan
of $140 million, it
will be a mere smidgen.
Bank President.
Have you received the money
back from Assemblyman Jin?
Tell me.
Did you deliver the money
to Assemblyman Jin or not?
Of course not.
I have not received it back.
Yes. You haven't so.
I understand well.
Secretary General.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil is
now like a cornered rat.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
This inspection is the first and last
parliamentary inspection for you.
I will beat you for Hyung Dal Soo's sake.
Did you deliver the money
to Assemblyman Jin or not?
I want to see you now.
What did you do with the designer watch
you received from President Lee Taek Jo?
Kim Gyu Hwan said he delivered
the money to Assemblyman Jin.
In this case, Secretary General
Baek must be behind it.
People don't believe me.
We can have the motion
for the arrest rejected.
I will appear in the prosecutor's office.