Ripped & Synced by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
I will catch Jin Sang
Pil using this friend.
Please approve it.
Episode 13.
Secretary Oh, get the car ready quickly.
Yes.
I am really sorry. I should
be here until the end.
But I am behind schedule
at other events.
Oh, don't mind us. Just work
hard on Assembly activities.
Yes.
Hey, Gyu Hwan. You stay until the
end of the event instead of me.
Yes. I got it.
If you have something to tell
me, you can tell it to him.
Yes. I understand.-
I am leaving now.
Goodbye. Thank you.
Assemblyman Jin. We love you!
We love you!
People's...Truth! Fighting!
Yes! Fighting!
Take care of them.
Secretary Kim. We
just collected some
donations quickly,
although it is not a lot.
Ah. If you provide it with
the donors' information,
I will make the political
funds' receipt available.
I understand.
Here it is.
Thank you.-Here.
Thank you. Thank you.
Who was it?
You got an offer to appear on the radio
show, "Greeting the Morning with Politics."
Well. Let's do it.
I will do it in the usual way.
By the way, what
is the main topic?
It's about the problems of
Babel Tower City Complex's
business, which is under
court receivership.
Ahh. You mean the very tall building
built at the Han riverside?
Yes. It was said that it has been the
biggest single construction project
in the country since Dan Gun ( THE
FOUNDING FATHER OF THE KOREAN NATION).
It became a hippo eating money
due to construction delays.
I will report to you as soon as
the questionnaire comes out.
Yes.
Oh yeah!
How is the remedial bill for
persons with bad credit going?
Well, we are working on it now.
We have to hurry.
Because I am probably known as a
person with bad credit, people
with poor credit from everywhere
are making repeated requests.
I feel sorry for them.
Yes.
Legislative debate concerning remedial
measures for people with bad credit.
The staff to research the problem
with government's support
measures for small business
owners and ways to improve it,
reporting the current state
of industrial accidents...
Within this month,
there are 5 activities
which were prevented due to a lack
of political funds.- It's serious.
Don't the fans of People's
Truth donate some?
They do. With their donation,
the office rent at the constituency
and Miss Lee's salary are paid.
There are some places that want
to contribute to Assemblyman Jin.
Where?- It's too obvious.
Companies and profit-seeking
organizations.
Can't only an
individual contribute?
There is a way to do it.
You are probably talking
about using a loophole like
cheating on how to contribute.
But we can't do that.
Everybody else is doing it. Why not us?
To do politics, we have to have money.
You'd better clean
around Assemblyman Jin.
Well. Attention!
From today, all staff in
this office will implement
an emergency system for
raising contributions.
What do you mean
raising contributions?
Call an acquaintance who
pays the annual income tax
at more than $100 and ask
for a political donation.
Make sure to emphasize that the
donation is tax deductible so they will
be able to deduct $100 from their
income tax at the end of the tax year.
Yes.- I will let you
know your quota.
For interns, do as
much as they can.
For the regular staff, 100
people per staff member.
100 people?
Excuse me, Aide Choi. I haven't even
stored 100 people in my cell phone.
Be quiet! With Assemblyman
Jin's income,
we are using half of it to pay a debt and
the other half to do political activities.
Is it true?
Well, by all means, we
must raise the money.
Understand?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Aide Seo. I got chills just now.
Huh? - I can sense the aroma of Madame
Hong (ASSEMBLYWOMAN HONG) from Aide Choi.
Brrr... Ice!
What is this?
You look so depressed these days.
So I want
to give some support
under my husband's name.
You know I don't like much
give-and-take among the assemblymen.
This is not a give-and-take
but my heart.
Assemblywoman Hong.-By the way,
until when are you going to
let him swing like that?
Don't you worry? The public
opinion for him at Gyeongje City,
is getting much better,
compared to previously.
While he is swinging his arms, he
will be caught on his blind side.
A crack?
Yeah. I remember you were
getting interviewed.
Did you get a job?
Is that so? I am just
calling to say hello.
Yes. Yeah. Hang in there!
Aide Choi is out of
touch with reality.
Really, most people my
age have part-time jobs.
Who would donate, right?
Secretary Kim, here's some mail.
To Mr. Kim Gyu HwanOffice
of Assemblyman Jin Sang.
Pil 1 Assembly Road,
Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul 07233.
Mr. Bae Gyu Hwan.
What is this? What is...
Ripped & Synced by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Transcription of Recording
RECORDING PLACE: Meeting
room at Han Gook Repair
Shipbuilding Company.
JIN SANG PIL: Are you
sure?Park Chang Ho:
YES! JIN SANG PIL: Then,
I saw the agreement...
Aren't you signing? Aren't you
agreeing to the settlement?
Wait for a moment. We are now
waiting for Chairman's phone call.
If Hyung Dal Soo leaves, I can't reach
an agreement even if I want to.
Call him quickly.- I'm saying this
because you brought up Bae Dal Soo.
Per the union request
for the Agreement,
the clause that Han Gook
Company shall recommend
people who want to get
hired to a subcontractor
is applicable to other workers. But since
Bae Dal Soo has a very strong character and
a disability, it is hard
to apply it to him.
Then, do you want
to exclude him?
Anyhow, even if he gets hired by a
subcontractor, he will not be able to work,
so let's just settle
without regard to him.
Are you sure? We will
not rehire Bae Dal Soo.
I understand.
We will not rehire Bae Dal Soo.
What are you doing?
What startled you so
much?- It's nothing.
Your eyes say it's not nothing.
What is this? It's not nothing.
Give it to me.
What... -I told you it's nothing!
You are showing
your seriousness.
Really, do you want to
fight with me here?
This is my personal problem.-
Did you get into trouble again?
You have to go to the company soon.
Get ready. What makes you so serious?
I am sorry.
I have something Aide
Choi asked me to do.
Really, he is very obedient
to Aide Choi's words.
He seems playing the death.
I am the boss. Aide Choi
is the second boss.
Do you get it? What a shame!
Well, go straight!
No, to the right! To the right!
Listen to me. Go straight!
Be quiet! Do you
want to get off?
Aiee! What a traffic jam!
Even now, may I turn on GPS?
If we are late...
I should have brought Gyu Hwan.
He is very good at directions.
Like a ghost.
- He used to be a designated driver.
- No.
He was born like that.
Even in Gyeongje City, he knows every
street as though he lives there.
Who lives where? Don't talk uselessly,
and pay attention to driving!
I'm looking forward to it.
We will do our best.
Don't worry too much.
You don't need to show
us out.- Then, I won't.
Good bye!
Kim Gyu Hwan!
Aide Choi?- What are you
thinking about so absorbedly?
No, no really. Just...
It's nothing.
Ucham! This young guy is so silly.
Did you eat a meal?
No, not yet.
That's good. I'm going
to have a drink with the
reporter at Shin Han. Do
you want to go with me?
I am sorry. I don't feel good.
I will leave early.
Is that so? Go home
early and rest.
Yes.
I am right. I will
check it before bed.
Who will help if we don't
help our Assemblyman?
I know you have difficulties.
Even so, would you
help a little bit?
Hey! Assemblyman Jin didn't
betray Hyung Dal Soo.
Hello! Hello! Sh*t.
Let me see... [PARK MI JA]
I am not sure whether
Unni Mi Ja lives well.
Who is Mi Ja?
Bae Dal Soo's ex-wife.
Since she is tough, she lives well.
Very well.
She remarried another person
because her husband got disabled.
There is no reason for not
living well for such a person.
It's me again to ask something.
You were close to Unni Mi Ja who
worked in the accounting department.
Are you still in
contact with her?
I don't contact her these days but when her
son marries, she will probably contact me.
Is it already time
for him to marry?
Gyu Hwan is about 30 years old.
Ah. That's right. His name is Gyu Hwan.
Let's hang up.
Is Dal Soo's son going to marry?
He is not going to marry.
It's about time to marry.
Time flies. Gyu Hwan is
already about 30 years old.
Look at us, getting old.
Then, Ae Ri.
What are you doing?
Before getting old, we should...
You are Bae Gyu
Hwan, aren't you?
Who are you?
You don't know me? Kim Jung
Min from Room 3 in 6th grade.
I was not sure because of
your glasses and your height.
You're mistaken.
Ae Ri! - O.M.G!
Even if Hyung Dal Soo gets hired by a
subcontractor, he will not be able to work.
So let's just settle
without regard to him.
Are you sure?
We will not rehire Bae Dal Soo.
I understand.
010-0099-9915South of Korea.
Hello?
Did you see the transcription
of the recording?
Who are you?
How did you know about me?
When Bae Dal Soo died, I was
busy with cleaning it up.
At that time, I got to
know that Bae Dal Soo had
a son over whom he gave
up his parental rights.
I was looking for him to
see how he is living.
Unexpectedly, he became Assemblyman
Jin's trustworthy secretary.
Why? Do you want to sue him?
What is your intention in sending
the transcription of the recording?
There is no way to confirm
your state of mind.
It surely looks like
you intended revenge.
I am not sure whether
you are acting,
but you look very close
to Assemblyman Jin.
Assemblyman Jin,
he wouldn't do it like this.
I admit that Jin Sang Pil
is good and genuine.
But at the sight of a gold badge
flashing in front of his eyes,
people are bound
to lose control.
Jin Sang Pil is also a human
with basic instincts.
That's precisely the
greed for power.
Enough of the nonsense.
Are you just naive or stupid?
Some time after Secretary General Baek
proposed nomination to Jin Sang Pil,
violence broke out at the
protest site between
the laid-off employees
and the demolition crew.
So?
At the time, Jin Sang Pil
wasn't at the scene,
and Bae Dal Soo was
admitted to the hospital.
That's when Jin Sang Pil reached
a settlement with the company.
Do you think the link
was a coincedence?
While Jin Sang Pil was running
the election campaign,
Bae Dal Soo got arrested
and even jailed after
doing a one-man protest
in front of the company.
Haven't you thought that it might have
been at someone's request or pressure?
How could Secretary Kim
deceive us like that?
He did look familiar somehow.
That explains why he
sometimes put on glasses.
Because he was afraid he would run
into someone he knew in Gyeongje City.
In case someone might
recognize him.
So what? Gyu Hwan is Dal Soo's
son, so what do you want me to do?
What do you mean, what to do?
We have to let him go.
Why?
What do you mean, why? Who
knows what he would do to you?
What harm would that kid
Gyu Hwan do to me? What?
He came here instead of working
for the police for which
he'd studied the whole time and
even got to the interview.
Just how much of a grudge
would he have had that
he would go all-in on you?
Assemblymen. I've also
become attached to him,
and it makes me sad to think
about what he's been through.
But even if we didn't realize what we
didn't know, because of who he is,
wouldn't it be impossible
to have him around?
I already knew that Gyu
Hwan was Dal Soo's son.
Huh?
You knew?
And you still went about
joking around with him?
I'm going to have him
by my side all the way.
So pretend you don't
know, please,
the fact that Gyu Hwan
is Dal Soo's son.
Assemblyman!- When I
became an assemblyman,
I was going to bring Dal
Soo to the Assembly.
That poor guy... No matter what,
by pulling strings or whatever,
I was going to get
him a good job.
But what happened to Dal Soo?
And then Gyu Hwan
showed up somehow.
Well, he probably
came for revenge.
I was actually pleased.
What?
I thought Dal Soo's son
was just a bastard son.
When he was going through
such rough times, I thought
he was a bastard for not even
calling or coming to see his dad.
But he came to take revenge for his dad.
How admirable is that?
Assemblyman.
For me, Gyu Hwan is Dal
Soo's replacement.
If I don't do anything wrong,
why would he do me any harm?
Even if he does,
whatever he does,
I'll be happy to take it.
So,
you two, please...
pretend you don't know.
This is hard.
What
do you want from me?
I know Jin Sang Pil is
pressed for political funds.
Now that he's become a celeb, he
has more things to take care of.
Along with more temptation.
Are you now telling me to give
you hints about his corruption?
You went in there
to do that anyway.
If you do that through me, we
can guarantee your safety.
Think about your father who
died tragically. You are...
You are Bae Dal Soo's son.
You're going to forget everything
after one drink, okay?
I'll think about that
after drinking first.
Seriously... I wonder
if this is okay.
Joo Hee's mom didn't
come in today?
No. She said she has an urgent
matter to take care of.
I see.
Is she having an affair?
Shush. Seriously.
Assemblyman, can I get
an autograph here?
I don't have an autograph.
What should I write...
Provided accommodation for former
employees including Tax Accountant Kim...
for taking a bribe, they're
expected to request
an arrest warrant today
at the earliest.
Look at that. It is
happening after all.
Declared bankruptcy.
Babel Tower City which drew attention as a
future new landmark in 21st century Seoul,
as the world economy collapsed and
the real estate market suffered,
the business has
taken a huge hit.
Because of corruption and financial
difficulties during the permit process,
construction has stopped.
Today, because of financial insolvency,
they expect a fierce storm.
Especially for the individual investors
who expected a guaranteed high return
from the Babel Tower City Fund,
there are strong concerns.
This is Jeong Min
Ah from KBC News.
In the end, I guess the thing that
should have exploded, exploded.
The minority party will seek a
parliamentary investigation.
Babel Tower City...
That's the abode of demons. If they
put their mind to digging it up,
lot of people will be hurt.
It could be turned into
a power type scandal,
and seriously undermine
next year's elections.
We'll have to stop this issue
from becoming politicized.
The Anti-BH faction should
keep the same pace with us.
But will the Anti-BH
faction's help be enough?
It's obvious that the Indifferent-to-BH
faction will feign ignorance again.
Parliamentary investigation?
Yes. The ruling party is going to
insist that we investigate it during
the regular parliamentary session
through parliamentary inspection,
without a separate
parliamentary investigation.
What do you think, Assemblyman?
Why not do both
the parliamentary
investigation and a
parliamentary inspection?
Then, let's have the press
conference announcing
your stance on a
parliamentary investigation.
Before the press conference, I
will send a memo to the press.
Okay. Well... Hello?
She always hangs up first.
She has no etiquette.
Did Aide Choi give you
an assignment again?
Yes. There is not a
day that I can rest.
Secretary Kim.
You drink this and then you
are going to go, right?
Yes. Thank you.
If you drank, you should have gone
straight home. Why did you come here?
I didn't feel like
going home and
I had no other place to go.
Suddenly, I thought about you.
Jeez.
Hey, stop with the nonsense and
hurry up and tell me.
What is going on?
It's nothing serious.
Just... Living is no fun.
What?
The person that I am...
I am so pathetic.
For me, Gyu Hwan is Dal
Soo's replacement.
If I don't do anything wrong,
why would he do me any harm?
Even if he does,
whatever he does,
I'll be happy to take it.
Kim Gyu Hwan,
I don't know why you are
acting this way but
from my viewpoint, you are now
living a satisfactory life.
Is that true?
You know I am not the type to make
up something just to sympathize.
Just a moment.
Yes, Secretary Oh.
No matter how much I think
about it, you should know.
Yes, go ahead.
Secretary Kim... is
Bae Dal Soo's son.
I think he bears a grudge
against the Assemblyman.
I see.
I'll just go.
Oh.
Okay.
Oh, Aide,
I'm grateful.
Okay.
Get going.
Don't show it in
front of Gyu Hwan.
I told you I got it.
Oh?
Sister-in-law!
Why have you come...
Did something happen?
Why have you come?
You... can you help me?
Why? What is it?
What is the matter?
That is... I... was cheated...
Oh, Kyung Ah!
Why are you like
this?-Sister-In-Law.
Sister-In-Law, are you okay?
My money... Please
get my money back.
What money?
My money. Honey, please
get my money back.
Honey...
Babel Tower City Fund?
Because they said the return will be
a few times the deposited amount...
I was a crazy wench.
Where did you get that money?
The money I earned cooking meat and all
OF MOTHER'S MONEY: In total, $30,000.
Wow, this woman... really.
You are fearless. Fearless.
Honey. You are an assemblyman.
Can't you go meet with the
bank president just once?
You have power.
Can't you go tell him
to return my money?
Does what you say
make any sense?
That money... is my
mom's life-savings
and Joo Hee's college
tuition funds.
Having lost that
money, how can I live?
Because I am sorry
and mortified,
how can I face my
mother or Joo Hee?
Honey.
I am beg of you like this.
Please once!
You can do it, can't you?
You can do it, right?
You're home.
Yes.
Pretend that you don't know.
Okay?
Okay.
He looks like his dad.
The demise of Babel
Tower City is a tragedy
created by pariah-capitalism
to make easy money
and current government's
incompetence.
If there's truth to uncover,
we can reveal it as
much as we want at the
parliamentary inspection
which will be held during the next
regular parliamentary session.
I am asking the majority party.
The citizens are wailing...
The opposing party must first correct the
habit of trying to politicize everything.
We need to open a parliamentary
inspection immediately.
The citizens are watching.
How's the public opinion?
Although it shows that we should open a
parliamentary investigation by 6 to 4,
we can more than hold out.
Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil is the variable.
If even a member of the ruling party
demands parliamentary investigation,
we may lose the currently
tight public opinion battle.
But Assemblyman Jin's
response is a bit unusual.
What do mean by strange?
According to reporters,
he said he was going
to hold a press
conference this morning.
They just got an email saying
that it will be delayed.
The so-called "accompanying
secretary" overslept
and didn't even know that the Assemblyman
had gone out. Does that make sense?
I'm sorry.
Usually Secretary Kim or
Assemblyman wakes me up.
Today, the two of them left.
Secretary Kim's phone
has been turned off.
Last night, did something
happen to the Assemblyman?
What?
What happened? Nothing happened.
Looking at you, something
must have happened.
I said nothing happened. Ae
Ri, why are you saying that?
I see you everyday to know.
Hurry up and talk!
What's going on?
To be honest, Sister-In-Law
came by our house last night.
Exclusive benefits for
Hanmin Bank's main branch
customers.When you join Babel
City Tower Fund, Benefit 1...
Re-open the bank and
inject public funds!
Inject! Inject!
Return my life's-blood money!
Return it! Return it!
Inject public funds!
Inject! Inject!
Return my life's-blood money!
Return it! Return it!
Inject public funds!
Inject! Inject!
Return my life's-blood money!
Secretary General, I have
found out why Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil postponed
the press conference.
Hanmin Bank's President Kim called and said
Assemblyman Jin had asked for a meeting.
Why?- It's because of the
Babel Tower City Fund.
His wife supposedly
suffered a huge loss.
President Kim asked
me what he should do.
I drew a firm line, telling him it was not
something we would get involved with.
In that case,
President Kim seems
to have only one choice.
How are you going to
compensate the damages?
I am sorry about
your wife's losses.
Am I here right now in the
capacity of my wife's husband?
What?- Am I here as
my wife's husband?
Can't you see this, huh?
When you sold this fund,
about how risky it is,
how an investor might
even lose his shirt,
I heard that you did not
fully explain that.
I asked the people outside and heard
that there was material omission.
No, everything is spelled out in
the investment funds brochure.
But when a seemingly
reputable bank like this
keeps luring them with high
interest and huge returns,
of course they will believe
the words, rather than read
the itty-bitty fine print on paper.
Then, President,
do you read all these
warnings before buying
them? No, you just trust
them and buy them!
Because they advertise and
say they are delicious!- Jeez.
Compensate the clients' damages.
Assemblyman, because
of this incident,
not only the clients but the bank
too has suffered enormous losses.
Look here, the people
outside right now
are about to lose
their life savings!
They are about to swallow their
tongues and commit suicide!
I, I tell you this in no
uncertain terms, President!
I will subpoena you to an
Assembly investigation hearing.
Inject it!
Return my lifeblood money!
Return it!Return it!
Inject public funds and
return my lifeblood money!
Excuse me.
Return my lifeblood money!
Are you Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's secretary?
Yes, I am.
Here. This is a free present
given to VIP clients.
How can you act like this with
the press conference coming up?
I am sorry. I had a
personal errand to run.
Did you see the Hanmin
Bank President?
I heard that your
wife suffered losses.
You shouldn't concern
yourself with that.
Don't be like this and
give me the details.
Because that president
is a master of lobbying,
I feel uneasy. That's
why I am asking...- Well,
I told you it was
none of your concern.
Before being an assemblyman,
I am Kim Kyung Ah's husband.
I will take care of it myself.
The press conference originally scheduled
for this morning was put off to 7 p.m.
If you demand an
Assembly investigation,
the opposition parties can draw the ruling
party out to the negotiating table.
I will give it a thought.- What?
I said let me think about it,
since we still have time.
Okay.
What about Secretary Kim?
He's not back, yet?
He said he was going to drop
by the Assemblyman's house.
Why the Assemblyman's
house, all of a sudden?
I wouldn't know that.
He seems to bear a grudge
towards the Assemblyman.
What is it?
I thought it was about time
that you told me something.
Today, there was that meeting
with Bank President Kim.
What are you talking about?
A chance like this does not come often.
You must steel your heart.
Oh, oh, and to err on the
side of caution, don't
even think about not
delivering it to him.
Aide-nim!
What were you doing
here just now?
Move. I said move!
What is this?- What's
the matter with you?!
Won't you give it to me?
Give it to me!
I am sorry. Sorry...
This is for Joo Hee, drop
it off at the house.
Okay, I got it.
What is this? Did you get
a complimentary gift?
What is this?
I can't do it, so you
return it, Assemblyman.
What, punk?
If you return this, what are you going
to do about your wife's lost money?
I heard that you are using all your
salary for political funds too.
At this rate, do you think you can
afford to send Joo Hee to college later?
This punk, seriously! Do you
really want to take some beating?
Stop posturing.
This money... They are
definitely giving it to you
so you won't ask for
investigation by the Assembly.
You just have to
keep silent once.
Ahew, this troublemaker,
really...
You are going ahead with the evening's
press conference as planned, right?
If you lend your
support, without fail,
we will secure an investigation
by the Assembly.
Yes, right... Is there...
a problem?
No, not a problem, but just
personally, I have a
lot to think about.
That we will not respond at all to
demands for an Assembly investigation
is our party's both Pro- and
Anti-BH factions' firm position.
Why don't you start worrying about
your graceful exit strategy now?
If an Assembly investigation won't work,
then we will ask for a special prosecutor.
Because you had no confidence to push
through a special prosecutor's appointment,
you clamored for an Assembly
investigation, isn't that so?
By the way, did you pay off
Jin Sang Pil or something?
What do you mean pay off?-
He seemed ass-whooped.
Are you blackmailing him
with some flaw of his?
Well, maybe he is
finally growing up.
Assemblyman Park,
there is a rumor
that Jin Sang Pil is reluctant to
hold this evening's press conference.
For a person who used
to wriggle out at every
turn, like a baby octopus
out of a market bag,
why is he, all of a sudden,
being a shrinking violet?
If a person does something
out of the ordinary,
that means he is feeling
sheepish about something.
Then, perhaps, Jin Sang Pil
grabbed himself some breadcrumbs
from that Babel place?
And you?
Aish, what do you take me for?
Until this day and
hour, I have never
even once stood in the lobby
of the prosecutors' office.
If Jin Sang Pil
does not hold a
press conference,
for sure, it feels like he
has received something.
It must be rat poison, huh?
Return our lifeblood money!
Return it...Return it...
We'll take an hour break.
Mom, it must be hard for you.
Joo Hee...
I am sorry.
It's okay, Mom. Don't cry.
Mommy is
really sorry.
What do we do now?
That money is my
mom's life-savings
and Joo Hee's college
tuition funds.
Hello?
I will see you tonight at
7:30 at the same place.
Are you saying he asked
to meet first, for sure?
Yes.
Kim Gyu Hwan must have caught
Jin Sang Pil accepting a bribe.
I understand.
I am sorry, it was
a pressing matter.
At any rate, an
Assembly investigation
must be stopped no matter what.
Please tell the Elder that such a
thing will never come to pass.
Really, will it be okay if I
report it to him like that?
Of course.
The customer cannot be reached.
After the beep...
It looks like the Assemblyman
will not hold a press conference.
You still cannot reach
the Assemblyman?
Right, his phone is
still turned off.
Is someone working
on the Assemblyman?
Working?
This (MONEY SIGN), I mean...
Hello... Assemblyman!
Where in the world
are you right now?
Ahew, really stinks,
the smell of it.
I will come to the media room
with your prepared statement.
No, not that.
Let's go with
something stronger.
What?
Yes, I am Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil,
People's Spoilsport of the Gookmin
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
About this Babel
Tower City scandal
that has completely robbed.
So laughable...
so many working people of
their dreams and hopes,
I will state my position.
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Watch this.
The Babel Tower City
project has been
an endless string of
noises and suspicions,
about the project as a whole,
from selection of the developer
and government permits, to the
borrowing of an astronomical sum.
In order to uncover the truth
about this Babel Tower City
which is like a symbol
of our nation's
widespread corruption
and moral hazard,
through a special prosecutor who does
not have any conflict of interest...
What?
An impartial and - What?
Special prosecutor?-
no-holds-barred investigation...
Wow, I've got to hand it to you,
that People's spoilsport...
Transcending party
differences...
Yes, Secretary Lim.
We have a huge problem.
Assemblyman Jin Sang.
Pil is giving a press
conference and...
Did he demand an
Assembly investigation?
Not an Assembly
investigation, but
a special prosecution.
Finally,
I would like to convey
my true feeling
to one person among
many victims,
in despair
over this catastrophe.
Joo Hee's mom,
I am really sorry.
No matter what I had to do,
I really wanted to get
you your money back,
that lifeblood money
you saved up by serving
meat and doing dishes.
But I realized I am no longer
a person who should do that.
I realized that I am not a person
who can just look after my family.
Those people who were
crying with you...
I realized that I am a person
who must care about
those people as well.
Mom...
I am really sorry.
I am sorry, Kyung Ah.
That is all.
Say hello. This is Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon.
Have a seat.
The reason I came today is to put
you at ease, Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan.
Please trust me and say
anything without reservation.
Then, I will tell you honestly.
Because I was not convinced by Chief
Secretary Lim's transcript alone,
I put temptation in his way.
Don't be impertinent and beat
around the bush. Just cut to
the chase, about his meeting
with the Hanmin Bank President!
The chase?
This glass of water,
consider it thrown at Chief
Secretary Lim instead of you.
The one who hurt my father, the one
who made the police arrest my father!
Surely, it was all
your doing, Secretary
General Baek.
Won't you shut up!
Enough.
You can leave now.
Secretary General, I am sorry!
Secretary Kim.
Aide-nim.
About what happened to
the Assemblyman today,
will you tell me?
Why are you asking me?
No matter how much
I think about it,
the errand you ran today
doesn't seem to be limited
to Joo Hee's stationery.
The bribe the bank
president gave,
I delivered it to the
Assemblyman, satisfied?
If you tell me to quit, I
will quit working here.
Kim Gyu Hwan!
I hope you
get the weight off
your chest now
and work cheerfully.
What do you mean by
that?- I know that
your biological father is Mr.
Bae Dal Soo.
The Assemblyman
has known about it a
lot longer than I.
Knowing who I am,
why did he let me
be all this time?
Because to the Assemblyman,
you are the same as Mr.
Bae Dal Soo.
The Assemblyman
wanted to come to the
National Assembly,
together with Mr. Bae Dal Soo.
The Assemblyman is seeing
your late father through you.
Kim Gyu Hwan,
let it all go now.
I will leave first.
That's right, Joo Hee.
You have to stay by your mom's
side and take care of her.
Umm.
Call me right away
if anything happens.
Oh, okay. Good night.
Aide Choi!
Secretary Kim has disappeared
without a trace.
I heard that you had
found out, too,
that Gyu Hwan is
Hyung Dal Soo's son.
Yes.- Did you...
maybe tell Secretary Kim?
Yes.
Why did you tell him?
Why did you tell
him about it, WHY?
Because I couldn't
turn a blind eye to Secretary
Kim suffering between
his feelings of vengeance
and admiration toward you.
I am sorry.
Aide Choi didn't
do anything wrong.
Secretary Kim has to live
his own life, too, now.
That is right.
How much must that nice lad
have suffered in his heart?
I am sorry.
I don't have the courage to
face you as Bae Gyu Hwan.
Please forgive me.
But, Assemblyman,
I really despised you
at the beginning.
Now,
I admire you.
Please take care of your health.
Ah, this troublemaker, really...
The bill appointing a special
prosecutor to investigate the.
Babel Tower City bankruptcy has
passed the National Assembly.
The Assembly originally took a passive
position, but when popular opinion
favoring a special
prosecutor erupted after.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
moving press conference,
the Assembly passed the special
prosecutor bill led by the
opposition parties and Gookmin
Party's Anti-BH faction.
When the special prosecutor is
installed, the businessmen and
government officers involved in
the Babel Tower City project,
the so-called den of fiends, are expected
to be subpoenaed one after another...
You've seen it now, right?
That is who I am.
Yes, you're so great.
But Secretary General Baek must have
received a huge blow this time.
That special prosecutor bill was passed
because the Anti-BH faction betrayed him.
That is what the Anti-BH faction aimed for.
To deal Secretary General Baek a deathblow.
I will relay the VIP's message.
He asks you to step down voluntarily
from the Secretary General's position.
W-what did you say just now?
Because he said you were to announce
it this week, get ready for it.
I will see the Elder
and hear it from him directly.
Let alone a private meeting, he said he
didn't even want you to contact him.
Yes, this is Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, the
people's servant who always tries his best.
Ah, yes, is that so?
Then I am Barack Obama.
Sheesh, really.
Who is it for you to answer it like that?
It was a prank call. He
said he was the President.
Since I'm so popular nowadays, I'm
getting tons of prank calls too.
The President?- Yes.
Yes, this is Choi In Kyung.
Yes,
I am currently serving as
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's aide.
Yes, he is next to me right now.
- Please take the call.
- Who is it for you to be so tense?
Hello?- Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil?
Yes, that's me. Who are you?
I... am the President.
Ripped & Synced by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Assembly~Preview~.
I will never step down on my own.
Please bet your political careers on me.
I think an order was handed
down from the Blue House.
Then, what is going to happen
to Secretary General Baek now?
I would like to receive the
Anti-BH faction's help.
Just leave promptly.
There is no guarantee that a chance
like this will come your way again.
Aide Choi!
Tomorrow, Assemblyman,
you must give a speech
accepting the position
of Secretary General.
Let's now try heavy-duty politics.
Let's turn the tables!