All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Episode 17.
Prosecutor's Office.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Thank you for appearing.
Assemblyman, I am notifying you
of your rights to refuse to make
any statement which may
incriminate you and to
have an attorney present
during the questioning.
Shall we start the questioning?
Oh, go ahead.
I tell you this in no
uncertain terms...
Mr. President, I will subpoena you to
an Assembly investigation hearing.
Have you made such a statement?
Yes, I have.
It was with the intention to ask him
to bear responsibility for making
materially misleading statements in the
sale of the Babel Tower City Fund.
Isn't it true that right
after your meeting with the
president, in the Hanmin
Bank underground garage
you received a bagful of cash from
your secretary, Kim Gyu Hwan?
Do you really want
to have a beating?
Stop posturing.
This money... They are
definitely giving it to you
so you won't ask for
investigation by the Assembly.
You just have to
keep silent once.
Yes, I did.
The accused has consistently maintained
that he received it and returned it.
Are you going to continue to interfere
with the questioning like this?
I am supplementing the statements that may
be used against him in a court of law.
He is exercising his
legal right to counsel.
I can have you forcefully
removed if you keep doing this.
If I were you, Prosecutor,
I would not do that.
I am an incumbent assemblywoman
from the ruling party
and unlike my client,
I am steeped in the notion that an
assemblyman ought to enjoy many privileges.
I will make a lot of noise.
Assemblyman, why did you return
to the bank president's office?
To return the money.
Bank President Kim stated that
was to ask for more money.
He was lying.
You will find out if you look at
the CCTV tape from his office.
If you look for it,
I went in with the box of money
but came out empty handed.
Except for the public CCTV
from the underground garage
that shows you getting
money from Kim Gyu Hwan,
all tapes were past the mandatory
record-keeping period and were erased.
Give me some other evidence.
I will come to the media room
with your prepared statement.
No, not that.
Let's go with
something stronger.
What?
If I really was tempted
by that money,
why would I have said
those kinds of words?
Because the bank president had to be
scared for him to cough up more money.
Look here!
Assemblyman Jin.
Okay. Fine.
Let's say I did like you said.
Then, if I am that kind of a person, why
would I ask for a special prosecution?
So that you could deny it like
this, even if the fact that
you received a bribe was revealed.
Isn't that the truth?
Wow, you really are
something else.
You don't need to answer.
Prosecutor, your
unreasonableness is a bit harsh.
The suspect is the kind of
person who received a watch
as a bribe and immediately
converted it into cash.
Whether that's unreasonable, I
guess the judge will decide.
The fact that the suspect took the money
and bought food for the homeless,
that is also the accused's
consistent position.
Honestly, I don't believe
the suspect's statement.
I only believe in evidence.
You really do live
a tiring life.
If you want to avoid going to
jail, show some remorse and
admit to the charges.
Not just to avoid
going to jail but
even if you want to give
me a death sentence,
I can't admit that. I won't.
Do you understand?
There is one thing I must
absolutely point out.
Even if Assemblyman Jin
admits all the charges,
if the arrest motion fails to
pass the Assembly this evening,
nobody can detain Assemblyman Jin.
You know that, right?
Of course I know. But do you think
the arrest motion will fail to pass?
Motion to Consent to Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil's Arrest.
How is the arrest
motion being handled?
The assemblymen are
gathering one by one.
But don't be too hopeful.
Since the Anti-BH faction
decided to vote autonomously,
there is still a chance to block it
with help from the opposition parties.
Ahew, I'll say...
I wish Democratic Party Leader
Oh Sae Chang would help...
The arrest motion will not, by
any chance, fail to pass, right?
Do Hyeon... it's Oh Sae Chang.
Aigoo, long time no
see, Assemblyman Baek.
Long time no see.
Congratulations, belatedly,
on your becoming
the party leader.
Since a person who is not
an incumbent assemblyman
took on the important
position of a party leader,
there are many difficulties.
But in a few months, you
will gobble up the windfall
voting district Secretary
General Baek relinquished.
Like a thief burglarizing
an empty house.
Well, whether I'm
burglarizing an empty house
or the owner is avoiding
the encounter first...
Which is the case?
Well, it's all in the past.
More importantly, about the motion for
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's arrest;
How are you going to handle it?
Well, I have spoken
to our assemblymen,
so wait and find out.
Oh, by the way, Assemblyman
Baek, if it's hard for
you to settle down in
Gyeongje City, come back.
I will welcome you any time.
I will do that.
Isn't Oh Sae Chang, by any chance, telling
their assemblymen to save Jin Sang Pil?
I put before you the motion to consent to
National Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's arrest.
I think we have to
discontinue the questioning.
Why? Go on.
The result of the
arrest motion came out.
9 Motions Including
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's.
Arrest Passed during
the Plenary Session.
Even though it was not an instruction, I
recommended to our assemblymen to vote yes.
Our Korean Democratic Party will
let go of parliamentary privileges
and address our countrymen
in a humble manner.
Ms. Choi In Kyung, did
you see the news?
Yes.
The only remaining hope is the court's
hearing of the warrant's validity.
When the arrest motion has passed, do you
think the judge will deny the warrant?
I will see you in the courthouse.
Please take care of the Assemblyman.
In Kyung!
After questioning by the
prosecution, Assemblyman Jin
is en route to the court
for the warrant hearing.
You want me to hold
a press conference?
Yes, please urge non-custodial
interrogation for Assemblyman Jin.
What are you talking about? Jin Sang
Pil's arrest motion has passed.
The passage of the motion means that you
consent to the Assemblyman's arrest.
It does not mean he
has to be arrested.
Before being an assemblyman, as a
person with human rights, he has
the right to be questioned while
maintaining his personal freedom.
Sunbae-nim, please help us.
I understand your feelings.
But you know better than I how I am kind
of riding Gookmin Party's coattails.
Not just coattail riding, but you've
become Secretary General Baek's lackey.
Hey, Choi In Kyung, are you really going
to keep saying those sorts of things?!
I am saying this for your sake.
Stop ruining yourself and
join my Assemblyman now.
What?!
Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi has joined
the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
If you join as well, it will become
a force to be reckoned with.
That is the only way for
you to overcome the stigma
of being a migratory bird
and do politics with pride.
Oh, yes.
Oh, Assemblyman Jo, you will
have to play the trumpet.
What?
I support Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's interrogation under custody.
No words can express the
distress I feel for
having to call for a fellow
assemblyman's arrest.
However, the cozy relations
between politics and business
are like a mass of cancer cells
that kills Korean politics.
The deep-rooted corruption of Korean
politics where dirty money changes hands
between politicians and
businessmen must disappear.
In Kyung,
let us not meet as sunbae
and hoobae in the future.
That's what I hope for, too.
I am Assemblywoman
Cheon No Shim.
Even though Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's arrest motion has passed,
I firmly believe that
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
is a person our Assembly needs.
I want Assemblyman Jin
to be released and
stand trial while carrying
out his legislative duties.
Accordingly, I have decided
to submit a petition
to the court to deny.
Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's arrest warrant.
I wish a lot of like-minded
fellow assemblymen would join me.
Assemblyman Park, do you want
to sign one of these too?
Petition?
Yes, Cheon No Shim and
Jin Sang Pil's staff are
handing out these petitions
together in the Assembly Center.
I guess they want to give these to the
judge assigned to the warrant hearing.
What are you doing right now?
When an opposition party
assemblywoman is getting
in knee-deep like that
trying to help him,
if we, as fellow party
assemblymen, turn a blind eye,
people will call us unfeeling.
No,
we conservatives have humanity, too.
We should show them.
Do you think the prosecution will do
nothing if Jin Sang Pil is released?
Do you think
the prosecution does not
know about Lee Taek Jo
handing out designer
watches to assemblymen?
While they are overlooking it because of
political pressures, let sleeping dogs lie.
Come to think of it, if he
did something wrong, he
should eat bean rice
(EUPHEMISM FOR GOING TO JAIL).
Lay low for the time being.
Because the sword is in the
hands of the prosecution.
Ah, yes, quickly call your old man
and ask him to put his seal on it.
What is this?
This is Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's office.
Have you reviewed the petition we sent you?
Here.
To those doubful assemblymen,
you have to highlight
no risk of destruction of evidence or
flight as much as possible, understand?
Yes.
Thank you. Aide-nim,
Assemblyman Lee Sam Tae of
the Korean Democratic
Party will endorse it.
Run and get it.
Yes.
The accused is an assemblyman of the
Republic of Korea. The people...
What are you doing? We have no
time, type it up fast, fast!
Aide-nim, here!
Okay. Aide Seo, how about
the Anti-BH faction?
Aigoo, I got it, I got it.
Hang up, hang up.
All Anti-BH assemblymen
are saying no.
What? When they agreed to vote
autonomously on the arrest motion?
I guess they have had
a change of heart.
Those bastards...
This won't be enough to
change the judge's heart.
Yes, this is Choi In Kyung.
Aide-nim.
Kim Gyu Hwan?
I... have a favor to ask.
The accused is an assemblyman and as
such, there is no risk of flight.
I acknowledge that there
is no risk of flight.
However, using his privileged position as
an assemblyman, he may spoliate evidence.
He relinquished his parliamentary
immunity and voluntarily
appeared. Please take
that into consideration.
The law should be more stringently
applied towards a public figure.
Probable cause as to the criminal act is
lacking. Please deny the arrest warrant.
Please, Your Honor.
I already asked the prosecutor
but she did not allow this.
Please let me see Bank President
Kim Doo Shik face to face.
I think I know why
he lies like that.
I will give you a
chance to speak later,
so be quiet and sit down.
What is Choi In Kyung doing?
We have arrived. We
are right outside.
Aigoo, you should have come sooner.
Petitions, petitions!
Assemblywoman! Has
the hearing started?
Of course it has started.
Why is he here?
He is the son of the late Mr.
Bae Dal Soo, the laid-off
worker from Korea Shipbuilding
and Repairs Company.
Bae Dal Soo?
Bae Dal Soo!
I want to testify that the designer watch
and bribe from the Hanmin Bank president
incidents all occurred
because of me.
Because the Assemblyman has known about
Secretary Kim's identity for a long time,
if he had really wanted the
bribe, he would not have gotten
it through Secretary Kim. He
will testify to that, too.
Aigoo, these people, seriously!
Then, if Secretary Kim testifies,
can he somehow not get arrested?
That's up to the judge.
The prosecution won't let you alone.
Have you come prepared for it?
Yes.
Petitions for Denial of
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's.
Arrest Warrant by Cheon
No Shim and 22 Others.
Those are petitions
submitted by 23 assemblymen
including Assemblywoman
Cheon No Shim.
They are asking for a
non-custodial investigation
according to the principle
of presumption of innocence.
Please take them
into consideration.
Additionally,
there is a witness who wants to testify
to the innocence of the accused.
Please give him a
chance to testify.
Who is it?
It is the accused's secretary, Mr.
Kim Gyu Hwan.
Objection! Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan
is an abettor in this crime.
Even if he were an
abettor, if his testimony
would help in deciding
the accused's arrest,
he ought to be given
a chance to testify.
But, Assemblywoman Hong!
What are you talking about?
Why would the kid come here?
Your Honor! I request Mr.
Kim Gyu Hwan's testimony.
No! Your Honor, that
is not necessary.
The kid who should be studying now...
why would he appear here?
Your Honor!- No, you cannot allow it.
You absolutely must not!
Secretary Kim, get ready.
Just stay here.
His testimony has been denied.
What do you mean denied?
Please ask the judge again.
I must give it.
Assemblyman Jin's objection was more
decisive than the judge's opinion.
What?
Assemblyman Jin seems to have
worried about possible harm to you.
Then, what will happen
to Assemblyman Jin now?
The arrest warrant was signed.
Aigo...
Arrest...?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
[BREAKING NEWS] Arrest Warrant of
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil Issued.
Sang Pil. Hey, Sang Pil.
Let me go and move away.
Let me go.
Sang Pil.
Did someone die or something?
Why are you overreacting?
Sang Pil...
For a guy, you cry so easily.
I apologize for how
things turned out.
No, because I didn't
do my job properly,
it's my responsibility.
Let me entrust the
office to you and
hold this for me for awhile.
Don't wear this
and get arrested.
Don't worry.
By whatever means,
we will exonerate you from
this wrongful accusation.
Assemblywoman Hong,
let me entrust the.
Indifferent-to-BH faction
headquarters to you.
What do you mean headquarters?
Because I'm on my way to open a
branch office in Seoul Prison.
Even so, I am still the head.
Okay, I know.
Hyung, stop it. Stop crying.
But...
You said Gyu Hwan came.
Where did he go?
Jin Sang Pil. Jin Sang Pil.
Jin Sang Pil!
Assemblyman! You must
have had a hard time.
We believe in you, Assemblyman.
Thank you.-Be
strong Assemblyman!
Thank you.
Assemblyman, fighting!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil!
Assemblyman, go safely.
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil!
Oh, wait a second.
Gyu Hwan.
Gyu Hwan. Gyu...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Let's go.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil Jailed.
The Fall of "People's Truth".
Arrested and Jailed Last Night over Illegal
Political Funds and Bribery Charges.
Secretary General, the Hanmin bank
president requested a session with you.
Probably he wants to
ask for a lighter
punishment for his crime
of offering a bribe.
Secretary Im.-Yes,
Secretary General.
Don't ever mention that
matter before my face
in the future.
I understand. I will
take care of it.
You used to call for conservatism with a
warm human face, reformed conservatism
that is not hung up
on vested interests.
I invested my hope in the
sunbae who was that person.
Please come back to
yourself of that time.
Of course Reporter Kim,
the Indifferent-to-BH
faction is alive and kicking.
Of course, Assemblyman Jin
has been detained but
he is still an assemblyman
until convicted.
Moreover, I, Hong
Chan Mi, am here.
Yes, yes.
You are here, Assemblywoman?
What is it, Ms. Choi 00?
I'm saying good-morning to the deputy
boss of our Indifferent-to-BH faction.
You're prohibited from coming
within a 1-meter radius of me.
Assemblywoman, please
preside over our meeting.
What meeting?
A meeting of the Indifferent-to-BH
faction headquarters.
Headquarters?
Sim Dong Cheon?
Yes.
From now on, the
Indifferent-to-BH.
Headquarters aide assisting
Assemblywoman Hong
will be Secretary Sim.
Wow!
Are we getting back
together like this?
Yes.
"Hello again though I hate you."
Oh, well,
he is not my type, but
I will do as told.
So, what is the meeting agenda, Ms.
Choi 00?
How to break Hanmin Bank
President Kim Doo Shik.
I won't have much
trouble, right?
At the most, you will get
fined for offering a bribe.
Please use your influence
with the prosecution.
Bank President.- Yes.
From the beginning, there was
only one term between us.
In exchange for our
turning a blind eye to
your illegal lending of
$140M to Bando Group,
you will deny the fact that Jin
Sang Pil returned the money.
That is so, but...
Still, please give me
some consideration.
Well, I will give it a try.
Just how do you intend to
get the bank president?
We'll have to hire some people.
What do you mean some people?
You drag the guy
into a dug hole.
Then, you just shovel the dirt on him.
One shovel at a time.
Until he says the correct
thing, until the end.
Because that's too violent,
in the food that he eats,
let's secretly poison the food.
Then, I guess we have
to start tailing him.
Tail him?
When we get a chance,
bug his car as well.
Bugging?
My uncle sells stolen bugging
devices pretty cheaply.
Aide, should I buy a few with the
political contributions we received?
Oh, really! Really!
After you ask an
assemblywoman to come, what
are you trying to do?
Are you fooling around?
With normal tactics, we can't change
the bank president's mind, can we?
What?
No... the Indifferent-to-BH
faction is a place like this?
Yes, it is like this.
I'm really going to go crazy.
Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi, welcome
to the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
Please have a seat.
Now, we will really start the meeting
to get the Hanmin Bank president.
Yes, let's get him.
What is this?
Reporters, long time no see.
I am Gookmin Party's
Hong Chan Mi.
Regarding Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's arrest and imprisonment,
I will state our Indifferent-to-BH
faction's position.
The issue of this case is whether
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
returned the money he had received from
Hanmin Bank President Kim Doo Shik.
While Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil who is
denying the criminal charge is in prison,
Bank President Kim who has confessed to
offering a bribe is free to strut around.
This is wrong.
We, the Indifferent-to-BH
faction, demand that Hanmin Bank.
President Kim Doo Shik who is the
cause of this scandal resign.
Moreover, we make this solemn request
to the Financial Supervisory Service.
Hanmin Bank is a financial
institution where
vast sums of public
funds were injected.
We are requesting that you
immediately conduct a special
audit of the Bank and Bank
President Kim's activities.
Kim Doo Shik, Resign!
Resign! Resign!
Conduct a special audit!
Conduct it! Conduct it!
Kim Doo Shik, Resign!
Resign! Resign!
Conduct a special audit!
Conduct it! Conduct it!
Kim Doo Shik, Resign!
Resign! Resign!
Conduct a special audit!
Conduct it! Conduct it!
The economy will suffer if you poke
around a financial institution now!
How can you be swayed by this kind
of perverse demand for scrutiny?
Yes, then...
Tell Bank President
Kim not to worry.
Yes, I understand.
Secretary General Baek must
have used his influence
with the Financial
Supervisory Service already.
Jeez, we have to have a
stronger card to play.
The card calling for the Financial
Supervisory Service audit was just a feint.
A feint?- Our Indifferent-to-BH
faction's hidden punch is this.
According to Article 127-2 of the National
Assembly Act, request the Board of Audit
and Inspection to conduct the following
audit regarding Hanmin Bank management:
Board of Audit and Inspection?- Article
127-2 of the National Assembly Act.
The National Assembly may,
by resolution, request the.
Board of Audit and Inspection
to conduct an audit.
The Board, after receiving the
request, within 3 months,
has to report the audit
findings to the Assembly.
A resolution means a majority
of the assemblymen must agree.
Is there anything our matchless
Assemblywoman Hong cannot do?
Ah, you sly fox...
Board of Audit and Inspection... A
resolution for an audit request...
Hong Chan Mi is the primary
sponsor and to gather 10
co-sponsors, she is contacting
opposition party assemblymen.
Jin Sang Pil disappears but now,
Hong Chan Mi is causing a ruckus.
Even if one assemblyman
seems like nothing,
when you look into it,
they can be scary.
What is this?
You look so depressed
these days.
So I want to give some support
under my husband's name.
The Citizens' Federation
for Transparent Politics
claims that Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi of Gookmin Party
circumvented the law and
gave political contributions
to the party's prominent
assemblymen illegally
and reported her to the
National Election Commission.
They alleged that
Assemblywoman Hong, with an
eye to the next year's
election nomination,
provided the party leaders
including Secretary General.
Baek Do Hyeon, under the names
of her husband and parents,
political contributions that
exceeded the legal limit.
Assemblywoman, the National
Election Commission
will come to audit our
books and accounts.
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
Although I haven't lived long,
I get to be slapped after
giving money, I guess.
What is it that you want?
I heard that you are sponsoring
a resolution to request
the Board of Audit and
Inspection for an audit.
Stop it.
You may have thought that I would get
afraid with this kind of thing but no way!
Just because of my giving
you improper political
funds, do you think something
will happen to me?
In any event, I have no lingering
feelings for the Assembly Hall so
I have nothing that scares me.
This was just a
warning.-What warning?
A warning that shows you next time,
you may be hit with a harsher thing.
If you want to at least
practice law next year,
it will be good to keep
my warning in mind.
Secretary General Baek!
Warning, my ass.
Aide-What about
Assemblywoman Hong?
Earlier, they say she left
work in the afternoon.
You can give her a call. She's
probably working around here.
Her phone has been turned off.
What?
I think she's a bit
intimidated after being
reported to the National
Election Commission.
It's normal for anybody to get a bit
nervous when they experience those things.
Since Assemblywoman has a strong
will, don't think futile thoughts.
You must not tell the Assemblyman about
Assemblywoman Hong disappearing on us.
I got it.
Whether the food we
privately sent him was
edible, whether he wants
any books or magazines,
whether he has enough in
his commissary account,
you must make sure to
check and tell me later.
I'll be back.-Yes, okay.
Secretary Byeon! This.
Even though Assemblyman Jin is
not there, you seem very busy.
You know about the resolution for an audit
by the Board of Audit and Inspection.
It seems like Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi might
not want to do it. Why
don't you give it up?
It seems like you still haven't come to
your senses after getting a slap from me.
Please... let's not live as
trash but as human beings.
If you keep it up
this way, Aide Choi,
you might get really hurt.
Now, you don't even hesitate
before making threats.
Well, do as you wish.
I'm not the type to be
had by a piece of trash.
Secretary Kim!
It's been a while.
How the two of you are here...
Assemblyman Jin said that he knew from a
long time ago that you were attending here.
Assemblyman is asking for you to visit.
When is a good time?
Let's not do this here but
let's talk while eating.
Okay, let's go have
something yummy.
I don't intend to do that.
Wait a minute.
What do you think about joining
the Assembly office again?
For me...
The mere sound of the po from
politics is quite disgusting.
I was deceived by Aide
Choi for a moment.
I thought politics was so cool.
That's why I tried to make a bill through
the struggle, which didn't work.
By the way,
after all, it is trashy.
Secretary Kim.
Because it is trashy
or disgusting,
are you going to ignore it
for the rest of your life?
No matter how much you
despise or deny politics,
it is always governing
the whole of your life.
Anyhow, it is a worthless life.
I don't care whether it
is governed or whatever.
Let them do whatever
they want to do.
Kim Gyu Hwan.
I know you are acting like this because
of feeling guilt towards Assemblyman.
That isn't your fault.
So don't blame yourself.
That's right. I have
heard the story.
Our secretaries all
understand you.
Let's stop here. And I am
asking as a favor that
you don't look for me anymore.
Secretary Kim!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Who are you?
Aide Choi, how are you?
I am not very good.
Why?
Omo! You look worn out.
Didn't you sleep last night?
Yes. I was filming by
myself last night.
A mysterious thriller,
horror movie.
I seem to be getting
sensitive these days.
Hello.
Aide Choi, I got your mail.
To Aide Choi In Kyungc/o
Gookmin Party, Assemblyman Jin.
Sang Pil 1 Yeongdeungpo-dong,
Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul.
It doesn't show a sender.
What is this?
Aish! It looks like flour.
Aide Choi, weren't
you splattered?
Uhh! Da Jeong, what is this?
Turn your head. It's there too.
Aide Choi, report
this to the police.
Police?
This white powder must...
signify white terror
(STATE-SPONSORED TERRORISM).
Stop it.
I am right. Someone is threatening
Aide Choi with an act of terror.
Be quiet!
For a while,
we have to keep this secret.
If Assemblyman hears
this, nine out of ten,
he will tell us to stop
the audit request.
Do you understand?
Aide Choi!- Absolutely,
no one is to disclose
this matter.
Ah.
Ah, you came.
Have you been good?
Of course. It is not bad at all.
The meals are delicious.
There is no one nagging.
It's like a paradise.
Sit down. Don't I look
like I'm gaining weight?
Sit down quickly.
That's why I told you I would
request special visitation.
A special visitation
allows more time.
We can see each other more
comfortably in an office.
What is this glass between us?
It looks miserable.
Aigoo. Did I come here
to be treated well?
It is not right for me as an assemblyman
to get special treatment in jail.
Sit down quickly. We don't
have much time left.
When I look at you this
way, it's refreshing.
How about Assemblywoman Hong?
Is she alright?
I heard she was accused by the
National Election Commission.
She is courageous.
Since she's grown up sheltered,
she must be disturbed.
As soon as I get out of here, I will
knock Secretary General Baek down.
Should I break out of here
and get out right now?
Aide Choi, are you sick?
Pardon? No, I am not.
You look weak. Did
something happen?
Nothing happened.
Oh, no. Have I seen you
only once or twice?
Just looking at you,
it's not true that nothing happened.
It is written
on your face that you have
something worrying you.
There is nothing to worry about.
In case you were worried,
I just came to show my face
and tell you to be strong.
I know that you are
having a hard time.
I am sorry that I am merely
staying comfortably inside here.
When I get out of here, I
will really repay everything.
Yes. You must pay me back.
If only to receive what I
am owed from you, I must
get you out of here.
I will surely do it!
Aide Choi.
Without the rank insignia
(DISREGARDING RANKS),
may I tell something
in my heart?
Go ahead.
Except my wife,
among the women whom I know,
you are the most beautiful,
the smartest,
and the best-hearted.
You are saying that
I am the best, aren't you?
No. I mean I appreciate you.
That such a person
became my comrade...
Really,
truthfully, extraordinarily,
I feel sorry and
thankful.
Aigoo,
I can't even give
you a handkerchief.
I am such a silly goose.
I heard Assemblywoman Hong
is shutting herself up.
Probably, she is exercising
self-discipline since she
has been accused by the
National Election Commission.
Is she so timid?
She was running wild to
utilize the Audit Board.
Anyhow, there will be no demand for an
audit submitted to the National Assembly.
By the way, what business
prompted you to ask to see me?
Since it looks like the
Indifferent-to-BH is quiet,
would you make a written promise about
the division of party nominations?
Assemblyman Park, just believe me and
let's go with a gentlemen's agreement.
If you were the old Secretary
General Baek, I would.
Right now, it is difficult
to do it that way.
I think that Jin Sang Pil
was framed.
The most likely person
behind the false accusation
is Secretary General Baek.
I won't make a gentlemen's
agreement with such a person.
Then, I can't help it.
I will break the
agreement on the division
of party nominations.
You don't want
to do politics any more, do you?
In the future if the division of party
nominations between factions surfaces again
the list of names of
Anti-BH assemblymen who
received a designer watch
from President Lee Taek Jo
will be distributed
to the media.
Secretary General Baek.
What's wrong with you?
Assemblywoman, I was scared! You
should have made some noise.
What should I do when the
door opened spontaneously?
Where and what have you
been doing all this time?
What do you mean? I was
hiding out and came back now.
You pretended to be all strong
but you were scared off
when you got a punch from
Secretary General Baek?
I had to pretend to be scared, so Secretary
General Baek would lower his guard.
Yes?
KANG SANG HO: Assemblywoman Hong.
What became of the request for
an audit of Hanmin Bank to the
Board of Audit and Inspection?
I can surely support you for the sake
of financial development in Korea.
Fighting!
Secretary General Baek and
Anti-BH have become estranged.
Anti-BH seems to be using us in order
to attack Secretary General Baek.
How about it? Do you
realize the difference
of levels between Choi
In Kyung, you, and me?
Today, I acknowledge it.
Well. Let's start.
Okay. Follow me.
Pardon?
The audit request for Hanmin
Bank to be audited by the Board
of Audit and Inspection,
submitted by Assemblywoman Hong
with the support of the opposition parties
and the Anti-BH faction in Gookmin Party,
passed the National Assembly
Political Affairs Committee.
The audit request will come
to a vote at a plenary
session of the National
Assembly next week.
If passed, the Board of
Audit and Inspection
will conduct a
comprehensive audit of.
Hanmin Bank President Kim Doo Shik
and Hanmin Bank's overall business.
Baek Do Hyeon.
Baek Do Hyeon keeps calling us.
Listen to me carefully.
From now on, there is
absolutely no compromise.
Even if...
one of our arms or
legs is amputated
we will cut off Baek Do
Hyeon's neck this time.
What on earth did you do so far?
I will commit suicide by biting
my tongue here if we are
audited by the Board of Audit
and Inspection of Korea.
We will take care of it
before the plenary session.
I can't rely just on what you say.
Would you tell Secretary Baek to meet me?
No, I can't do it.- If you keep
acting this way, it will not be good.
If I so choose, not only
you, Chief Secretary Im, but
don't you know Secretary General
Baek will also be done for?
Bank President Kim Doo Shik!-
I will not die by myself.
Tell that to Secretary General Baek!
Hello? Hello?
What is it?
The guests from the Assembly came.
Who? Secretary General Baek?
Oh... Oh.
Our Assemblywoman Hong will explain
the Indifferent-to BH's perspective.
After passage of the request for
audit at the plenary session,
will you be audited by the Board
of Audit under public scrutiny,
or will you reveal the
reason you made a false
accusation against
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
and throw yourself upon the mercy of
the court and hope for a plea bargain?
Oh... oh... no.
Right now, what on earth
are you talking about?
Bank President, if you come clean,
we intend to submit a petition
requesting a reduction in your sentence.
We are not irresponsible,
unlike Secretary General Baek.
Oh, no.
Why are you guys here?
Move aside.
Hey, how do you speak informally
even though you are younger than me?
Won't you let me go? Let me go!
Hey!- Chief Aide Im Gyu Tae.
I received the flour you sent well.
Ah... I will deliver this as a present.
Befitting someone working in
the financial field, Bank.
President Kim was very meticulous
in taking care of business.
Voice recording 0002:30.
What is this?
Listen to this with Secretary General Baek.
Then, we will leave now because
of the press conference.
Reporters, I am telling you
this beforehand as a tip.
Call your news desks and tell them to
reserve the Front Page Top News sections.
Please use your influence
with the prosecution.
Bank President.- Yes.
From the beginning, there was
only one term between us.
In exchange for our
turning a blind eye to
your illegal lending of
$140M to Bando Group,
you will deny the fact that Jin
Sang Pil returned the money.
That is so, but...
Still, please give me some consideration.
Well, I will give it a try.
Bank President Kim Doo Shik has testified
that Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
threw back the money to his face.
This is the fact, the truth.
Accordingly, Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's indictment based on perjury
was null and void from the very beginning.
The prosecution must withdraw
the indictment and the court
must set Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil free immediately.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Assembly.
Indifferent-to-BH! Fighting!
Please stop them for me!-
Since you are quick-witted,
you must know very well how
you should handle yourself.
A petition to urge Baek
Do Hyeon's resignation?
Please relay this to the VIP.
It's a list of the designer watch
recipients within the Anti-BH faction.
Don't even think about
clumsily dragging us in today.
Please end this with the minimum
punishment in the least amount of time.
There must have been a
certain deal struck among.
Baek Do Hyeon, Park
Choon Seop and the BH.
I am here to announce the bill
which I am determined to pass.