All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Episode 18.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Sang Pil.
Assemblyman.
You suffered a lot.
I congratulate you
on your release.
Thank you.
All of you really,
really suffered a lot.
Congratulations.
National Assembly.
Thank you. Now,
let's go get them.
What?
Secretary General Baek.
Let's go.
Delete what's in here.
Hurry.
Hey, won't you get
rid of it quickly?
Hey, USB!- Okay.
Up there. That's right. Hurry
up and take the hard disk.
Quickly get it wiped clean.
Hurry.-Yes, I understand.
Hurry! Hurry!
Hello?
What did you say?
Secretary General, they say that
the investigators have arrived.
Please block it. If I get arrested,
I'll go to jail immediately.
You made the situation
like this and...
what is it that you
want me to do?
Secretary General.
I have no way to do
that immediately.
Secretary General.- Secretary
General, we'll be entering.
Because you can think on your feet,
you'll know how to handle it.
Secretary General...
What are you guys
doing right now?
I'm sorry, Secretary General.
We are from the.
Prosecutors' Office and we
ask for your cooperation.
Im Gyu Tae.-Yes?
Your arrest warrant. We
are arresting you on
charges of defamation and
destruction of evidence.
Let's go.
Secretary General.
Why do you want to go in there? I told you
that the police will take care of it.
Because Secretary General Baek sent
me to prison, I ought to thank him.
What is this? Where did everybody go?
They are not even outside.
What did I tell you. There
is no way they'll be here.
They ran because
they got scared.
What is the motive
for your crime?-Were
you ordered by Secretary
General Baek?
Secretary Im, did all this happen because
of Secretary General Baek's order?
The Secretary General has
nothing to do with this matter.
With a sincere thought that a demagogue
like Assemblyman Jin must be eliminated,
I did everything on my own.
All of you move. Move.
Is it really true that you
did everything on your own?
The Secretary General has
nothing to do with this matter.
With a sincere thought that a demagogue
like Assemblyman Jin must be eliminated,
I did everything on my own.
(Baek Do Hyeon's Chief.
(Secretary insists he
committed the crime alone.)
Yeah, right. Sincere
thought, my ass.
It appears they will be looking
into who is behind the matter.
This is KBC news.
Assemblyman Park, he is doing that hoping
that the Secretary General will save him.
It's because the only person he can
trust is Secretary General Baek.
But... if the feather
won't budge like that,
what's going to happen to
the main part of the body?
Once the feathers have
been plucked, there'll be
countless people who would
cook it up and eat it.
What?
We can just wait
with a spoon ready.
Reporters, take a look
at the haetae statue.
Haetae is an imaginary creature who's
supposed to crush evil and create good.
What would be the reason they have
this statue in front of the Assembly?
Political schemes such as the one that
happened recently must be eradicated.
Are you saying you also think there's
someone behind this incident?
Every citizen knows already,
who the mastermind is.
If the investigating
authority feigns ignorance,
they'll have to face huge
resistance from the citizens.
I demand an investigation against Gookmin
Party's Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
Im Gyu Tae is just
a mere minion.
At least this time we mustn't
make the mistake in which
we just pluck a feather
and let the body survive.
The investigating
authorities must summon.
Secretary General Baek
Do Hyeon immediately...
and reveal the truth behind the
scheme with crystal clarity.
How can something
like this happen?
I have nothing to do with it.
You can't just say you have nothing to do
with it. You have to take responsibility!
What do you mean,
responsibility?
Our party is about to take
a hit because of you.
Assemblywoman Park.
We have no more to say.
Make a statement regarding
this incident ASAP,
and decide what
you're going to do.
What do you mean, decide?
What are you talking about?!
How dare you? Do not interrupt
when the party leader's speaking!
Let me be clear. I can't
leave you with the task
of choosing nominations
in this circumstance.
Party Leader.
Please leave.
Yoon Jeong Soo, that person
is leader of the party
in name only but now, he
acts like a real leader.
I made a puppet into the
party leader and...
He thinks you have no
more strings to pull.
So meet up with VIP and get Chief
Secretary out of jail ASAP.
You have to save yourself too.
Because you are an astute politician, you'd
better get your act together somehow.
I trust you know what to do.
What's the matter?
Do Hyeon.
Here comes the stew.
Wow, it looks good!
Let me know if you need more.
I can make it fast.
How come there's just tofu? How
many tofu dishes are there?
They taste good. You're
being fussy for nothing.
You eat 'em
all, then.- Yeah.
Aigoo, really.
Now that we're all gathered
together, shall we make a toast?
Indifferent-to-BH, fighting!
Fighting!
But Assemblywoman Hong, are you
really going to keep sitting there?
Did you forget the conditions for me
joining Indifferent-to-BH faction?
Eating at the same table with
Choi Double 0 is prohibited.
Just come over here. Conditions, my butt.
What are you doing?
Sit here.- What
are you doing?
It's weird, you
sitting there alone.
Assemblyman Jin.- Just come.
Come!
Sit next to Aide Choi. Hurry!
Seriously.
From what I heard,
you were a perfect couple.
Don't even bring it up. Remember
the old movie we watched?
Starsky and Hutch.
They were even better.
Nah. They were men.
Thelma and Louise.
Are we Chinese restaurant ad stickers?
Stop sticking it everywhere.
I don't want to be considered
at the same level as her.
Ah, bad temper.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
What are you trying to do?
I'm giving you my heart.
See. She says it's her heart.
Miss So Min, have you tried to
get in touch with Gyu Hwan?
Pardon? That's...
You know his number?
Yeah.
I want to call him.
She called him several times, but
he doesn't answer, she says.
Look here, everyone.
We can't not sing on a great
day like this, right?
That's enough. Whose clamorous
noise do we have to hear again?
Stop acting like a fool
and sit down already.
I changed my repertoire.
You're too much.
Seriously.
Why doesn't someone else sing?
Miss So Min.
Huh? Me?
Or Da Jeong?
Get out there, together.
Yeah, do it!
Me, me, too.
♫ Touch my body Body ♫
♫ Touch my body♫
♫ I know you want it.
Come up to me.♫
♫ I have wine and sweet
chocolate chocolate ready
♫ A bit tender and just for
you a little warmed up ♫
♫ My face is turning crimson in
the reflection in your eyes ♫
♫ Take the wheel. Right, two
hands up toward the sky ♫
♫ Yeh baby dancing with
me you're my star♫
♫ Touch my body let's
do it a little faster♫
♫ Oh everybody higher
than the blue sky. ♫
♫ Now the rhythm is great. You
and I under the hot sun. ♫
♫ My body body Touch me body ♫
♫ Baby so good now I
feel it's paradise. ♫
♫ Baby so nice just by
ourselves summer night
♫ Bit by bit, one step, two step.
You and I in the moonlight. ♫
♫ My body body Touch my body♫
♫ Touch my body Body ♫
I have to see VIP and tell him I have
nothing to do with this incident.
Secretary General Baek, let's
not become any more disgraced.
What did you say?
If you really are VIP's
close aide, act like one,
don't be a burden and
deal with it yourself.
Because you are an astute
politician, you'd better get
your act together somehow. I
trust you know what to do.
Have you heard the Supreme
Council will be held?-Yes.
They're trying to push through
Secretary General Baek's dismissal.
Seeing the timid Party Leader Yoon
Jeong Soo's attempt at a quick
procedure and conclusion, there must
be mediation between BH and him.
Secretary General Baek is
now in the Nakdong River...
A duck egg. (A saying that means
someone has been totally isolated.)
What is this? Why are you
suddenly well paired again?
What are you doing by standing
over there? Sit here.
Are you serious?
You are getting muscles on your ugly legs.
Sit quickly.
Thank you.
By the way, Secretary
General Baek seems to be
doing some tricks like
political engineering.
He won't docilely resign.
Before, when you were about
to become Secretary General,
he demanded secession of the
President from the party.
There is one thing that
bothers me about him.
What is it?
As one of those closest
to VIP and having the
most actual influence
in the ruling party,
the intelligence that
Secretary General Baek has!
The intelligence?
The statement that urges
Baek Do Hyeon's resignation?
You have to funnel the wind before
the Supreme Council meeting is held.
That's how that worthless person, Yoon
Jeong Soo, will get his strength.
I got it.
The eel-like punk!
Let me see...
Yes.
What's the occasion for this visit
to my office, Secretary General?
I came to deliver something
to Assemblyman Kang.
To me? What is it?
Oh... What...
What is it?
Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho.
My name is listed here?
Do you remember President Lee
Taek Jo who gave a luxury watch
to Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil and raised a scandal?
Lee... Lee Taek Jo?
This is a list of the Anti-BH assemblymen
who received those luxury watches.
Oh, yes.
Deliver this to
Assemblyman Park.
Until the Supreme Council meeting ends,
do not take any action but stay still.
Gookmin Party.
So, did you decide?
Yes.-You thought well.
Then, before the Supreme
Council meeting opens, have
the press conference to
announce your resignation.
My decision is not to do that.
Party Leader, I am aware that
you have a rather intimate
relationship with Chairman
Kim of Yoongwang Company.
What is the meaning
of your saying that?
Earlier, I know that you
and Chairman Kim went
together to Central America
for economic matters.
At that time, the amount of travel
expenses you received was...
Secretary General Baek.
This is but one of the many pieces
of information that I have.
If you are interested in other information
that I have, then dismiss me.
Today, the Supreme Council should
adopt an official position
that I had nothing to do
with Im Gyu Tae's case.
Then...
Yes, Chairman?
Connect to the BH quickly.
Are you saying you won't dismiss
Secretary General Baek?
Chairman, why are you
doing this all of sudden?
For now, I understand.
I'll call you back.
Assemblyman's
prediction was correct.
Party Leader Yoon
changed his position.
I just said that. This prediction
came from Aide Choi's brain.
I see. The VIP praised her
from time to time but
I see that you were
worthy of the praise.
Anyway, because of this one
loach (bottom-dwelling,
(eel-like scavenger), whether
it's the party or the BH,
face isn't the only thing lost.
Secretary.
Please, relay this to the VIP.
What is this?
It's a loach recipe that the
Indifferent-to-BH faction devised.
Recipe.
Gookmin Party.
Gookmin Party's 57th Supreme
Council Meeting for 2015.
Agenda: Secretary General
Baek Do Hyun's Dismissal.
Party Leader Yoon's
not here yet.
He must have a lot
to think about.
Do you really think
you can hold out?
Punk, I guess he has
something he can count on.
Hello, Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu.
It's been a long time.
You're suffering a lot,
Secretary General Baek.
Not at all.
What's the occasion? The main body
and Avatar rarely come together.
Are you here to watch?
I came to warn you.
This is a fight between
you and the leadership.
Don't threaten us or try
to get us involved.
You're not the only one
with classified info.
I'll keep that in mind.
I wish you luck.
Thank you.
Do as Assemblyman Jin says. That's
the right thing to do for the party.
Party Leader, they're just jumping
to conclusions by themselves.
Don't let them deceive you.
Jumping to conclusions?
We're aware of both of your involvement
in Party Leader Yoon's corruption.
What?- Did the Blue House really
give such information to you?
Yes.
That's a lie. There's no way the Blue
House could've done such a thing.
Then, shall we head straight to the
press conference and expose the truth?
I have nothing to hide. Do
whatever you need to do.
I understand.
Choi In Kyung, let's go.
You two ladies. What's so urgent?
Wait there for a bit.
Party Leader.
Don't you understand why
I brought this here instead of
making this public right away?
Reason? Are you saying you
did this for me or what?
Why would I do that for you? I
don't even like you that much.
I did it because
I don't want to.
You don't want to do what?
I want to be a politician,
not someone who exposes things.
What... expose?
Yes. What I've seen the most ever
since I came to the Assembly...
What I saw happening so often that
I'm sick and tired... were exposés.
Someone did something to someone, someone
swallowed up how much from someone...
Exposing everything and taking
everything off and just...
Stabbing someone's back... and most
of them turn out to be rumors...
and fabrications and...
They're all like that.
So?
I've done that a
few times myself,
but it's not very good for mental health,
and it seems quite addictive, too.
But the bigger problem is that the
citizens are really sick and tired of it.
They're really disgusted.
Party Leader. Please
do as I say this time.
Let's not deceive the
citizens anymore, please?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
What a nice sight.
I'm don't feel good about this.
Do you think
the Indifferent-to-BH is
cooking up something?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
The Gookmin Party's 57th Supreme Council
Meeting for 2015 will now come to order.
Three members of the
Supreme Council submitted
a petition for the dismissal of
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
I'll listen to what Secretary
General Baek has to say first.
First,
for worrying the party and the citizens
due to my chief secretary's offense,
I feel deeply sorry.
But since I have nothing to do with
Chief Secretary Im Gyu Tae's crime,
I believe I have no
reason to be dismissed.
He sure has a thick face.
If I turn out to have committed
even the slightest wrongdoing,
I'm willing to accept any kind of
appropriate legal consequences.
But until then, I would like diligently to
fulfill my duty as the Secretary General.
I request that the Honorable
Party Leader Yoon Jeong Soo
as well as the Supreme Councilmen
make a wise decision. Thank you.
We'll make the final decision.
We will not accept the petition for
Secretary General Baek's dismissal.
How despicable.
We will present
an urgent matter.
Urgent matter?
Since I became the chairman
of the ruling party,
it has been more than 1 year.
During that time, I don't
think I fulfilled my
promise made to the
people and party members
to carry out public-office
innovation and reform.
Besides that, events up
to the case of Secretary.
General's Chief Secretary
damaging an assemblyman, etc.
Have mired the party in
confusion and chaos.
Since I fully realize the heavy
responsibility borne by a party leader,
I will resign
the position of party leader.
What? Resignation?
I, also, will do the same as
the Chairwoman of the Party.
I will resign too.
What on earth are you doing now?
Resignation?
Gookmin Party Regulations
Article 172:
If more than half of the
Supreme Council resign,
the organization of the
party leaders shall be
dissolved automatically.
Don't you know that?
Wow, he doesn't know it
yet, because he landed
in the Gookmin party
only a few days ago.
Then, what is Secretary
General Baek going to do?
The leadership of the party is dissolved
so there will be no Secretary General.
It will be an auto-resignation.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Yes. President.
I watched how one
cooks the loach.
By the way, isn't
it too extreme?
Yes. It is extreme but...
I will read what my aide
wrote a short time ago.
If we are to regain the citizens'
confidence in government and the party and
if there is to be stable leadership
during the latter half of my term
it would be best for
incompetent party leaders
and Baek Do Hyeon to resign.
That is my opinion.
What are your thoughts?
My thoughts? Yes. My
thoughts are important too.
My thought is that catching only
one loach will be not enough.
After taking out all the water and catching
the rest, then we have to refill the water.
Assemblyman! Manners, be polite.
Yes. I think we have to
fill the water again.
Yes. I understand.
If you rely on us,
we will try to do it.
Yes. Goodbye, President.
Aide Choi.
You, too.
Citizens.
We are sorry.
Following the resignation of
the Gookmin Party leadership,
the party will temporarily be
run by an ad-hoc committee.
Floor Leader Choe Joon Goo, who is
acting head of the Gookmin Party,
revealed at a press briefing
that a convention to elect the
party's leadership will be held
either at the end of the regular
legislative session in December
or in January next year.
...is something
especially different. Our.
Indifferent-to-BH's
position is firm.
Meanwhile, Assemblyman Baek
Do Hyeon, who is suspected of
suborning perjury by the President
of Hanmin International Bank,
appeared behind closed doors to
be examined by the prosecutor
and then returned home today.
It is known that Assemblyman Baek flatly
denies the allegations against him, but
the prosecution intends to carry
out an intensive investigation
by summoning him again
to confront Mr. Im.
Once called the Seo Dae Han
Administration's Crown Prince
and classified as a next-term
candidate for President,
Assemblyman Baek is on the brink
of becoming a political pariah.
Assemblyman.
You didn't go to bed?
Yes. I have something to do.
Oh.
You really are trying
to make something?
Yes.
But what kind of bill?
Just... I want to make a law
for the ordinary
dads of this world.
Huh?
But since I don't know what to do,
it is possible I might not make it.
I think I still won't
be able to draft it.
Assemblyman Jin.
Gyu Hwan isn't showing up now.
But why?
I don't know what.
He didn't enroll this month.
Actually when you were in
jail, Aide Choi met with him.
Aide Choi did?  - Yes.
She asked him to come
back to your office,
but he refused.
But why?
Even when he hears the
"po" in "politics"
he told her it makes him sick.
What she said is, it seems he feels
remorse because you were arrested.
He has become more cynical.
Honestly, I'm concerned.
Okay. I understand.
Thank you for telling me.
But... Aide Choi
said you would worry
so I was absolutely
never to tell you.
If you were to say I told you...
But why is everyone more
afraid of her than me?
Just the sound of her bawling
you out terrifies you.
You're a hopeless wuss. A wuss!
What is so scary...
Oh.
Aide Choi.
Assemblyman, is is true
that the money you received
while in prison was
given to the prisoners?
Ah, that money?
Yes, I... that...
I bought and shared tasty side
dishes too with those around me...
That money would have paid the
car rent expense for a month.
Did you think we were in a
position to be helping others?
That's true. I know, but I felt sorry that
I was being released from prison first...
I'm sorry. I forgot that.
Secretary Song, what
are you doing here?
What? Ah I was... asking
for advice about life.
Assemblyman. Thank you
for the wise advice.
Yeah. Okay.
Ask anytime. About living life.
Yes.
What are you saying?
Aigoo. Life...
She's still an adolescent.
What now?
While checking the documents
seized by the prosecutor
I found a file.
What is this?
It's the bill that
Secretary Kim drafted.
A Proposed Bill Re:
A Second Chance.
Is this everything?
Yes.
A Second Chance?
So random. What the heck
does "Second Chance" mean?
I too have never heard
of this before.
Hey Song. Did you do
an internet search?
Yes. I tried, but there
isn't anything much.
It's just some scribbling.
Because Secretary
Kim drafted it.
Could it have something
to do with his father?
I knew it! I knew it!
That's surprising.
When Hyung Dal Soo got divorced,
he lived life like a widower.
So isn't the bill made for people who
live alone and those who remarry?
What does the law
have to do with that?
You hook up with someone
and live together.
What are you up to?
Speaking of which, we also
should have a comeback together.
Have I even had a first?
Jeez. Stop making a fool of
yourself in front of the staff.
This feeling is a
first for me too.
There's something I figured out.
Is there?
I knew you were a
computer, really.
Secretary Kim. He wanted to make a law
about a consolation prize for losers.
Consolation prize?
Just... I want to draft a bill for
the ordinary dads of this world.
But then, how did you know what
it is by looking at the title?
A long time ago there was someone
similar who drafted a bill like this.
A long time ago?
Yes.
Chief Secretary Im, has
it been really hard?
It's unfortunate you
are in detention.
I will do my best to prevent somehow
your serving a prison sentence.
Will you go so far as
a suspended sentence?
Do it as quickly as possible.
It would be great if it
was a minimum sentence.
I will claim substantial
compensation after I get out.
- Chief Secretary Im.
- Don't forget
your political life...
depends on this.
Let's make a
consolation prize law.
Consolation prize law?
Think about it. You have multiple
competitions in this world and
competition by necessity
has winners and losers.
When there is only a reward for the winner
without any consideration for the loser,
how far can the world go?
How do you intend to show
consideration for the losers?
By giving a belief that life is not
over after you have lost once.
How will that be done?
By giving an opportunity
to try again.
A Second Chance.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Eight years ago. Do you remember
the Second Chance Bill,
which was not submitted
to the Assembly
because the party's
policy panel opposed it?
That was your
original resolution.
I am looking forward
to seeing you admit
your past mistakes and
making a fresh start.
Secretary Lee.
Please make a U-turn
at the next light.
Yes, Assemblyman.
Yes.
Hankook University Professor Park Young
Sam and Attorney Yoon Sun Hae seem
to be strong candidates to chair the
Emergency Response Commission (ERC).
Really?
They would be okay.
How did they decide to make up the
Emergency Response Commission (ERC)?
One from each faction and the rest will
be filled by public figures from outside.
One per faction, does that include
the Indifferent-to-BH faction?
Just get ready to print new
business cards for Assemblyman Jin.
Assemblyman.
Aren't you happy? An Emergency
Response Commission
member is at the same level
as a supreme councilman.
Can't you just do it,
Assemblywoman Hong?
But I am in the National
Election Commission's
clutches over a political
contribution issue.
People will cuss me out, saying I
haven't come to my senses yet.
I guess you're like this
because you feel uncomfortable
about factions divvying
up the positions.
But this is an emergency.
You have to be
there to counterbalance
the Pro- and Anti-BH
and to help out the chairperson
coming from outside.
I really don't feel like it. The
very sound of it is unattractive,
Bidet... (Korean pronunciation
sounds like toilet seat or obese)
If you won't do this either, I
will really quit this office.
Why do you bring up this
unnecessary topic again?
I really mean it.
Why are you like this
again, scaring me...
If you're scared,
be an ERC member!
Ah, I got it. I will do it.
Really?
Ah, yeah...
You should have
done this earlier.
Assemblyman Jin.
Yes?
As the old saying goes,
never hang on to a
daughter-in-law or an
aide who wants to leave.
Should I introduce you
to a very capable aide?
Oh, well, can you do that for me?
Even better
if the person doesn't engage in
drunk drivel and is amiable.
That kind of person is a dime a dozen
in the Assembly Hall. The age group?
The younger, the better...
I guess.
If you are going to buy a skirt
anyway, go for the vermillion one
(prettier, better one). Trends
cannot be ignored in politics.
A guy would be better. I
can go to the bathhouse
with him and we can scrub
each other's backs.
Guy? Bathhouse...
Do it.
What? You want me to
step down from the.
Strategy and Finance
Committee chair position?
But, why are you saying
this out of the blue?
Just quit if I tell you to quit.
But, this old man,
has he gone senile?
Assemblyman Park, do you know
how meaty that position is?
Do you know how much I wined and dined
assemblymen to occupy that seat?
Assemblyman Kang.
You will have to take
our seat on the ERC.
Ah, well, ERC...
Emergency Response
Commission member? Me?!
It's about time that you
take a party position.
Do well.
Oh...
Assemblyman Park, thank you very much!
I will work hard!
Yes, work hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
A glory to my family.
Assemblyman Park.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Go to the investigating authorities
and promptly admit the charges.
Hiding behind an aide is not
something an old hand should do.
I intend to get Mr. Im Gyu
Tae out as soon as possible.
Do you have that kind of power
still remaining in your hands?
I will have to regain it.
Because one defeat does not
mean no second chance.
It is getting late.
Why don't you go back now?
Actually, I
have a very dangerous
item in my hands.
But it is also an item
you would covet a lot
if you were to see it.
What is that?
Presidential election
funds that were not
reported to the National
Election Commission.
If you help me with my comeback,
I will gladly give it to you.
Oppa, it's me, Joo Hee.
Have you been well?
Yes, go on.
Aigo, really, so gruff. When you
answered only after one million calls.
Sorry. I've been a bit busy.
What's up?
Oppa, what are you doing tomorrow?
If you have nothing
to do, would you like to
go to a PC room with me?
Oppa, I am dying of
boredom nowadays.
But I have so much to do lately. I
don't have time to play with you.
Ah, really. I wouldn't ask you for this
kind of favor if only my dad lived with me.
Joo Hee.- Huh?
I'm sorry but don't
call me in the future.
Don't text me either.
Um, I got it.
Good-bye.
Oppa!
Really just one game, okay?
Okay. Just one game. Let's go!
You could be a pro gamer. How can
you move your hands so fast?
It's because I did
martial arts, why?
Ah... I want to play with
you like this everyday.
Joo Hee.- Yes?
I have an exam coming up soon. So
don't call me for a while, okay?
I understand.
I will leave first.
Uh huh. Good-bye.
Yes, Aide Choi.
Assemblyman, where are you right now?
Hurry and come back.
Why? Did something happen?
The atmosphere is ominous.
Assemblyman.
What's the matter?
The deputy party leader had an emergency
meeting with the floor leaders.
A rumor is circulating that
they are going to announce
the members of the Emergency
Response Commission.
Without consulting us, just among
themselves? Where is Assemblywoman Hong?
She went to the meeting
place but was refused
entrance because they
said it was private.
These people, really.
Assemblyman.
Assemblywoman, what happened?
We got shafted.
I am Assemblyman Kang
Sang Ho who has been
selected as a member of Gookmin Party's
Emergency Response Commission.
I will tell you the names
of the five people
who were finalized as
the ERC members today.
As members from
outside the Party,
former Supreme Court Justice Park
Joo Young, Professor Jo Jeong Hwa,
these two people were appointed.
And as inside members,
I, Kang Sang Ho,
and Assemblyman Baek
Do Hyeon were chosen.
What the heck is this?
Assemblyman! But isn't
Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon
currently being investigated
by prosecutors?
Oh,
but he is neither indicted nor
are his charges proven, right?
I will continue and
announce the chairperson
of the ERC that everyone
is curious about.
Until the next party
convention, the chairperson
who will lead our
Gookmin Party's.
Emergency Response
Commission is...
Assemblyman Park Choon Seop.
Emergency Response Commission
Chairman Park Choon Seop.
Assemblyman Park.
You seized the party leadership.
Congratulations.
Congratulations
on your comeback.
Let us work well
together in the future.
Please take care of me.
There definitely was a certain deal among
Baek Do Hyeon, Park Choon Seop, and the BH.
Cornered Baek Do Hyeon must
have offered something
while pushing Park Choon
Seop as the chairman
of the Emergency
Response Commission.
What is that?
Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon oversaw the
affairs of the past presidential election.
For sure...- The
election-related funds?
Yes, that must be it.
I will further analyze
the situation and come
up with a counter-strategy
as soon as possible.
Just let it be.
What?
No matter what foolery the Pro-
and Anti-BH factions engage in,
let us just do the
work that we have do.
Assemblyman, I understand
that you are disheartened.
But because of Assemblyman
Baek's power hunger,
the leadership of the ruling party fell
into the hands of the tired old power.
Are you saying we
should ignore it?
I'm not saying this
because I'm disheartened.
Nor am I ignoring it.
I just want to stop exchanging
blows and fighting.
I want to start doing
real politics.
What is the real politics
you have in mind?
Lawmaking.
Assemblymen are not fighters.
They are lawmakers.
They are elected so that
they can make good laws that
would better the people's lives
even by a slight degree.
But look. How much remains
of the regular session now?
Not much.
Aide Choi.
Assemblywoman Hong.
No matter what foolery
other people engage in,
let us just go our way, okay?
Yes, let's.
Yes.
I was short-sighted.
I am sorry.
Gyu Hwan.
Assemblyman.
What are you doing
here right now?
When you should be studying,
what are you doing here?
I am doing this so I can study.
What?
Leave. The business
will be open soon.
Hey, did Hyung Dal Soo also know
about what a troublemaker you are?
Don't bring up Father.
I still
cannot laugh and talk
about him with you.
Leave. The owner
will be here soon.
Leave what, punk?
Call him and tell him
you're quitting.
And register as an intern again.
I won't make you work overtime, so you
can attend a night school, got it?
Let's go.
I have no thought of that.
Just leave.
Let's go, punk.
Didn't I tell you
I don't want to?
Listen to me, please, punk!
Why on earth are you
doing this to me?
Because I'm Bae Gyu Hwan?
Because you think you can erase your
guilt towards my father this way?
I don't need all
this almsgiving.
So just go.
Yes, punk, it's because
you're Bae Gyu Hwan.
So I want to show
you, that's why.
You, punk, said just the sound of
"po" in "politics" makes you retch.
So let's go. I will show
you what real politics is.
Stick by my side and watch.
Got it?
Chairman, Jin Sang Pil is giving
a news conference right now.
This fellah... did
he catch on somehow?
Yes, I am People's Spoilsport
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, the
big boss of Gookmin Party's
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
The reason I am here today...
is not to expose something.
Nor am I here to criticize
the Pro- and Anti-BH
factions suddenly being
very buddy-buddy lately.
My purpose for being here
today is to introduce
a bill that I must absolutely, undoubtedly
pass during this regular
session of the Assembly.
What the...
Yes, I know.
That this kind of story is
not newsworthy, I do know.
But you have to publicize
these kinds of stories too
so that we assemblymen would
try to make even better laws.
It won't take much of your
time, so listen carefully
and I hope you report a lot about it.
Ms. Choi In Kyung, over there...
Yes, the bill I will
primarily sponsor this time
is one that allows our country
and society to support,
and to extend a helping hand
to those among our countrymen
who could not help but
fall down, despite
having done their utmost
to live diligently.
Namely, a bill to support giving a
second chance to those who have lost.
But what kind of bill name is like that?
Just by hearing it, I can
tell it's about populism.
All the while I was making this bill,
there was a person who did not leave
my thoughts even for one moment.
That person worked harder
than anybody else.
He was more conscientious
And more than anybody else...
he was a really great father.
But because of just one defeat,
because of that defeat...
he was a person
who broke down so helplessly, so painfully.
If to that person, just one
more chance had been given,
no, even if he could have had a belief that
one more chance would be given to him,
in my opinion, I absolutely believe
that he would not have
climbed that tall crane.
That person is...
Even though some of you
might remember, probably
almost everyone must have
forgotten him, probably so.
The late Mr. Bae Dal Soo...
the laid-off worker from Korea
Shipbuilding &amp; Repairs Co.
Assemblyman...
has bet even his life on this bill.
If something goes wrong, that
will be your responsibility.
Yes, so for me, the real
name of this bill is...
Bae Dal Soo...
yes, it's Bae Dal Soo's Law.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki