All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
What do you want to ask me?
Oh, there is a matter we are
internally investigating.
Internal investigation?
You know Hanmin Bank?
Hanmin Bank...
You received a shopping bag with money in
it from the bank president's secretary
and delivered it to Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, right?
Tell me, did you deliver it to
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil or not?
6th Day of the
Parliamentary Inspection.
Topic...
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Episode 16.
Dong Cheon.- Yes.
You didn't leak this questionnaire to
the Ministry of the Environment, right?
Absolutely not.
Oh, wait...
I guess even a busy
person like you
participates in the
parliamentary inspection?
Because I'm an assemblyman before
being a secretary general.- Yeah...
How do you find your first
parliamentary inspection? Doable?
Haven't you seen the
mid-term announcement from
that Parliamentary Inspection
Monitor or something?
I made the candidate
list for being the best
assemblyman during the
parliamentary inspection.
That deserves congratulations.
Shall I tell you one more thing
I should be congratulated on?
Our party conducted a public opinion
poll in Gyeongje City yesterday.
Secretary General, you
got 35% and I, 58%.
Public opinion is like a lover just before
jilting you. Don't count on it too much.
Didn't I tell you before
that I would never lose to you,
if only for Hyung Dal Soo's sake?
I... will trample you.
There is a fact that you
must be aware of, too.
That this inspection is the first and
last parliamentary inspection for you.
Ah... just one look
and I can tell
you are brewing some stinking sh*t.
I better be careful.
Then.
2015 Parliamentary Inspection by
Environment and Labor Committee.
See this, okay? See
this right now.
These are the numbers
showing marine pollution
due to the industrial
wastewater in Gyeongje City.
Look, in BOD from 5
to 16.4, 4.5 to 18.95 in COD.
Take a look!
How many times is this!
Are you going to kill them all?
Are you crazy?!
What are you doing not
managing these things!
Are you going to kill
everyone in Gyeongje City?
Don't touch the glasses!
I'll give this to you, so
take it home and study it.
Take a very careful look.
Frame it, put it up on the
wall and study it everyday.
Play it, Secretary Park.
A group of experts,
my staff and I
personally went down to Gyeongje
River and tested the water quality.
Our Director of Korea Water Quality
Management Company, take a look.
Take a good look. Is
that a river now?
Huh?
Does that look like a river?
What do you see?
Does it seem like sewage water?
Do you think that was
pumped from a septic tank?
That is none other than the
Gyeongje River. The current.
Gyeongje River where all
fishes have died out!
Huh?! What are you
going to do about it?
What are you going to do about all those
fishes? You hurry and revive them now!
Moving on to the next one.
Do you see that, huh?
Are you tending a green tea
field in the river, now?
Green tea field, green tea field?
What are you going to do?
What kind of management work
are you doing, seriously!
Stop fidgeting with your glasses.
Why do you, why...
I even personally
brought a sample.
Do you see this? I thought you
might not believe it. I didn't
put anything in it, I just
ladled this out, personally.
Taste it.
Here, this too. You are
getting plenty today.
Why are we not prepared?
Are you sticking it to me?
From tomorrow until the end of
the parliamentary inspection,
prepare all questionnaires like that.
Go back to your seat.
Only my aides can do it. Not
everyone is capable of that.
And do you admit this levee construction
in Gyeongje City was done shoddily?
It wasn't shoddy work.
Not shoddy work? Are you sure?
You can get punished for perjury during a
parliamentary inspection. Don't you know?
Seeing how you're touching your
glasses, it is a lie. Fine.
I will read you all of the
materials I prepared.
First... Ah, ah, ah. Chairwoman,
please give me more time.
Enough already. Other assemblymen
have to question too.
But I have to do everything I prepared.
When I came with this much preparation...
If you do everything at the
beginning, what does that make us?
Are you the only one
doing the parliamentary
inspection? When we've
prepared as much as you?
Wow, between fellow party
members, you're so petty.
Assemblyman Jin, I
will give you my five
minutes of additional question time.
Use that.
Aigo, thank you, Assemblywoman Cheon!
Aigo, thank you.
Did you see that? When even an opposition
party assemblywoman is like that?
But please give it to me
quickly, the 5 minutes?
Oh, it's working well.
Witness, from now on,
to the questions I ask
answer in no uncertain terms.
Understand?
Are you really not going
to submit the materials?
Don't you know this is against the
Board of Audit and Inspection Act?
What? A meal?
That place's taste has changed, unlike
the good old times. But I know...
Now, did I ask for a meal or materials?
It's not like I'm going around hungry.
Send them to me by midnight.
Hang up.
But what do they
take an aide for?
Rain, rain. Eat the rain man.
Which one do I eat? Which one?
Of course you have to eat ssangpi.
That's right!
Rain ssangpi.
That's right.
What are you doing?
I'm just taking a breather
from making press materials.
I'm going to go to Aide
Choi and tell on you.
It's fun, right? Right?
So much fun. You can't
lose the money I've won.
I got it, I got it.
Just because they don't have to work on
questionnaires, they are being too much.
Yes, why?
Environment and Labor
CommitteeMeeting Room.
Aide Seo, you did write a
questionnaire to support companies
with innovative environmental
technologies, right?
Yes, but why?
But the Assemblyman
does not have it.
What did you say?
When I worked so hard to
make this questionnaire,
how can you take this out?
It does not fit the tone of the
Assemblyman's legislative activities.
But that the government should
give some support to companies
that come up with cutting-edge
new technologies...
Why does that not fit
the Assemblyman's tone?
It does not fit.
Look here, Aide Choi.
Even though you're the
senior aide, this is
exceeding your authority.
I'm in charge of questionnaires.
I was not going to
bring this up, but
that questionnaire. Didn't a new technology
company solicit you to write it?
What? What do you take me for...
Special interest
legislation after getting
lobbied for it, that is
not the only evil thing.
Making special interest
questionnaires like this one after
getting solicitations, that
practice also has to disappear!
Since the Assemblyman does
not know about this, be
careful not to repeat this
sort of thing in the future.
What do you mean the
Assemblyman doesn't know?
Do you even know who
that company owner is?
Who?- President
Lee Taek Jo of SOI.
Lee Taek Jo?
I mean that $5000 designer watch that
almost cost Secretary Kim his job...
The person who gave that.
The Assemblyman
returned that watch.
Who returned what now?
When the giver says he
didn't get it back.
What?- How could I stick it out
without writing him that questionnaire?
Give it to me. I will
return it to President Lee.
It's okay. The punk who
received it must return it.
Parliamentary inspection
is no small job.
Really...
Aide Choi, get me Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi's address.
So I can try to see her.
Give me an honest answer to the
question I'm about to ask.
Why are you like this again
all of a sudden? What is it?
What did you do with
that designer watch you
had received from
President Lee Taek Jo?
I got cash for it and bought
bread for homeless people.
Don't joke around!
I'm not joking.
You are not joking?
If you don't believe
me, ask Gyu Hwan.
He worked like a dog for
several days because of that.
Didn't you say you
exchange emails everyday?
Why don't you just confess?
From a trustworthy source,
we got very detailed information
about your involvement
in the delivery of the bribe
before summoning you.
Because I was not convinced by Chief
Secretary Lim's transcript alone,
I put temptation in the
Assemblyman's way.
Pleading the fifth, may get
you left holding the bag.
Fine. Why don't you
just leave for today?
Take out money from the
Assemblyman's salary
tomorrow and buy the exact same watch
as the one President Lee gave.
Okay.
Forget it, why do that?
You stay quiet, Assemblyman.
Clearly you have violated
the Political Funds Act.
But, just... It's
just, it's okay.
If I had that kind of money, I'd
rather buy my Joo Hee some clothes.
Would it have been any
better to do that?
Are you some sort of a benevolent thief who
robs from the rich to give to the poor?
Why did you buy homeless
people bread, why?
Then, should I have bought
those people in poor health
alcohol? Of course I should
have bought them bread.
Assemblyman!
I am sorry. At that
time, I did not know
that things would
get this serious.
You just try this one more time.
Then, I'm really going to cane you.
Me too.
7769? Call.
Who is it?
Oh, hello. I am Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, the.
People's Spoilsport who
always tries his best.
Is Assemblywoman Hong
home, by any chance?
No, she is not.
Oh, really? Then, do you by
any chance know where...
Hello?
Hello!
What the...
Does this run in her family?
Why hang up so suddenly?
Seriously...
Yes, this is Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, the.
People's Spoilsport who
always tries his best.
Assemblyman.
Oh, it's you, Gyu Hwan.
Yes.
Okay,
have you been well?
Where are you right now?
Hey, punk, while an elder is
greeting you, how can you
abruptly ask for the whereabouts?
Punk, do you really want
to get some beating?
I said where are you!
I am out to meet
someone, happy, punk?
I would like to see you now.
Now?
Gyu Hwan, let's meet
at home.- Assemblyman!
I'll get home soon, so let's meet at
home in a little bit. I've got to go.
Assemblywoman Hong!
How can an assemblywoman
not come to the Assembly?
Because you are not even showing your
face in the inspection hearings,
reporters and NGOs are up in arms
about that, do you know that?
I am prepared to be reviled.
During my press conference to announce
my resignation, I will return my salary
and apologize to the people.
Are you really going to resign?
Yes.
No, don't do that. Just join
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
I will be good to you.
I guess you're mistaken because
I opposed your expulsion.
But at that time, just
out of embarrassment...
I did that because I didn't
want to be embarrassed.
It's okay if you do not join
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
But isn't quitting the
Assembly too much?
When the people put you there.
The people
put me there?
Of course.
No.
I was just the newest model...
the brand-new latest product.
What, newest? A new model?
During the general
election 4 years ago,
displayed in a window of the
shop called the Gookmin Party,
the latest item with a glitzy
design but of unproven quality!
That was Hong Chan Mi.
Why do you torment
yourself like that?
What's wrong with you, when
you are pretty and smart?
You talk well. You're diligent.
It's just your personality
that is a bit...
When I was selected as a
proportional representative
and entered the Assembly
with high expectations
I heard the words the staff and reporters
were whispering behind my back.
What did they say?
Hong Chan Mi, a pretty face
put on the general election.
Hong Chan Mi who picked
up a windfall gold badge.
Sooner or later, she
will fall out of fashion
and after 4 years, Hong
Chan Mi will be flung
into a pile of drastically
discounted sale goods.
Yes, so that may be why
I was so hung up on
getting a nomination.
Because I didn't want to
acknowledge what was said,
But...
But, truthfully, I,
Hong Chan Mi, I was
really the worst.
You still have a lot of time.
The game is not over yet.
Muster up courage and
let's walk together.
Okay?
But, Assemblywoman Hong...
Frankly, I...
do not dislike you,
Assemblyman Jin.
But when I see you, I
feel very uncomfortable.
Am I that shabby?
Our Aide Choi didn't speak
harshly, to that extent at least.
I want to quickly
forget how cheap I was.
But when I see you, I cannot.
What?
Let us never see
each other again.
Assemblywoman Hong!
Kim Gyu Hwan.
What are you going to do when
you see Assemblyman Jin?
Whatever I do, what
business of yours is it?
Just now,
I got a statement from the Hanmin Bank
employee who delivered the bribe to you.
That is a lie. I do not
know anything about this.
Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan, you
are under arrest.
Secretary General, Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil is now like a cornered rat.
Secretary General?
Do Hyeon, is something
bothering you?
Eh, punk.
How did I end up like this?
What are you talking about?
No, it's just... that
thought came to me.
I understand that your pride is
hurt because of Jin Sang Pil.
But don't worry about that rascal.
I will cut him out.
No need for that.
Because it's coming
to an end now.
You, do you want to be jailed?
That will be a huge obstacle if
you want to be a civil servant.
Everything is bound to come
out when cross-examination
is conducted and the CCTV
footage is analyzed.
Answer me. You
received it, right?
Yes, I received it.
You delivered it to Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, right?
Yes.
Yes, Prosecutor. Kim Gyu
Hwan says he delivered
the money to Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil.
But the Assemblyman must have returned the
money. You're doing all this for nothing!
But the giver says he
never got it back.
What?
Sang Pil, can't we
just eat first?
But we have to eat together
with Gyu Hwan when he comes.
The stew and all
this will get cold.
Then we can re-heat them.
Your call is not answered and will
be connected to the voicemail box...
Why isn't he answering?
Do you think maybe he got into a
car accident on his way here?
Don't say such an unlucky thing.
Three spits
(AND WHAT YOU SAID
WILL NEVER COME TRUE).
Besides this questionnaire,
is there any other
favor you did for
President Lee Taek Jo?
No.
Delete the questionnaire
file right away.
Okay, I understand.
Who are you people?
What are you doing right now?
We are from the Central
District Prosecutors' Office.
Search and Seizure Warrant.
Please cooperate with
our search and seizure.
You didn't even take
off your shoes.
No...
It's okay if you do not join
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
But isn't quitting the
Assembly too much?
When the people put you there.
Last evening, the Seoul
Central District.
Prosecutors' Office carried
out a search and seizure
of Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
residence and Assembly office.
Bribe?- During the past Babel Tower
City bankruptcy scandal, Assemblyman Jin
met Hanmin Bank President
Kim Doo Shik who had sold
his wife, a Mrs. Kim, a
share of the related fund,
and by threatening him
with service of a subpoena
to a parliamentary investigation, allegedly
extorted $20,000 of illegal money from him.
Yes, it is true that I... met
with Bank President Kim.
And
it is also true that
I told him I would
subpoena him to a
parliamentary investigation.
However, it is nonsense that I acted
with the intent to extort money.
The prosecution immediately
arrested Assemblyman Jin's former
secretary, a Mr. Kim, and
questioned him on related facts.
Mr. Kim allegedly stated that
he had delivered the money
he got from Bank
President Kim's side to.
Assemblyman Jin in the
bank's underground garage.
It is true that the money
was delivered to me.
But that very day, I met Bank President
Kim and returned it right away.
Directly. Frankly, because my
wife and daughter were on my mind
it is true that I wavered a bit.
If you want to punish me for
that, I will gladly pay for it.
From Bank President Kim's
ASSOCIATE:It's true
that the Assemblyman
returned in a few hours
but Bank President said
he demanded more money
because it was less than
the amount his wife lost.
When he refused,
he left in a huff
and when he called for
a special prosecution
out of the blue, the
president was shocked.
The prosecution plans to summon
and question Assemblyman.
Jin after completing analysis
of the seized evidence.
This is KBC News...
Wow, what a
ridiculous bastard...
After having done that,
in that press conference.
"Honey... I'm sorry.
I... am not a person who can only
look after my family, right?"
Didn't he say that?
The case feels somehow...
a bit... strange.
Ehhh, really.
The prosecution opened up the case to the
public because they feel sure about it.
The only thing remaining for
Jin Sang Pil now is to stand
in the mugshot line and
get his ID photo taken.
You just watch. No
doubt about it.
Secretary General,
congratulations.
You can leave now.
Assemblyman Jin, are you going to
respond to the prosecution's call?
This is the parliamentary inspection
season. I don't have time to go there.
Are you saying you will be unresponsive?
Please tell us!
Tell us.
Assemblyman.
I... cannot cooperate with the
prosecutors who only believe.
Bank President Kim's lies and
paint me as a shameless criminal.
If they want to see my face, they
will have to drag me there by force.
Just one more word.
Let us go in now.
Enough already.
I am sorry.- Assemblyman!
We will distribute additional
press materials soon.
By when...- We
are sorry, sorry.
Assemblyman!
Ahew, but if a wife does not tell
her husband, who does she talk to?
Isn't that so?
Don't worry and just take
good care of Joo Hee.
You... are really okay, right?
Yes, that is what I said. Our Aide
Choi said, with regard to assemblymen,
unless they are caught in
the middle of committing
a crime, the prosecution
can do nothing.
Right, that is the kind
of person I am right now.
So there is nothing to worry about.
Right.
Okay, okay, bye.
This matter...
Secretary General Baek is
behind this, no doubt.
Gyu Hwan... What is
happening to him?
It seems he's still in
the prosecutors' office.
Don't worry.
Since they have to release him within 48
hours of arrest, he will be out in no time.
Since I have given all my
statements, I can leave now, right?
Let me just confirm
one more thing.
What is this?- We found this while
recovering data from your laptop computer.
Tell me what that is.
Okay then.
Did somebody die?
Why are you all so crestfallen?
You can't possibly be thinking that
I pocketed that money, can you?
There is no one here
who thinks that.
Da Jeong, why are you crying?
It's just that... I'm so mad at
these absurd things taking place.
I am sorry.
Don't cry. Why cry?
Your Assemblyman won't
even bat an eye at this.
Secretary Song, how are
the netizens' responses?
Half on the Assemblyman's side,
half on the prosecution's side.
Good, that is plenty.
Aide Seo.- Yes.
Please work with Secretary Sim
and Da Jeong to wrap up the
parliamentary inspection that
is soon coming to an end.
I got it.
Everyone else will work with
me to wage a nationwide
campaign asserting the
Assemblyman's innocence.
But will it work with just us?
Just now, Jin Ji Mo leaders all over the
nation called saying they would help out
together with the
fan club members.
Really?- Uh huh.
See? Even if the sky caves in on you,
there will be a way out of it for us.
There are people who believe
in JSP till the end!
So let us cheer up and
fight for it. Aja!
Aja.
Eh, why are you guys like this, really?
Louder! Aja aja!
Aja, aja, aja!-
Scorchhh...
What is scorchhh?
Assemblyman, the designer watch
President Lee Taek Jo gave you...
just came up in an article.
Huh?
Jin Sang Pil Received a Designer
Watch from a Businessman, Too!
Revealed that he
liquidated it and used the
cash...Prosecution will
prove it was a kickback.
How did they find
out about this?
It's Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil!- I
heard that bastard is a total thief?
I had thought we finally got ourselves
a pretty decent assemblyman, but...
This is why the have-nots should
not get involved in politics.- Aish!
Hyung, just come.
Hurry and come.
We urge that Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil be detained and investigated!
Even though Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil is claiming
that he bought bread for homeless people
with the designer watch he received,
he's lying through his teeth!
In a seized parliamentary inspection
questionnaire, the prosecution
found a proposal to provide
financial support to the company
run by the person who
gave the designer watch!
A person like Jin Sang Pil...
Let's go quickly.
...should no longer waste the
people's blood-like taxes!
Everyone! Please sign the petition
for his arrest and interrogation!
A motion to approve Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's arrest is before the.
Assembly that just concluded
inspections of the affairs of state.
Today, the government submitted
to the Assembly a motion
to allow Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's arrest so he can be
interrogated in custody
over bribery charges.
The Assembly plans to open a plenary
session soon to address the arrest motion.
Under current law, the Assembly
in receipt of an arrest
motion must propose an
opening of a plenary session
and vote on the motion in
that plenary session 24 hours
after and within 72 hours from
the report of the motion.
An arrest motion can be passed only if a
majority of the assemblymen are present
and if a majority of
that quorum agree.
It is not clear yet whether
this motion will be passed.
In fact, there have been
many incidents where
an arrest motion failed
to pass the Assembly.
You will only get more depressed if
you keep watching this kind of news.
Go home early today.
People do not
believe what I say.
It's not that they
don't believe you,
but as much as they liked you,
they've received a huge shock.
With time, they will change.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
What will happen if the legislature
passes his arrest motion?
Eight or nine out of ten, he
will be taken into custody.
Custody?
If things go wrong, he may not even be able
to leave jail until the end of his term.
No matter what, we have to block the
arrest motion from being passed.
What do you think about
writing to all Assembly
members, pleading with them
not to vote for his arrest?
No. If the Assemblyman
makes such a move,
he may get criticized for
using parliamentary immunity
against being arrested during
the session as a shield.
He was framed anyway, so what's
wrong with using it as a shield?
Insist on the injustice of
passing the arrest motion...
I know it is a
huge favor to ask.
However, the only person
who would help our.
Assemblyman right now is
you, Assemblywoman Cheon.
I am sorry, but that
will be difficult.
Assemblywoman...
As you know, my party's position
is that we should curtail
or repeal parliamentary
immunity.
Even though I feel sorry for
Assemblyman Jin, I am afraid I can't.
I am here to ask your learned opinion about
the motion to allow Jin Sang Pil's arrest.
The prosecution is too insolent.
They should not scoff at
the legislature like this.
Consider the citizens'
sentiment nowadays.
If it fails to pass, the whole of
the legislature will be reviled.
Okay, I will send a message
to Assemblyman Kang.
Thank you.- But...
isn't this the sort of matter handled
by the floor leader?- Excuse me?
Secretary General Baek...
Lately,
you seem to violate too often the
lane change and speed regulations.
In the past, while observing
the traffic rules,
you drove very cleanly too.
I guess lately I
feel a bit pressed.
I will be more careful.
At any event, I guess this is
the end of Jin Sang Pil too.
Dad!
Startled me... Hey,
how did you get here?
Is it true that you
will get nabbed?
Who told you? Who said
that I would get nabbed?
Then, that "allowing arrest"
thing, what is that?
Where did you pick that up?
Hey, if you are a ninth grader, then you
should ask a ninth-grader question.
Tell me quickly! What is that?
Your daddy is an assemblyman.
A person who does a
very important job.
But when Daddy is working
hard on an important job,
the police ahjussis cannot
catch Dad, willy-nilly.
They have to get all the other
assemblymen's agreement.
Then, other assemblymen
must oppose it for you.
That's right.
But, your Daddy is the most popular
one among the assemblymen.
So in terms of celebs, I am on the
same level as Ahjussi Song Hae.
So everyone is on
your Daddy's side.
You're telling me
the truth, right?
Truthfully. Daddy will
never get nabbed.
Yes.
Aide-nim.
Kim Gyu Hwan?
You've had a really
hard time, haven't you?
I am sorry.
Isn't there a way for me
to help the Assemblyman?
For now, laying low
is helping him.
Staying near the Assemblyman may
only raise the prosecution's
suspicion needlessly.
It's all my fault.
Don't blame yourself too much.
Even though you may have been
responsible for the luxury watch,
being momentarily
tempted by the money
received from the Hanmin Bank president
was the Assemblyman's fault.
At the time...
I forced the Assemblyman to
accept the money against his will
when he told me to
return it immediately.
What?
So if the Assemblyman
actually accepted it,
I was intending to give a tip to.
Chief Secretary Im Gyu Tae.
What do you mean Im Gyu Tae?
Secretary General
Baek's Chief Secretary?
Yes.
What are you saying?
What brings you here?
Is it true that
you incited Secretary Kim
Gyu Hwan to feed you
information about Assemblyman
Jin's corruption?
If it's true, is that a problem?
Leave.
You piece of trash!
What?
What is happening?
Secretary General Baek.
So you've met Gyu Hwan,
together with Secretary Lim?
I only met him because he said
he had information to give.
The fact is he changed
his mind and just left.
Like hell!
The real fact is
you have become a
scumbag politician
who goes around digging
up other people's dirt.
Yes.
That's what has
happened to me now.
And I
am willing to sink a lot lower
than this toward the bottom
if it is expedient.
Understand?
Get ready to provide food and supplies to
your Assemblyman when he is behind bars.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
What do you mean it's difficult?
Why are you saying it's difficult
to consent to the arrest motion?
We're not the
government's minions.
We don't have to process
it without hesitation
just because they
send us a motion.
But we're talking about
Jin Sang Pil here.
Yes. Even though Jin Sang Pil has been
behaving inappropriately all this time,
he is a fellow assemblyman,
eating at the same table.
Strangling him with our own hands...
that's a bit... you know.
Just be honest. Something's
bothering you, right?
It's not me. It's
Assemblymen Choi and Nam.
It seems President Lee Taek
Jo fed them with something.
Stupid fools...
They say Lee Taek Jo's
wife imports watches.
Wow... if it seems for
their own benefit,
no questions asked, they just drop off
these watches to those assemblymen.
I'm guessing it might
be dozens who got them.
Did you get one too?
Jeez. What the heck do you see me as?
Gracious!
I...!
I returned it the day
before yesterday.
With the vote coming up, it's
developed into a headache.
Why suffer a headache over it?
Just let the assemblymen who
approve it vote to approve
it, and the ones who oppose
it vote to oppose it.
Just let them vote
however they want.
The Anti-BH faction decided to vote
autonomously and not in a bloc today?
Yes. I positively heard Assemblyman
Kang Sang Ho's aide say that.
But why this... don't you
feel it's a bit odd?
Sorry, I'm late.
Assemblyman.
Yes?
Why?
Whom am I secretly meeting?
Oh Sae Chang. The Korean
Democratic Party Chair.
Am I going to join
that party now?
Then I won't be Jin Sang Pil
but will become Jin Sang Bird.
When it comes to birds, let us raise
just one bird, Jo Woong Bird.
Oh Sae Chang is a
reasonable person.
If you explain all the
circumstances leading
up to this and ask
for his cooperation,
there is a possibility that the
Korean Democratic Party also
will decide to vote autonomously
like the Anti-BH faction.
Autonomously?
If that happens, there's a good
chance the motion will be voted down.
Voted down?
You're saying it
can be defeated.
Yes. I'm going to
contact him right now.
I have a friend among Party
Chair Oh Sae Chang's aides.
Wait a moment, Aide Choi.
Yes?
I will just do it.
I will appear before
the prosecutor.
Assemblyman, are you
in your right mind?
My mind is clear, of course.
After agonizing over it all night,
that's the decision which emerged.
You understand that way.
I will go see Joo Hee and Joo
Hee's mom and come back.
Meanwhile, get ready for my appearance
at the prosecutor's office.
Why on earth are you doing this?
I'm saying that the
motion to allow you to be
arrested can be defeated.
Defeating it does not mean
I won't ever be arrested..
It's only until the end of the legislative
session that I have immunity.
Until then, somehow, conditions
favorable to you can be created.
Don't you know the regular session
will end when the first snow falls?
Until the first snowfall, you want me
to hear people saying "son-of-a-bi*ch"?
What?
I can't do that, seriously.
So... -Assemblyman.
This time, please let's do what I decide.
Without "but"...
No!
Are you out of your mind?
Don't you know what'll
happen if you appear at the
prosecutor's office now?
The prosecutor already applied to
a judge for an arrest warrant.
The court still has to review
it and sign off on it.
But, as of now, chances of your
arrest warrant getting denied
are extremely slim.
See? You are to eat bean rice, bean
rice (EUPHEMISM FOR GOING TO JAIL)!
If that happens, then
it can't be helped.
What, you punk?
Secretary-nim.
Why are you like this, Hyung?
Then it can't be helped?
How can you say such a
thing to Ae Ri and me?
Are you saying we
should just watch
you wearing a prison uniform and
chowing down bean rice, punk?!
Assemblyman, for Kyung Ah and Joo Hee's
sakes, too, you shouldn't be doing this.
I have already made up my mind.
Just because you're doing
this, which citizen
would understand how you feel?
Only you will just
end up being a fool.
All the difficulties you've
gone through so far...
They were all for nothing and
it will be the end for you!
Why is that the end?
It is not the end.
What did you say?
The real end for me
is that I hide behind
that parliamentary immunity or whatever.
So the people
believing that this People's Spoilsport
Jing Sang Pil is a real son-of-a-bi*ch.
So they will believe that
the Indifferent-to-BH thing
we did was all just
putting on a show.
That would be the real end.
Let's just say that I somehow got arrested.
That I am all locked up.
Then, Aide Choi, and you, Hyung, and
Secretary Oh, and our secretaries...
will you just play around?
Of course not.
You will work even harder.
To get me out.
To prove my innocence.
So how can that be the end?
When I have you people.
Hey...
Aide Choi.
Yes?
You said you didn't
want to make me
into an assemblyman who shines just
for a moment and then disappears.
Yes.
Then let me go.
I'm sorry.
Assemblywoman, what brings
you into the office today?
I wanted to do something
before I resigned.
What's that?
The motion to arrest
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Pro-BH and Anti-BH must be
playing pat-a-cake together.
At least I should vote
against it, as a neighbor.
How can you change your
position just before the vote?
You scared me.
Who's changing his position?
The arrest motion. I heard
you were going to vote yes.
So what do you mean,
an autonomous vote?
I never said such a thing.
And the autonomous vote,
isn't that a good thing?
Let's not tire ourselves out like this.
Please unify Anti-BH faction's votes.
Assemblyman Jo.
Democracy itself is exhausting.
Are you not going to do democracy
just because it's exhausting?!
Ha!
Where... Yes.
Voluntarily go to
the prosecutor?
Who? Jin Sang Pil?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil decides
voluntarily to go to the prosecutor.
Jin's side insists on his innocence and
emphasizes that he will be openly interrogated
by the prosecutor regardless of the
Assembly's decision on his arrest motion...
Voluntarily go to
the prosecutor.
What is this?
Please take good care of them.
I have great faith in you.
Please help Aide Choi out a lot.
Assemblyman, please don't
worry about this office.
Yes.
Secretary Sim, spend less time
drinking, singing, and dancing.
Yes, I will.
You've lost a lot of weight.
For Miss Song, I
have a special gift.
What is this?
Gyu Hwan's phone number.
Assemblyman, don't go.
Do well.
Da Jeong, do well too.
Don't be too disappointed with the
National Assembly. Understand?
Yes.
Secretary Oh, what's with you?
Huh?
That’s what I’m saying.
Why am I like this?
Why is everyone's mood
like this, really?
Is Assemblyman Jin going
somewhere to die?
Assemblyman Jin is obnoxious, so
even the jail won't accept him.
So he'll come back in one piece.
Isn't that so?
I don't think so.
Assemblywoman Hong.
From the looks of everyone's moods, you're
really voluntarily going to the prosecutor.
Yes, well, there's that.
Now that you're entering a
lion's den, who's your guard?
Is it So-and-So Choi who's the
star of the tabloid rumor?
We're a combo, you know.
What can an aide do with the
prosecutor outside the Assembly?
I'll introduce a
good lawyer to you.
Lawyer?
Who?
Me, Hong Chan Mi.
What?
Why are you suddenly
becoming my lawyer?
I can't give you any money.
I don't have any.
Gosh.
I got so frustrated watching you
two fools that I couldn't help it.
Fools?
The two of us?
Assemblyman Jin.
Now I am a discontinued item with
only a few months left of her term.
But if it's okay with you, Assemblyman, I
will work with you for my remaining months.
With me?
I will join the
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
Assemblywoman Hong.
Please take care of me.
But!
Choi In Kyung is barred
within my 2-meter radius.
Also prohibited from eating
together or seeing me alone.
No...
Aide Choi, what do I do now?
This is trouble.
I'll make one for you.
I'll make you a
really great wrap.
Kimchi, kimchi.
Garlic too.
And... I should put
the soybean paste.
Of course.
Looks delicious.- I
don't do this for Mom.
Jealous, aren't you?
Cheers!
Ah.
Ah, seriously.
Delicious!
Delicious.
You get a glass.
Yeah?
You, too. Joo Hee. Have a drink.
It's really been a long time.
Cheers. Say something.
Our family will stay together forever!
Okay. Forever!
This is good. Why aren't you eating?
Have a sip.
We trust Assemblyman Jin!
Cheer up, Assemblyman!
He's coming!
He's here!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
From this point on, don't answer
the reporters' questions.
Just a word about how you feel.
Okay.- Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Let's go.
Okay.- Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
What made you decide to come voluntarily?
Tell us how you feel about
getting investigated.
Are you still denying all charges?
Yes. I'm innocent.
What made you make a voluntary appearance?
What do you mean, by innocence?
Are you prepared to be detained?
Tell us. - Say something.
Assemblyman Jin, please tell us
what made you make an appearance.
Assemblyman!
Please give us another
word.- Assemblyman!
Please tell us why you're voluntarily
going to the prosecutor.
Please give us another word.
Assemblyman!
You're the best.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki