Assembly~Episode 3~
All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Sang Pil, you run
for the office.
If I run for the office, what?
You think things will change?
I wanted the strategic
nomination.
At least you can tell me who you are
thinking about in Gyeongjae District.
I wish for you to run as an
assemblyman under the Gookmin Party.
Just how much money did
you get from the company?
Why did it have to be him?
Without saying too much,
let's rescind Jin Sang Pil.
In the beginning most
refuse but I have not seen
a single person who could
refuse until the end.
Am I really doing
the right thing?
In politics, the quality of a person
is more important than the career.
I have to be a good Assemblyman.
There is a hyung that I like the most.
Because of him, I have to do it well.
Then, do it well. Do well!
Sang Pil.
Sang Pil, Hyung Dal Soo...
What did you just say?
He fell from a crane, you punk!
-Hyung Dal Soo did?-He was
taken to Gyeongjae Hospital.
Wait.
The atmosphere over there
must be frightening.
If you just go, some
unpleasant thing may happen.
-So what? Are you saying
I shouldn't go?-Yes.
Yes.
Stop talking nonsense.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Look. Look. Sang Pil came.
Who the heck are you
that you show up here?
You ask because you don't know?
-I guess he came to boast about becoming
an Assemblyman.-Get out of my way.
This leper bastard! Where
are you coming in?
Hey, punk. Let this go.
Why are you blocking? Let him go.
You guys!
I am sorry but
please move aside.
Now, you know how to pretend being gentle.
Stop showing off and get out of here.
I said for you to stop!
-Go back!-Let this go!
- Where are you
going?- Let me go.
Hey, let this go!
You can't get in!
What do you think you are doing?
Assemblyman.
Please calm down.
Sang Pil, over there.
Move. Move. Move.
Hyungnim! Hyungnim!
Hyungnim!
I think the police have contacted
Bae Dal Soo's younger sister.
Quickly contact the ship
building company to tell them
to meet with the younger
sister as soon as possible.
The usual compensation and the
funeral, just in case he dies,
tell them to settle with her
on other options as well.
Yes, I understand,
Secretary General.
-Are there any other
family members?-He used to
have a son but he gave
up his parental rights.
Becoming a policeman is your dream but
why didn't you go to the police academy?
Actual Police
Officer Examinations
Episode 3Are these the actual exam
questions from the last few years?
Of course. I asked questions after
searching the Police Exam Cafe
(INTERNET SITE) and asking all
of the policemen whom I know.
But really,
did CEO Choi ask you
to make this for me?
I said yes already but
why are you asking me so
many times? Anyway, since
I did the most work,
if a question comes from that, you
have to buy me something yummy.
Yes, if it comes out.
Hello?
By any chance, is this Bae
Gyu Hwan's phone number?
Who are you?
Aigoo. I realized it's you when
I heard your voice right away.
Gyu Hwan! I am your
paternal aunt.
You got a wrong number.
I will do as you wish.
From now on, I don't have
a biological father.
Yes, I'm Gyu Hwan.
What is the matter?
I wasn't going to
contact you but
because he's your biological
father, I thought
you should know. That's
why I am calling you.
Whatever happens to that
person, I have no interest.
Your Father is in the
hospital right now.
What did you say?
As the result of the last by-election
for the 19th Assembly held yesterday,
each of the ruling party and opposition
parties won 2 seats so they are tied.
Therefore, the ruling
party, Gookmin Party,
retains with 151 seats, more
than half of the Assembly seats.
- Hong Chan Mi, you grew
up a lot.- The Googkmin
Party succeeded in their
goal of keeping a majority.
Next in the news...
the candidate honored
with the most votes in
this by-election is...
-Yes. Sunbae-Nim.- Jin Sang Pil,
candidate from Gyeongjae City .
Bae Dal Soo has been
moved to the ICU.
What about the surgery result?
The medical staff didn't tell us but
the surgery result doesn't look good.
What about Assemblyman Jin?
Is he still at the hospital?
Isn't it true that there are many
ways to make a man into a bastard?
Even if it were not so, this
punk, lacking ability...
became an Assemblyman and it makes
me suffocated and my brain explode.
Hyung, you're being too much.
Hurry and wake up.
You have to wake up so you can climb
not only a crane but Mt. Everest.
You have to go up to the top and
shout out with a microphone.
That Jin Sang Pil, in order
to become the nominee,
betrayed his colleagues
and Hyung like a scumbag.
Huh?
Hyung. Wake up quickly. Seriously.
Why are you lying there?
What did I do so wrong?
It was you, who made me the chairman
even though I didn't want to.
Please wake up.
When the sun rises, the
reporters will come.
So?
Do you want me to run away?
Did I commit a crime?
Think coolly. It won't be
good if you cross them.
Whatever happens, happens.
I just arrived. Where
are you, Aunt?
KJH Intensive Care Units
Father.
I have to do the
Assembly job well.
Even if I can put the public
into the second place,
because of Hyung, whom I like
the most, I have to do well.
Ahee. This noodle is hard.
Skip the election press interview and
hand out the press release only.
To the reporters, who call to get
comments from Assemblyman Jin.
Assistance Seo, you
give a few words.
As you know, please no comment
about Bae Dal Soo's case.
Would it be better if
you do it, instead?
- What are you talking about?- I am
in a hurry to do something else.
I have to register
him at the Assembly.
Assemblyman Jin,
please accept this.
It's a certification for being elected
from the National Election Commission.
What are you doing here
instead of going to Seoul?
What you are holding
isn't a drink, is it?
Assemblyman Jin!
Then, I'll be going to the
National Assembly Building.
Aide Seo!
Dad.
Patient.
Sang Pil.
Doctor!
Dad, can you recognize me?
It's me, Gyu Hwan.
You came.
Dad.
Sang Pil.
I'm sorry.
Dad, try waking up.
It's me Gyu Hwan and
not Jin Sang Pil.
Sang Pil.
Take care of my son.
My son...Gyu Hwan
is going to be a police officer.
Dad.
I have to see him wearing
the police uniform
before I die.
Certainly
I'll show you when I am
wearing the police uniform.
Choi In Kyung, you are tough.
Woman Warrior. Warrior.
Come out.
So that you can work off the alcohol,
go to a sauna and get some rest.
Think of a reporter looking
at you in this condition.
From the first day of your term,
the gossip article of your
being drunk will spread all
over the internet and SNS.
it will become wallpaper
on the internet and SNS.
Whether it becomes wallpaper
or smeared all over the place,
it has nothing to do with you.
Isn't that right?
For a person who so badly
didn't want to become an aide,
it's strange.
Hello?
I'm Byeon Sung Gi. It's because
Sang Pil is not answering...
are you perhaps with him?
Go ahead and talk.
I'll relay it to him.
Yes.
I understand.
Assemblyman Jin,
Bae Dal Soo has
passed away.
Even though he was transported by
ambulence to a nearby hospital,
he untimately died.
The police who investigated
the case concluded that
-Bae tried to occupy the
crane as a protest but fell
down.- Mom. Is there
something happened to Daddy?
He is not answering the phone
since yesterday. Mom! Mom!
-Be quiet, wii you?-
Chairman Bae of Committee
to Recover Lost Jobs,
Death from fall.
The death of Bae Dal Soo is
not a simple death from fall,
but the product of conspiracy,
between Jin Sang Pil
blinded by the nomination
and the immoral leaders
of the ruling party,
political murder!(CHEON NO SIM,
FLOOR LEADER SOCIALIST PARTY))
We are demanding that Jin
Sang Pil, the former single
candidate of the coalition
of the opposition parties,
reveal to the public the money he
received to defect to the ruling party
and resign from the
Assembly right away.
A male in his 50's died from
fall at the Korea Shipbuilding
&amp; Repairs Co.,
Haemyun-dong, Gyeongjae City.
Is #7014 here?
#7014? Kim Gyu Hwan?
What is the reason for wanting
to become a police officer?
-Kim Gyu Hwan.-Yes.
Please tell us your
motive for applying.
It was my father's wishes.
-If you were to make it, you
father will be very happy.-Yes.
I am not sure whether you
read the news but even
this morning, an unfortunate
thing happened.
Tell us the opinion of
each of you about the
culture of the aggressive
demonstration.
The freedom of demonstration
or gatherings
guaranteed by the Constitution
should be protected,
but aggressively violent
demonstrations should not be allowed.
Demonstrators must also
improve their awareness.
Also, the incident of death
of the laid off employee
at Korea Shipbuilding
&amp; Repairs Company,
is a tragedy born of
misunderstandings, that if you
keep making an impossible
demand, it will be granted.
As for me,
I too,
think that is wrong.
Is that it?
Please put more efforts into your answers.
Didn't you prepare for the interview?
I too have a prepared answer.
However, if I say that, I don't
think I can forgive myself.
What did you say?
Climbing the crane was
making an impossible demand?
That's right. It
may seem that way.
However, you listen to
me, you son of a bi*ch.
The real reason that person
went on the crane is
because he had no place
to stand on the ground.
So, he had no other
place to go but there.
You understand?
2015 National Police Officer's
Examination Interview
Supreme Happiness for
the Life after Death
Eat one of these.
How can they finish a
funeral in half a day?
Is that woman his
real younger sister?
Because the company wanted
to finish it quickly,
they gave her money.
Byeon Sung Gi, over there...
If you are finished with
your show, get out you jerk.
Dal Soo will be so pissed that he won't be
able to close his eyes. Get lost, you punk.
Just go away.
Why do you come here? Get lost!
Get out here! Get lost!
Get lost! Quickly!
Get lost.
Would you say a word about the opposition
parties' demand for your resignation?
I have nothing to say.
What do you think about the claim that you
betrayed the deceased to get nominated?
Move aside.
What did I do?
It is time for the
assemblyman to go now.
Let's go without saying
anything, quickly.
Right. Let's go.
Let me go.
What do you really
want to ask me?
want to write about?
You want to write that I
killed that person, right?
Because I was crazy
about the gold badge,
I secretly schemed
with the company
and ignored my colleagues and
made that person climb the crane.
Don't you want to
write that way?
Write whatever you want to.
Try to write whatever
you want to!
Jin Sang Pil is the betrayer.
Say that Jin Sang
Pil is a murderer!
I killed Bae Dal Soo. Write it.
I will not even blink my eyes.
Please understand that
he got shocked too much.
Bae Dal Soo
Gyu Hwan.
It feels good to play
with your dad, right?
Yes, I want to come
and play every day.
Okay. I'll put in lots of overtime
and bring you here again.
Really? I'm excited.
Look. Please, look over here.
Oh, look there. Kimchee...
Bae Dal Soo
Gookmin Party
Jin Sang Pil, Sudden
Blast During Condolence!
After receiving Choi In
Kyung's phone call, we
blocked a couple of media but...
I am sorry.
Secretary General, Media
Chiefs and I have decided
to go have a drink.
Would you like to come?
Jin Sang Pil, Sudden
Blast During Condolence!
Oh my god!
Yes.
I understand.
You know that there is a welcome
luncheon tomorrow for the
elected Assemblyman, right?
Before your introduction,
give a brief apologetic
statement in regard to
the incident that took
place at the mortuary.
Did I...
Did I really do wrong?
If you were a common
person, you might not me.
But as a politician,
you did very wrong.
Not the incident during the
condolence, but the nomination.
I thought that was the best way.
People think very differently.
About that, it is hard
for me to say something.
If you give a sincere apology
tomorrow, you won't have
any problem with
legislative activity.
Legislative activity? What
legislative activity?
When Hyung Dal Soo is in
that condition, what -
what legislative activity?
Next year, I will run
in Gyeongjae City.
I didn't want to stomp on you and
that's why I picked Jin Sang Pil.
Then, I'll contact you tomorrow.
Choi In Kyung.
I was thankful.
Okay.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Retract your call for Jin
Sang Pil's resignation.
Hey, Do Hyeon. Are you trying to
interfere with internal affairs?
Stop playing around and tell
me what you really want.
Oh, you wouldn't take the bait.
You know the five civil affairs agendas
my party is pushing for legislation?
In the next special assembly session,
send no more or no less than just two
to the main floor for
serious consideration.
Hey, we are a regime-worthy
political party too for all
purposes and intents. We
should produce some results.
I will give it a review, so turn
down your volume from now on.
And keep an appropriate distance
from the Socialist Party.
I will first see what
you guys would do.
This is Baek Do Hyeon.
Sunbae, it's In Kyung.
Okay, talk.
Assemblyman Jin has disappeared.
- They haven't found
Assemblyman Jin yet?
- Yes.
Yes, we are in the middle of reviewing all
the CCTV footage from Gyeongjae City.
Secretary General, what should we
do about the welcome luncheon?
There was one call to
Joo Hee this morning.
From the Assemblyman?
Yes. Because the call was made from a
public phone, I did think that was odd.
What did he say?
That he went to cool his head so even if
he doesn't call, not for us to worry.
Ahew, it's certain
that he is hiding out.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil has
not appeared at the luncheon?
Secretary General Baek
says that he asked for
understanding because he
wasn't feeling too good but
it's a bold faced lie.
Jin Sang Pil's whereabouts are unknown
and all communication has been cut off.
Since my hoobae, who is a
policeman in Gyeongjae
City, tipped me off, this
is no misinformation.
Secretary General Baek,
he must be having
a difficult time.
Choi In Kyung, can't you even take care of
one Assemblyman? subtitles ripped by riri13
It's my fault. I was
too complacent.
Let's tell the
prosecutors and National
Intelligence Service to
look into the matter.
Assemblywoman Hong.
-Why? I can't?-Of
course you can't.
-Assemblyman Jin is not a criminal.-Did
I say that he was a criminal?
-It's because the situation is
dire.-If the situation is dire,
is it okay to break the law?
This is a very serious
violation of human rights.
Assemblywoman Hong, weren't
you the secretary for
Gookmin Party's Special
Committee for Human Rights?
In Kyung, stop it.
Look here, Choi In Kyung.
Yes, Chief Lim.
Secretary General, it's time for you to go
to the Executive Round Table Conference.
Gookmin Party
Party Executive Round
Table Conference
Assemblywoman Hong,
is everyone here?
Yes, everyone who had respondedthat
they would attend is here.
I will ask the reporters
to leave after you and
Secretary General are done
with your opening comments.
Why should we keep it closed-doorwhen
there is no sensitive issue to discuss?
Let's make the whole thing open.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Then, we will start Gookmin Party's
Executive Round Table Conference.
Aigoo, I am a bit late.
Oh!
Party Leader, long time no see.I
trust you have been well.
Yes.
Aigoo, I'm so dazzled it is
hard to shake your hand.
Assemblyman Park, you're
a king of hyperbole.
Aigoo, Secretary General Baek,
You've worked hard
for the election.
Thank you.
How nice that your
work bore fruit...
Furthermore, there is an item
to change the party rules
to staff the Recruiting Committee and
Women's Committee with full-time employees.
I will finish my briefing
of the party business.
Are there any assemblymen
with separate items?
Good, all good.
The opposition parties are
trying to politicize the death
of the Korea Shipbuilding &amp;
Repairs laid-off worker.
We must not allow
such ugly old ways.
The best response to
unreasonableness is no response.
Our party can only look
after the people's lives.
Very good comments, good.
All good,
but about Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's response...
I think it's a bit lacking.
Even though it's because
of his inexperience,
at times like this, he
should be more forward
and give his explanations
as well as retorts
where appropriate.
So our party can
be at more ease.
Because Assemblyman Jin was very
close to the late laid-off worker,
I think he feels morally responsible
to an extent that's unnecessary.
Please consider it as his taking
time out to self reflect.
But self reflection and hiding
are very different matters.
Assemblyman Park, did
you just say hide?
What basis do you have
to say such a thing?
What do you mean a
basis to hiding?
If he doesn't answer his phone and if no
one knows where he is, isn't that hiding?
Is there anyone here who can contact
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil right now?
Since we already have
many reporters here,
I will say a word.
As a senior assemblyman, I urge
you, Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Hury and show yourself
before the people
and explain yourself
and apologize.
One more word.
In the event this event
grows even worse,
those of you who have led the party's
nomination of Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil,
I hope you make responsible
decisions including
resignations from party posts.
Assemblyman Park!
Party Leader, why don't we move on
to the next itme on the agenda?
Political Opinion Daily
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
Sudden Disappearance
The sh*t has hit the fan.
(BEING IN) politics
is a promise.
A promise to the people.
At a time when even running around
for the people is not enough,
what does he mean by disappearing?Who's
going to take responsibility for this?
Or who should take
responsibility?
The person who's given
him the nomination.
7th Day after Jin Sang
Pil's DisappearanceAnti-BH
Faction Clamors for Baek
Do Hyun's Resignation
Jin Sang Pil, this person,
where on earth is he?
From the very beginning, he was
unfit to be a national assemblyman.
If he was a fit person, I would
not even have chosen him.
Sunbae-nim, I have
always admired you.
And I will continue
to do so, but
this time, I was a little
bit disappointed in you.
Because of your impractical
choice, he has
lost the most important
thing in his life.
Sunbae-nim, this time you
were a bit too much.
Secretary General, this is
the joint statement that
Korea Democratic Party's
and Socialist Party's
spokesmen just made.KDP
and SP's Joint Statement
We propose to expel Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil from the Assembly.
If Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil does not appear by
the opening day of the
special assembly session,
they will make a proposal at
the Assembly to expel him.
Our In Kyung is getting
prettier and prettier.
And Sunbae-nim,
you've grown younger.
Do you also get
Botox injections?
Hey, punk, if I had money
to get that kind of shot,
I would rather employ one more
person in my constituency.
Sunbae-nim,
The proposal to expel Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil...You're just bluffing, right?
Kid, what do you take my party for?
synced by riri13
We are a very clear-cut
opposition party.If
we say we'll do it,
then we'll do it.
To pass the proposal, two thirds
of the quorum present must agree.
Are you confident that
you can get it passed?
We've already finished communicating
with Park Choon Seob's Anti-BH faction.
If Jin Sang Pil does not show
up at the special session,
it will be this for
him right away.
Jin Sang Pil's whereabouts
are still a mystery.
When the opposition parties
makes the expulsion proposal,
please everyone, without exception,
participate in the vote.
Compared to the
opposition parties,
we only have two more seats.
It's regrettable that we will
lose a life blood-like seat.
But it can't be helped.
Baek Do Hyeon...
Let's drag him down from the
secretary general position.
Yes, Head Monk.
Yes, I see.
I am sorry to impose so often
on your venerable school.
Yes, then...
Yes, So Min.
CEO, this is totally looking
for a needle in a haystack.
Until when do I have
to do this sh*t?
Until you find the needle
in the haystack. Why?
What do you mean why?
My legs hurt, my
wallet's running low,
and I have a man
I miss in Seoul.
Now, I will stop.
Don't be impertinent and sweep all
the Buddhist temples in the area.
Even though Assemblyman
Jin is non-religious,
Mr. Bae Dal Soo was a Buddhist.
He must have staked his seat at some temple
to hold a prayer ceremony for Mr. Bae.
Then, why don't you look
for him yourself, CEO?
And I am not even your
employee any more.
If you find him, I will recommend
you for the secretary job.
Right, I'm your easy prey, prey!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Vikii
Yes.
Umm...
How are you?
Are you the only aide?
Yes, as of now.
I will separately get Assemblyman
Jin's permission later.
Hire some interns for now.
Yes.
Hello.
Did you call me?
I've thought about it a lot
after hearing your words.
You are right.
I was too much.
No, I was a coward.
I overreacted. I am sorry.
Even if it's to wash away
(ATONE FOR) my cowardice,
I don't plan to just sit and watch
Jin Sang Pil crumble any more.
What are you saying?
I hope you help out
Assemblyman Jin.
Are you
asking me to be
Assemblyman Jin's aide?
Just a few months will do.
Help him just until he hits the
ground running at the Assembly.
Assemblyman Jin is a person
who can't possibly hit the
ground running, not in a few
months, not in a few terms.
Bismarck said,
politics is the art
of the possible.
There is nothing
impossible in politics.
Let's stop.
This is a meaningless
conversation.
Assemblyman Jin is in a
expulsion crisis and
nobody knows where he is.
Assemblyman Jin
is at Tae Ahm Temple
in Tongyoung.
When you know where he is,
why are you doing nothing?
My going there to forcefully drag
him back...That's meaningless.
Assemblyman Jin will
keep causing trouble
and every time, I will
be hounded by clamors
to take responsibility
for his nomination.
A person whom Assemblyman
Jin trusts and who
can stay by his side
to help him must go.
As for me, I wish you
can bring him back.
Bae Dal Soo is comfortably
resting at a good place.
No place could be
worse than here
because anywhere people
live, it's hell.
Politics was made so that people's power,
not God, can save that hellish place.
Right now, you are refusing that
precious role and responsibility.
Just tell me why you came.
If you do not attend the
special assembly session,
your expulsion
will be submitted.
I was going to resign after I
send off Hyung Dal Soo but
I'm thankful they are
expelling me on their own.
I'll help you.
I'll be your aide.
Now, please go and
attend the Assembly.
If you didn't eat, have some
temple food before you go.
Are you really going to
be this irresponsible?
You want to throw away the position
that the people voted for you?
People are having hard
time making a living.
At least, let's lessen
one more mouth to feed.
Aren't you embarrassed in front of Mr.
Bae Dal Soo's memorial altar?
Even under the worst of
circumstances, Bae Dal Soo
went the path he chose.
Unlike you, he didn't
run away like a coward.
Let's stop it already.
Assemblyman Jin.
I understand why you
are acting this way.
How much you liked Mr. Bae Dal Soo and
so how much you're suffering now...
Stop it already!
I said for you to stop.
-Just stop
now.-Don't run away.
That is how you
are going to make
Bae Dal Soo's death
worth something.
I'll wait for your call.
Yes, Joo Hee.
Why didn't you call.
I was worried.
I'm sorry. Your dad
was a bit busy.
Dad, are you okay?
Of course, I am.
How about your mother?
Did your mother say
anything because of me?
She didn't say anything.
Check your phone. She
may have called you.
Okay, I got it.
Let's hang up.
This woman is just too much...
Hyung Dal Soo
You've got mail.1
New Message
There is one voice mail.
It's the first message.
Sang Pil, it's me, Dal Soo.
I had something to tell you but
since you aren't answering,
I guess you are super busy.
I don't have to see the voting
result because it's so obvious.
Sang Pil, congratulations.
My only wish was to
be reinstated but
now, I have one more wish.
That is for you to do well.
It's you becoming
an assemblyman who
gives hope to people like us.
I am about to climb a crane.
I will come down even if only one
of my two wishes comes true.
Even if I don't
get the job back,
if you become an assemblyman who
receives the people's applause,
I will come down.
See you then.
Yes, right now I am in
front of the Assembly
Hall where a special
session is about to open.
The main session is about
to open in a few moments,
but Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
cannot be seen anywhere yet.
Secretary General,
-Didn't you get any call
from Assemblyman Jin?-No.
Seriously, he is an
incomprehensible human.
Because of Assemblyman Jin, I heard
that you were having a difficult time.
Of course not.
It's just that I don't feel good about
you aligning with the opposition party.
Since you've only
worked all this time,
stepping down and taking a break
won't be too bad.
He must come...
Do you think he'll come?
We have to leave it
up to the heavens.
If I last just one more year,
I get civil servant pension.
It's not working out too
well in the last year.
Jin Sang Pil
Since we have a quorum, we
will open the first meeting of
Assembly plenary session.
Before we start with
the orders of the day,
the four assemblymen elected
in the by-elections
will swear in first.
Assemblymen Jin Sang Pil,
Lim Jin Gyu, Jung Jae Won
Hong Sung Min, please
come out to the podium.
Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil, aren't you here?
No, he is not here.
I will go to submit the
expulsion proposal.
Disciplinary Dismissal of
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
Because Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil is not present,
only the three assemblymen
will swear in.
Everyone in your seat, please...
Wait!
Please take good care
of me, Aide Choi.
Congratulations on your first
attendance, Assemblyman.
What qualification do
you have to enter here!
Don't speak roughly to
your fellow assemblyman.
Shut your mouth!
All Assemblymen and
women, please stand up.
Pledge, I solemnly swear before
the people of Korea that
I will abide by
the Constitution,
and strive to promote the
citizens' freedom and wellbeing
and for our motherland's
peaceful reunification,
putting the national
interests in the forefront,
...
will conscientiously and
faithfully carry out
the duties of an assemblyman.
Assemblyman, Jin Sang Pil.
Lim Jin Gyu.
Jung Jae Won.
Hong Sung Min.
Hyung Dal Soo, you're
still there, right?
Wait and see.
I will definitely make you
come down from the crane.
National Assembly of
the Republic of Korea
This is a statement of apology
to all Korean citizens.
Just read it correctly
the way it's written.
I will take care of the rest.
Apology to All Korean Citizens
I heard that you almost lost the secretary
general position because of me.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
It is not like I don't
understand how you feel.
Just...
I cannot overlook it twice.
Do you understand?
Oh, oh, of course. If I
repeat something like that,
then I'm really a
total scoundrel.
Don't worry.
My respected citizens of Korea
and fellow assemblymen,
I hereby make it clear
that the allegations of
collusion with Korea
Shipbuilding Repairs Co.
that some party members
made are baseless.
As I have explained earlier,
I can firmly state that
it was a win-win settlement that Mr.
Bae Dal Soo wanted as well.
Consequently, I do
not bear any...
legal or moral responsibility
for his death.
Finally, people of
Korea, I am sorry.
At a co-worker's
regrettable death,
I felt unbearable sadness.
What? Unbearable sadness...?
An assemblyman and his
aide will stay there.
Please find a quiet and affordable
place as soon as possible.
Is there any place affordable
and quiet in Yeouido?
You said the intern job
interview was today, right?
Please give me the applications of
those who have passed on the papers.
- Here it is.- Okay.
Hello!
Here.
Hello.
-Put it down somewhere
appropriate.-Yes.
You have more staff now.
I guess Ms. Choi In Kyung has
decided not to acknowledge me?
How can that be...
Hello, Assemblywoman.
Where is Assemblyman Jin?
He is going round and greeting other
assemblymen with Secretary General.
Being his next-door neighbor, I've come
to congratulate him on his move-in.
In Kyung, tell him
that I've dropped by.
Yes.
Work hard then.
Be careful on your way
back, Assemblywoman.
That girl is now blatantly
talking down to me.
So, you're saying you're an
assemblywoman and I'm an aide.
Oh my!
What is it?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
ResumeKim Gyu Hwan
It's my aspiration to work at the
international organization in the future.
The reason I'm applying for the
internship at the National Assembly
is to gain necessary experience required
to work at the international organization.
An intern in the Assembly has to do
rough and tough jobs too at times.
Do you think you can stoop to
them with this kind of resume?
More important than the specs,
I think the important
thing is one's sense of
membership and character
as a team member.
I will think of it as a learning
opportunity and work hard.
I will let you know by tomorrow.
You can go.
- Thank you.- Yep.
- What are you doing
here right now?- Pardon?
I see that you didn't
pass the police exam.
But what are you doing here?
Am I not being interviewed
for an internship?
Why?
Pardon?
You failed the exam and
can't even see your
immediate future.Since
I'm an aide here,
you want to somehow mooch
off of an acquaintance?
No!
No, I applied before you
became an aide here.
I was a bit surprised to see you too.
Okay, what made you apply?
Because I admire Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil stands for the
sufferings of the unemployed and...
Enough. You fail.
- What?- Just leave.
What's the reason?
You are not a kid fit for
the National Assembly.
What do you know about me
to make that judgment?
The National Assembly is for
those interested in politics
or those ready to love.
At least you whom I know are not.
-CEO.I'm telling you this
because I care about you.
Stop this foolishness and
retry to make the police.
Leave.
Assemblyman.
Oh, you were in the middle
of an interview? I'm sorry.
Don't you know me?
No... it's my first time meeting you.
Even if just once, that damned layoff...
Getting that done to us
is our wish come true.
Did he pass?
No, he was rejected.
Why? What's the problem?
Not so much a problem, but...
If not that, then let's pick him.
Assemblyman.
This guy's wish is to get fired.
Let's slave drive him
to death and the moment
he makes a mistake, let's
just fire his ass.
What?
Here.
Father, this person... I'll end him.
Watch me.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
AssemblyPreview
No one here in Yeouido is expecting
anything from Assemblyman Jin.
Hey, Jin Sang Pil, don't
be a scaredy-cat, punk!
Those of the steely nerves
are not the only brave ones.
The ignorant tends to be brave.
Are they asking the assemblyman
to lead this inquiry?
He was nudging a public
servant with something.
The only person who can make me into a
proper national assemblyman is Aide Choi.
Haven't I told you what is the best
to be done for Assemblyman Jin?
What should I do with an assemblyman whose
lips are effectively glued together?
Do I look so laughable to you?!