All characters, party names,
and incidents appearing
in this drama are fictitious
by the creative works.
I am hoping that you, Chairman, would
run as our Gookmin Party nominee.
What did you just say?
I would like to give you
a strategic nomination
to run as our Gookmin
Party's candidate.
Do we have the sort of relationship
where we would be trading jokes?
I'm not at all the type
of person to joke around.
What did you just say?
- Let's talk separately later. Leave.
- Sunbaenim.
In Kyung...
Leave.
Let me be the one asking.
What are you doing right now?
I have promised the people that we would
present a new candidate in Gyeongjae City,
which is a stronghold
for the Gookmin Party.
I think you are the person who
would satisfy that promise.
You mean me? Why?
Aren't you the leader of
the unemployed workers?
I want you to be in the
National Assembly so
that you can help not
only the unemployed but
that you'll be active in social justice
for the weak. That is my expectation.
You really will give
me the nomination?
There is one issue which must
be resolved before we do that.
-What is it? -I understand
that you've been
reported and sued by
your company multiple
times including the lawsuit
for money damages.
Before getting our
party nomination,
each of the lawsuits which are
ongoing should be dismissed.
How?
Through compromise
with the company.
Do I seem to be the type of dupe who would
fall for a ridiculous trick like that?
Just how much did you get
paid off by the company?
When you make the decision
I will handle the negotations.
No matter how angry, I'm the type
that never makes the first swing.
Consider yourself lucky.
Take a couple of days
to think it over.
Excuse me!!!
I will look forward
to your call.
Assembly~Episode 2~
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
At the beginning of this
administration, you won by 5% even
with the title of the President's
Crown Prince, right?
In any event, it would
be best to run in next
year's election from a
different constituency...
Amazing. I never imagined there
would be anyone who would decline
Gookmin Party's nomination to
run for the Gyeongjae seat.
Over the years, I've enticed
many people into politics.
Most of them refused initially,
but I've never seen
anyone resist to the end.
That is how a human befriends
(GETS ADDICTED TO) power.
Why him?
Why am I the wrong person?
I think he's more
qualified than you.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you in advance.
I just can't understand.
Call me after
you've calmed down.
Sunbae-nim!
I still haven't heard
any convincing answer.
Episode 2
SUCCESSFUL TEST APPLICANTS:
10214 Kim Gyu Hwan
Kick it high, okay?
I'm listening. Talk.
I saw the news. You've
quit as chairman, right?
Did you call me to confirm that?
No.
Umm... I passed
the written test.
Then...
are you now going to
become a police officer?
There is a physical fitness test and
an interview but I feel confident.
When I pass them, I'll
go down to see you.
Why do you want to come here for?
Just be good to your parents.
Stop it already. I know you're
doing that delibrately.
I'm not a child any more.
What do you think you know?
Dad! Hello?
This rascal...I guess he did it.
Please give me your decision
by the weekend. Baek Do Hyeon
You still can't decide? Didn't you take
the chairman position to run for office?
I'm sorry. Please give me a little
more time to think about it.
Chairman Jin, timing is
everything for an election.
Before Gookmin Party decides
on its candidate, you have to
throw your hat into the ring,
so you can get attention.
We can't wait any longer. The day
after tomorrow is the opening
day for opposition parties'
joint campaign headquarters.
Then, let me ask you a question.
Let's say I get
into the election.
When the election is over, what
are you going to do for us?
Pardon?
Let's chat. Come out.
Why are you acting this way?
Didn't you say okay yesterday?
-Hyungnim, let's settle with the
company first and decide.-Why?
-Did the company say
they want to settle?-No,
I just think it will
work out if I try hard.
Settlement? You can always do that even
after you start running for the office.
First, go in and tell them that you
will run and then, let's talk again.
-Hyungnim.-Quickly,
let's go back in.
Sang Pil!
Isn't that Ae Ri?
- Ae Ri!- Come over here.
What's up?
Ae Ri, what brings you
to this lowly place?
Have this with the men.
Let it go.
Sang Pil, a letter
came from Kyung Ah.
A letter?
The girl is brutal. When
the husband is about
to run for election,
she won't show up.
I'll be back.
What is up?
We are going to eat out tonight.
Joo Hee's mother, you
have to be there.
It's okay. Have it without me.
-Welcome.-Welcome.
Did you get yourself a man?
What did you say?
It's not, right?
No, I did get one.
I see that you don't.
Just forgive me once.
Please, Kyung Ah?
- Ah, really.
- Hey, big rib!
Let's think of Joo Hee.
Since when did you think of Joo Hee?
Do you even know her birthday?
March 30. As her dad, don't
you think I know that?
Then, what day is today?
Hey, today is... April 2
You know I have a
lot to think about.
To be sure, it's not like
you're trying to be a
neighborhood chief but campaigning
to be an assemblyman.
It hasn't been decided yet.
Enough. Just return the
paper with your stamp.
If not, I'll see you in court.
Why are you being so prickly?
Let this go!
Don't you have any conscience? When you
see how I live, don't you feel anything?
Then, what can I do? Let's
persevere a bit more.
A bit more. A bit more.
It's been 4 years already.
You can actually say
persevere a bit more again?
If I get reinstated, you
and Joo Hee's hardship
will end and our
happiness will start.
Reinstated, my ass!
Even the judge won't reinstate you.
If you set up a tent
and cause a ruckus, the company
is going to reinstate you?
Then, what do you want me to do?
Should I just quit everything?
Enough, I don't want to talk to you
because I'm sick and tired of it.
Anyway, Joo Hee and I will
take care of ourselves.
With Bae Dal Soo whom you can't
live without, go demonstrate and
live like that.
Hey, Kyung Ah.
Hey! I'm not going
to divorce you.
I won't divorce!
Why is it so expensive?
Joo Hee. Jin Joo Hee.
Hey, rascal!
That surprised me.
What is this? I was surprised.
Were you surprised?
Dad, I heard that you were
going to be an assemblyman.
Oh. I don't know
about it just yet.
What kind of style is this?
Shave and clothes, too...
So pathetic.
What did you say, rascal?
Pathetic?
- Pathetic.- To your dad...
you're ducking me?
-Here.-A gift? What is up?
I don't want your butt to
hurt when you are studying.
Dad.
I'm sorry but it's okay for
me to exchange this, right?
Since when did it have a hole?
Go ahead and exchange it.
By the way, how is the
divorce with Mom going?
This woman tells all sorts
of things to a kid.
Don't worry. That
will never happen.
Can't you just divorce her?
What did you say?
For me, I wish you
would do as Mom says.
Why?
Well, just because.
Joo Hee, you don't
like your dad either?
What are you talking about?
I really like you.
Then, why did you
say those things!
That surprised me.
Why are you yelling?
To be honest, Dad,
you have no ability
to make Mom happy.
I'll keep being your daughter so
let's let Mom go. Okay?
-Joo Hee.-I'm sorry.
Dad, I have to go in.
Election. Fighting.
Poong Kyeong Motel
Shouldn't we at least sign a binder for the
campaign office lease before we leave?
Hurry and load the stuff.
CEO, is something going on?
How many times do I have to
say that I don't feel good!?
Tell me honestly.
You are not going to get
the nomination, right?
A demonstration must be
taking place somewhere.
We'll win fighting to the end.
Sang Pil, what happened
with your wife?
I asked the assemblymen to
give us a bit more time.
When you hear this, call me.
This guy...
What is he doing that he
has his phone turned off?
Maybe he really is
going to divorce?
Divorce is not such
an easy thing.
Well, you divorced... Punk...
Hyungnim.
I think those bastards came
to take down the tent!
♬ When my eyes misty.
♬ In my heart when
it's full of...
♬ When my thoughts are
full of Kyung Ah, I
♬ think of you.
Dang.
Kyung Ah, I...
Hey! Let me sleep!
Aren't you sleepy!
I'm sorry.
Sleep well.
Really.
♬ Come back to me.
Come back to me...
Pl..ease.
Hurry up and get over here.
You came.
These as*holes, really.
All this is because they are afraid
that you'll run for the office.
Look how they came
when you weren't here.
What about Hyung Dal Soo? How
come I don't see Hyung Dal Soo?
Why isn't Hyung Dal Soo here?!
What happened?
Hyungnim.
Hyungnim, are you okay?
After he got a pain reliever shot,
he fell asleep a moment ago.
-What did the doctor say?-Except for a
fractured bone, they say he's okay.
For a guy who has no strength, he was
so ferociously going against them...
If it wasn't for Choi In Kyung,
we would have been arrested
at the emergency room.
Who?
At the police station,
that woman...
I'll be leaving now.
As to Bae Dal Soo's arrest
issue, you don't have to worry.
- Why are you doing this?-
Why did you show up there?
The takedown, Secretary General
Baek ordered it, right,
to push me to decide! In
collusion with the City, right?!
-Takes one (THUG) to
know one...-What?
Look here, Jin Sang Pil.
When they stopped tearing down the tent
and when Bae Dal Soo didn't get arrested,
you should be thankful to
Secretary General Baek.
What?
I'll tell you one more thing.
Since you are being courted by
both the ruling and opposition
parties, you must feel good.
However, know this one thing.
Politics is nothing to laugh at.
I hope you don't turn
politics into a joke.
7 years ago
I'll refuse Gyeongjae district.
Conflict over party nominations
will worsen if I, one
of your closest inner
circle, take a sure winner.
Give me the metropolitan area.
If you don't get elected, then
just go to Gyeungjae district.
(Seo Dae Han: At the time,
Gookmin Party Leader,
Current President)I heard
you have ties to the place.
I'm confident. I will battle
for my first election,.
(THE PRESENT)
Jin Sang Pil I'm Jin Sang Pil.
You said you'll negotiate
a settlement, right?
If you accept the nomination.
Will that settlement
really work out?
Trust me.
Chairman?
Am I doing the right thing?
I also sometimes think
about such a thing.
Whether it's the right thing.
Or is this the
right thing to do?
Chairman, what do you think life
and politics have in common?
-What is it?-There
is no right answer.
There lies only choice.
Struggling to turn that
choice into the right answer,
that is life and politics.
Make your choice.
Hyungnim, come quickly.
Let's quickly go. Quickly.
It's urgent.
One. Korea Shipbuilding &amp;
Repairs Co., LTD. will,
for all those who want
to find new jobs,
make references to its affiliated
subcontracting companies.
One, to those who were fired,
company shall pay 100% of their
two years' worth of base wages.
One, the company and the
fired employees will
mutually cancel all criminal and
civil lawsuits against each other.
- There are no objections,
right?- Objections or not,
you never told us anything and
just made a settlement?
Isn't this dictatorship?
The committee rules give the
chairperson the authority to settle.
There are no objections, right?
Let's tear down the tent now.
What are you doing? The
fight is over now.
By whose will?
This is invalid! It's invalid!
It's not invalid.
-It's notarized.-You
punk, are you crazy?
Who told you to do such a thing?
I'm the Chairman, Hyung.
You think I gave you the position
so you can do such a thing?
Let's rescind. Because there
was too much opposition,
call and tell them
that is the case.
Hyungnim, please stop already.
And then, let's run
for the office.
Look at them wanting to settle when
they saw that you were going to run.
If we do well in the election,
we can get reinstated.
Just trust me once, Sang Pil!
We can get reinstated.
Please, stop!
Forget about the Assembly and try
running for Presidency! Still.
Do you think those bastards
will reinstate us?
Nevermind being reinstated.
We are about to be jailed.
Will you only wake up when
you become a convict and get
hit with $100-200K judgments
for monetary damages?
Punk, only to give up so
meaninglessly, did we
suffer so much! Don't
you feel wronged?!
Of course I feel wronged!
When I think about
the past suffering,
I feel so resentful
and wronged...
I feel so resentful and wronged that
my whole world seems to fall apart.
However!
It's not working. No
matter what sh*t we do...
it's not working.
Isn't that right?
Let's admit it now.
That we are weak. That we are nothing.
Nothing!
Let's admit it.
I'm sorry Hyung.
Sang Pil.
I came to pay my debt.
I forgot about it and thanks.
I'll pay the remaining amount after I
take the exam when I get a part time job.
It's okay. When you get money,
buy yourself car insurance.
No. My personality won't let me go
long without paying back debts.
Even if I have to drive you for
free, I'll make sure I pay you.
So Min, what is it?
Korea Shipbuilding &amp; Repairs'
labor dispute has been settled.
Breaking News - Korea Shipbuilding
&amp; Repairs' Labor Dispute Settled.
Secretary Lim, I want the
profile of our party's
candidate and not the
opposition party's.
That person is our
party's candidate.
What did you say?
City of Gyeongjae
Candidate Profile
This is nuts!
Hong Chan MiRuling Gookmin Party
spokesperson, proportionate representative
What the hell?
I will announce Gookmin Party's strategic
nominee to run in Gyeongjae City,
We, the Gookmin Party, are embodying
our affection for and committment
to serve the socially
disadvantaged and
have decided to
nominate Jin Sang Pil,
the former Chairman of the Korea
Shipbuilding &amp; Repair
Committee to Fight to
Recover Lost Jobs.
Who is that?
In an era of increasingly flexible
labor markets, Jin Sang Pil
is, simultaneously, a
symbolic figure who
represents the sufferings
of the unemployed and...
Where is the candidate
Jin Sang Pil?
When is the candidate's
press conference?
Isn't this candidate snatching
from the opposition parties?
Please answer the question.
Where is Jin Sang Pil now?
Over there, it's Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon!
Mr. Jin Sang Pil, who is currently taking
steps to join the party membership,
plans to get the Supreme
Council's confirmation and
register with the National Election
Commission as a candidate.
Heol! Wow!  - Nominee Jin
Sang Pil worked as a welder
for Korea Shipbuilding &amp;
Repairs Co., located in Gyeongjae
City, South Gyeongsang Province,
until he was laid off.
Afterwards, he acted as the
vice chairman of the KSR
Committee to Fight to
Recover Lost Jobs until...
his recent succession
to the chairmanship and
working out of a compromise
with the company.
With this, all candidates for the 4
by-election districts have been determined.
Now the campaign war between the ruling and
opposing parties will start in earnest.
Meanwhile, the opposition
parties started to protest
right away by demonstrating
in front of Gookmin Party.
The opposition parties
strongly condemned
this nomination as a
betrayal and collusion.
They stated that they would not nominate
a candidate for Gyeongjae City...
CEO, are you okay?
Can you leave me alone?
Okay.
What kind of nomination
process is this?
Is the nomination process
like winning a lottery?
Is it there to help out
the poor neighbor?
Assemblyman Kang, what is the
reaction of the local party members?
It's like a bee's hive.
If anyone puts down a flag
for a new independent party,
it seems like everyone will tender
their defection notice and rush out.
Really...
Why did Baek Do Hyeon make
that kind of a choice?
He is showing his true
colors.(Kang Sang Ho,
Nationalist Party, prominent
in Anti-BH faction)
When he was at Seoul National
University,(Kang Sang
Ho, Nationalist Party,
prominent in Anti-BH faction)
he was a left wing
student activist.
Jin Sang Pil...
Jin Sang Pil, I see...
Election Administrative Guide
Expectation Rising in
Gyeongjae over New Candidate
Politics is not
something that's easy.
I hope you don't make
politics into a joke.
-Who came?-That
person, Jin Sang Pil.
-Why would he come here?-To
discuss the election.
Hello.
Drinking during daytime...
Wow, you know how to drink.
I know you are not
happy to see me but
since the only person I
know in this field is you,
I wanted you to consult with me.
Please, sit.
Okay.
About what kind of things do you
want me to consult, client?
About politics. What should I
do if I want to to do it right?
You want to do
politics correctly?
Yes, I should since I
got the nomination.
Then, let me ask you.
If you have what it takes
to be in politics,
you would be able to answer the three
questions that I am about to ask.
Go ahead and ask.
-Who are you?-I
am Jin Sang Pil.
I am asking you what
your core identity is.
Oh, that.
A fired person. No, I
used to be a welder.
Pass.
Second, why do you want
to become an assemblyman?
The truth is that I wasn't
initially going to...
Third, as an assemblyman,
what are you going to do?
That is... also, I...
I haven't thought
about it yet so...
-Aren't you
embarrassed?-What?
To the citizens of Gyeongjae who
will give their sacred vote and
to the citizens of this
country who will pay your
campaign allowance with their
sweat and blood money...
aren't you embarrassed?
Yes, well...
It is embarrassing.
- But, in the future
I'll...- Please get out.
Didn't you hear what I said?
Get out!
I know you don't like me but do
you really detest me that much?
How can I?
Maybe I'm just jealous of
your sudden rise to fame.
(ED. NOTE: IN KOREAN HAVING A STOMACH
ACHE IS AN IDIOM FOR BEING JEALOUS,)
Have something to eat when you drink that
or you'll get a hole in your stomach.
(ED. NOTE. CONTINUED, BUT
SANG PIL MISSES THE POINT!)
Thank you for making time
when you are so busy.
Not at all. I was going
to visit you and report
to you about the nomination
situation anyway.
The Party members in Gyeongjae
are disgruntled.(Park
Choon Seob. Leader
Anti-BH faction )
There is also talk of an
independent candidate.
When a nomination is made,
that happens all the time
and also ends all the time
without much happening.
Well. Because this time the
candidate is so exceptional...
I'm worried if things
will go your way.
Sounds like you are
disparaging Jin Sang Pil.
It's not disparaging but it's the truth.
Young people these days
call people like Jin
Sang Pil a loser.
Young people with sense do not
call him a loser but an underdog.
How can I beat you
in a war of words?
This time...
you've made a mistake.
You should have found someone
who suits our party.
What do you think our
party's identity is?
Look way over there.
A bird flies using both
right and left wings.
Our party, to a great bird
called the Republic of Korea,
must be its right wing.
Don't resort to imperfect
imitation of the left.
But with pride and dignity...
That is a true conservative.
I, like you, am a person who
stands on the right side.
We just look in
different directions.
Assemblyman, for you a "right,
face" and for me, a "left, face."
The right side that
faces the left.
That is what I think
of being conservative.
Without saying too much...
let's take back Jin Sang Pil.
Assemblyman Park.
There is still the Supreme
Council's confirmation,
and we can cancel on him by finding
some convenient disqualifying reason.
You said you will not interfere with the
Gyeongjae District nomination matter.
I cannot gladly accept anymore of what you
say, even if you are a senior assemblyman.
Just what is the reason for your
obsession with Gyeongjae District?
At most his term will be 1 year and
he's only a half term assemblyman.
Because it's not like you to
force a guy like Jin Sang Pil,
I am asking you.
I will fax you a copy of
the statement announced
at the press conference
this morning.
Why don't you give
it a thorough read.
Dad, this is Gyu Hwan. I heard the
demonstration was over. How are you doing?
I'm worried about
you so call me.
It's here.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Vikii
Where is this place?
You.
Sleep some more. We
have some ways to go.
Why are you here?
I heard you told So Min to
call me because it was free.
I did?
Anyway, we are deducting
$15 from my debt.
Watch where you're going.
What do you think you are doing?
Women don't like politics.
Why do you think that women
won't like politics?
We have to talk about National
Party's nominee Jin Sang Pil.
Isn't he an unexpected person?
Nobody expected a person like that.
-Turn it off.-What?
Turn off the radio. Why did you do
it when I didn't ask? Turn it off!
Oh, okay.
But aren't you being
a bit too much?
You made such a ruckus
because you wanted to listen
to politics but today, you
are doing the opposite.
A person has to be consistent.
Will you say something?
Thanks, from now on
I won't be calling.
Hey, although I don't know
what the matter is...
cheer up!
Police...
Make sure you make it.
Alright.
You asked why it was
Jin Sang Pil, right?
In the next election, my
situation looks gloomy.
When things look bleak, I start to
remember things that I had forgotten.
My father, whom people
remember only as an
undersecretary of the
Department of State Affairs,
was the first ever appointed mayor of
Gyeongjae. With one month left in his term,
that I was born then.
Next year, I'll run
in Gyeongjae City.
Sunbae-nim...
I didn't want to step over you.
That's why I chose Jin Sang Pil.
They say a politician thinks
of the next generation and
a political hack thinks of
the next election only.
I thought I was a politician but
I was only a political hack.
I'm so confused right now.
I don't know what to say...
Hyung-nim, where in
the world are you?
I have something to tell
you so please call me.
What brought you here?
I am Seo Dong Jae, referred
to you by Secretary Lim
Gyu Tae of Secretary General
Baek Do Hyeon's office.
Oh, the person who is
going to help me...
Don't you know Hangeul? Hurry and
remove that so we can move our stuff.
Perhaps in Assemblyman Yang
Sung Gil's office that time...
Gyeongjae City is my expertise.
I'll do my utmost to assist you.
Ah, please look after me.
Now, fighting!
Fighting!
Fighting!The best!
Oh, yes.
Oh, below... Please go in.
Hey, assh*le. Did you stop the
demonstration to just get a gold badge?
What do you think you are doing?
This is political terrorism.
It's okay.
Hey, Jin Sang Pil.
I'll keep an eye on you to see
how well you eat and live.
Let's just go. What
a filthy sight!
No, these guys...
Candidate, are you okay?
Yes.
Oh, no. I rented
these clothes...
Give it to me.
Those small minded assh*les.
They were the first to
file job applications
and now they are
throwing a tantrum?
You came, Hyung?
Oh, really.
I'm going to start work in
about a month. Is there
anything I can do? You are
going to feed me, right?
Of course, would I let you starve?
What about
Hyung Dal Soo? Can't you
get in contact with him?
I don't know. He is nowhere
to be found. Nowhere.
You know that the original
draft was for me, right?
You must have not felt too well.
If I dig and mess up Jin Sang Pil,
you'll be in difficult position.
This is the best I can do.
Thanks. For now, concentrate on your
business. I'll see how I can help you.
No. I decided to close
down the company.
If I stay any longer, I'll end
up petitioning for bankruptcy.
Any thoughts for afterwards?
I'll have to think after
I get some fresh air but
I plan to become a
person who can demand...
a party nomination more
deservedly than now.
-I look cool today,
don't I?-Rascal.
Yes?
Secretary General, a
Korea Shipbuilding &amp;
Repairs laid-off worker
called Bae Dal Soo
showed up at the company and
started to go on a hunger strike.
Rescind the nomination.
Defeat Jin Sang Pil!
Hyungnim.
Before fasting, you have to
take anthelmintic medication.
Oh, and my assistant told me that
you can get arrested for illegal
campaigning if you call for certain
person's defeat in election.
Don't write stuff like this.
Because you went missing all of a
sudden, I was not able to tell you.
If I get elected, let's
go the Assembly together.
You know I can't do
anything without you.
Give me some help and...
if a good place opens
up, let's move.
-Sang Pil.-Yes?
Do me a favor. Get
out of my sight.
Hyungnim...
I'll be back.
Defeat Jin Sang Pil.
Nullify the nomination.
Popular opinion is
against Jin Sang Pil.
Former Assemblyman
Yang Sung Gil says
he has thought of having
his wife run as an
independent candidate.
Should I meet with him?
Let it be.
When the floor gets too hot, they'll kick
off the blanket and come out by themselves.
I understand.
Then, I'll heat up the floor
by giving it some fire.
Hurry. Hurry.
Gookmin PartyCity of Gyeungjae
IS ANGRY: Go away Jin Sang Pil
CITY OF GYEONGJAE IS ANGRY:
Go away Jin Sang Pil
Put a stop to back-door
nominations!
Put a stop! Put a stop!
I'm certain that the Anti-BH
faction egged them on.
They are the type to scatter on their own
once we get the nomination confirmation.
Secretary General.
The Office of Party Leader
called and said they
are calling off today's
Supreme Council meeting.
This means that they want to defer
Jin Sang Pil's confirmation.
Welcome, Secretary General Baek.
Have you met with the party
members from Gyeungjae City?
-I received their request to
meet but I refused it.-What?
I thought the Supreme Council
meeting should be held first.
Please hold a Supreme Council meeting
and confirm Jin Sang Pil's nomination.
As for me, I do not
like Jin Sang Pil.
Same for me.
Are there any reasons why Jin Sang
Pil cannot get the nomination?
He lacks qualifications
and capacity!
Supreme Councilman Kim,
are the qualifications
and capacity you speak of,
something like these?
SKY(SHORT FOR SEOUL, KOREA, YONSEI,
3 TOP UNIVERSITIES)-graduated
judges, prosecutors, lawyers
or high ranking officials,
top executives of publicly
traded companies, or CEOs of
well-established companies with
annual sales of $10 million or more.
Journalists or professors
image peddling on TV!
What did you say?
There is only one qualification
to represent the people:
A citizen of the Republic of Korea
with the eligibility to run.
Secretary General Baek,
behind the party members
making such ruckus outside
stands Park Choon Seob.
If we push through the confirmation,
the Anti-BH faction will use it
as an excuse to create a whirlwind
with an independent candidate.
Do you think you can
win with Jin Sang Pil?
Don't we have the party
leadership decision?
-What?-Party Leader.
I would like to request that
today's Supreme Council
meeting be held not here at the
party headquarters, but...
at candidate Jin Sang Pil's
office in Gyeongjae City.
Put a stop to back-door nominations
which ignore the will of the people!
Put a stop! Put a stop!
Put a stop to back-door nominations
which ignore the will of the people!
This is what I'm saying.
Party Leader, say something.
If you want, I'll resign from the
Party offices. Baek Do Hyeon.
What is this?
Assemblyman Park, the Supreme Council
members are flocking to Gyeongjae City.
I guess that pathetic Yoo Jeong Soo
tucked his tail in before Baek Do Hyeon.
-Why haven't you left?-What?
If you arrive later than the guest of
honor, it won't look good for you. Run!
Oh, okay.
I can still see your legs.
Quickly run!
Okay.
Even faster!
Move it to the left. Move the
whole thing to the left.
So it will hang straight.
Let's leave it alone. Go to the right side.
It's perfect.
No, it has to move left
so it can be centered.
No, you can't tell the
right apart from the left?
May you be victorious.
Assemblyman Park Choon Seob
Park Choon Seob?
He is a fifth term Assemblyman and
the leader of the Anti-BH faction.
But why would he...?
Sang Pil, look over there.
Hurry up and come out.
Hello.
They are the party members.
From city councilmen
to neighborhood representatives,
everybody came.
What?
I heard that you sent a wreath.
Thank you for showing your concern.
As a senior member of the Party,
I just did what I had to do.
By the way,
you must not forget the position
that I requested for Yang Seung Gil.
Of course. Then...
Nullify nomination.
Defeat Jin Sang Pil!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Nullify nomination.
Defeat Jin Sang Pil!
Here! Here!
Who is it? Who are you?
The person who was on
hunger strike, did he quit?
If you called me out,
talk. Why aren't you
saying anything?
If you have nothing to say...
I'm going to go back in.
Dad...
Look here.
I am a lowly pathetic person.
Since I'm a person who does not
deserve to be your father,
from now on, think of
us as total strangers.
How come you live like this?
Just what is that reinstatement? What is
it to you that you are hell bent on it?
What did you say?
Dad, are you stupid? How come
you are living so stupidly?
Watch what you say.
By doing this, what do
you think you gain?
What I want?
What I want is one thing.
That I, this Bae Dal Soo,
am not a piece of trash.
They use me as they please and
they throw me out in the
street as they pleased.
I am not that kind of
trash but a human being.
That I didn't live a wanton life to
be treated like a piece of trash.
I am confirming that.
Is that enough?
So what if one lives like trash? That
Jin Sang Pil is total human trash.
He's trash because he betrayed
you and got the nomination!
But look.
Now, that trash is going
to become an assemblyman.
All the people will bow to him.
He'll be walking around with stiff
shoulders and be treated well.
Why can't you live like that?
That's enough.
I'll say one more thing.
I'll do as you say.
From now on...
I don't have a
biological father.
Jin Sang Pil
Nominee Confirmation Certificate
To our comrade Jin Sang Pil, Gookmin
Party's candidate for Gyeongjae City,
please give a big
applause and a shout out.
Jin Sang Pil. Jin Sang Pil.
Jin Sang Pil!
Ballot
NATIONAL PARTY: Jin Sang Pil
In Kyung Consulting
CEO Choi In Kyung
I have something to tell you so please
come to Gyeongjae tonight. I beg of you.
What does he think he is doing?
As ballot counting starts
in all four districts,
each party leadership is
showing their nervousness.
Election Chairman Jin Sang Pil
In Gyeongjae City where 20% of
the ballots are counted so far,
The National Party candidate
Jin Sang Pil is way
ahead of independent
candidate Lee Yeong Ik.
With 34% of the ballots counted
right now, candidate Jin Sang Pil
has 73% of the vote. There is a
high chance that he'll be elected.
GYEUNGJAE DISTRICT:
34% REPORTING: Jin
Sang Pil 73.5%Leading!
Leading! Leading!
Gyeongjae city has counted
60% of the ballot. Candidate
Jin Sang Pil who is
winning by a landslide...
GYEONGJAE DISTRICT VOTE COUNT: Jin Sang Pil
74.1% with 60% of ballot count. Leading.
The first working class assemblyman ever
is about to be born in Gyeungjae City.
Oh! This just in. It's certain
that Jin Sang Pil is the winner.
LIFE LONG LABORER: Jin Sang Pil
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Baek Do Hyeon! Baek Do Hyeon!
Baek Do Hyeon!
Congratulations on being elected.
-Oh, yes.-What is the
reason for calling for me?
I heard that you closed the company down.
Is that right?
It's correct that I closed it down but
what is the reason for looking into it?
If you have nothing to do, I thought
of asking you to be my executive aide.
Now...you want me to do what?
I am allowed up to 2 4th-grade aides. If
Aide Seo outside and you, Choi In Kyung...
Look! I used to be the Blue House
Senior Executive Administrator.
If you did that, then you can't be an aide?
Assemblyman, that's not what
In Kyung is saying but...
If that's not it, then please do so. I won
by your strategic manual that you wrote.
Choi In Kyung is really great.
I can't bear to sit here. I'll just leave.
Please wait. I...
have to be a good assemblyman.
Besides the people, there is a
hyung that I like the best.
Because of him, I have to do good.
Okay, do it well. Just do it well.
You asked me a while ago
why I want to become
an assemblyman. Back
then, I had no answer.
Ever since, I've been racking my brain
for the answer, but I still don't know.
With my head, I still won't know in
the future. But I have to do it well.
So, do it well! Do it well. Well!
-In Kyung.-Choi In Kyung,
you know that answer.
At least you'll know what I should do.
Please help me.
I told you I don't want to.
Look for someone else.
-Don't just brush me off and
do it, please.-I won't do it.
Please do it. Really!
Sang Pil!
Sang Pil, Hyung-nim Dal Soo...
What about Hyung Dal Soo?
What did you just say?
He fell from a crane, you punk!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Assembly~Preview~
Hyung, I told you I'll
take you with me to the
Assembly House. Please,
will you wake up?
Is there any other family member?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil didn't
show up at the luncheon?
You still haven't found him yet?
Was I that wrong?
If he doesn't show up at the
special session, then it's this.
Let's drag down Baek Do Hyeon
from his important posts.
When he's become like that, what
participation in legislative activities?