Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
If just one more chance had
been given to that person,
no, even if he could have had a belief that
one more chance would be given to him,
in my opinion, I absolutely believe that
he would not have climbed that tall crane.
Assemblyman...
has even bet his
life on this bill.
If something goes wrong, that
will be your responsibility.
Yes, so for me, the real
name of this bill is...
Bae Dal Soo...
Bae Dal Soo and a second
chance, my butt...
Chairman Park, shouldn't there be
a limit to appealing to sympathy?
Politics...
being done this way...
is asking for trouble.
I am about to climb a crane.
I will come down even if only one
of my two wishes comes true.
Even if I don't get
the job back...
if you become an assemblyman who
receives the people's applause,
I will come down.
See you then.
So this was it.
What my father
really wished for.
If you know it now, stop
fooling around and come back.
This phone... can't
you give it to me?
All right.
Assemblyman.
What?
The bill... I really
appreciate it.
Hey, that sort of thing... should
be said once it is passed.
Do you think you have the
ability to get the bill passed?
This kid is selling
me short again.
Don't you trust me?
I trust you, but
I don't trust this parliament.
What, punk?
This is enough for me.
I will take my leave.
I will look for another part-time
job, so don't worry too much.
Gyu Hwan, you know
how obnoxious I am.
I will leave your spot
open until you come back.
Episode 19.
What are you doing
right now?- What?
You must think about working
with the Assemblyman
and realizing your
father's dying wish.
But what are you
doing right now?
I think
my presence will only burden
the Assemblyman more.
Kim Gyu Hwan!- I am sorry.
But I think this is the best
for both the Assemblyman and me.
For a runaway,
you come up with a
pretty good excuse.
Okay, go. Go and
live your life like a runaway.
With your perennial
test-taking buddies, talking
about three, five,
seven given-up things,
pouring out curses towards
the world, live like that.
Aide-nim!- When I was your age,
I at least had a conviction that I must
fight against the bad things in the world.
I didn't flee like
you, understand?
When you were young,
the world must have been
a really romantic place.
What?- Without any power,
you even considered
fighting against the world.
Should I tell you what my and
my friends' conviction is?
That if a friend wins,
then I will lose.
The politics that
you love so much...
has shaped such a world.
The economy is in
a very bad state.
During the remaining
regular session,
please lend your support
to pass economic bills.
I itch to do it.
But they are so different
from my party's position.
Economic austerity...
will be a problem.
Because of the
economic difficulties,
we must tighten our belt.
That is an old method.
We must rather increase government
spending to boost consumption.
What are you going to do if
an economic crisis results?
Didn't you see a few countries in
Europe suffering from that problem?
Our party believes that Korea
still has a strong balance sheet.
To maintain a strong
balance sheet,
our party's position is
that we must scrimp.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil seems
to have a different idea.
So, are you going to
lend your support
to that Bae Dal Soo's
law or something?
We are reviewing it.
I really like its spirit.
The largest opposition party
with 139 seats
will content itself with being a
trainbearer to a populist bill?
You got beaten
to the punch by
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
If I were you, Party Leader Oh,
I would find a new issue.
Gookmin Party Emergency Response
Commission Chairman Park.
Choon Seop and Korean Democartic
Party Leader Oh Sae Chang
met at National Assembly's
Sarangje House this afternoon
and exchanged opinions
about the current
political issues including
the regular session.
In the ensuing private
meeting, reportedly
they had an in-depth discussion about
policies to stimulate the economy.
While both sides are deeming
today's meeting satisfactory,
whether the issues discussed today
will be smoothly dealt with
remains to be seen...
Aish, darn it, why won't they say even
one word about Hyung Dal Soo's Law, huh?
It was on the 9
O'Clock News earlier.
Today's short story?
Just a one-line caption, does
that qualify as being reported?
But we should be
thankful even for that.
So deflated from the beginning,
what blasted law will
you manage to make?
Jeez, I will make one somehow.
I trust you, but I don't
trust this parliament.
What, punk?
This is enough for me.
The politics that you love so
much has shaped such a world.
Yes, Assemblyman.-
Did I wake you up?
I'm sorry for calling
you so late.
That's okay.
But is anything the matter?
Umm, Aide Choi.
Yes.
Let us...
get Hyung Dal Soo's Law...
passed no matter what.
Why aren't you answering me?
We can do it, right?
Yes,
we can do it.
No, we must do it.
Step one?
Now, everyone, thoroughly
prepare yourselves.
From now on, this is war.
What is Step One?
Introduction of the Bill.
Introduction of the bill?
In order to introduce a bill,
including yours, the primary sponsor,
10 assemblymen's
seals are necessary.
Cheon No Shim
I will get the seals of the other 3
assemblymen of the Socialist Party as well.
Aigo, thank you.
Thank you very much!
Bill Sponsors'
Signature Document.
Still, we are lacking 5 more.
I will find out if there were assemblymen
who introduced similar bills before.
Oh...
Good idea.
Aide Seo!- Yes.
Contact the aides of thoughtless,
troublemaking assemblymen.
Your assemblyman slapped
a street cleaner and
got cussed out. Do you
think that is in the past?
Just see what happens during
the election time. The rival
opposition party candidate
will bring it up again.
There is no way they
won't endorse this bill
since they are frantic
to change their images.
If he wants to get re-elected, he must
clean up his super arrogant image.
Hurry and get his seal here.
The bill was filed with the
Ministry of Government Legislation.
Aide-nim, Step One accomplished.
Then, we just need to
introduce it to the relevant
standing committee and
win their approval.
We have a hurdle to
overcome before that.
What hurdle?- The hidden
force of the Assembly...
the standing committee
expert consultant.
Chief Expert Consultant.
He is the head of all
legislative protocol
officers who preliminarily
review and report
on all matters of policy, including bills
that standing committees deliberate.
His report hugely influences the
judgment of standing committee members,
in particular those who lack expertise
or zeal for the committee they sit on.
To the government's civil
servants, the expert consultant
holds a power that surpasses
that of an assemblyman.
We must secure a positive opinion about Bae
Dal Soo's Law from this expert consultant.
Consultant, this... My aides
worked like dogs to make this.
For your easy perusal,
everything is categorized.
From public hearings, from
other countries' examples,
projected cost from the budget
office, everything is here.
Yes, please look at this; Take a good look
at this, and write us a review report.
Ah... but this seems to
require too much budget.
But that's just the government's noise
making. You haven't looked at any of this!
An expert consultant is a civil
servant working for the legislature,
not a parrot dispatched
by the executive branch.
Please be on the people's side and
write us a good review report.
And please skip such expressions
as "careful evaluation."
Do you understand or don't you?!
Good work. This will give the assemblymen
a positive first impression.
Really? See? I am at this level.
Now, if only the media would
lighten up the mood...
Don't worry. That's
my specialty.
Bae Dal Soo's Law is
not a simple bill.
It is a message of hope to our citizens
drained from cutthroat competition.
And...- Ad lib?
An apology from our world of politics,
which has been indifferent to
the tears of the defeated.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Introduction to the
Standing Committee.
I put before you the bill to
give a second chance to bankrupt
or laid-off citizens, primarily
sponsored by Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
STEP TWO: Introduction of
bill to the Standing Committee.
Assemblyman Jin,
please speak up.
Yes.
Yes, I am Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil.
I will explain the
intent behind this bill.
After the Asian financial
crisis of late 1990s,
cutthroat competition has become the
norm in all sections of society.
STEP THREE: Standing
Committee Review.
However, among the
citizens who have dropped
out or lost out in
the competition,
there are really honest
and diligent individuals.
A social system to save
and aid those individuals
is severely lacking.
Therefore...
Hyung Dal Soo must be watching
from up there too, right?
It's not the end...
Yes.
He must be.
...create such social
atmosphere and...
We have barely taken
our first step.
It's not yet the time
to be rejoicing.
...a second chance to laid
off workers and bankrupts...
Isn't that blood, blood?
Nosebleed!
Oh no, what should we do?
Assemblyman Jin!
I guess he overexerted himself.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Yes, I will go on.
So I think, to such people,
this is a bill that can
really give dreams and hopes.
I will just eat it.
But you are tired.
Just open your mouth.
Men should eat these things.
You want to eat it...
But Assemblywoman
Cheon sent this?
Yes, call her and thank her.
Oh, really, I should.
Speaking of which...
she's calling me.
Aigo, Assemblywoman Cheon, you shouldn't
have sent me this kind of valuable thing.
I did it to energize you when you
are giving valuable service.
Aigoo, thank you really.
Enough about that.
Assemblyman Jin, a problem has come
up in reviewing Bae Dal Soo's Law.
What problem? The committee
has decided to review it.
Not only members from Gookmin
Party, but also those from Korean
Democratic Party are saying
the review should be put off.
Wh-what?
Thank you, Reporter Kim.
I think I know the reason.
What is it?
According to the oldest hand
covering the opposition party,
the Korean Democratic Party is preparing
a bill similar to Bae Dal Soo's Law.
They are saying they won't play second
fiddle to the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
What do we do? If the Korean
Democratic Party introduces
a bill, Bae Dal Soo's Law
will get buried by it.
Or get absorbed into their bill.
Wow, really, they're
being too much.
Party Leader Oh Sae Chang!
Hello.
What brings you here,
Assemblyman Jin?
I heard that there is a factory
making designer knock-offs here.
So I'm here to meet
the factory boss.
What are you talking about?
About Bae Dal Soo's Law.
Let's talk for a bit.
If it's about that, meet our party's
policy committee chairperson.
That's why you can't
be the ruling party.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil!
If you're the number one
opposition party, then you
ought to play like one,
like a major-league team.
Either you support it or you don't. What
do you think you're doing right now?
Party Leader! I said let's talk!
Aish, Party Leader!
Aigo, Chairperson!
About my bill...
please urge the members
to review it soon.
This is a dereliction of their duty.
How many days has it been already?
Let's process a bill that was
introduced a short while
ago during this regular
session of the Assembly?
That's like saying let's do a sloppy job
and rush review and rush process this.
It's the opposite! I'm saying let's not
hold up the review and processing!
Let us all remember a verse from
the poet Midang (PEN
NAME), Seo Jeong Ju.
"For one blossom of
chrysanthemum to bloom,
I wonder if scops owl has been
crying that much since the spring."
In order to create something,
a long time of patience and
suffering is necessary. Isn't
that the meaning behind it?
How can you use a bird even when
you are giving an example, huh?
A bird referring
to himself, huh?
A scops owl, is that a
migratory or resident bird?
Chairperson.
Considering how well the bill is drafted
and how society in general feels about it,
there is no reason to put
it on the back burner.
Particularly, before next
year's budget is passed,
this bill must be processed
so that the people
can start benefiting from
it starting next year.
Assemblymen need time to study
the issues covered by the bill.
Look here!
What have you been doing
not studying this,
all this time? When did
I give you this, huh?
Why don't you work all day and study all
night? Burn the candle at both ends!
Review during the day,
study during the night!
There is an event in my constituency.
So ta-ta.
Assemblyman Jo!
You worked hard.
Hello, Party Leader!
What are you doing?
I felt like I was rude
to you in the morning.
So I want to apologize to you.
Drink one of these.
Isn't that Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi over there?- Huh?
That's right.
She's better looking
in real life.
Thank you.- Yes.
It's an honor.
Let's leave already, huh?- Why?
The night is still young for me.
I'm different from you, Ms.
Choi Double-O. A
crowded place is a bit
troublesome for me.
An assemblywoman must
stay near citizens.
Day in and day out,
you eat and drink
behind closed doors. So
you have no way of knowing
the people's hearts.
Ms. Choi Double-O, you
have bad drinking manners!
What are you talking about?
You may not believe it, but I
have good drinking manners.
If you're curious, just
ask our Assemblyman.
Lie!
Assemblywoman.- Huh?
That badge, you know...
If you put that on,
are people really
going to
flip out?
Do you want to try wearing it?
That's okay.
It's okay!
Whether your mind flips out or
teeter-totters, I
want to see it too.
I said it was okay.- Stay still.
I'll put it on for you. Come here.
Assembly.
It's a badge!
Is it a golden badge?
I will give up on
self sufficiency.
The strategic nomination
you will give...
I want to receive it.
Here you go.
Why don't you wear it longer?
You won't have an occasion
to wear it in the future.
What did you say?- The way I see it, Ms.
Choi Double-O,
you are a born aide.
Like Aide Seo, fill
up all of 20 years
and go for the pension.
I will wear a badge for sure.
Is a badge blind?
To let itself be
worn by any bosom?
Patrons!
Today... this ahjumma...
says she will ring
the golden bell!
Wow! Bravo!
Eat a lot.
Long live Korea!
Order everything. Order all.
Aunt!
We will enjoy it!
Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi
will pay!
Thank you!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Let's go.
Assemblyman Jin.
Ah, yes.
Aigo.
Yes.
Why don't we have a
bowl of warm soup?
Yes!
Now, I feel like I can live.
This is my favorite restaurant.
How do you like their food?
Yes, the broth is
to die for, really.
Later, when you
become the president,
are you going to take this
chef to the Blue House?
Assemblyman Jin.-Yes.
All I can give to you
is this hangover soup.
Actually, I didn't come for help
without any particular plan in mind.
I came here for negotiation.
Then, let me hear your story.
The bill that Korean
Democratic Party is making.
When are you bringing it out?
Since I asked to hurry it up, I
believe it will come out soon.
By the way, why are
you asking about it?
Are you going to report
that it is an imitation?
No..No. As soon as possible and an
imitation that looks as real as possible.
I want you make
it that way.-What?
If you do,
I will withdraw my bill and
support the Korean
Democratic Party's bill.
Do you mean you'll
yield to my party?
I understand the opposition
party's position.
Next year, there'll be a
general election. After
that, there'll be a
presidential election.
You have to show
accomplishments to the public.
But Bae Dal Soo's Law came out
in the middle of your way.
So your position has
gotten obscure.
I am very sorry about that.
I don't need such
an accomplishment.
Just as long as the bill is
passed, I am okay with it.
Look at me,
Assemblyman Jin.-Yes.
I am offended by your remark
that implies our party
is pursuing a cheap way
to earn brownie points.
But I'm even more offended with
your hypocrisy in pretending
that you are not concerned about
getting the credit for it.
Let's stop here.
No, Chairman, hold on.
I might be a hypocrite.
Ah... yes. I am a hypocrite.
Actually, regardless of the
citizens, or who loses,
it seems I am doing this because I
want to make my heart feel easy.
Yes. This is right.
What do you mean, again?
In my heart,
there is a man
called Bae Dal Soo.
A high-rise crane over
40 meters high...
He climbed up that crane.
I...
That person has to get
down to the ground...
Only after that
person gets down,
can I sleep comfortably
with my legs sprawled out.
That's how I can feel at peace.
Party Leader, to make
my heart feel at peace,
I am doing this.
Therefore, once,
please help me once.
Please help me once. I beg you.
Yes. I understand.
Aide Choi, he didn't
go to his house.
Secretary Oh, how about
Assemblyman's phone?
It's still not turned on.
Shouldn't we report
this to the police?
He just told me to go home
first, so I just left...
Yes. Of course.
When he said to go home,
you didn't even look back
and just went while joyfully
singing "Lululalah."
Still, you have to know
Assemblyman's whereabouts!
I tried to do that. But
even if I asked that punk,
he is not the kind of
punk who would answer.
"That punk"? Is that word supposed to
come out of the secretary's mouth?
I am sorry, Honey.
I... mean Aide Choi.
If you use vulgar words
for Assemblyman one more
time, you will have to
move to Gyeongje City.
Yes. I understand.
Good morning.
Assemblyman.
Why? Did something happen?
Where on earth have
you been all night?
- I have been to meet my lover.
- Pardon?
My lover!
Whom... did you say you met?
Representative Oh Se Chang.
This is...
These are the five bills that the
Korean Democratic Party is pursuing?
Upon the condition that I
support those 5 bills,
I received his support
of Bae Dal Soo's bill.
Did I do well?
Assemblyman, did you really...
negotiate with Representative Oh?
That's what I am saying.
Can I step down now?
Assemblyman.
4TH STEP: Resolution from the
Committee with Relevant Jurisdiction.
Let's resolve the bill for the second
chance to the unemployed and the bankrupts.
Assemblymen who are voting
in favor please stand.
We made it.
I proclaim the bill is passed
by 7 for and 6 against.
1ST STEP: Proposal
of a bill2nd Step:
Submission of a bill to
the Standing Committee
3RD STEP: Examination of the
system and wording4th Step:
Resolution from the Committee
with Relevant Jurisdiction
5TH STEP: Legislation and
Judiciary Committee's Resolution.
Yes. We are almost there. Let's
exert a little more effort.
Secretary Byeon, really...
I'll try to get the trial
advanced as early as possible.
Although it is hard, please
bear it a little longer.
Is it possible to be given
a verdict of "not guilty"?
It's impossible.
Damn!
To try to wear a badge once, I worked like
the devil going through fire and water.
I can't help it. I will think about
an idea for a business here.
Secretary General Baek,
please get money
ready to invest.
Chief Secretary Lim!
Five large denomination
bearer bonds...
With that I will keep
my mouth shut forever.
Our party
was damaged to the extent that
the anti-BH faction was formed.
What do you think the cause was?
I am not sure.
It is because an
identity was missing.
While saying things like "moderate"
or "reform conservative",
clumsily turning to the left wing and
then the left wing again repeatedly...
as a consequence, we became
recognized without acknowledging
it as a hodgepodge party,
neither fish nor fowl.
I don't agree with you.
Future politics, whether for
the ruling or the opposition
party, must be led by pragmatic
thinkers who are moderates.
Politics has to be
done with an ideology.
In the world, such a thing as an
ideology for moderates doesn't exist.
Then, I will leave.
Secretary General Baek!
The reason the party
is floundering...
I think differently
about the cause.
Probably, it's because
of the cheap politician
who traded his soul for power.
I have researched European
legislation from the past
with content similar to the
so-called Bae Dal Soo bill.
Due to excessive government
spending, several European
countries are now on the
brink of bankruptcy.
I no longer think the second chance
law is a viable alternative for us.
Irresponsible laws which appeal to
emotions will ruin the country's future.
It is possible to make
all the citizens losers
while trying to offer
some a second chance.
I demand of Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil:
Please stop the emotional
politics that sell emotion
by using a laid-off
worker's tragic death.
Bae Dal Soo doesn't exist
anymore in this world.
The thing that is
called the law...
is supposed to be for the
people who are alive.
Really, he is great.
Great, Baek Do Hyeon!
Now, it's hard to
look forward to.
Gookmin Party members'
favorable votes.
Assemblyman, the Emergency
Measure Committee
meeting will be
held in the party.
Huh?
Bae Dal Soo's Law, under the
idea of protecting the losers,
is a bill ruinous to the country,
that ruins the country's
financial budget, discourages
the will to succeed or work,
and breaks down the motivating
power of social evolution.
As the head of the
Emergency Council for the.
Gookmin Party, I ask
that all assemblymen
participate in voting
during the plenary session,
and I hope you vote
against the bill.
Therefore, before finishing
the plenary session,
our Emergency Council
will not allow anyone
to go on a tour of inspection
abroad without exception.
Floor Leader, please make an
arrangement for everybody,
including the assemblymen
who hold the position of.
Minister concurrently and
who are hospitalized,
so that no one is absent and all will
be able to participate in the voting.
Baek Do Hyeon, in
opposition to the second
chance bill says, "There
is no Bae Dal Soo!"
What can you get by doing this?
What do I want?
There is one thing that I want.
That I, Bae Dal Soo, not be
treated like a piece of trash!
I am not a piece of trash
whom they use as they
please and throw out on the
street as they please,
but I am a human being.
To say that I did not
live so insignificantly
as to be treated like
a piece of trash.
That is it... the
one thing I want!
Are you satisfied?
There is no Bae Dal Soo!
There seems to be three or four
absentees from the opposite party.
Then if we don't do anything, this
means the bill will be rejected.
The only way to proceed now
is to get public opinion
to apply pressure on the
Gookmin Party assemblymen.
If Park Choon Seop is
browbeating them like that,
will there be any assemblymen
who will vote in favor?
Still, let's try to do it. We
came this far. We can't quit.
I have already enlisted
the support of the
nationwide Jin Ji Mo
members (JSP SUPPORTERS)
and social welfare organizations
who assist the underprivileged.
I will take care of the media.
Assemblyman.- Huh?
To the main gate of the
National Assembly. Quickly.
I am Bae Dal Soo.
Until passage of the bill, he said
he wouldn't move even one step.
Against Secretary General Baek's words
that Bae Dal Soo doesn't exist...
Do Hyeon.
The atmosphere is weird.
The one-man demonstration by the
late Bae Dal Soo's son in front
of the National Assembly has
struck a chord with citizens.
The sad death of the late
Bae, and his son's and.
Assemblyman Jin's heartbreaking
story have become public.
Now, enthusiastic support
for Bae Dal Soo's Law
is pouring in through
the internet and SNS.
I am Bae Dal Soo.
Religious circles, academic circles, and
famous entertainment circles as well
all are participating in the
movement of "I am Bae Dal Soo."
While the loud chants
especially from the
jobless, bankrupts,
unemployed young people,
and other socially
disadvantaged people
reverberate as proof
acknowledging Bae Dal Soo,
public support for the Bae
Dal Soo bill is skyrocketing.
To the bankrupts who do their best, I think
we need to give applause and encouragement.
That's why I am participating.
I think it is a
sincere movement.
I hope as many people
as possible will join.
Gyu Hwan.
Assemblyman.
Are you okay?
Yes. I have no problem.
This fool punk.
How will it go tomorrow?
What do you think?
Honestly, I don't know.
But... even if the the
bill doesn't pass,
I think I won't be
particularly sad.
Why?
People have come to find out
that father didn't
live a worthless life,
I am really thankful.
I am more thankful.
Gyu Hwan.
Yes. - Your father...
Let's bring him down
from the crane now.
Yes.
I am Bae Dal Soo.
I am Bae Dal Soo...
Yes?
Hello.
Undisciplined!
By the way, the plenary
session will be held
soon. What are the
secretaries doing here?
What do you mean what we are doing? We are
demonstrating to get the bill passed.
We finished our work.
What do you mean you finished?
There is a stack of
work in the office.
What are you doing
on the street?
I am Bae Dal Soo.
I am also Bae Dal Soo.
We are Bae Dal Soo.
What are you doing?
I am Bae Dal Soo.
We are Bae Dal Soo.
Assemblyman, the assemblymen
are scared right now.
What do you mean scared?
Public opinion in favor
of it is so high
that they feel burdened
to vote against it.
Do you do politics without guts?
I will take all the
responsibility.
Tell them to vote against
it without fear.
Yes.
If there is an assemblyman
who acts according to
his conviction or something
and votes for it,
he will pay for his conviction.
Tell them that as well.
Yes.
Gosh!
List of National Assemblymen
and Assemblywomen.
Why? You can't estimate?
No. If there is no breakaway
vote from the Gookmin Party,
the bill will
definitely be rejected.
There will be voting not according to party
lines. If you see the public opinion..
It is hard to take
an optimistic view.
With Park Choon Seop's charisma,
the assemblymen are overwhelmed.
Ah... What should we do?
I have... a good idea.
National Assembly- Vote now.
I proclaim the bill is passed.
Next, Agenda 65,
I present the bill that
supports the authority to
give a second chance to the
unemployed and the bankrupts.
The people who will vote
for Bae Dal Soo's Law
are implying that in Korea we don't already
have laws that give people a second chance.
They deceive the public.
Even now,
we give a tremendous amount
of aid to the unemployed
and the bankrupts through
all kinds of funds.
With the implication that the bill gives
one more piece of candy to a crying kid,
saying the existing aid is
tremendous is to deceive the public.
Some of the assemblymen
who want to vote against
it insist that, if this
bill goes into effect,
due to the need for 1 trillion won's
worth of supplementary budget,
national finances
will break down.
I want to ask a question
to those people.
A lot of people who have lost at
economic competition then despair,
give up economic activities,
suffer disease,
and wrestle with the temptation of
committing a criminal act or suicide.
How long are you going to keep your eyes
closed against looking at the conclusion of
research showing that the
annual cost to our nation
from social conflict is
tens of trillions of won?
Social conflict?
That happened because the
economy is difficult.
A little while ago, Assemblywoman Hong
mentioned that 1 trillion won as casually
as though it were petty cash.
That is not right.
Honestly, if you invest in a
corporation with that money,
jobs will be produced.
But with this way,
you give out pocket money as though
giving an allowance to poor people.
It will be...
the same as pouring
water over a duck's
back.(CRITICISMS HAVING
NO EFFECT ON A PERSON)
If you have that much money, you'd
better invest. After investing,
you have to revive the economy.
Last,
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, please
make a supporting speech.
Yes.
I am Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
A little while ago,
our respectable.
Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho
spoke in opposition.
I found it very
impressive. I will finish
my speech briefly,
after asking a question
to Assemblyman Kang.
What is he doing?
Assemblyman Kang,
do you know Lula?
What?
Excuse me, Assemblyman Jin. Don't ask
questions, just make your statement.
What does he think I am?
I know Roora, too.
The Angel Lost Wing.
♬ Let's go looking for an angel. Shaba
Shaba, one two three ♬ Is that it?
It is not that Roora. Rather, it's
Lula, the former President of Brazil.
Uh...
He should have said
the President Lula.
Assemblyman Kang said,
let's invest to
revive the economy.
I agree totally.
However, I don't
agree with the words
that giving money to the poor is
the same as pouring water
over a duck's back.
I will ask the question to Assemblyman
Kang, using Lula's phrase:
How come it's called an "investment"
when money goes to the rich
but a "cost" when it
goes to the poor?!
Yes?
Giving a second
chance to the losers
is a worthier investment than
any other investment.
I believe...
that.
I, Jin Sang Pil,
sincerely appeal to you
for support.
I don't mean to embrace
the ones who didn't
put in the effort
and didn't do their best,
and so failed in competition.
Like Bae Dal Soo, the
one who is honest,
like Bae Dal Soo, the one
who follows the rules,
like Bae Dal Soo, the
loser who did his best,
I mean to embrace those.
Then, the world where we live,
will become a little warmer.
There will be more days when we
meet and smile at each other
than the days when we
get angry or fret.
I believe that.
Please, this Bae Dal Soo's Law...
Please vote in favor of it.
I beg you.
Thank you for listening to me.
Don't tell me. The votes aren't going
to be according to party line?
Not at all... The votes will
be according to party line.
More than a fifth of the
members, 82 of them,
including Assemblywoman Cheon No Shim,
have submitted a request that the method
of voting on this issue be changed.
Pursuant to Article 112, Paragraph
2 of the National Assembly Act,
we will have a secret ballot.
If that's the case, we won't be able to
find out the decisions of the assemblymen.
I will appoint assemblymen
to handle the poll.
Assemblyman Kim Dae Kyung, Assemblyman
Kim Jung Suk, Assemblyman Kim Kyung.
Won, Assemblyman Kim Jung Jae, Assemblyman
Park Chan Woo. Please work hard.
I can't bear it anymore
because I am so curious.
Aide Choi.
What happened?
Did it pass?
Aide Choi.
I hereby declare that the Bae
Dal Soo Second Chance Bill
has passed.
It has passed.
Assemblyman Jin, it passed.
Bae Dal Soo's Law passed.
Yes.
Assemblywoman, you really worked hard.
I...
The fact that it took me so long
to know what this feels like...
I regret it.
Thank you, Assemblywoman Hong.
Assemblyman Jin.
Assemblywoman Cheon.
Congratulations.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Assemblyman Jin.
Hello?-Aide Choi?
Mr. President.
I don't like how Assemblyman Jin works.
I apologize but...
I didn't call to scold you. It's just
that I was curious as
to how you were doing.
Excuse me?
I'm a bit envious of Assemblyman Jin.
How reassuring would it be to
have an aide like you beside me?
You flatter me, Mr. President.
Yes. Then work hard.
- What is it, So Min?
- Aide Choi, Chairman Park.
Choon Seop announced an
emergency press conference.
Our Gookmin Party Emergency
Response Council will
be sending recommendations
to President Seo Dae Han
regarding the current economic crisis and
in order to protect the
nation's fiscal well-being
on the following item.
Please veto the recently passed.
Bae Dal Soo bill.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki