All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Yes, this is Choi In Kyung.
Yes, right now
I am an Aide to Jin Sang Pil.
Yes, he is right next to me.
Take the call.
Who is it that you
are all riled up?
Hello?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Yes, that's right. Who is it?
I am the President.
Oh, yes, Excellency...
I mean President.
I am intently watching
what you are doing.
Thank you. You must be busy
but you've even called me.
Soon, I'll relay my intention.
Work hard.
Hello? President? Hello?
What did the VIP say?
He just says he's going
to send his message soon.
He didn't say anything
more specific?
No.
Is this a warning for me
not to mess with him?
I'll give you VIP's message.
He wants you to resign from the
Secretary General's position.
Why are you doing this? I told you
that VIP doesn't want to see you.
Please tell him again
that I must see him.
Then do whatever you want.
This is quite
fun.Episode 14.
Please look into it. There's definitely
something going on in the BH.
Thanks, Officer Kim. I'll buy
you lunch sometime. Bye.
Bi Gwang!To go!
To go, to go. This is fun.
Aide Choi, when are you going to hire
someone to replace Secretary Kim?
I don't have any plan. Why?
Then, at least change my partner.
Go, stop, go, stop everyday...
I'm dying here.
I'll tell him to
refrain from it.
So... why did
Secretary Kim quit?
Beats me. Maybe he really
hated his partner.
What?
Yes, this is Choi In Kyung.
Yes, Chief Secretary.
Pardon?
Yes.
What...
Aide Choi. Where is the
hearing held again?
It looks like you'll have
to go some place else.
Where?
Blue House, the office
of the Secretary.
Huh?
Because of you, the VIP is
really having a difficult time.
Well, I didn't mean to. I
was just doing my job.
Is that why you called me? You
know I never get intimidated.
Why would I?
Assemblyman.
What did the Secretary say?
Because what I heard
was so absurd.
What did you hear?
Was I mistaken?
What did he say?
Yes, it's me.
Just a bit. Please give a bit of time.
I'll meet with you and tell you.
Elder.
To me,
he asked me to be the Secretary
General of the Gookmin Party.
Secretary General?
Yes.
You suffered a lot
all that time.
Syned & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
These people finally recognize how scary
the Indifferent-to-BH faction can be.
Secretary General? I should have asked
him to make me the party's head.
Right?
But this place is pretty grand.
Pretty grand.
You worked here, Aide Choi?
That's the kind of woman that I am.
Consider it an honor.
I see.
Well, I did tell the Secretary that
I was going to think about it.
Is it really okay for a guy like
me to be Secretary General?
A few years ago, a
first-time proportional
representative of the
first opposition party
took the position of
Secretary General.
You taking the position wouldn't
be considered out of the ordinary.
But this is really odd.
Look. I did away with the
Prime Minister-designate.
And I demanded a special
prosecutor on the Babel thing,
so I've been chasing after one
thing right after another.
It is not like giving one more
piece of cake to the troublemaker.
Wanting me to be the Secretary
General is a little...
What VIP wants now by
enticing you to his side
is to raise his approval rating,
which has hit rock bottom.
And you will not only secure
the next election's nomination
but obtain the title of being the
close aide of the President.
Still, is it okay for him to
ladle things out like this?
As long as it's politically
beneficial, yesterday's enemy
becomes today's comrade.
That's the world of politics.
You call those things
political engineering.
What? Political engineering?
Yes.
Then, what will happen to
Secretary General Baek?
Did something bad happen?
Secretary General, in a few days
you know that there is an
election for the leader of
the Party chapter in the
district I am working on,
right?(HCM IS A PARTY-APPOINTED
PROPORTIONAL REPRESENTATIVE
ASSEMBLYWOMAN MEANING SHE
HAS NO CONSTITUENCY.)
The current leader of the
party members is not
an assemblyman so I
thought it would be easy.
But he is pretty popular
among the party members.
So, I hope you'll give
a supporting fire...
Choi In Kyung Sunbae-nim, I
want to see you for a moment.
Secretary General.
Let's talk later.
Thank you for coming.
Since you said you had
something to say.
I know about your resigning
from your position.
Seeing how you know,
I guess the Elder has
embraced Assemblyman Jin.
Sunbae, you were always going
full speed ahead until now.
And there were too many burdens
that you had to carry.
When you resign, allow some
leeway for yourself and
look back on your
political life.
You used to call for conservatism with a
warm human face, reformed conservatism
that is not hung up
on vested interests.
I invested my hope in the
sunbae who was that person.
Please come back to
yourself of that time.
In Kyung.
Yes, Sunbae.
I am thankful for your words but
one important fact is wrong.
Yes, Secretary. Relay
it to the Elder.
This Baek Do Hyeon will not
resign from the Secretary
General's position.
I will never voluntarily resign.
Sunbae.
Will President Seo Dae Han
throw out Baek Do Hyeon?
Direct Attack During Yesterday's
CABINET MEETING: One Who.
Ruined the Party While Influencing
Peddling Must Resign!
The Secretary General is coming!
What do you think about President
Seo's comment about your resignation?
If the one the President was referring to
was, indeed, me, I think he's mistaken.
If the President will see me, I am
willing to go and explain myself.
Are you saying you have
no thought of resigning?
Well, I don't remember having done any
wrong that requires my resignation.
This way.
Secretary General Baek, don't show your
ugly side and just resign promptly!
Why don't you stop saying
resign and tell me the reason.
You ran the party
into the ground!
I guess you are talking about.
Prime Minister-designate Joo
Cheol Soon's withdrawal and the
passage of the Babel Tower
City special prosecution bill.
But the party floor
leaders in charge of the.
Assembly must bear
responsibility for those.
Even if the party was run into the ground
as you say, Supreme Councilwoman Park,
don't you think that before the
Secretary General, the Party.
Leader and Supreme Council
should bear responsibility?
What? Hey, you, Baek Do Hyeon!
But, why are you using
informal speech with him?
Assemblywoman Hong, don't side
with him and just be quiet.
Secretary General Baek, if you keep doing
this, we can forcefully remove you.
Before it's too late,
resign honorably.
I have no thought whatsoever
of voluntarily resigning.
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon!
But, how can the so-called
Supreme Council
not even take care of a
mere Secretary General?
That's why you get called
the Lowest Council.
Where do you think this is,
to barge in like this?
I have movies I want to show
Secretary General Baek, so I'm here.
What movie? "Avatar"?
Avatar, my butt.
There are so many Korean movies
that far excel "Avatar"...
Here, take a look. "Leave
While They Are Clapping,".
"When You Leave, without Adieu"!
Secretary General Baek,
just leave promptly.
Don't you have any pride?
Secretary General
Baek, resign already!
The die has been cast already.
Yes, resign!
Just resigning will
be good and pleasant!
Do you know how serious the
situation is right now?
This is the perfect time, okay?
Step down.
A Gallup poll showed that the opinions
favoring your resignation are only 30%.
Those opposed to it are 50%. If you
hang in, you have a winning chance.
Tell Assemblywoman Hong Chan
Mi to schedule meetings
with Assembly news desk chiefs.
But... I can't get in touch
with Assemblywoman Hong.
I think an order has been handed
down from the Blue House.
Syned & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Deliberate Bankruptcy, Unpaid
Wages, Save Our Families!
Workers Are Not
Disposable Goods!
You Are Being Too Much.
Strike, Illegal? No, Layoff Is!
Guarantee Stable Jobs.
I saw you demonstrating with a pitched
tent in front of the Assembly Hall.
So I've come all the way to
your company.- Thank you.
Because of these kinds of company
owners,even good ones get cursed at.
But this president
did go to jail.
But he has committed
pretty serious crimes.
And saying our unpaid wages can
be addressed in a civil lawsuit,
the government keeps
sidestepping our problem.
The way I see it, the president
certainly siphoned money to elsewhere.
Assemblyman, please
use your influence.
No matter how hard we
scream, it just won't work.
Yes, I understand.
I'll do my utmost...
I will really try hard.
Assemblyman Jin, Aide Choi is
ordering us back as soon as possible.
Why?
Baek Do Hyeon is getting
crucified right now.
Huh?
Gookmin Party Leadership
Demands Baek Do Hyeon's.
Resignation and Anti-BH
Faction Joins in.
The Anti-BH faction
can be like that.
But just at a word from the President,
how can the party leadership...
Wow, how can they do this to him,
between the same Pro-BH members?
There is no permanent friend or
enemy in the world of politics.
This is the outcome of cold calculations
and the workings of survival instinct.
Rather than Baek Do Hyeon, a
power with a very murky future,
they chose Seo Dae Han,
the current, live power.
Of course, cash is
better than a check.
This kind of thing is called
political engineering, right?
The thing that you talked about.
Well, yes. I guess
you can say that.
Even so, Secretary General
is persevering pretty well.
He is trying to drag
this out so that he can
find a way to reconcile
with the President.
We shouldn't just
sit around either.
Of course. Secretary General
Baek must step down
so our Assemblyman can
gobble up Gyeongje City.
Even if Secretary General
Baek resigns, another
candidate will come out from
the Pro-BH faction anyway.
Whether our Assemblyman
can get the nomination...
Assemblyman, you might as
well also take action now.
I have no interest in
this kind of mud fight.
Dong Cheon, there's a standing committee
meeting today, right?- Yes, there is.
Hurry up and prepare. All
of you, go back to work.
Deliberate
bankruptcy...Unpaid wages...
How come they are not coming?
Did something happen?
I have to talk about the unpaid
wages today, without fail.
Assemblyman Jin, are the Gookmin
Party members not attending today?
No, they are very busy studying
about political engineering.
How come Korean Democratic
Party members are not here?
Over there, they are not just
studying but having a symposium.
What?- A party convention.
Oh, that's right. They
are doing that today.
Then, I guess I can't talk about this.
I have to talk about this.
Assemblywoman, how about just you and
I talk about this? What can we do?
Assemblyman, the result of the Korean
Democratic Party's convention is out.
Oh, really. Let's see.
[NEWS] Oh Sae Chang's
Non-Mainstream Faction Wins.
Korean Democratic Party
Convention by a Landslide.
Wow, here, the big boss
himself was shown out...
Wow, what will Assemblyman
Jo Woong Gyu do?
That total thug.
Serves him right.
I am sorry to come to a funeral house (IN A
SADDER SITUATION) to bemoan my misfortune.
You snarled at him too much during the
period leading up to the convention, Punk!
Do you know what Oh Sae
Chang's close aide
told me? Because I
majored in education,
I should look for a place where I can
open up a cram school next year.
I told the party boss that I'm
going to switch party affiliation.
What?-If I go out
and set an example,
those assemblymen out of
Oh Sae Chang's favor?
Their buttocks will
be dancing to leave.
Do Hyeon, you take the assemblymen who
favor you and leave the party too.
That makes no sense.
Why doesn't this make any sense? Political
parties breaking up before an election...
It has happened countless times in
the history of Korean politics!
You're drunk. Stop it.
I've already come up with
a plausible cause too.
I will take a stand against
regional political parties, smug
in their regional popularity,
and build a national party!
I will realize a true policy-focused
party that will transcend left-right
ideologies and emulate the middle-way
principles of practical politics!
Do Hyeon, let's try
and do heavyweight
politics now.Let's
overturn the status quo!
Jo Woong Gyu Declares
Defection...
Jo Woong Gyu is going around
yapping about how there
will be defecting members
from the Gookmin Party, too.
Is it possible for Secretary
General Baek to leave the party?
This might be Jo Woong Gyu's deception.
Don't hastily assume things.
Secretary General.
Secretary General,
what brings you here?
As the leader of the Pro-BH
faction, I came to make a proposal.
What do you mean, proposal?
I'm sure everyone knows
there's talk about a
party realignment with Jo
Woong Gyu's defection.
So, are you saying that we should
leave the party as a group?
Obviously the political situation in the
immediate future is extremely uncertain.
If you want to be the
surviving members, entrust
your political future to me.
What do you mean by entrusting
our political life to you?
A 20% approval rating for
the President entering
the second half of his
term is unacceptable and
50% of the people are against
Baek Do Hyeon resigning.
I am asking you to
choose one of us.
Jo Woong Gyu's withdrawal
from the Korean Democratic.
Party is creating tension
for the Gookmin Party.
Discussion of the possibility of
a defection by Baek Do Hyeon,
who has been under pressure
from President Seo Dae Han
to resign, is becoming the
center of the tension.
While it is a known fact
that Baek Do Hyeon has
contacted the Pro-BH faction
assemblymen in succession
an analysis is being raised
which is not overly speculative
that there will be a secession
to form a new party.
Secretary General Baek.
What is the motive for airing dirty
linen among the Pro-BH faction?
I have none. It is
whatever you hear.
The more you do this, don't you know
that you are further angering the VIP?
The thing that I know is that there could
be another faction within Gookmin Party.
Within the Pro-BH faction
there is a faction, the B-BH
faction consisting of assemblymen
who are breaking free.
What?  -The B-BH faction
are coming out in the open
with the possibility of
holding Jo Woong Gyu's hand.
Secretary General!
To prevent that situation from
happening, all you can do is
to set up a private meeting
between Elder and me,
not to stupidly take in
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Stupidly?
Let's see if what you
wish will happen.
Yes, Secretary General.-Get
me a trustworthy reporter.
Yes, I understand.
Yes. Yes, goodbye.
What did the Secretary say?
About the Secretary General proposal,
he told me to keep it a secret.
He is worried that if
it becomes public, the.
Gookmin Assemblymen will
be shaken up by the news.
You must not mention it until
Secretary General Baek resigns.
By the way, do I have
to do it?- Pardon?
I mean, if I play pat-a-cake
with the President,
I am afraid the citizens who have
believed in me will be disappointed.
Look at what you
have done up to now:
Opposition to the party's
opinion about the
real estate law; Opposition
to appointing the.
Prime Minister-designate;
And passage of the
Babel Tower City special
prosecution bill...
Until when do you want to clean up the
matters that someone else brought up?
Real politics is what
you have to make.
If I become Secretary
General, what can I make?
Renovation of the party nomination
and reform of the party.
The chance to correct
our politics right from
the root, fundamentally,
has come to you.
Really...
Excuse me. Assemblyman, a strange
article appeared on the internet.
What kind of article?
Assemblyman Jin, you are the next
Secretary General-designate...
Right now, what kind
of article appeared?
What were you listening
to while I was talking?
Assemblyman, if the reporter
was not out of his mind,
he should have written it as
some kind of possibility.
It looks as though he wrote
it while he was drunk.
Should I have his press pass
revoked at the reception desk?
Seriously!
Who on earth leaked
it to the press?
Seeing how you know,
I guess the Elder has
embraced Assemblyman Jin.
Why?
Aiee, Assemblyman Jin is inside.
Wait for a moment.
For a moment for me, also.
What are you doing?
I will tell him so please
wait a little bit.
Please, for a moment.
Wait a little bit!-
Assemblyman Jin!
Ah, Aide Oh!
Now...
Assemblyman Jin said he has
no comment about this matter.
Assemblyman Jin! For a
moment.- Is the article true?
That is... For us...
For a moment! Please
keep your voices down.
Assemblyman Jin!
Assembly Jin, is the content
of the article true?
Have you heard the story about
the Secretary General-designate?
Yes. It is true that I
received the proposal.
I said I would think about it.
Let's go.
When did you receive
the proposal?
Chief! That article is
not a false report.
In Kyung! In Kyung!
In Kyung!
Ms. In Kyung... Is it true
what Assemblyman Jin said?
Yes.
Dae Bak! - An event!
How can the President act this way?
Who has worked so hard meanwhile?
Such a rogue villain!
If Assemblyman Jin becomes Secretary
General, all of us may get kicked out.
Don't you think so,
Assemblywoman Hong?
Syned & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Secretary General!
We will entrust
our political lives to
you, Secretary General.
You are doing too much!
A special presidential pardon?
Yes... The chairman...
There is a rumor that he will
be released from jail at
the end of the month by a
special presidential pardon.
Oh, no. That's too much.
Aide Choi, did you find out? Will he
receive a special presidential pardon?
The government refused to
confirm the information.
Because it is
personal information,
they can't reveal it even if
an assemblyman requests it.
Seriously, these people...
Aide Choi. Let's do it. The
press conference!- Pardon?
I am opposing the special presidential
pardon for the entrepreneurs including him.
Really, the employees didn't get paid
so they are starving on the street.
What did they do so well
that they will receive a
special presidential pardon
and get released? Right?
I fully agree with you. But
just let it go this time.
What are you saying?-A
special presidential
pardon is decided
by the President.
While the President and Secretary General
are fighting under water right now,
you can't fall into hostility
with the President.
Why, if I stand out, you are afraid
I won't become Secretary General?
I don't care about that, so
arrange a press conference soon.
I have explained so much to you,
the reason why you have to
become Secretary General.
Well, let's do the
press conference!
Think again, please.- No.
I will proceed.
I can't do it.- Aide Choi!
I can't do it!
Do you think something will be
changed even if you act like this?
No, nothing will be changed.
However, think about it.
Is there any guarantee
that you will get another
chance like this again?
Do you want to throw away the
position of Secretary General over
the matter of a special pardon for
an unscrupulous entrepreneur?
I absolutely cannot
agree with you.
Aide Choi.
Yes.
Do you know? - What about?
Right now, when I see you,
you look like a technician, a
political engineering technician.
I am very interested in watching your
bloody fight with the President.
I have been a comrade
with Elder for 10 years.
It's excessive to express
it as a bloody fight.
It is said that political power
does not last for 10 years.
If the power doesn't
last for 10 years, will
the political comrade
last for 10 years?
What is your business?
I want to receive help
from the Anti-BH faction.
What's the condition?-
Right now, there are about
35% of Anti-BH Assemblymen
in Gookmin Party.
I will ensure that you keep this
ratio at next year's nomination.
45 percent.
40 percent.
Do you think you will get nominations
from Secretary General Jin Sang Pil?
I will send Assemblyman
Kang Sang Ho.
Wow, this house is really nice.
Really it's nice.
Assemblywoman Hong, the
price went up a lot?
Sit down please.
Yes.
This looks like Chiang Kai-shek (LEADER
OF THE REPUBLIC OF CHINA) and Mao.
Zedong (CHAIRMAN OF THE COMMUNIST PARTY
OF CHINA) united their countries.
Secretary General, please
tell us your intention now.
If Elder doesn't change his position by
the National Assembly session tomorrow,
Pro-BH members who follow
me will switch to Anti-BH.
Both of you announce
the joint statement.
With what kind of subject?
Secession from the party.
Secession from the party?
Secretary General!
I haven't heard about
secession yet...
It is not us, but the President.
President?
I will summarize the statement.
The essence of the existing state
of affairs that makes the ruling
party the Blue House's pawn is a
resurrection of corrupt politics.
The President leaves the
party to the assemblymen
and members and withdraws
from the party.
The President's term lasts for 5 years
but the party must last for 100 years.
Hopefully, giving up your lingering
attachment to the party,
you will devote yourself only to the
citizens during the remainder of your term.
Secretary... General Baek,
this seems too strong.
Secretary General, we are
confronting the President.
I already delivered my
intention to Chief Secretary.
Whether this statement will be announced
or thrown into the garbage bin...
it depends on Elder's decision.
Right now, when I see you,
you look like a technician, a
political engineering technician.
BH Chief Secretary.
Yes. Chief Secretary.
Pardon?
BH called us. At the National Assembly
session tomorrow, Secretary General Baek
will request the President's
secession from the party.
Yes?
Wow, Secretary General
Baek is really brave.
BH decided to confront him, too.
How?
BH will appoint you as Secretary General
at the National Assembly session tomorrow.
What? We haven't decided it yet.
You must make a statement of acceptance of
the position of Secretary General tomorrow.
As soon as you finish your
speech, under the name of the.
Supreme Council of the party, the
party delegates will declare
non-confidence in Secretary
General Baek and
appoint you as
Secretary General.
What is this, without
any discussion with me?
What do you think about it?
I will follow your decision.
Then...
Aide Choi?
I am sorry about earlier.
I spoke without thinking.
No. They were not wrong words.
They were wrong words.
You are still upset.
I am sorry.
When a man like you becomes an
assemblyman, I don't want you
to become a politician who
flashes briefly and disappears.
Your goal is to receive
the public's applause but
my goal is to get such an
assemblyman re-elected.
Syned & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Dad!- Huh?
Phone.
Who is Baek Do Hyeon?
Baek Do Hyeon.
What brought you
all the way here?
The person who will fight
with the President tomorrow?
This neighborhood is very quiet
even though it is in Seoul.
Are you accepting the position
of Secretary General?
Whew. You came here because
you are getting anxious.
What should I do? Because
the Indifferent-to-BH
has never been promoted
by the head before,
I can't decide.
What should I do?
Just be satisfied now with
your national popularity.
Being Secretary General is
not something you can do.
You appear to be
scaring me a lot.
I just might do it.
I have waited on the
Elder for 10 years.
Even if you should become
the Secretary General,
you will only be dishonored
as the Secretary General
with the shortest term in the
Gookmin Party's history.
I can't help it.
I will be Secretary General.
If you ignore my warning,
if you become Secretary General
tomorrow, we will declare
that the President must
withdraw from the party.
You can count on that.
Assemblyman Jin, you will be buried so deep
you will never be able to dig yourself out.
I will accept the
Secretary General's post.
Think carefully.
The Spoilsport originally
doesn't think a lot.
Gookmin Party Emergency
General Meeting.
AGENDA: Party Normalization
After Crisis.
I am at the National
Assembly where an emergency
meeting of the Gookmin
party is being held.
President Seo Dae Han's demand
that Baek Do Hyeon resign
as Secretary General, which
has been made public,
along with Jo Woong Gyu's withdrawal
from the Korean Democratic Party
are in the center as the behind-the-scenes
stories of a political shuffle.
Today's meeting is expected to be
a turning point in the situation.
In this situation...
Yes, while I am speaking
at this moment, Secretary.
General Baek Do Hyeon
is making his entrance.
My position is firm. I
am standing my ground.
If you want to remove me
as Secretary General,
find an appropriate ground for disciplinary
sanction, and get ready to sanction me.
How dare you talk
about discipline?
Stop being absurd and
step down honorably!
How can we drag down
the Secretary General?
What are you doing while
he's still talking?!
Be quiet!
You be quiet!
Get down. Down.
My fellow countrymen.
And my Gookmin Sunbaes
and fellow members...
Regardless of my
faults, I regret that
an event as unfortunate as the
one that has happened today
had to happen.
As Secretary General
I bow my head before the
citizens and offer my apology.
Don't just apologize.
Resign honorably.
Stop clapping!
Get down now! Get down!
Just Resign!
Well, as expected the devil is good.
Baek Do Hyeon appears pitiable.
Because our citizens have
a lot of compassion...
they will put pressure
on the President.
The basic problem is Jin
Sang Pil, the hopeless guy.
Members take a firm stance on
Baek Do Hyeon's resignation
as Secretary General which
he says is impossible!
That's all.
VIP hasn't made any moves yet?
No.
It's not too late to reconsider
the defection declaration.
If one draws a sword,
one should wield it.
At this rate, something
disastrous could happen.
That's what makes
politics interesting.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
will make a statement.
Yes.
The leader of the
Indifferent-to-BH faction,
I am Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
If I...
were to become the
Secretary General,
let me tell you the first
things I'm going to be doing.
It's the acceptance speech.
First, the nominations that are shared
among the Pro-BH and Anti-BH factions.
I'm going to get rid
of those first.
The leader of the Pro-BH
faction and So-and-So
Hong who always
follows him around...
The leader of the Anti-BH faction and Mr.
Avatar right next to him...
I will never give nominations
to those assemblymen
who lead the faction battle.
If you're just going to
talk nonsense, step down!
Let him talk!
How dare you order me around!- What
are you talking about right now?
And, I'm going to make a ruling party
whose level is equal to the Blue House.
I'm going to push forward
things that are done right,
and oppose to death
the wrong things.
If the President orders
some weird errands as if
the party is some kind
of a branch in Yeouido,
be it some kind of an order, a call for
a favor, or a request for cooperation,
I'm never going to do it.
Is he now saying he's going to
be the Secretary General or not?
Let's listen some more.-
Hurry and step down!
And the assemblymen here.
Yes, well,
now that I've been around here for a while,
there are a lot of good assemblymen, too.
There are quite a few. I should reward
them of course, reward them a lot.
Publicize them a lot, too. But
the assemblymen who desert their
own principles and stay at the.
Assembly only in order to become
employees of Gookmin Corporation;
Those who do other things
instead of attending
important meetings
at the Assembly;
Those assemblymen who,
when the aides pour their
efforts into drafting
the questionnaires,
they walk around showing off their gold
badges without even taking a peek at them:
Be careful. If I ever catch you,
it's going to happen in the blink
of an eye. You'll be surprised!
Hey, Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil! Stop
the nonsense and get down here!
Is he a thug or what?!
He has no respect for elders.
Get down here immediately!
Assemblyman Jin. Stop that talk and
just make the acceptance speech.
Don't you see that's what I'm doing?
You be careful, too.
What are you doing now?
I'm saying, if it's the Secretary
General who does those things,
then I'll accept it.
It's none other than JSP,
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil,
the most popular guy in Yeouido, the
leader of Indifferent-to-BH faction.
When he becomes the
Secretary General,
shouldn't he do those things at least
to be able to save his face a bit?
But I'm sure he's not appointing
me to this to do those things.
Why? Because those people who are
experts at political engineering
picked me after punching
in the calculator!
Political engineering?
Assemblymen here, by any
chance do you know Mi.
Bang Precision Engineering
Technologies, Ltd.?
The chairman of that company went
bankrupt on purpose and ran away,
so the employees didn't
get paid at all.
Right now, the employees
demonstrate in front of the.
National Assembly building by
putting up a tent every day
to receive their unpaid salary.
The chairman committed a lot of
wrongdoings as well and went to jail.
But soon, he will be released from the
jail with a special amnesty or something.
Well, Assemblymen here, did you know about
it? You didn't know about it, right?
Mi... Bang... Precision? Well...
Today's my first time hearing about it.
Do you know about it?
There is no way for
you to know it!
Everyday, you are studying so hard!
The political engineering!
What on earth is the Secretary General
position? What is so great about it?
Everyday you try only to read his mind!
Everyday you go back and forth in a flock!
That's why, before our
eyes, before our noses,
so many pitiful people are
always, always, crying,
Everyone can't see that. All the
assemblymen and assemblywomen.
This punk has a way with words.
Executive Director Baek. No,
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
I won't do it.
Until the day when the East
Sea's waters andMt. Baekdu
are dry and worn away. (LYRICS
OF THE NATIONAL ANTHEM)
Until finishing the national
anthem and sounding a beep.
So do it for a very long
time, Secretary General.
Do Hyeon has been to the Palace
of the Dragon King underwater.
Yes, Elder.
Come by in the evening.
Let's have dinner.
Yes, I understand.
This is a real plea to you.
Please let me not ask
this kind of plea, again.
Stop political engineering please!
Let's do politics! Politics!
According to my researching
about the politics:
We shall fulfill a role
in assuring all citizens
are leading a worthwhile
and dignified life,
promoting the mutual
understanding, and
maintaining the public order.
Syned & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Blue House, Gookmin Party, Baek
Do Hyeon Vote of Confidence.
Jin Sang Pil. Resolution
of Precision.
Engineering Technologies,
Ltd Past Due Wages.
As expected.
Yes? Aide Choi.
Secretary Kim is preparing
for the civil service exam.
Civil service?
But how did you know
that, Aide Choi?
Without me knowing, the two of
you have been keeping in touch?
I got an email.
Please review the incoming bills which
have been requested for joint submission.
How can I know all of them just looking at
them? I need explanations. First sit here.
And I saved this... Eat this.
I'm due to have tea with
a reporter so I have to
prepare the materials. I
will let Aide Seo in.
But...
This time, her grudge
lasts for a long time.
You kicked out the Secretary General
position. Of course, she got upset.
Secretary Oh, have some.
No, thank you. Look at these
consignment expenses.
After the sound of a beep,
you will be connected
to voice mail. To record
a message, press 1...
Sunbae Jo Woong Gyu, I haven't been able to
contact you and I'm concerned about you.
When you get this
message, please call.
Hello, Assemblywoman Hong.
Why is she like that?
Say there. Say there,
Secretary Byeon!
Can you please play Go-Stop
just with your hands?
Okay.
Way to go. I will
blow it all up.
Aide Choi, this resolution...
I don't understand well...
this part...
'Establishing the system
of common prosperity...'
Aide Seo is responsible
for resolutions.
Assemblyman, are you
wondering about anything?
I will be happy to explain.
Oh, it's okay.
What makes you so giddy?
Haven't you heard the
news about Madam Hong?
What about Assemblywoman Hong?
-At the district.
Madam Hong had marked
as her territory,
there was an election for selecting the
leader of the party chapter today.
She was defeated badly by the current
leader of the party chapter. Yoohoo!
Then, isn't she going to get
nominated there next year?
Probably not!- Since she was crucified
by the local party members,
it won't be easy
to get nominated.
If Madam Hong shows up at the main building
next year after losing her gold badge,
I will really ignore her.
Assemblywoman Hong!
Where is Secretary General?
He is outside right now.
Where outside?- Yes?
Where?!
I am regretful to hear the
result of the election
for selecting the leader
of the party chapter.
What?
Regretful? If Secretary General
had supported me properly,
would it have happened this way?
It's a misunderstanding,
Assemblywoman.
What?
Misunderstanding? Tell
Secretary General.
I want to hear the explanation
from him as soon as possible.
A national political party
promoting the middle line...
My challenge to become the cornerstone in
the foundation of such a national party
has failed.
However, I will start
taking up a new challenge.
Leaving behind the worn out
liberals, I am being embraced
by the arms of the
future-oriented conservatives.
It's not for criticism without
providing alternatives.
I'm doing it in order to join hands
with responsible political power.
I have decided to join
the Gookmin Party.
Finally, I would like to
express my gratitude for
my lifelong friend and true comrade,
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
In Kyung.
Are you disappointed?
Ultimately, is securing the nomination
and being elected in the next election
more important than
your political beliefs?
Choi In Kyung.- Do
Hyeon, it's fine.
See it from my viewpoint, In Kyung...
There have been politicians
who believed that their creed
was the most important.
So the pure-hearted were made fun of
and were defeated in the elections.
But In Kyung, the
fact is it's scary.
Aren't you afraid of having fingers
pointed at you as a migratory bird?
A migratory bird can fly farther
than a bird whose wings are clipped.
Because in order to fly
a bird must exist...
Aide Choi! Aide Choi! Which
past conference is this from?
Secretary Song, did Aide Choi
already leave for the day?
No, she just went out for
a breath of fresh air.
What fresh air?
The Jo Woong Bird.
It seems she's upset about
that Jo Woong bird.
Jo Woong Bird? What
is the Jo Woong bird?
The migratory bird who
chose the Gookmin Party
as his new habitat,
that Jo Woong bird!
Aide Choi.
I'll be going home now.
Come here and sit first.
Well, I don't want to drink.
Just drink a little, okay?
When you're sad,
it's best to drink.
When you drink, it's best
to do it with a friend.
Friend?- Outside of
work, we're friends.
We're about the same age.
What are you doing? Sit down.
Just hold on and let's
have a drink together.
There are a lot of things
that I'm sorry to you for.
Stop being angry now.
Do you think I'm angry
because of you?
Aren't you?
It's because I'm embarrassed.
What are you talking about?
You caught me, Assemblyman.
About me... being a
political engineer.
Ay, that was just me spewing
out words without thinking.
Ahjumma, please give
us more soju here.
Okay.
When I think about it,
the things that I was
confident that if I did well,
the things at which I thought I was
excellent compared to others...
But it's all mostly just
a big mess of cheap tricks.
Those cheap tricks
are what people like
Secretary General Baek,
those political engineers, do.
What you do is art. Art!
A-R-T.- Bastard.
I'm praising you, but how
could you curse at me...
Are you in a drunken
frenzy?- What?
Are you saying politics is
the art of the possible?
When did I... Seriously...
Yes, Baek Do Hyeon.
Yes, Jo Woong Gyu.
You two have driven a nail
into your hoobae's heart.
I'll see how you two
do good politics.
Ahjumma, one more
soju here, please!
What are you talking about, one more?
That makes no sense. Stop it now.
Today, I'm Golden Bell here.
(The Golden.
(BELL PAYS DRINK FOR
EVERYONE IN THE HOUSE.)
What Golden Bell now?
You're just cursing.
You don't know Golden Bell?
Assemblywoman Hong
Chan Mi was pissed.
How are the other assemblymen's
reactions to bringing in Jo Woong Gyu?
They weren't good.
That is just a taste of what things
are going to be like in the future.
What?
We've transferred in the new student. Now
we have to take care of the troublemaker.
From now on, I won't tell you
to do this and do that anymore.
From now on, do whatever
you want, Assemblyman!
Me too. I also won't tell
you to drink anymore.
I must be crazy.- What's
the point in saying that?
I am not some kind of
damn personal servant!
Absolutely not!
Ah, let's go quietly, please!
Why do I have to be quiet?
Because I'm an aide
are you dissing me?
I'm a woman who came
from the Blue House.
The Blue House!
Yes. Now please be quiet.
Let's go quickly.
This is your neighborhood.
What are you going to
do if other people see?
So what if they see? It's okay!
It's okay!
What's with you? You must
have really gone crazy.
People of the neighborhood, hello!-
What are you doing? Hurry!
I'm Choi In Kyung.-
Okay, enough!
This guy here!
This is the assemblymen I'm helping out.
Gookmin...
Hurry, let's go.
L-Let go of me.
You're so obnoxious.
What now?
The words that I
really want to say...
Can I say something without
caring about rank?
When have I cared about rank?
Go ahead. Do it. Do it.
Hey, Jin Sang Pil.- I knew she would do
this. That she would drop honorifics.
You are to me
extraordinarily ugly,
obnoxious, ignorant and poor
out of everyone I've aided.
But
Jin Sang Pil, you!
Even so...
you're the best.
The best.
Jin Sang Pil... must leave the party.
Must.
Aide Choi, you're the best too.
The best.
Syned & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki