All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
From now on...
for you and the
Pro-BH faction...
I will do anything.
I came here to tell
you my determination.
Leave.
Please forgive me for
my past transgressions.
Right... right now,
what are you doing?
What is this?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
Introduces 0 Bills!
This article doesn't
make any sense!
Episode 6Ah, seriously.
How long has it been since the
assemblyman joined the Assembly?!
Aide, you are friendly with
this reporter on their
news desk.Hurry and ask
him to change it for you.
If I go through the desk, I will get
singled out by field reporters.
Where's Secretary Kim?
Where do you think a person who ran
laps in the midsummer heat went?
Where?
If this happens one more
time, I will let you go.
Secretary Kim.
Aide Choi told me to
give this to you.
Ah, yes.
Aide Choi does try to
look tough on her job.
She's not doing that
because she hates you.
So don't be too sad about it.
I'm not sad.
She was rather cool, I thought.
What?
How proud she is of herself, I
only realized this time around.
Not everyone has
that kind of pride.
Secretary Kim, you look at people
from such a positive angle.
In my eyes, she appears like
a returned single (DIVORCEE)
flailing with the only thing
she has left, her pride.
Returned single?
Reporter Kim... My old man entered the
National Assembly only yesterday.
You have to understand that he
has no legislative track record.
The 3 assemblymen who entered
together with Assemblyman Jin...
seem to have introduced
a few bills.
Eh, commonsensically speaking,
would those be proper bills?
They must have been recycled bills
that were scrapped a long time ago.
So?
Please delete my assemblyman's
name from the article headline.
If there is a good item, I will
reserve it just for you, huh?
A salad-green guy with such
a stiff neck (HAUGHTY)!
May he get a cervical
disc herniation!
Who is this?
Hello.
- Have you been well?- Yes.
What brings you here,
Assemblywoman?
I'm here to give my briefing.
I'm a woman whose job is
spokeswoman, you know.
- How about you, In Kyung?- Why would a
woman whose job is to be an aide come here?
I came to fix an article.
In Kyung, now I see that you're the type
who gives in to reality really fast.
What kind of article is it?
So unlike you to be
procrastinating on your job.
Look through it all.
25. Hong Chan Mi 22.9%
What is this?
For all intents and purposes, I was a woman
whose job was being a lawyer, but what?
In the Assembly, my rank
as a legislator is 25th?!
If I'm the 25th out of
300, what is the GPA tier?
You're probably about...
in the second tier.
I'm a person who graduated
from a foreign language
high school (GOOD HIGH SCHOOL)
with a first-tier GPA.
Within this month, make it the first tier
and within the top 5 in the whole school.
But Assemblywoman, that is... if you
give us a little bit of time...
I don't have that kind of time.
Starting next month, I will
send everyone, except the
female secretary and intern,
to my hometown district.
Didn't you send Secretary Sim packing
and hire a local office manager?
Is an electoral district
some bathroom toilet bowl?
Can it be loosened up and
unclogged by one person?!
Still, Assemblywoman, wouldn't
that be a bit harsh...?
This person, seriously, now!
Don't expect humane treatment from
a proportional representative (not
elected, but appointed) with less
than 10 months remaining in her term.
Because right now I can see
nothing beyond blazing a trail
in my own constituency and
getting a party nomination.
Everyone, bear this in mind.
From now on, for
the Office of Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi,
the first objective is to
get a party nomination,
the second is a party
nomination and the third...
also is to get a
party nomination.
The VIP (PRESIDENT OF
KOREA) is deeply worried
about the second half of
the parliamentary year.
It is understandable.
When there are mountains
of bills to be processed,
the opposition party, with
the next year's general
election in mind, will take
uniformly hard line positions.
Leaving the opposition parties
on the back burner, why
don't you first do something
about the Anti-BH faction?
They keep throwing a monkey wrench at
every turn and it is really maddening.
Please tell the Elder that I will
do a thorough housekeeping job.
You have to do well.
If even the latter half of the
parliamentary year goes awry...
we will be lame ducks.
"Lame duck" -an elected
official still in
office after the election
of his/her successor
Do the Party Leader's job right!
You are the ruling party's leader, not
some frontman for the Blue House!
But are you saying, right now, that we
should make a strategic nomination?
Then, I can't participate
in a meeting like this!
Did something happen
at the Blue House?
You don't look so well.
I'd better tie up the
Anti-BH faction.
How?
By using our power, the right to give party
nominations for the next general election.
-Party nomination rights?
- I should make a special committee
under direct party control to
improve the party nomination rules.
These assemblymen at the end of
their terms... Just the sound of
"nom" from party nomination will
make their hair stand on end.
Just the fact that the party
nomination talk has started
within the party will be enough
to freeze them with fear.
So you are saying, frighten them
to make them follow meekly.
Assemblywoman Hong, please openly
make a statement that we should
make a special committee to improve
the party nomination rules.
Are you asking me
to bear the brunt?
I know it's burdensome
in many ways.
However, punches like this must be
thrown, even among the Pro-BH faction,
by my direct associate assemblyman
to deliver more impact.
But, Secretary General...
Just one wrong move and I might
become the target for Anti-BH
hatred and be forced out of
the spokeswoman position.
While trying to make
my own constituency,
the only title I can flaunt is the
longest-serving spokeswoman for the party.
Things like this must be
undertaken by someone with
adversarial zeal, like
you, Assemblywoman Hong.
Secretary General...
So far, I have never refused
anything you asked me to do.
To the extent that even though
I'm a married woman, they
mockingly call me Secretary
General's Yeouido wife.
- Assemblywoman
Hong...- I am sorry.
Please leave me out of
this just this once.
Don't you want to see me
in the Assembly next year?
Aigoo... Hey, everyone!
At least put a popsicle in
your mouth while doing that.
You're doing this to survive.
What a shame it will be if you
get heat stroke and fall sick.
Here. Everyone share.
Those of you fasting, there
is ice water here. Take it.
Oh, thank you. Come
here, everyone.
Everyone, hurry and come.
Hello?
Assemblyman Jin, it was
Aide Choi and she said
if we don't return promptly,
she will sack me.
You are back?
Yes. Did everyone eat?
- Yes.- Assemblyman.
Where were you?
I was outside to get
some fresh air.
Please see me for a second.
What's wrong with her?
Jeez. I'm going to go crazy.
Aide Choi is a bit rough
toward the assemblyman.
Everyone in the Assembly Hall acknowledges
that she is an assemblywoman-level aide.
An aide is an aide, what
assemblywoman-level?
Then, what is our assemblyman?
What do you mean by that? Obviously,
he is an intern-level assemblyman.
What is this?Dear Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon
As you know, as a first-term
assemblyman, I am lacking in many ways.
If I ever did something to displease
you, please understand that it was a
mistake made out of inexperience, and I
beg for your generous forgiveness...
It's a letter to Secretary
General Baek.Please
transcribe it in your
own handwriting.
Forget it.
If you read it, you will see that it is
not a real letter of remorse or apology.
This is just a pretext and I
will personally persuade him.
Forget it, you can
take this away.
I guess you are doing this out of hurt
pride, but this is nothing in Yeouido.
There are countless spineless
people who even kneel before
the influential party members
at times of party nominations.
I said, just take that away.
Assemblyman, at this rate,
you will be branded
as an assemblyman without
any sense of presence.
You may just disappear without even being
able to start working for your goals. So...
Aide Choi!Enough already.
I agreed to the change of the standing
committees as you told me to do.
The work I want to do
right now is not this.
Let me do what I want to do.
I will listen.
What is the work
that you want to do?
I...
So that a person like me
is not produced again,
I want to make a law
that prohibits layoffs.
You can draw up as many
bills as you wish.
But enacting them into law is
not within your present power.
Then, a law that does not
let mom and pop stores
like Department Head
Oh's just go belly up!
That also would be impossible,
using your current influence.
Then what do I do?
Should I just swagger and
sit around like this?
Just hand out popsicles to
the people demonstrating
outside the Assembly Hall, huh?
Stay that way?
Did I become an assemblyman
to do those things?
Don't overstate things.
I am simply telling you
about your limits as a
first-term assemblyman.
But you didn't say those
things when you told me to
transfer to another committee.
So you tricked me.
What do you mean by tricking you?
Please do not say that again.
Just answer your phone.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Yes, Secretary General.
This evening, I have a dinner
get-together with close
assemblymen at a Korean
restaurant called Gyeongwon.
I'll have a seat
reserved for you.
Yes, I understand,
Secretary-General.
Later.
What did the Secretary
General say?
Tonight, at a place called Gyeongwon or
something, with his close assemblymen...
he will have a dinner and
he asked me to come.
This is why seniors
are different.
In the end, the Secretary General
first held out his hand.
In great contrast to you, whose pride
was hurt at a trivial thing like this.
At any rate, congratulations
on your escape from ostracism.
Oh, I'm so grateful
to be congratulated.
Today's meeting is probably among Secretary
General Baek's close associate assemblymen.
Close associates?
Even within the Pro-BH
faction, there are many
sub-factions depending on
the patrons or backgrounds.
Of course, the core is
Secretary General Baek's close
associate assemblymen whom
he directly cares for.
- Assemblyman, you are here?
- How are you?
Everyone is here already.
Oh, is that right?
Aide Choi, you did
very well this time.
About what?
About Assemblyman Jin kneeling before
Secretary General Baek, you know.
It was a divine move.
Who knelt? Assemblyman Jin did?
Weren't you the one
who put him up to it?
Assemblyman Jin, welcome.
Oh, my apologies. It seems
I got the timing wrong.
You were invited late on purpose.
It's your first
attendance and we needed some
time to welcome you properly.
Properly?
Let's all give our Assemblyman
Jin a round of applause.
Welcome.
The Financial Supervisory Service says
Saejin and a Taiwanese company NOTec may...
do an M &amp; A.("M
&AMP; A": merger and
acquisition of
another corporation)
Saejin and NOTec Merger...
Including some businessmen
in the upcoming
special presidential
pardon, how is that going?
I think there is a severe
clash of opinions between
the Ministry of Justice and
the financial agencies.
I think we'd better put the house
in order before something happens.
Park Han Sae, who has been promoted
to become the National Daily's
political news editor, is a person
with a strong pro-opposition tendency.
Please take that into
consideration when you
do future interviews
with the National Daily.
Park Han Sae... he
is meticulous...
Meticulous... he's meticulous...
- Assemblyman Jin.  - Yes?
I will relay to you the Party Leader's
message I got before coming here.
What?
We've decided to appoint you
to the currently vacant seat
of the chairman of the party's
Employment Policy Committee
and as vice chairman of the
third political division.
Oh, congratulations!
Wow, as soon as you join
us, you get party posts.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Thank you.  -
Congratulations.
Now, the Seo Dae Han (PRESIDENT
OF KOREA) Government
is coming to the latter
part of its administration.
The silky smooth road from the
earlier times of the administration
has disappeared and only a wild,
thorny path lies before us.
We are the only people on whom the
Elder can rely until the end.
Now...
why don't we all share a drink
to renew our firm resolve?
Here is to the Nation,
People and Party!
Cheers!
Ah, yes...
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
♫ I am sailing ♫
♫ All the way across the sea ♫
♪
Oh, you're a good drinker!
One more shot.
♪
In the end, the Secretary General
first held out his hand.
In great contrast to you, whose pride
was hurt at a trivial thing like this.
About Assemblyman Jin kneeling before
Secretary General Baek, you know.
It was a divine move.
Aide Choi.
The congratulatory message is not
anything urgent.You can go home now.
It's not that.
Thank you for today.
What?
About this. It's a perfect fit.
So Min has very good eyes.
Aide Choi. From
now on, I will...
really do my best.
You do that.
Aide-nim.
Notice
Appointment of Chairman for the
Party Employment Policy Committee
and Vice Chairman of the Third Political
Division (EMPLOYMENT, ENVIRONMENT, WELFARE)
What is this? Jin Sang
Pil has been named the
chairman of the Employment
Policy Committee?
I will send you additional news about Jin
Sang Pil's appointment to party positions.
Yes, as the chairman of the
Employee Policy Committee...
Is the assemblyman going
to take party posts?
Why are these people just
handing out things like this?
It's because the assemblyman
is very capable.
He is a very street-smart
person, to begin with.
To begin with?
Since when have you known the
Assemblyman to say that?
I'm sorry.
Don't talk nonsense.
♬ Let's ride a horse. ♬
♬ Let's ride a horse! ♬
Sing! Sing!
Our Secretary General...
Secretary General! Secretary
General, I'm sorry.
Our Secretary General,
fighting, fighting, fighting!
Assemblywoman Hong!
Fighting!
♬  I can't help it. ♬
♬ Let's ride a horse. ♬
♬ It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay! ♬
♬ Let's ride a horse... ♬
Aigoo, Chief Lim, why didn't
you have a drink with us?
Where have you been?
I'm fine.
Please take this.
The Way A Party Nomination...
This...what is this?
It's a matter decided
by the faction.
Please broach the subject in tomorrow's
party main incumbents' meeting.
Me?
The Way A Party Nomination Is
Made Must Be Debated Soon!
The way a party
nomination is made?
Of course, officially it has to be
represented as your personal belief.
Then...
At this age, do I have to
wait for you to get drunk
and escort you back and
even cook for your fast
relief from a hangover?
Aish, then, just stop,
if you are so butthurt.
I will bear it for
Ae Ri's sake, aigoo.
Ae Ri, my butt.
Aish, you disloyal punk!
With your hyung waiting
outside, did the expensive
liquor travel down
your throat smoothly?
It just went down
straight and easy.
It went down straight.
Hey, you should have
said something.
You just wait if this
ramen tastes bad...
What is this?
This is the Han River here.
You know my blood
sugar is high...
Eat, eat, eat it up.
Oh, Aide Choi!
I came to ask him something.
Am I disturbing you?
Aigo, what, what, what is it?
Come here and eat
ramen while we talk.
It's okay. I'll wait outside.
Hey, after meal, look here!
Did you do something
wrong again?
Aigoo, really...
Why, you should have come in.
If the ramen gets soggy,
it will be inedible.
Sorry to disturb you
while you were eating.
How was your first
factional meeting today?
It was just... interesting.
Hearing a lot of things that I
could not get from newspapers...
In the near future, you will experience
many changes in your day-to-day life.
Reporters will follow you around
and government agencies and
big corporations will get men
specifically to deal with you.
The stiff attitudes of the party
incumbents, let alone those
of the government officials,
will turn around completely.
Aigoo, I guess factions
aren't liked for nothing.
That faction is like a thorn
attached to a beautiful rose.
If you become intoxicated
by the sweetness a
faction brings, you can
lose your soul to it.
Use your faction, but you
cannot let it enslave you.
Okay. I got it.
Did they, by any chance, give
you an order at the meeting?
It's a matter decided by the faction.
Please broach the
subject in tomorrow's party
main incumbents' meeting.
- Me?- Of course, officially it has to
be represented as your personal belief.
An order?
I'm asking because I'm
uneasy about their excessive
kindness. They even
gave you party posts.
I didn't get anything.
Okay, I guess I was
overly sensitive.
I'm sorry about what
happened this afternoon.
For raising my voice
over nothing.
That's okay. I was impolite.
I am sorry.
Our Aide Choi is, after all,...
a magnanimous person,
magnanimous.
Magnanimous (KOREAN PRONUNCIATION ENDS
WITH "BAE," HOMOPHONE AS STOMACH)!
You're the best.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Magnifico!
Goodbye.
The Way A Party Nomination Is
Made Must Be Debated Soon!
Gookmin Party Headquarters
The opposition parties are organizing
a special consumer economy committee
and planning a national tour.
We can't just sit
still and do nothing.
Since the supplementary budget
bill was passed too, in order to
maximize the effect, how about
we ask the central party office
as well as branch offices in
the provinces and cities to
organize special committees
to stimulate the economy?
That's a good idea.
The Supreme Council
will review this.
Okay, then, we will move on to
discuss miscellaneous items.
Is there any assemblyman
who wants to speak?
Yes, I..., hmm, I will speak.
Next year's general
election is not far off.
That election..., I mean, how we are
going to make party nominations...
I felt like I had to say
something about that.
Assemblyman Jin, you can't bring
up such topic willy nilly.
What do you mean willy nilly?
I'm an assemblyman,
too, and I think I
can talk about this.
Quick! Record this and send
the file to Aide Choi!
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!-
Umm, okay, yes.
Or whether we will do an open...
open primary...
I think we have to decide soon.
Open Primary - a primary
election in which the
public participate and
directly select candidates
So what I'm saying is whether
a screening committee
will screen candidates
like we're doing now
or whether we will
do that open...
open primary...
I think we have to decide soon.
Did he consult you
about this first?
Ahew, this old man really, when
I was so patient with him!
What do you think you're doing?
What do you want now?
Last night you told me you hadn't
gotten any order from them!
I got it this morning.
Don't lie to me. Do
you think I'm stupid?
If I had told you yes,
you would have thrown
a fit again, telling
me not to do it!
That's why I did it.What
did you tell me before?
Except for breathing, we would
discuss everything together!
I didn't want to put you
in a difficult position.
Okay?
What did you say?
Then, are you going to be
an aide all your life?
You can't be on bad terms with Secretary
General Baek!That will be all my fault.
My throat hurts from
riding a horse too much.
In any event, I will take
care of that faction stuff.
Don't worry about it.
I want to rest.
Oh, my throat.
What in the world is this
party nomination for
everyone to be making
such a fuss over it?
You know, assemblymen are like terminal
patients with only 4 years to live.
A party nomination decides whether they
can live it up for another 4 years or...
live a life that's worse than that
of a dog whose owner just died.
I know that but...
Why does Aide Choi
look so worried?
The right to give party
nominations is under the hands
of Pro-BH faction. At the
position of Anti-BH faction,
they will be panic-stricken when they hear
about the party nomination all of sudden.
Our Assemblyman Jin threatened
them with a knife like this!
Jin Sang Pil does not seem
to be in his right mind.
Baek Do Hyeon must have
controlled him behind!
He tried to make us
boiled down with fear.
Yes that's right.We just can't
let him say whatever he wants.
Yes, that is right.
Jin Sang Pil...
crawled between Secretary
General Baek's legs
in the end (REPRESENTS
ABJECT SERVILITY).
Right now, I will go and tell Jin
Sang Pil to take back what he said.
If he doesn't listen, then
I'll just rip his mouth apart.
Leave him alone. What does
that bumpkin know anyway?
Assemblyman Park.
Please let's do
politics gracefully.
ANNOUNCEMENT: Re: Gookmin Party General
Meeting.Today 10am, Room 246 at the Main
BUILDING.AGENDA: Making a Special Committee
to Improve Party Nomination System.
These rascals! A party
general meeting is convened.
It seems like they will make a special
committee to change the party
nomination system, using Jin
Sang Pil's comment as a pretext.
No. Really.
Does this make sense?
How dare a first-term
assemblyman do such a thing?
This...
Well, don't go, Assemblyman Jin.
You did enough for your share.
How can an assemblyman not attend
the Assembly meeting? Don't worry.
Assemblyman.
Go back.
Today's General Assembly Meeting
is held behind closed doors.
I know, but...
How can you bring up changing
the party nomination system at
a time like this? One wrong move
and the party can break up!
Right! Right!
You can't just say no unreasonably!
It is
about time that we
discussed this in earnest.
-  Right! Right!- No.
It's not!
This has an intention to
tame a specific faction!
Not just one or two political
parties have ruined
themselves, playing games
with party nomination rules.
It's not necessary to
discuss all now! In the
middle of tumult due to
the party nomination,
where is Secretary
General Baek, in charge
of the party nomination?
Why is he not here?
If there is any staff on duty here,
bring Secretary General Baek right now!
He is on the provincial
tour right now.
We'd sooner believe a cat that pretends not
to have eaten a canary in its stomach.
There should be a limit
to his cowardice.
Pay attention to your words?
What do you mean by cowardly?
He made his recruit add
fuel to the fire and he
just enjoys seeing the
fire across the river.
You don't call that cowardly?
- Yes. Right.
- That make no sense.
Excuse me!
Hearing your words, it seems I
am the recruit who made trouble.
This recruit wants
to say one word.
I have no business with
you, Assemblyman Jin.
Just keep sitting there. It is the middle
of this senior assemblyman's speech!
How can I keep listening to your
nonsense, Senior Assemblyman?
What?
Please do not lower your speech.
I... for real...
am not saying this because someone
told me to. I am sincerely speaking.
You know why the citizens
don't vote much?
Whether it's the ruling or an
opposition party, you kick up such dust
during every party nomination season.
Because they hate your uproar...
- Yes. Right.
- That makes no sense.
Surely, when it is time
for the party nomination,
someone, surely, will bring up resurrecting
someone while killing off somebody else...
Arguing like that, you will
surely fight over the spots.
Yes?
Oh really!
If we don't want to disappoint
our citizens this time,
whether it's the top-down
nomination system, which
we have right now, or
Open Pri-- or something,
or whatever... LISTEN!!
This time, let's do our homework and come
up with a proper party nomination system!
Now, a first-term newbie with the ink on
his election certificate still drying,
are you impertinently preaching to
your sunbae assemblymen here or what?
You got that right. I
am preaching right now.
What is he saying now?!
No, really, that rascal!
There is no other way for that bastard!
Let me go!
Let go of me! Assemblyman
Jin, come here!
Ahjussi, you should
come over here.
What? There is no way I
am letting you off today.
What are you going to do
if you won't let me off?
Those are Kang Sang Ho
and Jin Sang Pil, right?
- I said, let go of me.
- Hold it in please.
Let him go. Let's see what he does. You
three look like The Three Stooges.
Hey, Jin Sang Pil, for a guy who
used to be a welder at a factory...
What did you say?! Such a rude bastard!
Come here, you punk!
What? A factory?
What is wrong with a factory? What
is wrong with welding? Huh?!!!
This rascal is..
You need a national license to
do that.Do you even know that?
Do you have any such license? At
the most, you might have a driver
license, gotten after about 10 fails.
Just by looking at you, I can tell.
Hey, this puppet for the
Pro-BH Faction! The only
thing moving alive on your
body is your mouth! Punk!
If I am the Pro-BH faction's
puppet, are you the
Anti-BH faction's avatar?
Have you seen it?
I'm asking you whether you've seen
that movie "Avatar." Probably
not, because you were busy being
entertained and playing around!
What? Entertained?
Play around?Let me go!
- You really... - STOP!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
A special committee to improve
the nomination system.
Let's create one.
Assemblyman Park!
But...
if you don't do the
job properly...
I am not going to just
sit still and watch.
Assemblyman Jin.
You will regret today.
Let's do this properly.
Please leave.
You did well. The Secretary
General will be very happy.
The Anti-BH faction has agreed to
installation of a special committee.
Aide Choi, without any
manners, what are you doing?
Today, I am here not as Assemblyman Jin's
aide, but as Secretary General's hoobae.
Chief Im, please go outside.
Ok, what is that you
want to say to me?
Were you always this
cruel, Sunbae-nim?
Why am I cruel?
Wasn't it enough for you
to use Assemblyman Jin
as your 1-year frontman
in Gyeongjae City?
Now you're using him
as Pro-BH faction's
hitman as well. That is
why I am speaking up.
I am asking you. He
is a pitiful person.
Do not step on him even more.
When you fearlessly asked me for the
strategic nomination in Gyeongjae City,
I thought you had changed
a little bit.But in
the end, In Kyung, you
have not changed at all.
What are you trying to say?
It was when I first got to know the
Elder in the Blue House now...
So I guess it's been about 9 years.
You came to see me and
talked very cheerfully.
That you had gotten a divorce and
you could not bear the loneliness.
So that you would get
remarried to politics.
Why are you talking
about that...
all of a sudden?
I liked the lights
in your eyes then.
Because they were still bathed in the same
pureness from our college circle days.
If I use a person like this as my staff,
then I would not go astray in the future...
That's what I thought
it would be like.
So?
However, that kind of
pureness cannot be a leader's
quality even though it
may be a staff member's.
A leader is required to be cruel
at times and cold at times.
Not only did I change, but you have
also changed too much, Sunbae-nim.
In Kyung...
if you really want the wear the badge,
learn how to be cold and calculating.
Don't be swayed by
cheap compassion.
But what is, doing what will
bring benefits to you...
Think about that strategically
and act on it dispassionately.
Sunbae-nim.
If you can't do that,
you will probably stay a
staff member forever.
2015 Forum for
Innovative Entrepreneurs
Baek Do Hyeon, Gookmin
Party Assemblyman-
Now, we will introduce
today's guest speaker.
Please welcome Assemblyman
Baek Do Hyeon, who is
the Secretary General of
the ruling Gookmin Party.
Let's give a round of applause.
Enterprises.
They are very
important, aren't they?
We, of the Gookmin Party,
to you, our innovative
entrepreneurs, during
this year 2015...
Our national hourly
minimum wage...
It was such an honor to listen
to your learned lecture.
Nothing at all.
Please give a lot of
help to Assemblyman Jin.
Will there be a reason not to?
Yes, then, please go in.
Be safe on your way,
Secretary General.
-Assemblyman Jin.-Yes?
This is my company's
commemorative watch.
Is it? Thank you.
I'll see you often
in the future.
Please, go in. subtitles
Yes, go in.
Hey, where is the car?
Yes, the car is parked there.
Since this is a commemorative
watch, take it, or
if it's a woman's watch,
give it to Da Jeong.
-Okay.-Let's leave fast.
I'm hungry.
If you really want
to wear the badge,
learn how to be cold
and calculating.
Don't be swayed by
cheap compassion.
But what is, doing what will
bring benefits to you...
Think about that strategically
and act on it dispassionately.
Yes, this is Choi In Kyung.
You're Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's aide, right?
Yes.
We are the "Opening Your Morning with
Politics" team from KBC 1 Radio.
We would like to invite
the Assemblyman to the
show regarding the
comments he made today.
A live broadcast at the
studio will be hard but
if it's pre-recorded before the
broadcast, it is possible.
Okay.
Since we have to work on the answers,
please send the questions list.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Vikii
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
Lee Taek Jo
What did you do there?
Well, that is...
I was looking at what book the
assemblyman was studying.
Just like the assemblyman,
you want to cram-study politics?
Well, yes...
If I don't want to get kicked
out, I have to try something.
Why are you holding a camera?
Are you already suffering
from an occupational hazard?
You don't have to walk around
cradling it like that.
TO FOLLOW UP: Confirm any payback.
Check if any sponsored
bill or work for constituents
is related to SOI...
Aish, he should smile a little.
His eyes are intimidating.
Look at those old farts...
- I will first check with the
authorities and contact you.-
Please take care of this for
us, no matter what, Ms. Aide.
Yes, I will try. Good-bye.
Aide.
We are from the Korean Businessmen's
Federation.Can we briefly meet with...
Oh... Can you wait a bit?
Please sit.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
Aide Choi?
Reporter Kim.
Is there any good
information from the Party?
-There isn't any.-Come on, you
said you'll give me some sources.
I have to take back a
kill to the editor.
It's not something I
can manage overnight.
Sunbae Choi... I
said I'll do it.
Wait just a bit.
I'll do it for you.
- Where are Aide Seo and
Secretary Sim?!- Huh?
These guys really...
-Yes.-Yes.
Thank you.
To save your face, Director,
I will just overlook this case.
Oh, thank you.
The trouble with Aide Seo is
that he has too good a heart.
If you are really
thankful, next time,
let's have a round
of golf together.
That's not even hard.
But, Aide-nim, you should start gradually
thinking about wearing a badge, too.
Aigoo, for that mere thing!
What is that, anyway?
All things considered, life...
is best lived thinly
and long. (BETTER TO LAST LONG AS A NOBODY
RATHER THAN DIE EARLY AS A SOMEBODY.)
Now, let's drink to that.
Is there a fire or something?
Oh, Sunbae.
Why are you in such hurry?
- It's time that my assemblyman would
be returning.- Working so hard.
Why would you be so loyal to a
hooligan like Jin Sang Pil?
Still, he's the assemblyman
your hoobae is
assisting.That expression
is a bit too much.
Am I Hong Gil Dong's (fictional character from a Joseon
novel, famous for the expression of "not being able
to call his father father" because he was illegitimate)
brother not to be able to call a hooligan a hooligan?
I met a reporter who frequents the
ruling party office over lunch.
- Do you know what he calls
Jin Sang Pil?- What?
Do Hyeon's pet dog.
- What?- My beloved
hoobae, In Kyung.
Why do you live like this?
Yes, So Min, why?
Where are you?
Come back quickly!
Moreover, Kim Bok Soo, Chairman of Korea
Industrial Development Corporation,
interfered with the Assembly
Hall remodeling job and
ordered an illegal contract to
be entered with a named company.
He is accused of receiving an enormous
kickback from the construction company.
It's the Secretary
General's instructions.
Kim Bok Soo, make him lose the
election, no matter what.
As such, I hereby demand
Chairman Kim's
immediate resignation
and the prosecution's
rigorous investigation.
Chairman Kim was the only remaining
chairman of a state-owned
corporation from the
administration before the last.
Is there, by any chance, some political
motive behind this exposure?
What political motive when I
am calling a wrong a wrong?
I didn't speak falsely.
It would be better if he
doesn't hurt someone.
Isn't that right, Aide Choi?
In regards to improving
the nomination process,
did you see the list
of assemblymen?
I saw it. It wasn't too bad.
He was bothered that
he did use a trick.
Although our side is one
person short on the committee,
if it's that close, we could
just sign off on it, right?
This time, I will have to sign off on it
directly with Secretary General Baek.
What?
You see, I have to collect
some amendments from him.
I know what you're
going to say, but
since I don't feel that good,
let's take it easy today.
Really! Are you going to
legislate in this crappy manner?
I asked you to take it easy.
I want to know why you
are overdoing things.
Overdoing what?
The reason why you knelt
before Secretary General Baek.
Without distinguishing whether it's fire or
water, the reason for being overly loyal!
There's nothing like that.
Then, I'll ask you
something else.
The fact that you
have become a slave,
-how does it
feel?-Look here!
You said a while ago that I can't make
the kind of laws that I want to make.
So, if you do it this way,
did Secretary General
say that he was going to
make those laws for you?!
Probably not.
Because he won't like
those kinds of laws.
Then, why are you
being this way?
Secretary General can
do other things.
What do you mean other things?
The nomination.
With the pathetic
state I am in...
I can't do anything in
the next 10 months.
Even if I died and woke up.
I am going to get the
nomination regardless.
Since I poured out my heart...
so that I can get the
nomination, Aide Choi...
help me.
If you had contacted me, I
would have gone to see you.
The one who is thirsty goes
to find the well for water.
First of all... I am
sorry you raised out of
the blue an issue in
the nomination process
which was scheduled to be
discussed later in the year.
I'll keep your regret in mind.
I'm not very adept at
managing the party factions.
In any case, I am willing to endorse...
whichever candidates you propose
to sit on the special committee.
Seeing that you're caving in so easily,
I expect there are strings attached.
We really do speak the same language.
-Please say it.-Because
we were ambushed,
we were helpless when we were attacked.
Judging from the current attitude, you can
count on a battle for future nominations.
But considering our morale at the
moment, a fight is meaningless.
If it can somehow be done
what do you think will
improve the attitude of
the Anti-BH faction?
Cutting off the neck of the
main opponent would do it.
Jin Sang Pil.
Can you omit Jin Sang Pil...
for the next election's nominations?
Assemblyman, I have
something to report to you.
Why didn't you go home yet?
I was going through the contribution
funds account summaries and it seems...
there is $100 from your wife.
Gyeong Ah did?
Hyung, please get the car.
Why didn't you get off work?
Yes. I was looking at some of
the National Assembly records.
Secretary Kim is seriously
diligently studying.
You know how to eat meat, right?
Yes.
Secretary Kim, you really
have a great appetite.
He eats well.
Ah that's right; but Secretary
Kim, where's your hometown?
It's Busan.
Really?
But seeing you closely, I feel
like I have seen you somewhere.
What?
Oh no, I think you seem familiar,
but depending how I look, you
don't seem familiar as well.
I do hear that often, since my
facial impression is a bit ordinary.
Dae Bak!
Joo Hee!
It's meat! It's meat!
I'm so hungry. I thought
I would faint and die.
Hey! Wash your hands first and then eat.
You act just like your dad. Eat
slowly and little by little.
Look at her eat.
Hi.
Hello.
You look cute. Eat a lot.
Why did you donate? You
don't earn much as it is.
I did it, since Joo Hee
asked me to do it together.
Do you want to live together again?
I'm sorry, but I don't have
the confidence to do that.
Why don't you feel confident?
You don't have to wash the
dishes at a funeral or
wash women's backs in the bath house
like you did a long time ago.
Even if you do it, I won't let you.
Don't worry.
It's not that.
Then what is it?
I just think you're a different person.
What?
You come out on the TV news and
are someone who just glares
after uncovering corruption.
You're not the person I used to know.
What are you talking about? I am still
THE SAME: Jin Sang Pil the welder.
Honestly, I want to be called
Madam and live a nice life.
But I'm scared.
Because you might tell me that
you want to break up again.
Okay then. I'll wait until
you get comfortable.
Go inside. I'll go.
Go.
A strange list appeared a bit ago.
Please look it over.
What's the important problem?
It's this.
What is this?
It's a list of 28 currently elected
assemblymen of Gookmin Party.
-So?-Most are too old,
or with bad legislative track records,
or with previous corruption records.
By looking at the list,
I am pretty sure that it's a 'hit list".
A hit list?
It's a list of people who won't be
getting the nomination next election.
Probably due to someone's mistake,
I think the list was leaked.
List of names for D Group
But your name is also on it.
Jin Sang Pil.
Next year, I will be running
in Gyeongjae District.
I am going to get the nomination.
Absolutely.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki