All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
I think that the entire SOC
budget must be cut, and
the present $15 billion worth of
government bond issue needs to be reduced.
Deputy Prime Minister,
please state your opinion.
Yes, Sunbae-nim?
I am a little disappointed
in you this time.
I am sorry that I didn't
tell you in advance.
Didn't I tell you what is the
best for Assemblyman Jin?
I am sorry but the best I
chose for him was this.
Whose decision is right...
you will know little by little.
I understand.
Don't try to dodge the
question so sneakily.
Say clearly whether you
will do what I said or not.
I will tell you my
position exactly.
If this committee
doesn't do what I said,
regardless of whether I belong
to the ruling party or not,
I will vote against the
supplementary budget bill.
No. Assemblyman...
Even if someone threatens
my life with a knife...
I will oppose,
absolutely oppose!
Supplementary Budget Bill Review
Hits Snag from Beginning-
The opposition who have met
an unexpected ally in...
Korean Democratic Party Assemblyman
Jo Woong Gyu- How bad must
it be to get that kind of comment
from a ruling party member?
This bill, as it is,
will never be passed!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Episode 5I'm here.
You worked hard, Assemblyman.
- How was I?- You
were the best!
Oh, really?
Did you see me questioning?
See me for a moment.
Why is that ahjumma like that?
Why on earth are you doing this?
Why are you like this again?
So scary...What have I done?
I pleaded with you just to follow
the written questionnaire.
Oh... you're doing this because I said I
opposed the supplementary budget bill.
It was because the Deputy
Prime Minister kept beating
around the bush and not
saying things exactly...
I got hot under the collar and
said it in the heat of the moment.
How can you say whatever because
you're hot under the collar?
I didn't use foul language. I
just said what was on my mind.
As an assemblyman, can't I even
say such things as I wish?
You cannot do as you wish!You should
have consulted with me first!
Am I a robot you operate...
- to consult with you about every
single thing?- Then, what am I?
If you're going to do as you
wish, why do I have to be here?
Okay, I understand. I won't
do this again in the future.
Now, how are you going to
cope with the aftermath?
What aftermath? Did I
do something wrong?
Yes, you've committed
a very huge wrong!
Ah, seriously.
Thinking this is boasting,
I wasn't going to say this.
But look at this now. "Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil Fighting!""You are cool."
"Brave Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil, I'm always rooting
for you." "I'll root
for you." "Fighting!"
"A true national assemblyman"...
The people's praises are no joke
because I voiced my conviction.
That is why you've
committed a wrong.
What are you talking about?
Assemblyman, you will now have to
retract that statement of conviction.
This is the most ludicrous experience
in my 12 years as an assemblyman.
We placed him to lead the
questions to increase the budget.
And what? He will absolutely oppose
it if the budget is not reduced?!
Secretary General Baek, how are you
going to bear responsibility for this?
No matter how ludicrous it was, you
should lay the blame at the correct door.
Complain to Assemblyman Jin,
not to Secretary General!
Assemblyman Jin is a newbie
here in the Pro-BH faction.
If a subordinate messes
up marketing, of course
the company president has
to take responsibility!
We thought he was on our side, too.
But he turns out to be
an X-man (UNPREDICTABLE PERSON).
What can we do about it?
- What?!- Stop it already.
Where are you going in the middle of
a discussion?Secretary General Baek!
Oh, that, that...
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
has caused big trouble.
It will be resolved soon.
I will only rely on
you, Secretary General.
A lot of Anti-BH assemblymen are
anxiously waiting for the budget money.
You will have to give up on
increasing the SOC budget.
Due to Assemblyman Jin's questions,
the public have started to
take a bigger interest in the
size of the supplementary budget.
Secretary General Baek, I thought you
were a person who keeps promises.
No, I cannot allow that.
To ask for more
is stretching it.
- Enlarge it.-
Assemblyman Park...
we don't have an assemblyman
who would demand an increase over the
amount the government has requested.
Secretary General Baek.
Creating something out of nothing
and making the impossible
possible... that is what the
really powerful can do.
Why don't you show me the power of the
most powerful one in our Gookmin Party?
Excuse me.
Secretary General, the
Korean Democratic Party
held a planning meeting
and have decided
not to agree to the passage of the
SFC's supplementary budget bill.
I think their strategy is to put
it to a vote at the Committee.
What are the head counts of the ruling
and opposition party members on the SFC?
Including Chairman Kang Sang Ho,
our party has 2 more seats.
If Assemblyman Jin opposes, the
same numbers of yeses and noes...
It will fail to pass.
Korean Democratic Party Indicates SFC
Vote on Extra Budget Bill Likely
Around now, the party leadership
- must be in great
turmoil...- Yes, he is here.
- Assemblyman.- Yes?
It's from the Office of the Party Leader.
The Party Leader wants to talk to you.
Tell him that he left his phone
here and went to exercise.
I already told him
that he was here...
Don't you have any wits about you?Can't
you even make that kind of judgment call?
- I am sorry.- You should be
more on your toes, really.
Give it to me.
Yes, Party Leader,
this is Jin Sang Pil.
- What?- I was relieved
when I found out
that you were
Assemblyman Jin's aide.
How can you disappoint
us like this?
I'm sorry.
As for Assemblyman Jin,
he is inexperienced.
But you have learned the ropes
properly under Secretary General Baek.
What do you mean by aiding
an assemblyman this way?
But Party Leader, I don't
think this is right.
Why are you scolding
a blameless person?
It's inappropriate to include an
aide in an assemblymen's meeting.
Why don't we dismiss her?
Leave.
Okay.
In Kyung, wait.
Yes?
Please take this away.
Assemblywoman Hong.
Okay.
They will demand...
Distribute a press release and retract
your opposition statement right away.
How can I unsay
what I've already said?
You are about to wreck
the budget review.
Do you even know what happens to the
machine if you apply the brakes suddenly?
Hold on.
From Aide Choi In Kyung
They will demand a retraction.
Do not retort but say you will
give it serious consideration.
Assemblyman Jin! How can you check
your text messages in this crisis?
I'm sorry.
I am instructing you
as the party leader.
Retract it right away.
Assemblyman Jin.
I am sorry but I cannot do it.
What?
When I was a layman, I really hated
politicians changing their words.
And how can I do it?
If your tongue has slipped,
then you should correct it.
How much did my tongue
really slip anyway?
I'm not saying I am
opposing it no matter what.
I'm saying we should reduce
useless expenses and reduce
the national debt. How is
that such a wrong thing?
Of course it's seriously wrong.
When the government wants to
work, insisting on cutting back
the budget... is that what a
ruling party member should do?!
If we are going to do
everything as the government
wants, then why are the
ruling party members elected?
Aren't the ruling party
members national assemblymen?
Aren't they the people's
representatives?
So impertinent. Who do you think
you're preaching to, huh?
A first term assemblyman
should put the party first!
Look here! What party (KOREAN
PRONUNCIATION: DANG)?!
Some Garden Balsam School Party? Are you
Maengoo?(Bongsoongah Hakdang was a Gag
Concert program and Maengoo was a character
in the show, synonym for stupid)
What, you punk?!
Supreme Councilman
Choi, calm down.
Where do you think you are? A green guy
like you, saying such disrespectful things!
Are you saying, if you
don't retract and the
bill goes to a vote, you
will vote against it?
Yes.
You cannot do this to the party
leader's face. Apologize
quickly and say that you
will carefully consider it.
I don't want to.
I got it. I got it, so leave.
Leave here right now!
I'll leave.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
What happened?
Just do whatever you want! Do you
think I will leave you alone?!
Didn't you seen my text message?
My personality doesn't allow
me to say what I don't mean.
Sorry.
You have the face of a person
with badly hurt pride.
Enough is enough.
I am more mad at you
than at Assemblyman Jin.
Do you know how much Secretary
General Baek suffered
from the Blue House today
because of Assemblyman Jin?
Conduct yourself properly.
The President's Senior Secretary for
Economic Affairs has called again.
He said the VIP was enraged
and wants the situation
taken care of as
expeditiously as possible.
I think you will personally have
to persuade Assemblyman Jin.
The stock market, that had been
on the rise for the past few
days due to the expectation of
a supplementary budget, fell.
Until noon, stocks that could
benefit from the extra budget,
including construction stocks,
led the upmarket trend.
But after Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's opposition
statement, feeling
increasingly insecure,
the market sharply declined.
In the event the budget bill review
continues to face difficulties
in the Assembly, related
industries including construction
are expected to
suffer huge blows.
Opinions from Industries
Affected by Extra Budget Bill
I don't want to see
them face to face.
Are you telling me to just
send away the industry
representatives who have come
all this way to see you?
So I have read this.
Isn't that enough?
The assemblyman said he would seriously
review the contents of the opinions.
How about seeing him?
I am sorry. He wants to organize his
thoughts more before meeting with you.
Is he refusing to meet with us?
If he plays it like this, his
next election will be difficult.
What is going on?
Secretary General.
Is Assemblyman Jin in?
As a ripple effect of your
statement, the passage of
the supplementary budget
bill has become unclear.
Not to mention that the
Blue House, the government
agencies, and related
industries are all in a panic.
That is how dangerous a
politician's words can be.
At a carelessly tossed
word, the world is rocked.
Then, are you saying a politician
shouldn't voice his own conviction?
A politician's words must hold one
more thing besides conviction.
A margin left for compromise.
Well, you talk smoothly but what you
mean is to leave a hole to back out.
Like a coward.
The essence of politics
is compromise.
Meeting the opponent's margin somewhere
inside your own margin... that is politics.
It is about time that you follow
the Party's position now.
Then, slash the budget. I
will agree to it, then.
That's impossible.
- Then, I can't change my position
either.- Assemblyman Jin!
Stop just saying "impossible" and talk
to the government to reduce the budget.
That's all the citizens' debt.
Do as the Secretary General says.
What you are
showing right now is not
conviction but conceit.
It's not conceit but certainty.
Certainty that I am right.
- Assemblyman Jin.- In
Kyung, you stay out of this.
I think I have told you before.There
is no correct answer in politics.
Even if there is no correct answer,
there can be incorrect answers.
As for me, I am certain
that what you are
asking for right now is
an incorrect answer!
Sunbae-nim!
Sunbae-nim, wait.
I will persuade him somehow.
Do you still think that you
made the right judgment?
I think I did what I ought
to have done as a secretary.
You gave courage to an incompetent leader.
You did what a secretary ought not do.
Assemblyman Jin will receive severe
disciplinary sanctions from the Party.
Sunbae-nim! Sunbae-nim!
Gookmin Party's leadership is reportedly
planning severe disciplinary sanctions
against Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, who has
opposed the supplementary budget bill.
Gookmin Party Leader Yoon
Jeong SooAs the Party Leader,
I cannot overlook an
individual member's whims.
While the government and
ruling party have staked their
life on the passage of the
supplementary budget bill,
the public attention is on Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil's next move.
Next news...
Will you adhere to your
position even if you
receive disciplinary
sanctions from the Party?
Yes.
About the point that your
opposition statement
is negatively affecting
the economy...
I do not think so.
I think our old man
is a bit cool.
What?
Frankly, our old man totally
pissed and ticked me off.
But watching him fight, with his
conviction, he just looks cool, you know.
- He will change.- What?
That conviction will
change, for sure.
You worked hard. Yes.
- Assemblyman says he
continues to oppose.-
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
continues to oppose.
Shouldn't we all go in there and
intervene with the assemblyman?
When he doesn't even listen to Secretary
General Baek,would he listen to us?
Go home, everyone.
Why? Why is the mood
like this in the room?
Assemblyman, with all due
respect, may I offer
you a word of bitter
(BUT HELPFUL) counsel?
No, you don't have to offer
a word of bitter counsel.
Okay.
Sang Pil!
I mean, Assemblyman, is it true that
you will receive disciplinary actions?
Not yet, but if he opposes the bill in
the next meeting,then that will happen.
- Come with me.- Go where?
- Hospital. Let's go quickly.- Why
go to a hospital all of a sudden?
Let's split open your tummy and
at least get out the appendix.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to go to the next meeting
if you're hospitalized.Hurry, let's go!
When I was enlisted, I
already got an appendectomy.
You don't have an appendix?
What happened with your trip to Gyeongjae
City? Have you met Department Head Oh?
No, I didn't get to see
Ae Ri at all.Then,
you don't have any
gall bladder either?
Should we, then, get your
liver chopped a little bit?
Aigoo, really, enough! Really!
Aide Choi In Kyung
Yes.
Resignation and Acceptance
What is this?
- It is a paper agreeing to the
resignation and acceptance
of positions.- What is
resignation and acceptance?
The party floor leader will
change your standing committees.
If you put your seal to it, I
will take care of the rest.
Are you telling me now to run from
the SFC to another committee?
Running or not, this is the
only solution to avoid
disciplinary action without
changing your stance.
How can this be the only solution?
It's just a sneaky move, sneaky.
People will laugh
at me even more.
Will you accept disciplinary sanctions
because you're afraid of being laughed at?
Aide Choi.
I will really, from the
next time on, consult
with you about everything
except breathing.
So please just this once, just this
once, give me your understanding.
From the next time on?
From the next time? From the
next time on, what will you do?
- What?- A first term
assemblyman, ostracized by his
party and subjected to heavy
disciplinary action...
I don't know what on
earth such a man can do.
If you do not put your seal here, there
is no next time for you, Assemblyman.
Ai, just a minute!
Why don't you let this
go before speaking?
Why won't I be able
to do anything, huh?
When there are so many people
praising me over the Internet!
What did I do wrong to
be able to do nothing?
I will give you an
example of legislation.
Even for a bill to be
introduced to the floor, ten
assemblymen have to put
their seals to that bill.
In order for a bill to be
enacted into law, among the
hundreds of assemblymen
present in the assembly hall,
a majority must approve. But
whom do you have beside you?
I am telling you clearly. Assemblyman, you
will not be able to leave any achievement.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Hey, hey...
- That's Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil, right?- Yes.
I heard that he would be reprimanded.I
guess he's here to drown his sorrow.
Aigoo...
What's up with this
kid, Jin Joo Hee?
Hey, rascal!
- Daddy!- Hey, rascal...
You're here?
- A surprise, right?-
Hey, when did you come?
- A while ago.-
Wow, my rascal...
- Wow, you've become really pretty,
huh?- Ugh, this alcohol smell...
- Did you drink?-
No, I didn't.
You did drink too! Ugh!
I didn't drink.
Wow, the view is totally cool.
Right? Huh? Really cool...
Hey, your daddy works there.
Don't underestimate me.
Should I become an
assemblywoman too, later?
Wow, if my Joo Hee becomes
an assemblywoman...
it would be a rascal assemblywoman,
rascal...Ruined. What should I do?
- Daddy, are you okay?- Huh?
- About what?- You were number 1 on the
search engines all day long today.
Oh, so you came because you
were worried about me?
Not worrying, but just...
- do well.- You did come
because you were worried, too.
Hey, do you even know
what assemblymen do?
I am no less than a
middle schooler.
They are people who make laws.
- Lawmaker.- Wow!
Did you come after studying this?
Wow, Jin Joo Hee.
- Daddy, can you make
this kind of law?- What?
-A law for 6 months'
school and 6 months'
vacation.- Really, you are...
in that respect...
Hey, I'm going to make a law
for school all year round.
But can you really make any
law you intend to make?
Hey, of course, your daddy is a national
assemblyman. What law can't I make?
I can make it all. Hey, all of
this, your daddy... makes it.
I am telling you clearly.
Assemblyman, you will not be
able to leave any achievement.
Daddy will make it all.
I must...
- What's wrong?- Huh?
No,
it's because Joo Hee comes here
personally to comfort her daddy,
I am so moved. You're
all grown up now.When
did you finish growing
up, my Joo Hee?
How dare you... the head of Na Rae
Girls' Middle School's best student?
The head of Na Rae
Girls' Middle School's
best student... Dad
touches it as he wishes.
This won't do. Want to fight?
You, in?
In!
- Bring it on! Bring
it on.- As they say,
As they say, enemies come face
to face on a single log bridge.
Kicking attack!
Take my welding technique!
Scorch, scorch...
As for me, I am certain that what
you are asking for right now
is an incorrect answer!
Yes, Secretary General.
Please set up individual meetings with
the Party Ethics Committee members.
Is it for Assemblyman Jin's
disciplinary actions?
Tell them in advance that
the severity I require
is suspension of his
membership rights.
The duration is to be a
minimum of one year.
But, Secretary General,
if his membership is suspended for a
year, Assemblyman Jin will not be
able to apply for a party nomination
in the next year's general election.
Some may say it is too harsh.
Assemblyman Jin has overstepped
the margin of forgivable error.
But can you really make any
law you intend to make?
Hey, of course, your daddy is a national
assemblyman. What law can't I make?
A first term assemblyman, ostracized
by his party and subjected to heavy
disciplinary action, I don't know
what on earth such a man can do.
If you do not put
your seal here,
there is no next time
for you, Assemblyman.
Running or not, this is the
only solution to avoid
disciplinary action without
changing your stance.
Yes, Assemblyman.
If I do that resignation
and acceptance thing,
can I continue to do
what I want to do?
At least, you will
have an opportunity.
How you avail yourself
of that opportunity...
is yours to figure out.
You will continue
to help me, right?
Yes.
Resignation and acceptance...
I will put my stamp on it.
Jin Sang Pil
I am a little late.
Isn't Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil here?
- Can't you see for yourself?- Did
you perhaps lock him up somewhere?
The way you talk,
really pathetic...
Yes, we've kidnapped him and as we speak,
a hole in the ground is being dug.
But Assemblyman Jo, are you really
going to put it to a vote today?
Of course we should.
Legislative Assistants, what
are you doing? Go find
Assemblyman Jin quickly!
No need for that.
What brings you here,
Assemblyman Park?
Would an assemblyman come to a
meeting to play the game of Go Stop?
Starting today, Assemblyman
Park has resigned
from the Environment
and Labor Committee
and accepted a seat on our SFC.
What are you doing, not removing
that name plate quickly?
Jin Sang Pil
Our SFC people, you all
look so bright-eyed, huh?
Now, let's start the discussion. We have
to be discussing to earn our salary.
We got stabbed in the back
by Jin Sang Pil again.
Now, then, everyone,
settle down.
Since we have a quorum today...
Assemblyman Jin!
Aigoo, Assemblywoman Cheon.
I was wondering why you were
showing some potential...
But in the end, you've tucked
your tail, haven't you?
Yes, I don't have a face
which can look at you.
A face? Did you have any
face to begin with?
Mr. Bae Dal Soo is looking down
from heaven.Be ashamed of yourself.
The supplementary budget bill has just
passed the SFC without any issues.
Whew.
What should I do about the disciplinary
action against Assemblyman Jin?
We should cancel it. Notify the
Party Ethics Committee members.
Yes.
But was there any need to send even
Assemblyman Park Choon Seob to the SFC?
If even Park Choon Seob is on the SFC, it
will be very uncomfortable in the future.
I had no other way.
I gave him a seat on the SFC so he
would give up an increased SOC budget.
That Jin Sang Pil
person, really...
Yes, because of my
foolish mistake
to the party and the elders
of the party leadership
I have caused distress.
I sincerely apologize.
In the future, things like
this will never happen again.
If I do it again, then I'm a real
scoundrel, really. I am sorry.
Please make me an appointment with
Secretary General Baek some time.
Why are your expressions like
that again, like you're angry?
About the Supreme Council, you could
have just sat down and said a few words.
Why did you have to enact
such a humiliating scene?
To get petted by them a little.
You said I wouldn't
be able to do anything if I
am branded by the party.
Why are you all or nothing, polar
opposites in every situation?
Because I am a welder,
a flame-like guy.
Scorch, scorch. Clang, clang.
You know.
Jin Sang Pil, White
Flag Submission!
Jackpot! Secretary Kim, I think you can
set up a fortune-telling business.
What?
A while ago, you indicated this would
be the outcome for the assemblyman.
Oh, this...
Secretary Kim, are your feelers
really that great, to begin with?
Just one look and I know.
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Vikii
You're Gyu Hwan, right?
Yes.
Oh, my! How much you've grown!
Don't cry. Your dad's hurt leg, it
will all get better in no time.
Right?
Excuse me, but who are you?
I am Oh Ae Ri. I am here
to see Assemblyman Jin.
Oh, nice to meet you. I am Aide
Choi, who had called you before.
Oh, is that so?
Aren't you going to eat?
Department Head Oh!
It seemed like you were
going to do something
for a while, but you've
completely surrendered.
Why did you do that?
Did you get scared?
Yes, I completely got scared.
But are you here to ask me that?
Let me just ask you one thing.
I have seen you destroying the Deputy
Prime Minister on the Assembly TV.
You even watch those things?
What you said then...
did you really mean it?
Of course.
Did you hire an
administrative secretary?
No, not yet.
Assemblyman Jin, from now
on, call me Secretary Oh.
Aigo.
I will do my best to assist you.
Thank you, Department Head Oh.
Everyone, please say hi
to our Secretary Oh.
Should we give her a round of applause?
Applause? Applause!
Aigoo, that won't work!
We've never lived in basement
apartments so we can't handle it.
What? A rooftop room? You're
driving me crazy, really.
Hot in summer and
cold in winter.
And when birds come and
shit on the rooftop,
that stench will knock
you dead, dead!
Try smelling it in summer. What?
At any rate, please scour
more and look into it, okay?
What? Okay.
Ahew, darn it!
Hyung, let's stop nitpicking
and just live anywhere.
Assemblyman Jin, I
have a favor to ask.
Please ask the police
to find Ae Ri.
Aigoo, it's okay.
Okay, what is okay? I cannot sleep at
night because I'm so worried about Ae Ri.
What do you mean you can't sleep? You
are only too good at snoring away.
Just hurry and go out
to the secretary area.
Mr. Assemblyman Jin!
- Aigoo, why are you doing this, making my
flesh crawl.- Hey, Mr. Assemblyman Jin!
I understand, so go out there.
Go out there and see.
Eh, you weasel.
After Ae Ri was
so good to you...
Assemblyman.
Made me so surprised...
All Right!
W-What was that?
I've brought your
instant coffee.
Ae Ri!
Please! Please call
me Secretary Oh.
I won't let you alone if you
make a scene before other staff.
Okay... Why are you
doing this, really!
Really? We can use
that place for free?
Wow, thank you, friend! Yes.
Everyone's been working so hard.Let's
eat out together today, okay?
Ohhh!!! Thank you!!!
Assemblyman, I have found the
house for you to live in.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Let me taste this one.
Oh, no. I thought we would have the fun
of doing karaoke after a long time.
After all, this assembly
office doesn't suit my taste.
Aigoo. Endure for 1 year.
As long as you endure,
you can transfer to the
office of the Ministry of
National Defense or any office
of the National Assembly.
Wow, amazing! Amazing!
Wow! Look at this!
So, for this place...
We pay a little bit of monthly rent
and live here. It's almost free.
This is my friend's guest house.
Her husband got
to go for a year's
sabbatical leave to the USA.
However, if you break or damage something,
you will be expelled from here.
Aihew! Don't worry about it.
It's so cool!
It's magnificent.
Well! For the servants called by the
people! Cheer for the Assembly office!
Cheer for the Assembly office!
Assembly office... Really...
Have some of this.
Have a lot.
You said it couldn't be better?
Yeah...
It's good.
From now on, Assemblyman Jin
will not sleep in the office.
We don't have to try to figure
out when we can go home, right?
Secretary Kim, how is it for you
working at the Assembly office?
It's as I expected.
How did you expect?
The dumping ground where
the human trash lives.
Pardon?
It's a joke.
What did you say?
I was joking.
It's really a joke.
This is Assemblyman
Jin's office.
We are trying to arrange
a meal time between
the Secretary General and
our Assemblyman Jin.
Would you let us know
when he is free?
He doesn't have any free time.
Ah, yes ―
Hello?
Ahh. This wench! How arrogant!
Aide Choi, she told me Secretary
General doesn't have any free time.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Hello, Secretary General!
I tried several times
to meet with you.
Oh, well. It happens
that I meet you here.
I have an informal gathering.
I have to leave.
Aigoo! Really! Our
Secretary General!
Really.
Unexpectedly, you
have a long grudge.
I will offer one
piece of advice.
Lay low and exercise more
self-control in the future.
Aigoo. Take out your anger.
It's all in the past, and
I apologized before.
The warning when you
became the assemblyman,
don't you remember that?
I never give my understanding
to someone twice.
Oh well, Secr...
Excuse me. I have
another engagement.
Farewell!
- See you next time.- Yes.
Sunbae-nim!
I am sorry.
Sunbae-nim. I should have known
beforehand that you are uncomfortable.
I thought, for my own self-comfort,
that you would understand us.
I understood immediately.
But Assemblyman Jin put our party
into a critical situation twice.
If I forgive such a person,
I will not be able
to control other
assemblymen's unpredictable
acts in the future.
Then...
you mean you are going to
break with Assemblyman Jin?
I have another engagement.
I have to leave.
Assemblyman Jin...
made a big decision in his
own way to accept the
withdrawal from the SFC and
transfer to another committee.
I wish Sunbae-nim would show
your generosity to him.
Work hard.
Even though it may take some time, we can
persuade him. So don't worry too much.
Yes.
Then, Aide Choi, you
take care of me well.
Yes.
Hello?
Are you Assemblyman Jin?
Yes. That's right.
I am Park Choon Seob.
In the meantime, you
have had a hard time.
No. It was okay. I didn't
have a very hard time.
The person who cleans the windows
has a chance to break the window.
When you tried your best, it happened.
So never be discouraged by it.
Ah. Yes. Thank you.
By the way, why did
you want to see me?
When a person meets a person and they eat a
meal together, do we have to have a reason?
Ah, yes. That's right.
However...
a man who does politics
is a little different.
Yes?
When I was a newbie, most politics was done
at the drinking table in the gisaeng house.
These days, it's done
at the dinner table.
By the way...
I can't understand well if
you beat around the bush.
And I have a tendency to
interpret things in my own way.
Do you mean whether you have
an agenda for me or not?
Assemblyman Jin.
I will ask you briefly
and directly.
Where do you belong?
Of course, I am
in Gookmin Party.
Not the party.
Within the party... Yes?
I thought you were a newbie
in the Pro-BH faction.
But you seem to be an unrestricted
free agent. That's why I am asking.
Well... for me...
Should we have to belong
to this kind of faction?
Politics looks
complicated, but...
in the end, it's a fight
over head counts.
In the large fight, party versus party, and
in the small fight, faction versus faction.
Without factions,
politics can't exist.
Are you trying to
recruit me right now?
Today...
I just came to encourage the
junior who had a hard time.
With this...
treat your employees to dinners.
Oh. You can't do that.
The Assembly's etiquette is not
different from the world's etiquette.
If the senior gives you
something, you just accept it.
Let's eat.
Yes.
Secretary Oh. Where did
Assemblyman Jin go?
Yes. A while ago, he left
for a lunch appointment.
That was not in his schedule.
Secretary Kim, try to find out
where Assemblyman Jin is.
Kim Gyu Hwan?
Kim Gyu Hwan!
I am sorry.
Because of Secretary Kim's
swimming in the morning,
he is not himself these days.
Kim Gyu Hwan! Go to
the front of the main
building of the National
Assembly and call me.
What?
I told you to go to the
front of the main building
of the National Assembly and call me!
Run quickly!
Okay.
Aide Choi. I am here.
I will give you 20 seconds to
run around the building. Run.
- I ran around the
building.- How many?
- What do you mean?- Run
again for 20 seconds.
Wow...
It is not better
than the dog-drills.
What does she mean how many?
Although I ran around again,
I don't understand yet.
Again for 20 seconds! Run!
Oh, I can't watch.
Run!
Run.
Run!... Run!
RUN!
Run!
(FROM SONG SO MIN) The number of pillars
surrounding the main Assembly building!!!!
It's 24.
I will give you 5 minutes. Come back
after finding out how many lights are in
the ceiling of the main Assembly building
by asking at the management office.
Secretary Kim, are you okay?
Where is Aide Choi?
She is in the conference room.
It's been 4 minutes and 32 seconds.
How many?
It's 365.
Sit.
The 24 pillars surrounding the
main building represent 24
solar terms (4 SEASONS AND EACH
SEASON HAS 6 SOLAR PERIODS).
The 365 lights in the
ceiling represent 365 days.
This means to work hard for the people
all 365 days a year without idling.
By the way, during your working hours,
you dared to allow your mind to wander?
I'm sorry.
If this happens one more
time, I will let you go.
Know that.
Yes? Aide Choi!
I have something to ask.
- What is it?- I want to know the
reason why you don't like me.
It is not that I don't like you.
It's that you are not
a kid who fits here.
Why do you think that?
Last time, you told Da Jeong that the
National Assembly is a dumping ground.
I know that wasn't a joke.
That's really your misunderstanding.
I drank too much on that day.
Then, it's a more
serious matter.
To kid who speaks a blunt
remark when drunk,
we can't let him assist an assemblyman.
Keep your head straight.
You have only one chance.
Hyung, here.
Why are you giving this kind
of stuff, Assemblyman Jin?
I will spend it well.
Ask Administrative Secretary Oh to
use it to help the needy neighbors.
Okay.
Yes?
It is hard to join Assemblyman Kim
Hyung Joon's Research Committee.
- Why?  - They are full.
You are not the kind of person
who doesn't check those matters.
They try to read Secretary
General Baek's mind.
Even though you feel frustrated,
take it easy and be patient.
That is the best right now.
I understand. Hang up, please.
What is? Baek Do Hyeon blocked you again?
Yes.
Aicham! What should we do?
When you are marked down, why are you
marked down by the head of the party?
Can you work well if you are treated so?
I don't know, either.
Stop the oppression of the laborers!
Stop it! Stop it!
Aigoo, Aicham! They
are having a hard
time on this hot day.- Stop it!
Stop it!
Assemblyman Jin, there are a lot
of pitiful people in Korea.
Politics looks complicated, but...
in the end, it's a fight over head counts.
Without factions, politics can't exist.
Turn the car around.
- What did you say?
- I said to turn the car around.
Oh...yes.
I told you not to...
I came here to tell you something.
I am sorry. I told him he would
not be able to meet you.
Chief Lim, go outside.
What is your business?
From now on...
for you and the Pro-BH faction...
I will do anything.
I came here to tell you
that I am determined.
Leave.
For my past transgressions...
please forgive me.
Right... right now, what are you doing?
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
AssemblyPreview
I will appoint Assemblyman Jin as
Environmental Health Vice-Chairman.
Why are these people
generous all of a sudden?
He is naturally worldly wise.
Please say this at the press
conference in Juhyeon-dong tomorrow.
I urge the prosecutors to
investigate this case closely.
I think I'll have to do it directly
with Secretary General Baek.
Am I a puppet of the Pro-BH faction and
an anathema to your Anti-BH faction?
You will regret what happened today.
Who knelt? Assemblyman Jin did?
You seem like a different person.
What did you just do there?