All characters, party names,
and incidents appearing
in this drama are fictitious
by the creative works.
Just looking at this
guy, I get excited...
While living, I got to wear
most kinds of badges, but
it seems there is no badge
like this in the world.
But I heard this
isn't real gold.
It is silver copper, 1.6 cm in diameter,
weighing 6 grams, which is gold plated.
It's not a badge. It's a symbol of
being the people's representative.
Anyway, so that I
can just wear this,
please help me out.
You have a prior record which
you didn't tell me about.
Convictions... 4 of them.
When a business man has
an unfortunate time while
working hard, he can get
a star (CONVICTION).
An election is not a battle of stars. (
A "STAR" IS ONE CRIMINAL CONVICTION)
In asking that now, do you mean you
are quiting being the consultant?
I'm saying your image
has to be laundered.
Laundered?
Are you in the midst of litigation
with the laid-off employees?
You lost last year in the appellate court.
You must accept all the employees back.
Episode 1
Workers Struggle Against
OppressionEliminate Out-Sourcing
Will I be doing something which
costs the company money?
I didn't even appear in court because I
don't want to see those guys' faces.
After coming here,
I've heard it all.
Will you show up?
Equal Justice Supreme Court
Wow! How long has it
taken to come here?
What do you mean how long?
It didn't take so long.
Hey, Sang Pil. Was
it about five hours?
One thousand, one hundred
and eighty seven days!
From getting laid-off and
submitting a suit to
today, it has been 3 years,
3 months and two days.
Everyone please rise!!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
I will announce my decision.
Plaintiffs, Appellants Bae
Dal Soo and 15 people.
Defendant, Appellee, Han Kook
Repair Shipbuilding Company, CEO--
I have a weak heart, originally.
Please let me concentrate.
Please.
You Punk, Sang Pil...
Order. Reversal of
the original judgment.
Congratulations!
It doesn't make sense.
It's not fair.
What did he say?
What did he say? Rever...what?
Be quiet!
- Continuing, the reason for the
decision...  - I have a question.
Please speak.
I am Organization
Chief Jin Sang Pil.
Something happened. Something.
As a thirsty deer
searches for water...
there was a boy holding
a welding rod instead
of a text book because
of his poverty.
From that time, for 23 years,
he has done only welding
very diligently.
But, one day, the
company laid him off.
He said he didn't want to get laid off.
Then he got fired.
When he asked for help from the
union, he got stabbed in the back.
He felt wronged so he protested.
Then, he was jailed
and got fined for
interference with business.
I have to pay compensation for damages,
100 million won ($100 THOUSAND).
So?
But, there is a hole to escape
even if the sky collapses.
The judges who sided with the
company at the first trial...
listened to us at
the second trial.
I...
like a mouse waiting for the
sun to shine into his hole...
have been looking
forward to today.
Only ask questions!
Yes. I will only ask a question.
Why don't you say "Sorry" to us?
What?
You pretended to be soothing a crying
baby, then slapped it on the cheek.
- You slapped the cheek again
that just got slapped. -Sit down!
I didn't finish yet! In
front of our factory,
there is a store that sells
cooked ramen 24 hours a day.
That store sells hotteok (A KIND OF SWEET
HOT PANCAKE) in the cold winter time.
By the way, when they cook hotteok,
they flip only once, not twice!
The hotteok is
flipped just once.
Is Korean Law inferior to a
hotteok that it is flipped twice?
Remove him from the courtroom.
These people are
crying right now.
Yes? Leave me alone!
Is it so difficult to
say one word, to say
you're sorry to people
whom you made to cry?
Leave me alone! Aisii!
Apologize! Apologize quickly!
Sang Pil!
Sang Pil.
Why? Will it demean the
judge's honor to apologize?
Do you feel ashamed?
We live with constant begging
because apologizing is not enough.
We are begging a money lender, begging
not to stop the water service,
begging a wife who
wants to divorce,
and begging our kids
who ask for tuition.
You cut our life line like this.
Is it so hard to say even
one word of apology?
- Remove him. -Apologize.
Take him out. Quickly!
Judges! Apologize!
"Sorry that the law can't
take care of you."
Say that!
Say, "Very sorry that the
law didn't protect you."
Why do you do that?
APOLOGIZE!
Why do you come here?
Are you doing well?
Do you think I am doing well?
How is going for you to
become police officer,
which you said you
were studying for?
Not yet.
If you have time to come here,
then study one more word instead.
Dad.
Now, you will stop, won't you?
- Gyu Hwan.- Yes?
Your father is not me,
but the guy who raised you
along with your mother.
The way I see it, it's not something
that you should be concerned about.
Reversal of the original judgment. From
law office team leader Park Chang Ho.
It worked out better
than I thought.
A CEO who is generous to the people who
were fired, despite winning the suit.
I can't do it. Even though the
grave's dirt comes into my eyes.
Absolutely not.
Then, I can't help. Please
find another consultant.
Party nomination.
You don't have to help me
with the campaign but help me
so that I can get the nomination
from the ruling party.
Being nominated is harder than winning
an election in Korea politics.
With your present resume,
you will be dropped in the
preliminary election.
I know you were at BH not
very long ago.(BH: The
Blue House, office of
the President of Korea)
Were you the senior administrative
officer for political affairs?
So?
Shouldn't the rulling party
nominate if BH approves?
Please intercede with the Blue
House political affairs office.
For a fee, I brought a big one.
If the result comes out well,
I will give another big
one as an incentive.
What do you think?
We must do politics
like this, very boldly.
According Public Officers
Election Act 47-2-1,
no one shall offer, declare an intention
to offer, or promise to offer
money, articles, other property
or a public or private position
to obtain a political party's
recommendation of a candidate.
Aigoo, why are you
being so scary?
Are you going to complain
to the prosecutors?
I am also friendly
with the prosecutors.
If you know the prosecutors,
please select from the
Central Election Commission,
the Civil Affairs Office
in the Blue House, and
the Nationalist Party's
Nomination Screening Committee.
You are the style of person who
tells a joke seriously and long.
Do you have proof?
The entire process of consulting
with a client is recorded.
Didn't I tell you about
this at the first meeting?
If you would humbly listen
to my last advice...
this won't be getting a ride on a
quick delivery service motorcycle.
Say it. I will
listen attentively.
Get lost from Yeouido (KOREAN EQUIVALENT
OF CAPITOL HILL) right now, you jerk!
This is an incentive.
This is how politics is
done, very transparently.
The landlord called earlier
and said if this month's
rent is in arrears too,
an eviction will start.
It's a scary world. Now even resignations
are sent in a certified format.
President!
-Don't worry. Starting
next week, I will
regularly appear in Issue
and Talk.-A regular?
After the broadcast, we will get more
clients.Oh, order me a voice recorder.
You said the Department
Chief signed off on it.
I am sorry. Who would have known that
the program head would reject you?
Why would the Program
Head?Why would that guy... ?
It's not a thing to get mad
at the Program Head for.
-Go plead to Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi.-Who?
Assemblywoman Hong told the
program head not to make
you a regular but to rotate
different assemblymen.
She means to hog
it all to herself.
Forget it, I will just
give up going on the air.
In Kyung, that is
complex, you know.
In the past, she might have
followed you around campaigning.
But now, she is an assemblywoman
and you are just a vendor.
Hey, PD Park!
Anyway, the only one who can change
Program Head's mind is Hong Chan Mi, OK?
You, what did you say
at the beginning?
Didn't you say your program head okays
everything as long as it's a pretty woman?
Hong Chan Mi is pretty too.
Nationalist Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi
Hong Chan Mi. Spokesperson
of Gook Min Party
Choi who?
This...
President of a consulting firm,
political commentator...
-Sunbae-nim, why don't you
just say it to me?-What?
Right now, she has a lot to
review before the meeting.
She said she was really sorry.
Did she say she didn't
want to see me?
She said she wasn't here.
Can't we think about
this just one more time?
Too much thinking just
brings too many thoughts.
That is the National
Assembly Hall, punk!
Because the law is like a dog pie,
judges flip it like a hotcake.
We are doomed to die anyway.
We should at least give
a wake-up call to this cruel
society before we die.
Let's go.
Hey, Sang Pil!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Where did you say the 21st
Century Congregation is meeting?
Look who is here.
Have you been well?
But why are you standing
around here and not coming in?
Because you seemed busy.
-Assemblywoman, if
you have a moment
now...-I'm sorry. I have
a prior engagement.
Assemblywoman, just
a moment is...
Well, a moment is not enough. We should at
least talk about the old times over a meal.
I will call you, In Kyung-ssi
(LESS POLITE THAN SUNBAE-NIM).
What? In Kyung-ssi?
Meeting Assemblyman Yang Seong Gil is
impossible due to certain circumstances.
But his constituents
are here to see him.
Does it make any sense
that we cannot see him?
Next in line!
Members of the Assembly
Visitors Reception
Sang Pil, what do we do now?
Let's just leave.
No other way. Break through.
Huh?
Break through!
Go in!
Bastard!
People who just barge in... please
make sure you don't let them through!
Oh, Assemblywoman!
-Sang Pil...-What is this?
Oh, Ahjumma, are you okay? Yes?
Ahjumma?
Sang Pil! An emergency exit!
Hurry!
I'm sorry, Ahjumma.
Are you okay?
But what are those people?
Hello...
I'm Assemblyman Yang's acquaintance. I
was wondering how the decision came out.
Oh, my!
Shut it! This, this,
take this and block...
I am Jin Sang Pil of the Hansujo
Committee to Recover Lost Jobs.
We are starting our sit-in
here, so please cooperate.
Please cooperate, okay?
Where is Assemblyman
Yang Sung Gil?
Assemblyman Yang Sung Gil!
Please come out
here!Please come out.
Ahjumma, are you joking? Aren't
you going to put that away!
What the...?
Look here.
Everyone, stop!
What is this?
Assemblyman Yang Sung Gil of Gyeongjae City
Loses His Seat Over Bribery Conviction
What are they saying now?
Don't you know Hangeul
(KOREAN ALPHABET)?
Hurry and remove that so we
can move our stuff. Hurry!
The areas requiring by-elections
are, including Assemblyman
Yang's constituency Gyeongjae City
of South Gyeongsang Province,
in all four places.
Meanwhile...
Gookmin (PEOPLE'S) Party is
planning to launch an emergency
panel to screen election
nominees this evening...
and work on the party's nomination
for the Gyeongjae City constituency.
Gookmin Party's Nominee
Screening Panel will be headed
by the party's secretary
general Baek Do Hyeon and...
President wants Go Yang Ho, the
former Secretary to the President
of Political Affairs, to be the
Party's nominee for Gyeongjae City.
Let's make it a
strategic nomination.
Korean Democratic Party
You got a call from BH (BLUE
HOUSE, PRESIDENT OF KOREA), right?
The Anti-BH faction will throw a fit,
if they find out.Since Yang Sung Gil
was one of them, they will demand
preservation of their vested interests.
Today's screening panel...Assemblywoman
Hong, please attend in my place.
What?Gong Shim Ui, Member of the
Nominee Screening Committee
Okay, I will.
For this by-election to replace
Assemblyman Yang Sung Gil,
the former mayor of
Gyeongjae City Nam Hyeon
Shik is seeking the
Party's nomination.
Then, there is no need
to screen or whatever.
Have you forgotten about
the principle of screening
out candidates with previous
corruption records?
But he was pardoned. (Kang
Sang Ho, People's Party,
3rd term Assemblyman, "Ban
Cheong", Anti-BH faction)
Among the current candidates,
is there any one similarly
competitive in terms of recognition
and organizational support?
We are talking about
Gyeongjae City here.
As long as it has Gookmin Party's
support, even a stick will win there.
Home grounds should be
tended with more devotion.
Don't you know the people
will wear their rubber
shoes backwards (CHANGE
THEIR MIND) in a moment?
Assemblymen, the election
is just around the corner.
How about leaving the party nomination for
Gyeongjae City to the party leadership?
But are you saying, right now, that we
should make a strategic nomination?
Then, I can't participate
in a meeting like this!
Assemblyman Kang!
I guess you're doing this with the order
from the Blue House, but you shouldn't!
What do you mean an order?What
basis do you have for saying that?
A basis? Look here, Assemblywoman
Hong, even though I
am pretty low in the pecking
order within the Party,
I have been elected three times.
Don't you think
I have a straw (INFORMANT)
in the Blue House?
Let's go.
Baek Do Hyeon did not attend?
He was the one who
usually ranted against a
strategic nomination as a
closed-door nomination.
Since he was in a tough position,
he must have put up Hong
Chan Mi in his place and asked
her to test the waters for him.
In any event, I don't think we
can make do with Mayor Nam.
Why don't we push for Lee Yeong Ik,
former provincial assembly speaker?
Park Choon Seob - 5
times elected member of
Gookmin PartyLeader of
the Anti-BH faction
Let it be. Same old same old.
You are so worry-free.
At this rate, if Go Yang Ho puts
on the badge and gets in, you know
our Anti-BH faction's prospects
will become even grimmer, right?
I do know. Not only we, but
also the person who has
been the neighborhood
bully will be put
in a tough spot.
I know it all too well.
Just waiting for the nomination,
I'm about to lose it.
Anti-BH faction's
opposition is too intense.
Didn't they always oppose me?
Just shove it in their
FACE.KO YANG HO: Previous
Head of Political Affairs
BAEK DO HYEON: Assemblyman. Secretary
General of Nationalist Party
Secretary Ko, the 20th legislative
election is only 1 year away.
How about laying out your wares
when the big market is on...?
Really. Are you saying that you want
to disregard the President's will?
It's been a long time since the
process started, so be aware of it.
How long on earth will they detain
a person without any cause?
I'm sorry. I think I
unexpectedly caused you harm...
Don't apologize. It's my fault that I
was near you when the bomb exploded.
Perhaps, do you work
for the government?
A long time ago, I was there for a few
years. Why? You want to beat me up?
No, it's not that but I
wanted to ask you something.
Assemblymen are said to fight in front of
cameras like a matter of life and death...
But when they're by themselves,
they supposedly call one
another brothers and play together.
Is that really the case?
-You are curious
about that?-Yes.
Hyung, why are you asking
about those things
when you know that it will
make her embarrassed.
I know you guys have lot of
resentment against Assemblymen but
I can't stand that you're
lumping the 300 members
of the Assembly together
and condemning them!
It's true that there are a lot
of ridiculous members, but there
are also a lot of members who think
about the nation and people.
-Then what about us?-What?
When there are so many
assemblymen concerned
with the people, why did
we end up like this?
Are we not people, but animals?
Are we dogs?Dogs? Woof woof?
That is being unreasonable.The problem
with your employer is just...
Yes, enough already.
Why? Let's hear her out.
Tell us.
Why listen? It's
same old bullsh*t.
What? Look here!
Choi In Kyung,
What? Same old bullsh*t?
How dare he when he looks
like shriveled old daikon?
Sunbaenim Baek Do Hyeon
- Sunbaenim? - It's been a long time. I
ought to give you a minute of my time.
I'm Jin Sang Pil of the Hansujo
Committee to Recover Lost Jobs...
I recorded it out of habit,
but I felt sorry for them.
How frustrated must they be to
do something that nonsensical.
Assemblyman Yang Sung Gil!
Come out!
We had times like this before.
Do you meet with people
within our circle?
They're all busy
making a living.
We think differently from the school
days.We don't see one another often.
Why did you hesitate
to contact me?
Just because.I'm trying
to stand on my own.
National Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon's
Assistant, Planning Team Leader in
the Presidential Campaign Office,
Senior Officer in the Blue House...
I didn't get any one
of them on my own.
Before it is too late,
I want to live as Choi
In Kyung and not as
Baek Do Hyeon's kid.
It seems BH has a lot of interest
in the Gyeongjae City election.
(FOR BH) To keep silence is
to be helpful, but any way...
-Did BH tell you to give the nomination
to someone in particular?-Yes.
The person who dismissed you.
Ko Yang Ho?
Once in the National Assembly,
that guy will try to be your boss.
Even now, I have a lot of bosses.
The Party Leader, the Party
Parliamentary Leader, the Party
Leadership Committee Chairman...
Not those bosses in name only...
Ko Yang Ho is the VIP's (PRESIDENT)
bestie and a big shot in his own way.
Even when he was the
secretary, he considered
the ruling party as
the Yeouido branch
office of the Blue House. If he puts on
the badge, how much worse will he become?
He may try to replace me as the
acting leader of the Pro-BH faction.
Of course.
If it's the response you're thinking
about... Ko Yang Ho will veto it.
Do you really mean it?
Instead I'm going to
nominate a fresh person
untainted by the old status
quo for Gyeongjae City.
Then, the people will like it.
Now, let's eat.
Yes.
Aigo.
Hey, come in.
How could you not go a moment
without causing trouble?
Thank Assemblywoman Cheon.
You could have gone to jail.
I am sorry.
Chairman Bae has been praising you a lot.
That you're upright to a
fault. (CHEON NO SIM, SAHWAE PARTY
FLOOR LEADER, 2ND TERM IN OFFICE)
Aigoo, Assemblywoman,
what?Even crooked mouths
should speak straight words
(CALL A SPADE A SPADE).
This kid is not upright to a fault.He's
a wet blanket, a wet blanket!
Aish, eat without
sputtering, please!
Did I sputter?
By the way, Hyung-nim,
now what do we do?We've
even lost the suit.
Can we keep fighting?
Speaking of which, I was a bit late
because we were talking about that.
Assemblywoman Cheon,
please speak.
Now, Assemblywoman
Cheon will speak.
Everybody must know that by-elections
will be held next month.
Our Sahwae (SOCIALIST) Party
decided to nominate single
candidates together with the
Korea Democratic Party.
Gyeongjae City has been
allotted to us (only one Sawhae
Party nominee will run out of
the two opposition parties).
But what does that
have to do with us?
As the only candidate from the
opposition parties for Gyeonngjae City,
our Party is hoping that
Chairman Bae Dal Soo will run.
What?
Me?
Lift your arms. Begin!
1 -2 -3 -4 5-6-7- 8-9-10-1-2-3-4
5-6-7-8-9-10Unity...
Struggle
Let's fight united until
the end.1188th day.
Victory over Korea
Shipbuilding Repair
2-2-3-4-5-6-7-8
Arm exercise1-2-3-4
Well, I'm telling you that
it's such a useless act.
What is the opposition parties'
nomination for Gyeongjae City?
That's a position that even a
passing puppy won't take, OK?
Why would you run in an
election that you can't even
win, waste money, and work
like a dog for nothing?
They said they would raise
the money and give it to us.
We're in a position where we'd swallow even
rat poison, if it's free. Just up and run!
-Hey!-Be quiet!
Sang Pil, what do you think?
What are you doing now?
Huh? I'm asking
what you're doing!
Look here, look here...
Hey, hey!Look here!
Are they telling us to die?
What's this?What's
this, this?(COMPANY FLUNKIES
ENTRANCE PROHIBITED)
Why? What?
Notice to Remove Illegal
StructuresForced
Removal in the event
of Noncompliance
Removal? Are these bastards
fanning the flames?
Oh, Chief Choi, hey, did you
guys drug (BRIBE) the City Hall?
What, jerk?
Hey, do you all want to die?
Hello! Hello, hey, don't hang up! Hey,
don't hang...Hello, hey, Chief Choi!
Hey, you bastard! Aish...
What's the matter?
It's the Labor Support
Team.They're saying starting
today electricity will be cut
off from the tents here.
-Are they trying to suffocate
us?-I guess they've
heard from somewhere
that I would be running.
(STUDENT DORMITORY AREA)
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Job Postings from the
Police Commissioner
A call from Hansung
Designated Drivers Service
How did your meeting with your
friend go?Will she lend you money?
Seon Min, I have a headache
right now.Let's talk tomorrow.
Did you not get it?What
are we going to do?
Goryeo Bank is notifying
Customer Choi In Kyung that
your loan payment for this
month has not been made.
In Kyung, why are you
living like this?
Please turn on the radio for me.
What is your analysis
of the Kookmin Party's
strategy for the Gyeongjae
City by-election?
By-election strategies are commonly
called "a ruling party's grave" (DEATH).
Because they are usually held at the
times of declining popular support,
opposition parties can sell
their theory of the people
making a judgment on the
ruling party's performance.
They will probably select a person
with a solid relationship with the
voting block and counter with the
constituency's diligent servant theory.
-You call that an analysis?-Like
the former mayor Nam Hyun
Shik or the former provincial
assembly speaker Lee Young Ik...
people who have matured
in the constituency...
♬ It's all right, let's go to my house.
♬(2PM'S SONG IS PLAYING)
What are you doing right now?
Oh, you seemed like you hated
it.Ladies dislike politics.
Why do you think women
would dislike politics?
Just turn it off.
So distracting...
No, no, wait, it must
be somewhere here...
I said enough, just turn it off!
No, no, just now here...
Red light!
(BUDDHIST CHANT)
I'm really sorry, I will
take care of it all.
What, no insurance?
I am really sorry.
Ah, really, wait and see if I
will leave this company alone.
Here, just a minute.
Why are you doing this?
Please give me just one break.
I am preparing to
take the police exam.
I don't think I can
afford to be reported.
How about the
damages I suffered?
Do you know how much money
I will end up forking out?
I'll pay you back as soon as possible.
I mean it.
Gookmin Party Stops
Screening Nominees
Stop screening nominees?
Because of a lack of
suitable candidates
they would stop screening? Where
have you seen such unreasonableness?
This is, in order to make a
strategic nomination later,
amassing unreasonable excuses.
As evidence...
Over there the Secretary General
is coming!Secretary General!
What do you think about
the allegation that this
is just taking steps for
a strategic nomination?
I guess it depends on
how you look at it.
Is the rumor that the BH
had a say in the Pro-BH
faction's insistence on a
strategic nomination true?
A party nomination is made by the
party, not by the Blue House.
-Just one more
question!-Just a moment!
Sunbae-nim, it's me.
Oh, yes, In Kyung.
What you said about
vetoing Ko Yang Ho...
Are you of the same
mind even now?
Once I find an alternative, I will
knock him down on the very same day.
Sunbae-nim...
Perhaps, that alternative...
being me, what do you
think about that?
I have no ties to
Gyeongjae City, but
I don't think that is a
decisive disadvantage.
I have built up enough experience
and I also have vision and passion.
- In Kyung...  - I will give
up on self sufficiency.
The strategic nomination
you will give...
I want to receive it.
I'm Korean Democratic Party
Parliamentary Senior
Vice President, Assemblyman
Cho Woong Kyu.
I am in charge of
coalition with the other
opposition party, the
Sahwae (SOCIALIST) Party.
I heard that, Chairman, you have
not yet made up your mind to run.
So I came running.
A guy who has hurt his leg on a plumbing
job and barely operates forklifts...
How can a guy like that
do something like this?
You are more than capable.
Hyung Dal Soo, what are you going
to do about Hyung Sung Gi?
Hyung-nim, I'm asking you what you're
going to do about Hyung Sung Gi.
Just hold for a bit.I'm
talking with the assemblyman.
Is is true that you've been a
welder for 30 years?Haigoo!
Now, do you call this welding?
I'm sorry. I've had such a
long period of inactivity...
Byeon Sung Gi.
You're here, huh?Come
out quickly.
-No...-Where, where
are you going?!
Byeon Sung Gi, won't
you come here!Byeon
Sung Gi, won't you come here?
Byeon Sung Gi!
Seriously!
Look here, Ahjussi!
Why?
I have to finish
the job by today.
What will I do if you chase
away the part-timer?
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
I guess you had a drink?
No.
Now, the reason I asked
you to gather like this
is I think I'll have to run.
Everyone must know that I'm not
doing this out of any greed.
If we are to bring new development
to the fight, no matter what...
What new development?
When they are throwing fits, cutting
off electricity and forcefully
removing tents, at the mere mention
of running in the election?
If you run and lose
and come back,
what do you think those
bastards would do?
-But there is no other way.-What
do you mean no other way?
Let's just make a deal
with the company.
We will acknowledge the
layoff and wrap up the
fight, and they will
discontinue their suits and
- just give us some compensation money.
Let's do that.- Forget it!
Why would we beg now after suffering
so much all this time for our cause?
Hyung-nim!
Even if we do, they are
not going to listen.
-Let's just talk about the
election today.-What election?
If we run in the election, do you
think something will change?
Why don't you acknowledge
that it's a chance to let
the people know about us?
You mean not us, but you!
What did you say?
Do you know how many days it has
been since Hyung Sung Gi left?
Do you or don't you know
about these people sniveling
every night since the big
loss at the Supreme Court?
Since you're getting business cards and
good treatment from this party man and
that party man, you are not even concerned
about those sorts of things now!
It's like you've
become somebody!
Punk!
Aigoo, Chairman!Chairman!
Why are you like this?
-Ah, really.-How can you
say such a thing
to me, punk, huh?
Overlook this.
Now I'm not going to fight
for worker's rights.
Good bye, all.
Hey, look.Hey, Sang Pil!
Sang Pil, why are you
doing this, really?
Why did you do that, Hyung-nim?
Sang Pil, Jin Sang Pil!
Vice Chairman Jin.
Let go of me.
The strategic nomination
you will give...
I want to receive it.
Aigoo, look who is here.
Welcome, Secretary General Baek.
They say people play baduk
according to their personalities.
Your stones move very neatly.
As for me, I've only
learned the baduk fight.
It has become a gonma
(HARD TO SAVE STONE).
It's as if I am looking at myself
sitting on the Nominee Screening Panel.
If you hold on to a hot
potato like Ko Yang Ho,
you'll only end up
burning your hand.
I'm telling you this
because I care about you.
Just use me or the Anti-BH
faction as your excuse
and drop him.
After that, what?
There is a person that
Assemblyman Kang is pushing for.
The former mayor
of Gyeongjae City.
He is of the old school.
Gyeongjae City is where Yang Sung
Gil lorded it over for 12 years.
And Yang Sung Gil was one of us.
It's my conviction that
party nominations shared
according to the faction
line are outdated.
Politics will become too inflexible if
you place conviction above all others.
Secretary General Baek...
conviction is there
for you to bend.
If you detach yourself from a party
nomination for Gyeongjae City,
I will make Ko Yang Ho cave in.
While you are knocking down rivals
and devouring Gyeongjae City,
you are telling me I should content myself
with not having to see Ko Yang Ho's face?
This, it's such a short
end of the stick.
If you say no, you'll hear Ko Yang Ho
announcing his candidacy this evening.
The baduk game will
become a bit messy.
In connection with the
rumor of the Blue House's
interference with the
party nomination,
Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho, a
prominent figure from the Anti-BH
faction, accused the Blue House of
an explicit exercise of influence.
Assemblyman Kang pointed to Ko Yang
Ho, the former Secretary to the
President for Political Affairs, as
the person chosen by the Blue House.
And he is calling for resignation
of Secretary General
Baek Do Hyeon, who is heading
the Nominee Screening Panel.
These people aren't even in
Mak Ga Pa (KOREAN GANG).
What should we do? People's
sentiment will get worse, since
we're fighting for the
government office from outside.
We can also get through in a new place
and not in the city of Gyeongjae.
When that happens, then the
seat numbers of the ruling
party and the opposition
parties will become 150:150.
We'll lose the party position that
we've maintained for 3 years.
If the ruling majority and opposing
minority status is altered,
you know the next step is resignation
by all party leadership, right?
BH2
It's because you're dillydallying that
the Anti-BH faction is acting so smugly!
Even if you have to
force and rush it,
nominate Ko Yang Ho before
the end of the day.
Do not forget. The
President is watching you.
About Assemblyman Kang's claim that the
Blue House exercised outside influence
over the Gookmin Party's
nomination for Gyeongjae City, the
Blue House has countered calling
it a baseless allegation.
Secretary General Baek Do
Hyeon is overseeing Gookmin
Party's Nominee Screening
Panel and his next move
is drawing all the attention
of the political world.
If Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon,
over the Anti-BH faction's dissent,
gives the party nomination
to Ko Yang Ho, the
BH's former political
affairs secretary,
an all-out war between
the Anti- and Pro-BH
factions of the Gookmin
Party seems inevitable.
Yes, Secretary General.
Assemblywoman Hong, I'd
better nip it in the
bud before the weeds
grow even thicker.
Call together all
Pro-BH faction members.
Yes, Sunbae-nim.
In Kyung
We will discuss the stance of
the junior Assembly members
with respect to the nomination of the
Assemblyman to represent Gyeongjae City.
Despite our mutual efforts
to build a more equal
relationship between our
Party and the Blue House,
allegations of the Blue House's
interference with the Party
nomination of its Gyeongjae
City candidate are being made.
We are deeply concerned
with this state of matters.
As such, for stable
progress in the BH-Party
relationship and for victory
in the by-elections,
we urge Ko Yang Ho, the former
Secretary to the President for
Political Affairs, who is in the
middle of all these allegations,
to make a firm decision not
to run in the election.
I am the chief secretary to
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
Why didn't Secretary
General Baek come himself?
-That will be all.-What will become
of the former Secretary Ko Yang Ho?
Why do they leave us alone and put
the knife to Ko Yang Ho's throat?
If they do that, isn't that
a form of insubordination?
If you say no, you'll hear Ko Yang Ho
announcing his candidacy this evening.
Let me file a civil petition.
Go ahead.
Yang Sang Gil says
an apartment is all
he has to his name.
Please find a place where
he can earn some allowance.
A place where he wouldn't lose his
face as a thrice elected assemblyman.
I will do so.
Baek Do Hyeon...
I thought he only had a good head,
but he also has a lot of guts.
KYH Report
He has had a long term live-in girlfriend,
an old college friend, Kim Ji Yang.
I will relay Secretary
General's message.If you
discard your lingering
feelings (OVER THE CANDIDACY),
Secretary General says he too will discard
his lingering feelings over that document.
Ko Yang Ho has distributed
to the media his
announcement of not
running in the election.
The rumor about his run is baseless
and he will dedicate himself
to nursing his wife, who is
suffering from a chronic illness.
I didn't know your wife
was so ill, either.
I'm sorry for our loss but I will find
and nominate another good candidate.
Please tell the President
that the junior members'
latest statement was not
out of insubordination but
out of our loyalty to keep
the majority government.
If necessary, I will visit the Blue
House and talk with him privately.
Through a media interview this
afternoon, Ko Yang Ho, the
former Secretary for Political
Affairs to the President,...
Have you seen the news?
Yes, I've seen it.
I will make preparations.
Bit it try.
Yes, I understand.
Yes, coming through!
Oh!
Aish, you should
have been careful.
I'm so sorry.
Call me when you've made up
your mind to get a divorce.
Go.
Go. Go, go, go!
Dad...
Aish, really...
Where are you?Come
back already.
This is the Legal Department of
Korea Shipbuilding and Repairs Co.
-Yes, this is Jin
Sang Pil.-This is the
severance payment you
had refused to accept.
You've made a good decision.
Hey, hey, hey, stop drinking.
You're drunk.You will miss
your bus at this rate.
Give me one soju.
Hey, what will a failed test taker do back
at home?I won't be able to face my mom.
One order of odorpyeo (STIR-FRIED
PORK CARTILAGE DISH), please.
Hey, let's stop eating and go.
Okay, let's go.
Aigo, I won't go, I
said I won't go!
I'm sorry, my friend
is too drunk.Let's go.
When I said I won't go,
why do you keep...!I'm
going to live here with
these homeless people.
It's better to go.
It's not easy to
be homeless.Go.
Ahjussi, do I know you?
Pshaw, what is this Ahjussi?
Fight?
Hey, hey, hey, why are you
like this?Let's just go, OK?
Gyu Hwan, I think this Ahjussi came
from fighting some independence war.
Look, it says fight, fight!
What, punk?
Does this look like a joke now?Do
you think I'm joking, punk?
Ahjussi, use words.
Aren't you going to let go?Did
you practice some martial arts?
-Stop already.-If I don't stop, are
you going to throw me a punch?
I said let's stop already.
You're not the only one
who got fired and is
living a miserable life.
Do you know what
getting fired is, huh?
Do you know how sucky
that is, punk, huh?
Seriously!
Do you want me to teach you
what getting fired is?
- Getting fired, that thing!
It's a dream
come true for guys like us.
- What punk?
Even if once, that
damned layoff...
Getting that done to us is our
dream come true, understand?
Go on, punk.
Go.
Let's go.
I am sorry about that, Ahjumma.
Since you said you were going to the
seaside, I happily tagged along.
But whose campaign are
you going to help?
Even here, unplanned
development is no joke...
Well, that is one
election promise.
Push throughGyeongjae
City Area
specific development...
Aish, tell me whose
campaign plan is that?
Mine.
Don't joke around! Who's going to give you
a party nomination... Wow, Baek Do Hyeon?
Keep your mouth shut until
the party announces it.
I'm going to bury you
if you divulge it.
I'm in Gyeongjae City
on a field trip.Enjoy
your meal. Respectfully,
Choi In Kyung.
I wonder what In Kyung
is doing nowadays?
Should I tell In Kyung
to organize an alumni
association among our
school circle members?
Just tell me the reason
you wanted to see me for.
At any rate, you are such
a dry person.I wonder how
you won a second term
like this?(JO WOONG GYOO)
And that, in Gyeonggi Province
that's as fickle as bubbling
porridge.(KOREAN DEMOCRATIC
PARTY VICE FLOOR LEADER)
I said what is your business?
Who is the head of my Korean Democratic
Party's non-mainstream faction?
Oh Se Chang, the former
governor of Gyeonggi Province.
I know that he recently
sought a party nomination
but lost out to a
mainstream member. Why?
He did not lose out, but supposedly gave it
up after getting our Big Boss's promise.
What promise?
That he would get to nest in
your constituency next year.
At the beginning of this
administration, you won by 5% even
with the title of the President's
Crown Prince, right?
What do you think will happen if you
go up against Oh Se Chang next year?
Tell anyone to bring
it on.I'm confident.
Oh Se Chang is a presidential
contender who has
been a three time governor
of Gyeonggi Province.
If you continue this way,
this time next year, you will
become an unemployed bum.
A Yeouido high-class bum.
Enough with your silly comments.
Just eat.
Checkmate!
Game over.
You can win with the elephant.
Vice Chairman Jin!
Sang Pil!
Let's fight for the worker's
rights in a refined way, really.
What are you doing with
a lousy cigarette now?
Chairman! Come out and
see!Vice Chairman Jin is here!
Have you been well?
Yes, have you at least
been eating regularly?
Yes.
Where have you been, punk,
to return only now?
I'm back from selling a kidney.
But they gave me a bit.
Let's barbecue some meat the
first time in a long while.
Yes!
Today, it's a daisy.
Tomorrow, it will be a rose.
Making passes, passes, passes,
you must fall asleep.
Now, I'm tired, bumblebee.
Bumblebee!
Tired of waiting, bumblebee.
Alone, this night is
so, so cold.-Cheers!
Aish, really!
Yummy!
-It's yummy, right?-Yes.
You're incorrigible bumblebee.
Bumblebee! Even though I
resent you, I love you so, so much.
Bumblebee!
What are you doing here alone?
It's comfortable, being alone.
I needed to think about something.
Hyungnim, there is something
I want to tell you.
Sang Pil,
there's something I want to ask of you.
What is it?
The elections...
you should run.
I'll hand down the chairman position
to you, so please run in my place.
Ah, don't talk nonsense.
Sang Pil! Look at me, with a bad leg
like this, I've even been divorced.
Why are you saying that right now?
If a guy like me crawls out there and asks
for votes, who's going to vote for him?
Got divorced by a cheating
wife and his only son...
To keep him from being called a cripple's
son, if he gave up his parental rights...
When told this, who in the
world will vote for me?
Tell them not to if they don't want to!
Are you going out there to win? What's
important is that you're participating.
Even if I lose, I should gain
a lot of votes and lose.
We need to gain even one more
vote so those people get scared.
When we rake in even one more vote,
this deaf-like world will listen.
Even if they're pretending, we
need to do at least that much.
Sang Pil...
after the election, no matter what
you do, I won't say anything.
So my wish, please, fulfill it.
Huh?
These are the ARS research results
from 500 people in the district.
Baek Do Hyeon 28, Oh Sae Chang 59.
The more serious problem is,
starting next month, people will
move into the apartment complexes you
attracted to the newly planned city.
The demographic is mostly composed of
thirty- and forty-something renters moving
in from the outskirts of Seoul and large
supporters of the opposition parties.
When it rains, it pours.
In any event, it would
be best to run in next
year's election from a
different constituency-
What you're saying!
Does that make sense right now?
You're telling me to
betray the people who
supported me all this time?
I'm sorry.
Leave.
Opposition, Labor Candidate
for Gyeongjae City Nomination
As opposition parties'
nominee for Gyeongjae
City, where they face
absolute disadvantages,
there is news of Mr. Jin Sang
Pil, the Chairman of Hansujo
Committee to Recover Lost Jobs,
fast rising as a strong contender.
Are you kidding me?You
won't put this away?
Mr. Jin Sang Pil was born in Gyeonggi
Province.He did not finish high school,
but entered Korea Shipbuilding
&amp; Repairs Co.
and worked there as a
welder for 20 years...
Tomorrow, the opposition party members
said they'd come to get a firm answer.
You don't need to worry about other
things, but just say one word, "OK."
Everything else I'll take care of, got it?
Yes.
Sang Pil! No... Chairman,
you have a visitor.
Visitor? Who?
Who are you?
Hello, I should introduce myself...
My name is Choi In Kyung.
Oh, yes.
You remember me, right?
What?
At the police station, the
same vegetables to the
same rice (GARDEN-VARIETY,
SAME OLD SAME OLD).
Ah, right!
But why are you here, Ahjumma?
You know this is a hotel, right?
Don't imagine anything wierd...
I wanted to meet quietly.
Who is it, someone who, in
the middle of the night...
You're really not trying to do
something weird to me, right?
Just follow me.
This is weird.
I have brought Jin Sang Pil.
Hello,
I am the KMT (NATIONALIST PARTY)
Secretary General, Baek Do Hyeon.
Of course I know you;
you're a famous person.
I'm sorry for bringing you here
in the middle of the night.
In Kyung, could you leave us for a moment?
Yes.
Please sit.
What is it that you want to tell me?
I'll get to the point.
The offer to become the opposition
parties' single candidate...Decline it.
Hey.
I am hoping that you, Chairman,
would run as our Gookmin Party nominee.
I would like to give you
a strategic nomination
to run as our Gookmin
Party's candidate.
What did you say?
Preview
Whom you have in mind, you can
tell me at least that much, right?
- Make a deal with the
company.- What are
you going to do for us
after the election?
Why is it that person?
In the beginning, most
people decline, but I've
never seen someone
decline until the end...
That removal... Secretary
General Baek ordered it, right?
Politics is not something that easy.
It is really right for me to do this?
In politics, what's more important
than experience is character.
Jin Sang Pil is garbage.
I have to do well.
Then do well! I said do well!