All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Episode 12.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki
I'm visiting my father for a while
because today is his birthday.
Is that so? Okay.
Come on up after you
show him a lot of love.
Yes. See you tomorrow.
Resume.
Kim Gyu Hwan.
Because there was something I wanted
to do in the national assembly.
What kind of work?
Become an assemblyman?
No, I want to become a trustworthy
staff member of an assemblyman.
So Secretary Kim, instead of wearing
it himself, tried to give this to me?
Yes, that's what I said.
I thought he was only good at martial arts,
but he has a good human character as well.
Why are you here already? I thought
it was your father's birthday.
I just went there to see
his face, that's why.
I see.
Why didn't you get
off work, Aide?
I am making a manual for bill drafting.
There is the Assembly's manual, but...
It seemed like it was
a bit hard for you.
You really didn't have
to go to that extent.
Just make a good bill. If it's crummy,
I will totally look down on you.
Yep, I understand.
Assemblyman.
I came back.
Did I do something wrong?
Secretary Kim went to Busan because
today is his father's birthday.
He went there to pay
his respects today.
Okay.
You did well to do that.
You did well.
I'll be out for a while.
Out for a while.
Assemblyman, I tell you,
he sure does have a way of
complimenting with sincerity, right?
President Seo Dae
Han, this morning,
designated Joo Cheol Soon, the head of
the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure
and Transport (MOLIT), as the new
prime ministerial candidate.
Prime Minister-designate Joo Cheol
Soon served on the Economic Planning.
Board and as a Ministry of
Construction and Transport official
prior to becoming the
MoLIT minister. His
background is entirely in
public administration.
He is reputed to be a figure with both
the necessary expertise and drive.
The Blue House has
stated that Prime.
Minister-designate Joo is the
most qualified candidate
who can overcome the pressing
issue of a depressed
economy and that is the
reason behind his selection.
The Assembly is planning to hold
a confirmation hearing as soon
as the prime ministerial candidate
appointment motion is made
and proceed with the
ratification process.
The arrogance of the
Administration knows no bounds.
Prime Minister-designate Joo, at the
time of his confirmation hearing as the.
Minister of the Ministry of Land,
Infrastructure and Transport (MOLIT),
caused all sorts of scandals due to
various alleged corrupt practices.
Can a person like this be the
Prime Minister-designate?
This is an appointment that
disregards the people's wish.
The nomination is an
admission by the Seo Dae Han.
Administration of the dearth of
competent people in its camp.
The people are no longer
hopeful or moved.
We urge President Seo Dae Han.
You cannot find a breakthrough
in these difficult
times simply by switching
the Prime Minister.
Great compromise arrived at
after an inter-party summit,
which has been consistently demanded
by the Korean Democratic Party,
is the sole way to revive the
country and its economy.
Please bear that in mind.
What?
Even if there is no competent person,
how can somebody like Joo Cheol Soon...
Secretary General, why didn't
you try to stop the VIP?
He is becoming more obstinate.
And those around him are
just agreeing with him.
Setting the Administration's
approval rate
aside, the party's approval
rate will plummet.
At this rate, can we win the
next round of elections?
Even so, what can we do?
The decision has
already been made and
we are the people who have
to implement his decision.
We have to ensure that the Prime
Minister's appointment is confirmed.
What do you guys think?
No, don't get up.
That Minister Joo Cheol Soon, is
he prime minister material or not?
His nickname is Bulldozer and he has a
reputation for being a good worker.
But his moral compass suffers
from many shortcomings.
From the opposition
parties' press conference
earlier, he seemed like a
very problematic figure.
When he was appointed to the
MoLIT minister position,
didn't he go through any
confirmation hearing?
Of course he did. Why
wouldn't he have?
But did they just let a person
like that become a minister?
The opposition parties objected like hell,
but it was all just swept away later.
Why?
Even if assemblymen object, ministers
are just appointed by the President.
Then, why do they hold
confirmation hearings?
There is that positive aspect of
the Assembly getting to examine
the character and expertise of
candidates for high office.
Once in a while, a problem
is revealed during the
hearing process and the
candidate voluntarily withdraws
or the President revokes
the appointment.
Aide Choi.
Yes, Assemblyman.
I don't like that person Joo Cheol Soon.
Let's do that thing, okay?
A Confirmation
Hearing Committee.
Hearing Committee?
Yes, let me just send him
away for good this time.
Why?
Assemblyman.-
Huh?- Here...
Yes, what is it?
Notice.
Special Committee for the Confirmation
Hearing of the Prime Minister-Designate.
What is this?
List of Committee Members
from Gookmin PartyChairman:
PARK CHOON SEOP; MEMBERS:
Hong Chan Mi, Kang Sang Ho...
Have they already come up with
the scenario among themselves?
Unless the party leadership
is out of their minds,
would they include the big boss
of the Indifferent-to-BH faction?
These people really... After
suffering at the hands
of our Indifferent-to-BH
faction so much, still...
Are they looking
down on us, huh?
Oath. I, a candidate for
high office, pledge, in the
confirmation hearing
undertaken by the country,
that I will follow my
conscience and, without any
addition or omission, will
tell the whole truth.
Special Committee for the
Confirmation Hearing
of the Prime Minister-Designate
Joo Cheol Soon.
Plagiarism in your
doctoral dissertation, a
massive profit from a
real estate transaction
that would put real
estate speculators to
shame, dubious exemption
from military service,
showering a certain company with
all the subcontracting jobs!
Do you think a person like this deserves
to be a country's prime minister?
Assemblyman Jo! Aren't you
tired of rebroadcasting?
Those stories all
came out during the
ministerial confirmation
hearing, didn't they?
If there is a problem, it should be rerun
not just once, but twice or three times!
Is there any allegation, voiced at
that time, that turned out to be true?
Let's stop mud-slinging and
just discuss whether he has
what it takes to carry out
the Prime Minister's duties.
Well said. Among the qualities
of a high government official,
is there anything more important
than the moral fiber?
Now, now, that is enough.
It seems as though the
designate did not apologize
enough in the last
confirmation hearing.
Since it's all water under
the bridge, speaking of
the devil, why don't you
apologize one more time?
Back then and even now,
I feel much remorse
that such allegations
were made against me.
But what Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu is
saying, are those just allegations?
There is no smoke
without any fire.
I think those are not
allegations but...
Wow, if those are true, really,
he is a total
scumbag, that person.
Tax delinquency of all sorts
including the income taxes.
Registration of a false address to send
your son to a good school district.
Entering into a so-called "down
contract" to falsify and
reduce the purchase price
for smaller tax payments!
I have a statement to make in connection
with the progress of the meeting.
I am in the middle of
asking a question!- Chairman!
Um, Assemblywoman Cheon, I
will give you more time later.
Let's listen to what
Assemblywoman Hong has to say.
This is the transcript from the
Prime Minister-designate's
past ministerial
confirmation hearing.
How can the questions
be exactly same without
even any changes in
the punctuation?
I will read back to you the
candidate's answer from that time.
Tax delinquency was by a
mistake and not deliberate.
Registration of a false address
and the down contract were
wrongs committed by me because
they were customary at the time.
I deeply regret them and feel
a keen sense of remorse.
Please come up with something
new if you can do so.
That's right.
Let's stop reruns and
turn to the main feature.
I don't even watch drama reruns
because they are boring.
My respected Assemblywoman
Cheon No Shim.
Please question him
concerning any alleged wrong
committed since he took
the office of minister.
He's really the incarnation
of corruption.
He's all sorts of crookedness
mixed in a bowl.
He's a bibimbap of corruption.
Aigo, that
person won't be able to
pass at the Assembly.
No, the appointment
motion will be passed.
What? How come?
As you've seen on TV, they
were all stories that came
out during the ministerial
confirmation hearing.
Unless something new is
found, the opposition party
will have a hard time
opposing the appointment.
Then, I have to go along with
appointing that kind of a person?
No.-Then, what? Abstention?
No.-Then, what is it?
Evasion.- Evasion?
What brings you here?
Because I was curious about
your party's position.
The Socialist Party
seems to be thinking of
vetoing the appointment
motion as one party.
Since they only have a few assemblymen,
they can easily unify their opinion.
But we have too many self-important
people, so it won't be easy.
Just leave it up to each
assemblyman's will.
Joo Cheol Soon. He already went through a
confirmation hearing to be a minister.
A ministerial appointment
doesn't have to be
confirmed, so we just
went through the motions.
But the Prime Minister
is a different matter.
If you oppose now, you
will only be acknowledging
the dereliction of your
duty at that time.
You'll just become
a laughing stock.
Now, I'm feeling hot
under the collar. I'd
better push objection
as our party position.
Your Korean Democratic Party has
as many as 139 assemblymen.
The appointment motion will
be put to a secret vote.
Is there any guarantee that
no aberrant vote will result
even if objection becomes the
official party position?
There isn't. But if a wayward
vote or two results in our loss,
the Korean Democratic Party will
also fall to the lows of the Garden.
Balsam School Party (GOOKMIN PARTY'S
NICKNAME AS CALLED BY JSP).
Don't overtax yourselves
to defeat him.
Just find an acceptable
way to avoid fighting.
So what is the bottom line
of all this Ahjussi's talk?
The person who leads a good honest
life is the best kind of person.
No matter how good a
student you are, if your
personality sucks, you
can't function in society.
And you can't be a good
person, understand?
Okay...
Hmm, I don't think the
response is that great.
Right. Does he think kids
nowadays like this kind of talk?
Why are you guys making so much noise
over there? Gyu Hwan, be quiet!
Aigoo, look at the time.
I entertained you so
much with my talk so time
just flew by, right?
So in the future, you know
those kids whose grades
are not that good or who
are not from rich homes...
you should not be
mean to those kids.
You know that thing much talked about
nowadays... snack shuttles (kids
(bullied into running chores for bullies
such as buying snacks for them).
I like pastry, but
things like that...
outcasting, things like this, you
should never engage in those things.
Then you cannot become a good person. But
we need to become good people, right?
When we grow up, becoming what
will make us good people?
An assemblyman
like you, Ahjussi?
Well, it's not like I am
boasting or anything, but
becoming an assemblyman
can also make you good.
My dad said all
politicians are thieves.
Aigo, no, it's okay. She can be right.
It's not totally wrong to say so.
But, do I look like a thief?
Aigo, it's already over.
At any rate, it was so nice to
meet you all today and next time,
I will return with fun stories.
Okay, it was nice meeting you. Be close
friends with Joo Hee and don't fight.
My dad said all
politicians are thieves.
Is something the matter? You
don't have a happy face.
No, nothing.
Aigoo, Assemblyman Jin!
Nice to meet you.
Oh, yes, how are you?
Please help me with the appointment motion.
I will count on you.
But what are the things said
during the confirmation hearing?
Assemblyman Jin.
Why? Can't I ask him?
Confirmation hearings
have long deteriorated
into mud-slinging fight arenas.
The opposition parties are just
trying to stick it to him.
But there are things that
turned out to be true.
That registration of a false address and
what was that, oh, the down contract.
Assemblyman Jin.
Yes?
Those were customary
at that time.
I was trying to lead a diligent
life and those things happened.
Please graciously overlook it.
Let's go, Minister.
Assemblyman Jin.
It will be better for you
to keep silent about
the ratification of
the Prime Minister.
Are you trying to intimidate me?
When I made a declaration
of indifference, I
clearly told you that I
wouldn't get scared.
Not just I, but the Blue House is
watching you too, Assemblyman Jin.
Oh, is that so? Please go
and tell that high and
mighty person that it is
an honor to my family.
Bastard.
This is just too much.
They've all plotted
together, together.
Everyone, give me
your attention.
Let us try this, huh?
Try... what?
A way to make the Prime
Minister-designate fail the confirmation.
We can just find his wrongdoings
since he became a minister.
Right? Let's try this.
The Indifferent-to-BH
faction's exclusive
confirmation hearing. What
do you think, Aide Choi?
But, Assemblyman, the opposition parties
have already rummaged through everything.
What?- That's why the
opposition parties
are resorting to reruns
of the old stuff.
So?- What?
So, then, should we just
watch such a human being
becoming the Prime Minister
and acting all stuck-up?
No, that's not what
I'm saying but...
We don't have the prosecutors'
right to investigate nor
are you a member of the
confirmation hearing committee.
There is no way the candidate will
just hand over information to us.
Is that what all of you think?
I guess you over there of course think so.
Secretary Song, do you also think so?
Hyung Seong Gi, Secretary
Oh, how about you guys?
What you say is right but...
Why get so heated about something
like that? No matter who
becomes the Prime Minister,
it's the same old, same old.
But, Da Jeong and Secretary
Kim, do you think so too?
Assemblyman.
As of now, we don't
have any way.
Ah, I see. Yes.
We don't have any way, huh?
I was the only one
who didn't know when
everybody else knew about
there being no way.
I am sorry. I was being the
only wet blanket around here.
What will happen to the
country at this rate?
A thief like Joo Cheol Soon
is the Prime Minister?
That's what I'm saying!- This blasted
country. I should just up and emigrate.
Why?
- I am here to take you home.
Drink one shot.
Aunt, give me a glass here.
Okay.
I... understand how you feel.
Such a person ought not
become the Prime Minister.
So that's why people
curse at politicians.
If a guy like me crawls out there and asks
for votes, who's going to vote for him?
Got divorced by a cheating
wife and his only son...
To keep him from being called a cripple's
son, if he gave up his parental rights...
When told this, who in the
world will vote for me?
It's about Hyung Dal Soo.
What he really wants...
do you know, Assemblyman?
Why do you want to know?
Please tell me.
Gyu Hwan... Yes.
Assemblyman.
I am sorry.
It's not something you
should be sorry about.
Still, I'm sorry.
The Assemblyman seems
to be very upset.
This is all because the
opposition parties are worthless.
Just lock the main
hall doors and
spread out their bedding there.
That should end the matter.
In the old days, countering
rush-throughs and what nots,
the opposition parties used to stage lie-in
protests and engage in physical fights.
But nowadays the law has been
changed and no such thing exists.
How did the law change
so it's like that?
That is a long story.
Aicham. - Oh!
That is right, that's it!
Constitution and Assembly-related
Law and Regulations.
Article 106-2 Holding
Unlimited Debate, Etc.
...when a conforming
request is submitted,
an unlimited debate can
be held, provided...
Why didn't I think
of this earlier?
But, anyway,
how can a person change
so much just because he
was named as a candidate
for Prime Minister?
From the time he was a minister,
the back bending angle
itself is different (MUCH
MORE STIFF, STUCK-UP).
He belongs to the old school.
Even now, he probably thinks
digging up the ground
and erecting buildings are
all there is to politics.
Looking at that, I realize
what poor judgment the.
VIP has when it comes to
selecting his cabinet.
If I were him, I would pick you
for the Prime Minister's post.
Setting aside the prime
ministerial position,
nowadays I feel like I've
become the BH's hatchetman.
Yes, what's up?- What
do you mean what's up...
I found a way to clean
up the pile of sh*t
you guys made and want
to tell you about it.
It's so predictable. You're
boycotting the main session, right?
No way in hell.
I've gotten one hundred
assemblymen's seals.
For filibustering.(Filibuster.
An extended
( debate which delays or
even may prevent voting )
What did you say?
Tell your assemblymen to bring their
sleeping bags to the session.
How was I?
Sunbae-nim... You are so cool.
What a cutie you are.
Um, what? Fili... what?
What-ster?
A filibuster means a
lawful obstruction
of progress in a
legislative assembly.
It was repealed for a long time and then
brought back to life a few years ago.
Under the name of unlimited
debate during the session.
If unlimited, can one person
go on for hours by himself?
If he can continue his statement
without leaving the lectern,
not a few hours but even
a few days will be okay.
Aigo, Aide Choi, how can
you talk such nonsense...
How can a person do that? At the
most, it will be 3-4 hours.
But, anyway, why are you suddenly
talking about that fili thing?
Aigo, what do they
mean by a filibuster?
Do they think we are in the US?
Since the vote won't
bring them a victory,
they are at least trying
to delay the vote.
Still, it's not such
a simple matter.
The special session ends
in 2 days, 48 hours.
But if those 100 bastards
blabber for 1 hour each,
that works out to 100 hours.
While listening to those
bastards, the special session
will come to an end without
much to show for it.
That is what they
are aiming for.
Not passing it in this
Assembly but dragging
it out until the next
regular session.
Pressure the Administration as much
as possible and if they get lucky,
the Prime Minister-designate
may voluntarily withdraw.
Yee-haw!
By now, Baek Do Hyeon's butt hole must
feel like it's sitting on a burning fuse.
I am sorry to ask to see you
at this late hour, Speaker.
It's fine. So,
what's the matter?
The filibuster, you
must not allow it.
If it's about that, I've already
notified each party's floor leader.
That I will allow it.-
That is why I am here.
Speaker, please reconsider.
It was lawfully requested
according to the conditions
and procedures set down by
the National Assembly Law.
I, the leader of the
legislature, must obey the law.
This is not over a general matter
like a bill or a resolution.
The motion to appoint the Prime Minister
is an urgent personnel replacement matter.
If you allow the filibuster, it will not
only lengthen the administrative vacuum
but also set bad precedent.
Before becoming the
Assembly Speaker,
I was once your Pro-BH sunbae. And
as such, I will say this to you.
Befitting your position as the VIP's
closest aide, please guide him properly.
What?
How can you let him
appoint a person like Joo.
Cheol Soon to the post
of Prime Minister?
I am a person who will
leave Yeouido in 1 year.
But how can I look forward to my
retirement when politics is in this state?
Speaker!- Be careful
on your way out.
For the Assembly agenda
8, I propose a revised
bill regarding the Employment
Insurance Fund Act.
Please vote.
Electronic voting machine
[YES]
I'll announce the
result of the voting.
Of the 278 attendees,
270 voted in favor.
The other 8 voted against the bill.
Therefore, I declare the bill passed.
Next, for Assembly agenda 9,
I propose a revised bill regarding
the Labor Standards Act.
I get to see the filibuster
that I had only heard about.
I wonder who came up
with such a great idea?
I know.
When will the agenda item on confirming
the Prime Minister be proposed?
At the end.
What should we do about
the BH and the leaders
of the Gookmin Party
being all roiled up?
Whether you are from the
BH or a party leader,
we have to come up some
kind of counterplan.
Are we just helplessly taken in?
Instead of sitting still here, why don't
we go complain to the Assembly Speaker?
I already met everybody that I
had to, but they won't budge.
This really...
Where is Secretary General Baek?
I told you to come with him.
I think he's organizing
his thoughts.
Please, let's wait.
Hello?
Elder, I am Baek Do Hyeon.
What happened?
I'm sorry to say it but I wish for
you to yield this time, Elder.
Why do you keep asking me to come out while
I am attending the Assembly meeting?
Before the agenda of confirming
the Prime Minister is proposed,
remove all your party members
from the Assembly meeting.
So that the ruling party members
can unanimously pass it.
Hey, Do Hyeon! I know you
are out of your mind right
now. But you have to say
something that makes sense.
I'll accommodate
everything you guys want.
Just do it that way.
Will Joo Cheol Soon withdraw?
No. An inter-party summit.
After the Prime Minister
takes the oath of office,
within 15 days, the
President will announce it.
You really mean it?-If you
want, I can put it in writing.
Let me report to my boss.
Now, now, everyone, let's leave.
What the...?
Look, look...!
Look here. What do you think all
of you are doing right now?
What is this?
Yes, Assemblyman.
All Korean Democratic Party
members are saying they are
taking an adjournment and
leaving and stuff right now!
What's happening?
Really?
Yes, everybody is
leaving right now.
I'll immediately find
out and call you.
(FROM JOO CHEUL SOON)To my
junior whom I love, sorry.
Aide Choi.
Yesterday, irrespective of the
Korean Democratic Party's position,
100 or so of the party
assemblymen voluntarily
submitted requests
for a filibuster.
That may be able to delay
appointment of the Prime.
Minister but it cannot ultimately
stop such appointment.
While minimizing the citizens'
inconvenience caused
by the administrative
vacuum in the government,
still in order to convey the
people's stern disapproval to
the Seo Dae Han Administration
and Prime Minister-designate,
all members of our party
have decided to boycott
the Prime Minister's
ratification vote.
Adjournment in progress.
So a lucky guy will stay
lucky, no matter what?
There must have been some sort of deal
between the ruling and opposition parties.
Deal? When businessmen enter into
deals, they usually make profits.
But this... Who will
benefit from this and how?
Oh.
Take a look at these so
you can feel better.
They are civil complaints
from Joo Hee's
schoolmates. There are lots
of interesting stories.
Because the school food tastes
bad, I don't want to eat it.
Assemblyman, who invented studying?
I don't want to study.
Assemblyman, please make a law so
that working late won't happen.
Humph...
In regards to that, everybody
did it that way in those days.
It turned out that way because I was
trying to lead a diligent life.
Please, be generously
understanding.
Aide Choi.-Yes?
When the kids grow up and
when they become our age,
if politics is still like
this, it won't do, right?
That's right. It can't be.
The right thing to do is to get
rid of Joo Cheol Soon, right?
No, we can't let him stay.
Ah, now, I will lay before you
today's last agenda item.
Agenda item number 145,
I lay before you the motion
to ratify the appointment
of Prime Minister-designate
Joo Cheol Soon.
In connection with this agenda,
originally there were requests
from 100 assemblymen including
Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu
for unlimited debate. However,
since everybody has left...
Still there is one remaining.
Because my aide took my
seal and stamped it on.
Assemblyman Jo Woong
Gyu's requesting letter.
Then, Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, please come
up and go ahead with your unlimited debate.
Yes.
I have so much here.
Aigoo, all the players
have left the ring and the
game is over. So what is
he trying to pull again?
At any rate, he's a
master of interference.
What does he plan to
do all by himself?
Um, Speaker, how many hours till
the end of the special session?
Since it's until
midnight tomorrow,
it will be 25 hours.
Oh, 25 hours. Okay.
Okay.22:59
25 hours.
Don't forget.
If you leave the lectern or stop
making statements for a while,
or if you keep making statements
unrelated to the agenda,
the filibuster will stop.
But don't you know me?
A flame-like
man among men,
scorch, scorch, huh!
JSP. What is with
the atmosphere?
Yes, I am Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil of the Gookmin Party.
I am also the leader of the
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
First, because I think
you'll be watching,
I will be talking to Prime
Minister Candidate Joo Cheol Soon.
Since it's not too
late, resign cleanly.
Apologize to the people.Stop it.
What are you doing?
Come down from the lectern!
What is with your attitude?
So, even if you are the only
one, you want to resist, huh?
Okay. Let's see.
I understand.
From now on,
Let me give it a
TRY: Filibuster.
Start.
12TH HOUR: 11:00 AM.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Yes, candidate Joo
Cheul Soon is...
even if the allegations made against
you are only allegations...
Mom, what is Dad doing?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
filibuster has passed twelve hours.
The special Assembly session
will close in 13 hours from now.
Whether Jin Sang Pil's
filibuster will succeed,
or whether ratification of
Candidate Joo Cheol Soon
will pass, all eyes are
turned to the outcome.
14 Hours Later; 01:00 PM.
I, Jin Sang Pil,
will ask of you.
Candidate Joo Cheol Soon,
please resign on your own.
Then, you will be applauded
by the people and
it's the only thing that
you can do for the people.
I understand so
stop and come down.
Enough already.- Mr. Speaker,
please stop him right now.
What do you think you
are doing right now?
Let me go home, please.
Be quiet! Your fellow assemblyman is
in the middle of making his statement!
Here. Here. Everybody,
please be quiet.
Assemblyman Jin,
please continue.
Okay, I'll continue.
The best thing Candidate
Joo Cheol Soon can do...
How many hours on earth has it been?
Driving me insane, seriously!
If you look in our Constitution...16
Hours Later; 03:00 PM.
Aide-nim...Proud of our
admirable history and tradition
our people...
Please send this quickly. So
Min, did you send the lyrics?
Hey! How can you be sleeping during this
crisis? Did you send the song lyrics?
After you do it.
Do this in order.
...movement... Aide, this...
...it seems like you
don't know about this...
I will read you the whole
of the Constitution.
ARTICLE 1-1: The Republic of Korea
shall be a democratic republic.
1-2: The sovereignty of
the Republic of Korea...
Nothing better than the whole
Constitution to drag things out.
...all state authority shall
emanate from the people. Article 3!
18 Hours Later; 05:00 PM.
In this beautiful land
of Korea, far and wide,
Grandfather Dangun
put down stakes
and founded a nation with humanitarian
ideals. Generation after generation...
Wow! He is a real
piece of work...
♬ King Dongmyeong who
built Goguryeo, Baekje.
King Onjo, Hyeokgeose who
came out of an egg, ♬
♬ Gallop the Manchurian steppes,
King Gwanggaeto the Great, ♬
♬ Silla General Isabu... ♬
♬ Master Baekgyeol at the
rice-flour mill... ♬
♬ King Uija with his
3000 court ladies ♬
♬ Gyebaek in the battlefield
of Hwangsanbeol
against whom Gwanchang fought ♬
♬ History flows forward! ♬
♬ Kim Yusin who has cut off his horse's
neck, Unification King Munmu ♬
♬ Great Monk Wonhyo and
water from a skull ♬
♬ Hyecho travelled to India ♬
♬ Jang Bogo, Prince
of the Seas ♬
♬ Dae Jo Yeong of Balhae,
Kang Gam Chan at the Battle
of Gwiju, Seo Hui's negotiations
with the Khitans... ♬.
Assemblyman JSP Fighting~- JSP so
hypocritical!- Is JSP being a party
pooper again?- ㅠㅜ I'm crying ㅠㅜ-
Let's stay up all night together~.
Riots!
KBC wants to air it live until it ends.
Turn it on.
Go on.
When there are these people...
It's on!
I'll do it again.
On this beautiful land...
That tone-deaf guy
is singing again.
Grandpa Dangun secured a land,
and founded the nation on a
philosophy to benefit many people.
There have been a lot of great
characters for generations.
King Dongmyeong who
established Goryeo, Baekjae's.
King Woonjoh, Hyeokgeoseh
who came from an egg...
22 hours elapsed, 9 pm.
Mr. Speaker!
It's been over a minute
since he stopped talking.
Make him stop now.
Stop the speech and
step down now.
Let's go now. I'm
seriously exhausted.
Assemblyman Jin. Are you
done with your remark?
No, no. I need some water.
He's about to collapse!
Get him to stop now.
Let us sleep!
Why bother bringing
water to him?
Just moisten your throat.
Have strength.
Thank you.
The best act of patriotism that.
Nominee Joo Cheol Soon can do
is not to become the
Prime Minister,
but to reflect on
himself and withdraw.
What's wrong with this?
What's going on?
Secretary Song. Didn't you
send the speech material?
I sent it all.
Battery, battery.
What the heck!
It's out of battery.
The print-outs of the speech.
Give it to him quickly!
It's over there.
Here.
You'll run to the Assembly
Hall at full speed, got it?
Gyu Hwan, the postcards.
Bring the postcards.
Postcards... In his office.
Hurry!
22 hours and 20 minutes elapsed.
9:20pm.
To be square and honorable,
even at the wind that
blows on the leaves...
Wait.
I'm having cramps.
Thank you.
22 hours and 40 minutes elapsed.
9:40pmThese are...
civil complaints that
my daughter's friends
sent me.
Here, they talk behind
their teachers,
complain about their school
lunches and all that stuff.
What does that have to do with
the motion of the appointment?
What are you talking about?
What jibberish are you
blabbering about now?
Assemblyman Jin. Please only speak of
things related to the topic on the agenda.
They're all related.
A few days ago,
I ran into someone
and he told me this.
The things that are illegal now
all used to be customary
in the old days.
It just so happened as he was
trying to live life diligently.
But you know what?
If you look here,
"Dear Assemblyman. My
dad has a bad liver,"
so his face is becoming
darker and darker.
"Please make a law so that he won't
have to work overtime every night."
"My mom, to afford
private tutoring,"
started working at a grocery store, and
ever since then, she gets easily annoyed.
"I wish the customers at the grocery
store were a little nicer."
"My mom..."
"My poor dad...
"My mom...
"My parents never
pass the interviews
and can't get a job."
What, these people...
Do these people live like this
because they didn't live diligently?
What's living diligently?
Being shrewd and sneaky, is that
living diligently? Is that it?
It's not! These people are the
ones that are living diligently.
These people who struggle to get
by each day, not breaking the law.
The moms and dads
of these students.
Mr. Joo Cheol Soon.
Don't you think so?
Don't you?
24 hours and 30 minutes elapsed.
11:30pm.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Assemblyman Jin. Are you
going to be alright?
Yes, of course. I'm
perfectly fine.
Next, what I'll say next is...
Mr. Speaker.
I'll ask one thing
to Assemblyman Jin.
Do you want to become a celebrity?
This is irresponsible instigation.
This is tyranny by the minority
camouflaged as a lawful act.
Now, the Prime Minister-designate
and this government
as well as every member of
the opposition party who
decided not to attend will
suffer a grievous wound.
And all the damage will
spread to our citizens.
Is this your so-called
politics for the people?
Yes.
To be honest,
I'm not sure if
this is for the people.
But I believe that this
is what the people
desperately want. Yes.
That's what I think.
I'll continue.
23:50 I, Jin Sang Pil,
demand again.
I urge Nominee Joo Cheol Soon
to withdraw voluntarily.
That's the only
way you can still
be applauded by the people
and give them hope.
The most patriotic act Nominee
Joo Cheol Soon can do
is not to become the
prime minister,
but to reflect on
himself and step down.
Lastly,
let me ask the stenographer.
All the things I
said until now...
You don't have to
record any of them.
But, for later,
for these kids, please make
sure to record these words.
Even if Nominee Joo Cheol Soon
gets appointed Prime
Minister, the citizens
will never acknowledge him.
That our citizens opposed him
from the beginning to the end.
That our citizens will
never acknowledge
someone who's committed such illegal
acts of corruption, not even a day,
no, not even a
minute nor a second,
as.
Our leader.
That they will continue
to do so in the future.
He really shouldn't become one.
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
It's past midnight, so I
declare everyone is dismissed.
Since the session is finished,
I declare the 347th Extra Session
of the National Assembly closed.
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Only Jin Sang Pil became a star.
Assemblyman.-
Assemblyman Jin!
Sang Pil! Oh no,
What about the medics?-Aide.
At least, you should have prepared
for that. How can you work this way?
Aide.-What?
Is he sleeping?-Yes.
Yes.
Aicham! Really!
Let's go.
Dang!
Wow. Now I feel I can live.
For a guy who can't stand to be
hungry, you really did well.
It's not that I was hungry,
I thought I was going to
die because I had to piss.
I thought I was going to piss
so I couldn't drink any water.
I should have... pissed
all over there.
But will you be okay without
going to the hospital?
Aihew! I have no problem
with doing this much work.
Hyung Seong Gi! Do you
remember that we used to work
all day and night for
double shifts all the time?
You are right! Right.
We used to bet who would work
more overtime within a month,
among you, me and Hyung Dal Soo.
Oh, no. You are not
a senseless idiot.
Why are you bringing up
Bae Dal Soo's name here?
Don't get bothered. It is okay.
Indeed, we used to do that.
Always, Hyung Dal Soo won.
He used to say he would not leave
his son uneducated due to no money.
So, he really worked very hard.
It looks like Bae
Dal Soo had a son.
Yes.
Well, what was his name?
Gi... Gi... Since it was a long
time ago, I can't remember.
By the way, why have I not seen
Gyu Hwan since a while ago?
I guess he went to bed
because he was tired.
Request to Draft a Bill.
Assemblyman!
Aren't you asleep?
No. I am doing something...- Oh.
You are really making something, huh?
Yes.
What kind of a bill?
Just... I want to make a law for the
ordinary fathers in this world.
What?
But, since I don't know what to do,
it is possible I may not make it.
Why? Try to make it well.
If you don't know well,
you can ask Aide Choi.
Yes. I understand.
Okay.
Have a sweet dream.
Go to bed quickly.
Tip off about Jin Sang
Pil's accepting a bribe
[YES] [NO]
SIO President Lee Taek Jo
[JPG] [JPG]...Delete.
Do you want to delete
the twenty items?[YES]
It has been a long time.
Yes. Sunbae-nim. Have you been doing well?
No, not really. Nothing goes well.
I lost face before Elder as well.
VIP did well to make Candidate
Joo Cheol Soon withdraw.
I have analyzed the reason why I
was defeated by Assemblyman Jin.
What is the reason?
The thought that you were my sole opponent.
Then, now, against Assemblyman Jin,
have you revised your plan?
For the person who doesn't
work with a brain, I
have no other choice but
to take a knife to him.
Sunbae-nim.
You'd better clean around Assemblyman Jin.
Then, that is a relief.
Among the politicians I have experienced,
he is the cleanest person.
Then...
Secretary General! I have
something urgent to report.
What is it?
I found a strange thing while checking
the people around Assemblyman Jin.
What is this?
Hey! Sim Dong Cheon! Do you want to die?
What is this again?
Didn't I tell you to check
before it went to print or not?!
I'm sorry. I did try to check but...
What?
What is this about?
What is it? Jin Sang, come on!
Immediately contact the printer and
tell them to print correction stickers.
So you want to put 20,000
stickers over the error?
Then, do we have to reprint
when we don't have any money?
Whatever is needed, we have to do it!
Yes.
Wait.
What is the matter?
Assemblyman. For your fan
club around the country,
your nickname has just been confirmed.
What is it?
"Gookmin Jin Sang".[PEOPLE'S TRUTH]
Gookmin jin sang.
People's Truth?
What?
It's a nickname that suits our Assemblyman.
PEOPLE'S TRUTH. GOOKMIN JIN SANG: Pil!
(PIL = "NEED" OR "NECESSITY".)
What did you say, you punk? I let you
loose these days and you... come here.
Hey.
His name is Kim Gyu Hwan but
his real name is Bae Gyu.
Hwan. He is the son of the
deceased Bae Dal Soo.
Bae Dal...
Resume.
This person is Assemblyman
Jin's secretary now?
Yes. Neither the staff in the office nor
Assemblyman Jin know his identity yet.
I will catch Jin Sang
Pil using this friend.
Please approve it.
I understand. I will be back.
Where did you say you are going?
Meeting room ♪2 at the second floor.
By the way, aren't you holding this?
Is it heavy?
This punk!
Resume.
Go for it!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki