All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
In a short time, a position at the
second level in the Secretary
General's office will be available.
Transfer to that position.
If you and I are estranged further, we will
never be able to meet each other again.
I don't want to lose you.
No matter what, you are my
closest and oldest comrade.
I am thankful for
your words, Sunbae.
But while going through
this, I've made a decision.
Decision?
Until the next election,
not as your aide,
but as Assemblyman Jin's
aide, I will remain.
I... want to make
him properly...
the next trustworthy assemblyman
from Gyeongjae City!
I don't know what potential
you discovered in him.
But it's all useless.
When you told me
to be his aide...
you cited Bismarck.
That politics is the
art of the possible.
I, too, am a person who
believes in those words.
Do you really mean to
take a stand against me?
You may lose all the
political assets you have.
I am prepared to risk them.
What is it that you want
that makes you go this far?
That a next-generation leader of the
Republic of Korea called Baek Do Hyeon
does not fall
further from grace!
- What?- While my body aids
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil,
my eyes will be watching
you, Sunbae-nim.
I will look forward to seeing your
dignified presence like the old days.
Do you have the confidence
to win against me?
If I didn't, I would not even
have started this conversation.
Baek Do Hyeon as a sunbae and
Baek Do Hyun as an enemy...
are two very different
people, you will find out.
I will be on my guard.
Secretary General, I have brought
the papers you need to execute.
Secretary General?
Chief Secretary Lim.
Yes, Secretary General.
Let's start... with
Gyeongjae City.
Yes.
Is Baek Seung Ro, the former
Undersecretary of the Department
of Home Affairs and famous for
his uprightness, your father?
Yes, when my father was the
appointed Mayor of Gyeongjae City,
I was born in his old age.
Wasn't your place
of birth Seoul?
Ah... A month after I was born, my father
was transferred to a post in Seoul―
During that process, my place of birth was
wrongly recorded in the family register.
But the exact place
where I was born was
Gyeongjae City, Hae
Woo-Myeon, Sang Won-Ri.
But the exact place where I was born was
Gyeongjae City, Hae Woo-Myeon, Sang Won-Ri.
Did you hear that,
Gyeongjae City citizens?
With Secretary General Baek...
Have you known that Secretary General
Baek was born in Gyeongjae City?
Please come out to the
secretaries' area.
What? She isn't even answering.
She thinks she's
all that, really!
Episode 8
Why do you ask a person
to come and go again...?
What is that?
Are we going somewhere?
What is this, now?
It's a weapon to fight
and beat the hit list.
What weapon?
Over 50% of Korean voters do not know the
names of their districts' assemblymen.
Even if they do, the number
of people supporting
that particular assemblyman
is half of that 50%.
That means there are very few
assemblymen with more than
50% recognition and 25% support
in their constituencies.
Why do you make me study arithmetic
at the beginning of the day?
Assemblyman, from now on, unless
some natural disaster strikes,
from Friday evening to early
Monday morning, and during
off-seasons, Monday through
Sunday, all week long,
you have to do things in Gyeongjae
City, your constituency.
Every Monday, as to whether
the soles of these
sneakers have been all
worn down or not...
you will need to
get my evaluation.
Are you kidding?
Rubber, these days, is so solid
and how can I, in a week...
Do you think you can win the people's
hearts without doing at least this much?
That is true.
Even to win one woman's heart, one
has to go through hell and back.
To win so many
people's hearts...
Of course we should do it.
Go into the district and
meet the local residents.
Engage them in conversations and
watch how they live day-to-day.
That is the first and foremost duty
an assemblyman should undertake.
Yes, well, I can do it
riding this, right?
Hello.
Assemblyman Jin Sang PilMobile
Civil Services Center
- Hello. Hello.- Fighting.
- Hello.  - Yes, yes. Hello!
Jin Sang Pil! Hello!
Hi!
Jin Sang Pil!
Watermelon! Come here, everyone!
Aigoo,
have this.
Eat.
If you can broaden the
road a bit and...
Aigoo, so thankful that
he even visited...
- We have to wait an hour.-
It's very inconvenient.
It is very
inconvenient, that is!
So you do seem to need 2 buses.
Reduce Bus Waiting
Time to 30 Minutes
I will do it.
- Do not worry.
- Excuse me Assemblyman, instead
of doing that, why don't
you sing us a song?
- A song... - Sing! Sing!
Sing! Sing! Sing!
♬ In this throbbing heart
of mine, full of dreams...♬
♬ Writing and writing love
and if you make a mistake ♬
♬ It has to be cleanly
erased with an eraser. ♬
Ahjumma, sing with him.
Sing together.
♬ If you use too-dark ink
from the beginning ♬
♬ to write love ♬
♬ It would be so so
hard to erase it. ♬
♬ Write your love in pencil. ♬
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil is
concentrating on the senior citizens,
small business owners, and
housewives of Gyeongjae City.
Changes in Support for
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
I guess he is trying
to woo the so-called
three major groups of
an electoral district.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's recognition
that stayed at a low 10% range,
has surpassed the 20% mark.
Favorable feelings are
also rising rapidly.
Secretary General!
I have something to talk
about, can you please leave?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Secretary General, your next electoral
district...Make that Gyeongjae City.
Because it's my hometown?
No, I am just back from
the fortune teller's shop
that Supreme Councilman
Park introduced me to.
It was a male shaman possessed by a
little lad ghost and he is known as
"tweezers" (EXTREMELY ACCURATE),
specializing in the political arena.
When I told him the four pillars
of your destiny (year, month,
day and hour of one's birth
creating that person's destiny),
southeasterly, he said in the southeasterly
direction lies your deliverer.
Assemblywomen Hong, you even knew
the date and hour of my birth?
What is this?
It's an election charm.
That is...
He said he'd give me a discount
if I bought a set (A PAIR).
- A set?- He said you must
keep it in your underpants.
In the underpants...?
Assemblyman Ahjussi Jin Sang Pil,
Ahjussi Secretary, thank you.
Secretary Kim.
Look at this.
Assemblyman Ahjussi Jin Sang Pil,
Ahjussi Secretary, thank you.
I think our assemblyman
is really cool.
How can you personally
think of making a bridge?
Right?
Was that really our
assemblyman's sincerity?
What?
Yes, Assemblyman.
One moment please.
How come you hide the complaints
received from the voters?
I told you to give it to me,
as soon as you receive it.
I forgot it.
Because I have a small head (GOOD BODY
PROPORTIONS), its capacity is a bit low.
Where did you say you left it?
I probably left it
somewhere on the desk.
I will hang up now. I need
to spray insecticide on
the pear trees before they
get damaged by insects.
Lee Taek Jo,
ChairmanSIO Corporation
What's wrong? Can't find it?
Assemblyman, did you receive
a watch from Lee Taek Jo?
A watch?
Oh, right! I received a
commemorative item or something
at the forum where Secretary
General Baek gave a speech.
Why?
- A commemorative item?  - Yes.
Then I gave it to Secretary Kim.
Secretary Kim Gyu Hwan?
Yes, but why are you
asking about that?
Are you sulky because I
didn't give it to you?
Hello?
What is this clueless talking?
Kim Gyu Hwan, are you
still not done yet?
Yes. I am almost done.
Hurry up, will you?
When I was an intern, I would've already
been kicked in the shin several times.
Yes.
What?
Kim Gyu Hwan, see me for a bit.
Did I make some sort
of mistake, again?
Why this is in the
assemblyman's drawer,
explain it.
Assemblyman gave it to me.
Opening this, I found
it seemed an expensive
brand. So I thought
I couldn't wear it.
Then, is it okay for
Assemblyman to wear it?
Pardon?
If, by a one-in-ten-thousand chance, this
gets leaked outside, what will happen?
Whether all the elements of the
crime of bribery are there or not,
Assemblyman will be the target
of distrust and criticism.
Furthermore, in some cases, he might end up
lined up against the police mug shot wall.
Since you studied to be a
policeman, you at least know that.
I didn't think that far ahead.
Okay.
Let's say it's okay to not tell me.
But what's
the reason for not
telling Assemblyman?
I am sorry, I forgot.
Are you using that
as an excuse now?
Nothing like this
will happen again.
Clock out from work right now.
Until you're contacted,
you're off work.
It's okay for you to
seek another job.
Aide!
Secretary Kim will take a few days off with
a personal matter. Please understand that.
Madame Aide!
Then what was I supposed to do?
- Kim Gyu Hwan.  - I...
I did not forget but I did
not report it on purpose.
Why?
When Assemblyman sees that, he
may want me to avert my eyes.
See that, what does that mean?
How come?!
Because it's a ₩
5,000,000 watch.
If Assemblyman also knows that
it is not a commemorative watch,
he will surely want to wear it.
You...
What do you know about our assemblyman
that you are spewing such words?
Madame Aide!
How well do you know our
assemblyman to say that?
Secretary Kim, what
is wrong with you?
Leave!
Leave right now!
Secretary Kim, just
say you're sorry.
Secretary Kim.
Wow, what rudeness!
Aigoo. What does it look like
for everyone to act like this?
One moment.
Give it to me.
I accepted this?
Yes. When someone offers you
something, don't be like a kid
and take everything!
There is no one who hands out favors
to assemblymen without a reason.
Wow! This watch is splendid!
So, Secretary Kim didn't wear this
and tried to give this to me, right?
That is what I said.
I thought this punk is good
only at the martial arts.
He also has a good
human character.
Give it to me. I will
return it to President Lee.
It's okay. The punk who
received it must return it.
I want to tip you off about
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
acceptance of an illegal bribe.
Who is it?
Are you surprised?
Assemblyman?
Wow! Cleaner than I expected!
What were you doing?
What? Did you see
something flashy?
How did you know to come here?
You... are a little tight...
with money...
by paying rent on
this room and living.
What brings you here?
This.
Since we received this together, we
have to take care of this together.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Vikii
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd
Here.
By the way, is it really
okay to do things this way?
What will happen if we return it? It
will end up in someone's pocket, anyhow.
Hey, you! According
to the Aides,
you barely considered me as
an assemblyman all this time?
Is it not okay if I do that?
Is it not okay?
Since you got fired, your
attitude has completely changed.
I will be leaving first.
Where are you going while
an elder is speaking?
- Let me go, please!
- Look at these eagle eyes!
If I don't let go, you are
about to hit me again.
I told you to let me go.
They say you should make
hay while the sun shines.
How about finishing up the
fight from the last time?
Since I came this far and
gave up everything, why not?
Aicham! There is a
cute side of him.
Come to work from tomorrow.
What?
You are lucky that Aide Choi
is generously minded, but
if you get into trouble with Aide Choi
again, I will fight with you head to head.
Why? You don't want to?
Your pride hurts?
Hey, where are you going?
Secretary Kim.
Hey, you punk!
Your swings are alive.
So full of energy!
Oh, wow...
By the way, have you heard?
Baek Do Hyeon appeared
on TV and said
that his hometown was not
Seoul, but Gyeongjae City.
Gyeongjae City?
Yes! Don't you think Secretary General Baek
has a thought of running in Gyeongjae City?
By the way, is it okay to
procrastinate like this without
doing the maintenance work
in your constituency?
A company where the CEO is
busy is not much of a company.
The CEO only needs to
maintain the executives well.
Aigo, let me ask you. Who
in the world are the
executives of the Park Choon
Seob Incorporated Company?
- Those people. - What?
Local administrative agency
directors, heads of social
and commercial gatherings,
alumni association heads...
I am talking about the
influential people in the area.
That is that, but the votes from deep
down the hierarchy are also important.
Doing things this way, you will
end up paying dearly for it.
Votes from the bottom layer are
important, but they are so fickle.
After 4 years of devotion, one wind
and they drop like the autumn leaves.
But the big shots' opinions
have a single theme.
What do you mean one theme?
Development of the area where they
live, farting their influence.
So, by when will you give it to me?
Should I keep waiting, huh?
Why are you on the phone so long? What
happened to what I asked you about?
Oh, and Secretary Oh, I think something
is left out of this. Check this properly.
Ah, yes, yes, that day, he
has a meeting scheduled...
Changes in Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
Approval Rates in Gyeongjae City (%)
Everyone, listen up.
Compared to the last month,
about our assemblyman,
Gyeongjae citizens' recognition and support
rates have, each by 10% and 12%...
increased!
Wow, jackpot, jackpot!
Great!
- Aide,- Yes?
A fax came in.
NoticeWe request an emergency
meeting as follows.
AGENDA: Joint Civil and
Administrative Meeting to Attract
a New Southeast Region Harbor
Project to Gyeongjae City
Aigoo, why?
I think you have to hurry and
go down to Gyeongjae City.
Is anything up?
There is a campaign promise
that the former Assemblyman
Yang Sung Gil dumped out there
about a development project.
It's about attracting a new
harbor in Gyeongjae City
and developing a hub harbor
in the southeast region.
The Support Committee has requested
an emergency meeting with the Mayor.
Support Committee?
It's a group of all the influential
people in the community.
Each of those people can move from several
dozen to several hundred voters' opinions.
You must attend it, Assemblyman.
Oh, of course I should.
Let's go, let's go quickly.
Mayor, at this rate, it
will take a millennium
before the new harbor
is built here.
How many years on earth have
you been dragging this out?
We are trying in 100
different ways, but
it's not easy because the central
government is pretty passive about this
and there are too many green-belt
areas in our jurisdiction.
That belt thing... shouldn't
you be unbuckling it for us?
Yes, I should unbuckle it for you...
I will try very hard.
Would trying be enough? Give us
some result within this year.
Next year is the
election, election!
Yes, I... will do my best
and try very hard, anyhow.
Ah, yes.
In the past, with Yang Sung Gil, I was
on very good terms, like friends.
Privately, I can use informal
speech with you, right?
Ahew, of course, you are...
older than me.
Don't hesitate and just tell me if you
need money to manage the constituency.
No, I am a hands-on type. Thank
you for offering, though.
I am a person who controls
at least 300 votes, with
my company employees and
get-together members.
Oh, yes... 300 votes?
I will give my son's
resume to your aide.
Please look into a special position
at a conglomerate company.
Resume
It is okay to rip it?
Yes, rip it to shreds.
But didn't you say
this was a 300-voter?
You can assume it's one-tenth
of the number he called out.
I will buy you another pair of sneakers, so
just meet another 30 workers at a company.
But this time, please
buy me a known brand.
Wherever you go, you'll come
across people like that.
And they are the main culprits
corrupting healthy political minds.
By the way,
weren't the Support Committee
people totally pigheaded?
It's not even building ships
at a shipyard, but they want
the right to build a whole
new harbor within this year.
Does that make any sense?
It's not their fault. It's
the fault of the politicians
who have, without sufficient review,
just because it would help with
their election, whetted the residents'
appetite for more development.
But why were they staying quiet all this
time and bringing it up like this only now?
Next year's the election, you know?
They judged that this
would be the time when their
words would hold most sway.
Then, what do I have to do now?
It's not an easy matter. You have
to give it a serious evaluation.
Wow, that is really...
the phrase I abhor the most.
Serious evaluation. Aide Choi,
you are no different...
Assemblyman!
But, Aide Choi,
Secretary Kim... won't he
ever come back to work?
He's not coming?
Are you really just going to play
around because it's vacation time?
- Should I go to the
National Assembly?- What?
Yes, this is Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil's Office.
By any chance, is Secretary
Kim Gyu Hwan available?
What?
He no longer works here.
If you're going to go to the Assembly
Hall, give this to Aunt Ae Ri.
I borrowed it from her the last time.
If you tell her that, she will know.
I'm going to sleep.
Why is that kid like that?
Consequently, I do
not bear any...
legal or moral responsibility
for his death.
My aide says that an assemblyman
is the people's servant.
Can you hear what
they're saying?
Shhh!
You still want to work?
Yes.
Why were you playing
hard to get before?
Huh?
After not working for a few days,
does your future look bleak?
I needed some time to
organize my thoughts again.
What do you think, Aide Choi?
I will leave it up
to you, Assemblyman.
How much do you pay for
your room every month?
$400.
400?
Then, after paying 400 from your internship
allowance, you won't have much left.
Go home and pack your stuff.
- What?- I said pack
your stuff, punk.
♬ Making passes, passes, passes,
you must fall asleep. ♬
♬ Now, I'm tired, bumblebee. Bumblebee!
I'm tired of waiting, ♬
♬ bumblebee. Bumblebee! ♬- What?
- Nothing.
♬ Alone, this night is so, so cold.
♬♬ Bumblebee! ♬
♬ You're incorrigible, bumblebee.
♬ Sing with me. ♬ Bumblebee! ♬
♬ You're a bumblebee that makes me cry.
♬♬ Bumblebee... ♬
♬ Alone, this night
is so, so long. ♬
Your belongings are rather few.
Aide.
Come out.
Instead of Secretary Byeon who likes
to sleep in in the morning, you
wake up the assemblyman and take
care of his breakfast and commute.
With that condition, I
agreed to let you stay here.
Okay. And Aide...
I really was sorry.
Thank the Assemblyman.
Since he was fired from
his past job, he said
how can he fire his
staff and threw a fit.
I really was going to fire you.
Okay, I understand.
Because I can see, I know you
are diligent most of time.
And because of that, when I see
you, I get a bit emotional.
-What?-In the
political field,
for a kid like you,
it's easy to get hurt.
It's because everybody looks for
results and not one's diligence.
Nobody pays any attention to
someone who tried and failed.
Isn't the world
basically like that?
Because I have experienced
it lots of times,
I no longer get hurt by it.
When you were arguing
with me a while ago,
you asked me just what I knew
about the assemblyman, right?
Yes.
What you said was right. How
much can I know about him?
However, I had this thought.
That if I tried something with
that assemblyman and failed,
I wasn't going to get hurt.
I wish for you to find
that side of him quickly.
That's why I returned.
The assemblyman that I'm
thinking about as compared
to the assemblyman that
you are thinking about:
which assemblyman is
the correct one...
I had thoughts about wanting
to confirm which one.
The reason is rather strange but
it's a good phenomenon for a staff member
to start getting interested in his leader.
- Yes.- I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
The campaign to attract a new harbor
to Gyeongjae City is getting heated.
They are supposed to launch a full-scale
campaign including large rallies very soon.
Then, you're saying there has
been no progress all this time.
No, you can't say no progress.
We are talking with the government
based on these documents.
And there are a few big problems.
One is...
the law has to be changed...
In order to do that, the
government says they
have to hold meetings
amongst themselves.
They are trying to drag this
out and just pass over this.
How can you just sit
there and watch it?
Assemblyman Jin, do you even have the will
to attract a new harbor infrastructure?
Oh, of course. We're trying
to enrich our village, right?
Isn't this what we
are trying to do?
Never mind the will,
we have to get this
done, no matter what.
That's what I think...
But the former Assemblyman
Yang Sung Gil...actually
did plan to get too big of a
budget, I think that is true.
That problem is...
Those people are
on edge right now.
How many times have I told you that you
cannot give them a passive impression?
It's not because I'm passive but
I feel uneasy, as if I'm lying.
Let's just give
it to them as is.
What do you mean as is?
Considering our Gyeongjae
City's financials, a
big harbor like that
does not make any sense.
We can tell them that, if we are
lucky, we can get them a small dock.
That was all former Assemblyman Yang Sung
Gil's hot air to the Gyeongjae citizens.
Can't you see that you will end
up a traitor, talking like that?
Wow, I, really...
We are not yet at the stage where the
next best thing should be mentioned.
Yes, Sunbae-nim!
I heard that you
clad Jin Sang Pil in
sneakers and are making
him sweep the floor.
Is that wrong?
I cranked up my
brain assiduously.
Do Hyeon's next electoral district!
It's Gyeongjae City.
- Surprised, right?-
Omo, really...
Really! So quickly
tender your resignation
and run into Do Hyeon's bosom.
Don't forget to leave some
water marks under your eyes.
Since things played
out this way, anyway,
I'm thinking of going all-in
for Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
This is why your
business tanked.
Is Jin Sang Pil even a
match for Do Hyeon?
Don't you think he has a
possibility with my help?
Do Hyeon also has
one on his side.
- His father?- Bingo!
The first appointed mayor
of Gyeongjae City.
Hello.
This is Do Hyeon.
Yes.
I am sorry, but
this time, Father,
I need your help. Yes.
Gyeongjae City Support Committee
for attraction of a new
southeast regional harbor
stated that they have appointed
Baek Seung Ro, the former Undersecretary
of the Department of Home Affairs,
as a standing advisor on the Gyeongjae
City affairs advisory committee.
Baek Seung Ro, the former
Undersecretary, is the father
of Secretary General Baek Do
Hyeon of the Gookmin Party.
When Gyeongjae was
raised from a gun status
(COUNTY, POPULATION OF
LESS THAN 150K) to a city,
he served the city as the
first appointed mayor
and he is known to possess solid
networks as well as goodwill
in the central political sphere
and in the Gyeongjae community.
Do we have to find out about this kind
of important matter through news?
Okay, please do not let
this happen ever again.
Those people, what do they take an
incumbent local assemblyman for?
What more would they
need when they have
Secretary General Baek's
father on their back?
Be quiet!
Aide Choi, I don't have a
good feeling about this.
As soon as it is known
that Secretary General
Baek's birth place
is Gyeongjae City,
his father puts down stakes.
Secretary General Baek... isn't he, by any
chance, planning to run in Gyeongjae City?
This afternoon, for Standing
Advisor Baek Seung Ro
they are holding a ceremony to
deliver the appointment letter.
What do you think, Aide Choi?
- What?- Secretary General
Baek is, right now...
greedily eyeing
Gyeongjae City, right?
From Secretary General
Baek's point of view...
there is no place that
he would not be eyeing.
Don't get tense before the
fact and Assemblyman, you
can continue as you
have done so far.
Ceremony to Present Appointment Letter
to Standing Advisor Baek Seung Ro
Together with the Gyeongjae
citizens' yearning
to secure a new harbor
infrastructure,
we present this letter to you to
appoint you our Standing Advisor.
Congratulatory
MessageAnd, also...
Wishing for the good health of our
Standing Advisor Baek Seung Ro,
who will work hard to attract the
new harbor to Gyeongjae City,
which is everyone's
long cherished wish,
I will end my greeting message.
It's Secretary General
Baek Do Hyeon!
Right now, the Standing
Advisor's son,
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon
has graced us with his visit!
Please give him a big
round of applause!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Long time no see.
What brings you here?
My father has taken
on an important
function.Of course I,
his son, should come.
Oh, yes... welcome...
Nice to meet you, everyone. I am Gookmin
Party's Secretary General, Baek Do Hyeon.
Not forgetting my father,
for entrusting this glorious duty.
Citizens of Gyeonjae,
I would really
like to thank you.
Since I am a Secretary General
who does the will of the Party,
I don't think I can
be of great help.
However, I believe the respected
Assemblyman Jin will be of great help.
In any event, I
sincerely hope that
the place of my birth will become a
leader in the economic development
of the southeast region.
Thank you.
Baek Do Hyeon!
Gyeongjae City!
Please, go up now.
I'm sorry but I have some matters
to take care of in Seoul.
After seeing you,
I feel energized!
From now on, we'll really
be supportive of you.
- Oh, thank you.
- Be safe on your way.
Mayor, bye.
Then, I apologize. Bye.
What are you doing now?
What's your problem?
The thing that you are
doing, Secretary General,
you seem like a guy who is looking
for land to build your house.
Are you afraid that I might
run for office here?
No, it's not that I am afraid.
You just look pathetic.
I feel pity for you.
For a person who
is heavy-weight...
When you were sitting during the meeting,
what do you think you looked like?
Looked like what?
As for me, I will go
anywhere that needs me.
Unless the people of Gyeongjae call,
I won't have a reason to come here.
Everything will depend on
what you do, Assemblyman.
Wow! With words, I don't
think I can beat him.
You win.
There is talk of you running in Gyeongjae.
What are your thoughts?
Since I haven't declared
to run in a district,
I think there will
be a lot of rumors.
Then, are you saying that you have no
intention of running in this district?
That subject will depend on the people
of Gyeongjae rather than what I think.
-Excuse me, we have to
finish the interview right
here.-Can you give us more
details about what you said?
If things work out well for you, you
have to treat me to something big.
I gave you the decisive hint.
Southeasterly direction.
I understand, I will treat you.
But a formal declaration of running
there... that would be too much, right?
Since there is an incumbent
Assemblyman from the
same party in the district,
I shouldn't do that.
I can look foolish.
Even though the opponent is
only Assemblyman Jin, still
you cannot ignore the advantages
he has as an incumbent.
It's better to uproot him
while the wind is blowing.
In politics, backlash is
scarier than a hurricane.
Since I met a good wind,
there is no reason to row.
Seeing how you are relaxed, I guess
you still have a hidden card.
Is Baek Do Hyeon eyeing the
seat for Gyeongjae?Secretary
General Baek is a slime ball.
Total slime ball.
-What?  - Jeez, you
snuck up on me!
Is Baek Do Hyeon eyeing the
seat for Gyeongjae City?
Baek Do Hyeon appears at Gyeongjae
City to attend the ceremony
to appoint his father as Standing Advisor
for the Support Committee for a new harbor.
Everybody to the
conference room.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
This is the list of the
members belonging to
the associations within
the Support Committee.
We are to inform them directly
about the Assemblyman's
activities to secure
the harbor project.
How are we to inform them?
- Three text messages, one email, and
one phone call a day.- Every day?
A list of responders with
attitude grades of C
or below should be drawn
up and given to me.
I will take on those people.
Do I have to do this too?
Whether Secretary General Baek
runs in Gyeongjae City or not...
depends on how the
Support Committee moves.
This is an emergency, so everyone, let's
just put in extra work for a few days.
You should be... a bit considerate toward
workers in their last working years.
Don't you think Aide
Choi is a bit weird?
What's weird about her?
Aide Choi's original master
is Secretary General Baek.
But isn't it weird that she is too
much on our assemblyman's side?
There's nothing wrong with that.
What?
Aide Choi is just discharging
her duties faithfully.
What the !*# Hey, Kim Gyu Hwan!
Even if you have to pull
all-nighters, you have to produce
one piece of promotional
material a day, understand?
Okay.
Oh-oh.
What?
The game is over.
What are you saying?
More than 30 Gyeongjae
City Organizations
"Come Baek Home" Baek Do Hyeon Fan
Club Initial Press Conference
We were deeply impressed by
Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon's decision
to give up his constituency
for the sake of the unity
and stability of his party,
with an attitude of
someone who sacrifices
his personal gains for
the party's benefit.
Moreover, we are so proud that
he is Gyeongjae City's
son who was born here.
We, the Come Baek Home
members, sincerely wish that
Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon will
come back to Gyeongjae City.
For Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon
to achieve a bigger dream
in Gyeongjae City,
we will do our best.
That is all.
Those punks are saying that Baek
Do Hyeon should run here, right?
Unless the people of Gyeongjae call,
I won't have a reason to come here.
I guess I'll have to run head
to head against Baek Do Hyeon.
The Support Committee
to attract a new harbor
has changed into a support committee
to attract Baek Do Hyeon.
Practically without lifting a
finger, he has turned all the
influential people of Gyeongjae
City into his loyal bodyguards.
I think I hear Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's wailing even from here.
Looking at this
guy, Baek Do Hyeon,
I think he was born with
excellent political
luck (FATED TO REACH
HIGH POLITICAL POSTS).
But somehow, when he
abandoned his own district,
a new district appeared that welcomed
him with both arms wide open
at Gyeongjae, the place he
says that he was born in.
Assemblyman Kang...
do you think that's
a coincidence?
The person who has declared to run
in Baek Do Hyeon's constituency,
is Oh Sae Chang.
Is it the Oh Sae Chang who is known
as the "burglarizer of empty houses?"
What if it wasn't burglarizing an
empty house? What if the owner...
ran away in advance knowing that a robber
was going to show up at his house?
Then, Baek Do Hyeon
already knew in advance that Oh Sae Chang
was going to run in his district?!
What is the reason for being so
fixated with Gyeonjae district?
At most his term will be 1 year and
he's only a half-term assemblyman.
Because it's not like you to
force a guy like Jin Sang Pil.
That's why I am asking you.
Baek Do Hyeon...
from that moment,
had his mind set...
on moving far away.
Moving?
Yes, Assemblyman Park.
By you, Secretary General
Baek, all this time...
I was completely fooled.
What are you talking about?
From the time that you gave
the nomination to Assemblyman
Jin, you were going to use him
for a year and discard him.
I didn't even know and
I asked you to omit Assemblyman Jin
from the next round of nominations.
-Assemblyman Park.-I do
understand to some degree.
Who in the Gookmin
Party would want
to go up against Oh Sae Chang
in the Seoul metropolitan area?
I will
give you some advice.
Go ahead.
I was in nine elections and
lost four times.
Do you know why I was able to
last a long time as a politician?
I don't know.
It's because I am not
afraid of losing.
But it seems like you
really dislike losing.
As for me, I have never
lost in my life.
If that's the case, you
can't last as a politician.
The real winner is
made by defeats.
Are you done with
giving your advice?
Your choice this time,
Secretary General Baek,
will come back to
bite you someday.
Assemblyman, where
are you coming from?
I think I can get
there in an hour.
Okay, while you are on your way,
I will wait with a few
options drawn up.
Sang Pil, if we go against
Secretary General Baek,
what is going to
happen to Aide Choi?
Does she have to quit?
Stop saying those
useless things.
- Hello?- Assemblyman Jin,
it's me, the Anti-BH Avatar.
What is the matter, Assemblyman?
-What is the
matter?-Assemblyman Jin.
It's not like we're kids; we are
politicians who maintain politics.
We should live, making
amends with each other.
Oh, yes. I apologize
for that time.
What do you mean apologize?
Please sit.
How are you doing? It's
really taxing, isn't it?
No, it's just...a bit.
In regards to Secretary
General Baek,
he shouldn't act this way when you
consider political etiquette.
How can he try to take
away the district from
a person that he gave
the nomination to?
He must have done it because he
was having a hard time, I guess.
Assemblyman Jin,
you were fooled.
What?
You know Oh Sae Chang,
of the Korean Democratic
Party's non-mainstream
faction fame?
Because that person will run in Secretary
General Baek's current constituency,
having found out about this
beforehand, Secretary General Baek
gave you the nomination
for Gyeongjae City.
So because of Oh Sae Chang...
he nominated me?
Oh Sae Chang is considered a
presidential-level candidate.
If the two run against
each other next year,
Secretary General Baek
will get beaten, no doubt.
So, after making a pushover
hold the place for him
in Gyeongjae City where
he supposedly was born,
he intended to take
it back afterwards.
What are you talking about?
Assemblyman Jin, look at
the situation around you.
Without an elaborate script,
things cannot play out
like clockwork like this.
Assemblyman, you have
been completely conned.
When you have thought it
over, come to see me.
Our Anti-BH faction
will help you.
I am hoping that, Chairman,
you will go to the
National Assembly and engage
in legislative activities
not only for the unemployed
but also for all
the underprivileged
members of our society.
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil!
Baek Do Hyeon! Baek Do Hyeon!
He said he would see someone briefly
and come back to the office, for sure.
Yes.
Aish, seriously...
Yes Sunbae-nim.
I have something to tell you.
Okay.
I will go outside for a moment.
Don't you think Aide Choi
is a bit suspicious?
What?
Very suspicious...
Who's this?
Since we met, do
you want to talk?
I'm a bit busy.
I don't have the presence
of mind to banter with you.
Hold on.
What do you want to say?
Let me just ask why on
earth you are so busy.
- What?- Is it for Assemblyman Jin
or for Secretary General Baek?
I'm curious as to your
intent behind this question?
As far as I know, Choi In
Kyung, you are our family.
But if you're acting for
the sake of Assemblyman
Jin, then that would
be treacherous.
And if it's for the sake
of Secretary General
Baek, then I guess that
would make me a mole?
Right. Between a traitor and
a mole, which one are you?
-Secretary Lee.-Yes?
-Cover your ears.-Y...yes.
- What are you doing?-
Hey, Hong Chan Mi!
What? Hey?
I am neither a
traitor nor a mole.
I'm just Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
aide, Choi In Kyung, got that?!
Right, how dare a mere aide
talk down to an assemblywoman!
If you act cocky one more
time, when they were
ranking the proportional
representative candidates
you sought me out and begged
me, crying and sniffling,
to schedule a meeting with
Secretary General Baek.
I'm going to distribute
flyers about that episode!
I kept holding it in and
holding it in, and do you
think I'm an abuse receptacle, you witch?
When did I?!
I kept holding it in and
you keep acting out.
Crazy... Hey!
Why did you put your hands down?
I made a formal request to her. Request!
How do you feel, getting defeated
before the proper game even started?
We just lost a point.
And still a lot of the gaming time remains.
Assemblyman.
Where have you been holed
up to return only now?
-Where is Aide Choi?-Aide Choi?
She is not answering her phone.
Tell her to come quickly, because
I have something to ask her.
Assemblyman, wait a minute.
Don't trust Aide Choi too much.
-What did you say?-She's diligent and
I know she's looking out for you.
However, something is strange.
Aide Choi is Secretary
General Baek's person.
She has no reason to do
something to offend him.
Hyung, Aide Choi is not
answering her phone?
I have something to ask her.
Hyung, go outside and look for her then.
Aide Choi went to meet with
Secretary General Baek.
Why are you telling me that now?!
What do you want to say?
I want to finish that race
before the race starts.
What is this?
Assemblyman Jin's announcement not to run.
It may be possible for
you to convince him,
because Assemblyman Jin
trusts you completely.
Sunbae-nim.
I will give him a position at a state-owned
company once he is done with his term.
Depending on his efforts,
he may get a chance to wear
the badge again in the
election after the next one.
Is what Chief Seo said true? Is it true...
that this is a hit list?
It's too early to make that conclusion.
It could be a document that
idle aides or reporters
made for fun.
Why is Secretary General
Baek doing this to me?
After giving me a party
nomination and having
a very hard time himself
because of that...
why, this late in the game,
why is he doing this to me?
Don't you have a guess?
I don't.
Think about it.
Only pigeons fight to death.
Lions stop when the victor
and loser become clear.
With you and me, the victor and
loser have already become clear.
Not yet.
For Assemblyman Jin and for you...
this is the best I can do.
Take it.
Assemblyman Jin.
Announcement of Intention Not to Run
in Next Year's General Election
Not run?
You should sit down first.
Is this the last task
assigned to you, Aide Choi?
This is a misunderstanding. I will explain.
No.
I have nothing to say so go outside.
- Assemblyman.-I'm not
your assemblyman anymore!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd