All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Assemblyman Jin.
How's the opposition party reacting?
Did it come out?
Just a while ago the Korean
Democratic and the Socialist.
Parties' floor leaders announced
mutual opposition to the veto.
A spokesperson for the
Assembly Speaker said that
the Speaker expressed
regret toward Park Choon.
Seop's announcement at
the press conference.
What about the Blue House? Are
they not saying anything?
The President is presiding over a
cabinet meeting on the issue right now.
What?
What happens if the
President vetoes the bill?
Bae Dal Soo's bill will return to the Assembly.
Last Episode.
When the National Assembly
votes on it again, it must
absolutely affirm the resolution
according to the law.
So what's the big deal, it
can always be passed again!
Aigoo, really.
Why are you guys
acting like that?
If it passed once, is there a law
that says it can't be passed twice?
Secretary Byeon, if the
vetoed bill is passed again,
two-thirds of the
assemblymen have to agree.
Two-thirds?
Two hundred of them
have to agree.
THERE IS ONE WAY: The Blue
House not rejecting it.
The Bae Dal Soo bill is a bill
which passed the National.
Assembly with the unconditional
support of the citizens.
All we have to do is to execute the bill.
Just executing it.
If by a tiny chance
the bill is vetoed
this act by the administration
will foolishly repudiate
the people's objective and the Assembly's
authority with a slap in the face.
Aide-nim Choi... the bill is
not going to be vetoed, is it?
I don't like the bill Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil is pursuing.
I am earnestly appealing
to President Seo Dae Han.
It will be fine. Let
us believe that.
I know. Yes. I know the economy
is facing hard times now.
But the Bae Dal Soo bill is not
a law to destroy the economy.
Because it will give hope to people
and make them work diligently again,
it is a law to
revive the economy.
Mr. President...
I earnestly appeal to you again.
I earnestly beg you.
Please don't veto it.
Mr. President... it's
wrong to veto the bill.
I earnestly appeal to you again.
I earnestly beg of you.
Do not veto the bill.
Anyway, if the rejection
process doesn't go well,
our situation will become dire.
Assemblyman Baek, did
you hear anything?
I don't know, because I don't have
much interest in this matter.
And from now on, I hope you won't
use me for your press conferences.
What is this?
Who do you think you are that
you come in here as you please?
What is the matter?
Park Choon Seop, do you
really have to go this far?
You? How dare you call
the party head, "You"?
Watch what you say!
How can we call a person the party head
when he requests a veto from the President?
The person who is the representative
of the parliamentary majority!
Can you ask to veto
the law passed by the.
National Assembly and
supported by the citizens?!
Are you even the representative
of the citizens?!
But this bastard is really
asking to be kicked out!!
Stop!!
Assemblyman Jim... Sit there.
I will just ask you one thing.
If you possibly know, please
tell me what the VIP intends.
As you already know it, nowadays
I am not in contact with him.
Assemblyman Baek, aren't
you ashamed of yourself?
Why are you saying
that, Secretary Kim?
Before the people and
before my father,
aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Assemblyman Jin.
At the drop of a hat, going off about
the representative of the citizens...
Who exactly are the citizens
whom you represent for?
What?
The citizens whom I, Park
Choon Seop represent for,
are not peope who want a second chance
or a chance to revive from the loss
but people who are
fighting tenaciously
to gain that.
Out of the blood, sweat and
effort of such people,
out the ashes of war, today's
Republic of Korea was created.
The Bae Dal Soo law...
is just a drug which would
make such the great people weak.
You got it?
Those great citizens...
Do you even know how they live?
The great citizens that I know
do not expect those things.
They just want to be happy.
Not getting fired
from their jobs.
Having a store that
does not become ruined.
Raising their children properly.
Those children's getting a job and buying
their parents undergarments. Those
kinds of things. (TRADITIONAL GIFT TO
PARENTS BOUGHT WITH FIRST PAYCHECK.)
Do you know?
Hello?
Yeah, what happened
at the meeting?
I got it.
What happened?
Assemblyman Park.
It has been vetoed.
President Seo Dae Han has
vetoed the Bae Dal Soo bill
which was approved by
the Assembly last week.
While saying that the bill is
contrary to the government's
economic reforms such as the
bill before the Assembly
to reform pensions and
he feared it would
heighten instability in
the nation's finances,
President Seo requested a
review in the Assembly.
Meanwhile, Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil, who led the.
Bae Dal Soo bill,
launched a counterattack.
The Bae Dal Soo Bill.
I will somehow make sure that the bill is
approved again in the plenary session.
Keep watching us.
The President shouldn't
do this kind of thing.
What the heck does he think
the legislative branch is...
Mr. Speaker, can you please
open the pleanary session
to put the Bae Dal Soo bill
up for reconsideration?
I suggest you just sit on it.
Why?
If 2/3 of the assemblymen
do not agree,
it will become
like toilet paper.
You know the likelihood
of being passed is zero.
Mr Speaker, whether it takes
2/3 or 3/3 of assemblymen
to agree, I have to make
it pass no matter what.
It's a problem that should
not be seen so simply.
If it is rejected after
reconsideration,
what will become of the
authority of the Assembly?
In the end, it'll result in only giving a
justification to BH that exercised the veto
I don't know much about such a
complicated thing, Mr. Speaker.
The Bae Dal Soo bill
must be reconsidered.
Mr. Speaker, please help.
This is not the problem that the
speaker can make the decision alone.
Between two negotiating parties, the Goomin
party will not change their mind at all.
If a request comes from the
Korean Democratic Party,
then, I'll think about it.
Oh, don't worry about that.
Rather than Gookmin Party,
the Korean Democratic Party
likes me more.
The floor leader and the leader of Policy
Planning Committee, both are not answering.
Representative Oh Sae Chang.
Why is the Korean Democratic
Party suddenly acting this way?
A little while ago, they did make a
strong statement of criticizing BH.
They just cursed BH loudly but they said
nothing about their future intentions.
It seems like they
want to back track.
Why would they back track?
Stop joking around.
Isn't that true, Aide Choi?
What Assemblywoman Hong
said is probably correct.
They probably feel burdened
because they think
it won't be passed although
it is reconsidered,
They didn't even try,
so how would they know?
I don't think so. They
probably put their phones
somewhere strange. That's
why they can't answer it.
If I keep trying,
they'll answer.
No, I ought to text instead.
Text message.
Assemblyman.
Why are you doing that?
Why are you suddenly making a serious face?
It scares me. What happened again?
Bae Dal Soo's bill seems to
have gone as far as it could.
When you are
re-elected next year,
Pursue it again at that time.
What are you talking
about right now?
Aide Choi, you've lost a
lot of your confidence.
What next year? We
have to do it now.
Don't you know the saying
that one must not put
off until tomorrow what
you must do today?
What Choi In Kyung is
saying is correct.
We now have no other way.
Why? Why is there no other way?
Why are you all doing like this?
Why not? It was passed
by the Assembly.
The Assembly is where to make a law.
That's why we made that law.
And it was passed.
What are you talking
"to give it up here"?!
This place is the Assembly.
Is BH the Assembly?
It doesn't make a sense,
right, Aide Choi?
I am sorry.
Bae Dal Soo's bill...
We made it!
We!
Assemblymen made it!!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Don't be too disappointed. You
did everything you could.
Dal Soo will appreciate
your effort, too.
Yes, Chief Secretary.
Tomorrow, you have
to come to the BH.
Are you trying to
convince the Assemblyman?
It means that we want to see
you and not Assemblyman Jin.
What?
Blue House.
The VIP wants to keep
you close to him.
Accept the Senior. Secretary Position
in the Office of Political Affairs.
Bae Dal Soo.
You suffered a lot.
The bearer bonds I talked to you about.
What happened to them?
Take care of your family
with this for now.
I asked, what happened
to the bearer bonds?
Just be happy that you were
released on probation.
I'll look for a good place for you
to work at an appropriate time.
Secretary General!
Chief Aide Im. My
patience has worn out.
Don't provoke me any further.
Do you think such threat
would work on me?
Take a good look at me.
Do I seem like the Baek
Do Hyeon that you served?
Don't piss me off anymore.
Before the citizens
and before my father,
aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Assemblyman, you have a
request for a meeting.
Who is it?
What is it that you want?
The Bae Dal Soo legislation. Please
help so it can be reconsidered.
You have the ability to
make it happen. If you
help me, you can not only
get it re-introduced,
but even get it passed.
Do I have reason to?
Yes, there is.
If you help me this once, I will not run
in Gyeonje City District next election.
What did you say?-If
it's like that,
it's enough of a
reason to help me.
Do you know what I
regret the most?
What is it?
Recommending you for the
strategic nomination.
I beg you.. Let me finish
this with my own hands.
Run. Do everything you can
to run for the election.
I'm going to stomp you.
When Aide Choi came to
me to become my aide,
she told me this.
That politics was created
to save the hellish
world by human power,
not by divine power.
So?
You, too... save yourself.
I'll leave now.
Choi In Kyung...
Let her go now.
What do you mean?
The elder proposed the position
of Senior Secretary to
the President for Political
Affairs to Choi In Kyung.
Are you talking about
the Blue House?
But I hear that that foolish
person declined it.
So that Choi In Kyung
can achieve her dream,
let her go now.
This is why I can't leave
the office at any time.
Isn't it the most basic rule for you to
be aware of where the Assemblyman is?
Why do all of you look so depressed?
Did the sky fall?
That's why, the more he's depressed,
the more we need to cheer up!
So he can get his passion back!
Assemblyman.
Just where were you,
without a cell phone?
We'll find a way to revive the Bae
Dal Soo legislation no matter what.
So don't lose heart too much.
Hey everybody! I have an
important announcement.
Aide Choi will
resign as of today.
Oh my, what's
he saying?- What?
Now that I've been
vetoed or whatever,
I've realized that we should have a
branch inside the Blue House, too.
So she is being offered to the President
as the BH Secretary for Political Affairs.
Awesome.
Assemblyman.
Secretary Oh. Dismiss Aide Choi
from her post as of today.
Dis-... dismiss?
I don't know how
you found out but
just because you announce it to the
secretaries, do you think I'll go?
Just go now. You have
to go and do big work.
Is there any other bigger
thing than being an.
Aide to the Indifferent
BH faction leader?
I am not going.-Aide Choi.
I know you are doing this so
that I can wear the badge.
Yes, I am going to
wear the badge.
I will wear it but not by the President's
backing but by your backing.
By my backing?
Of course. Next year I will make you
re-elected. After that, the 3rd
term Assemblyman, the leader of
the party, and up to President!
For all that, am I crazy
to go to the unpopular.
President, whose
remaining term is short?
Therefore, don't say those
words again in the future.
Aide Choi, you don't have
anything to do here.
Why do I have nothing to do?
Did I tell you I would make the
action plan for Bae Dal Soo's bill?
Don't you trust me?
I trust you. How many times
did I tell you that?
Still, you don't have
anything to do now.
You don't know how much
the secretaries have
to do. That's why you
keep saying that.
Don't be so stubborn. Call quickly!
Quickly!
No. I will send a letter by registered
mail that says I am not going.
That's enough. Please go!
No. I don't like it.
What kind of aide doesn't listen to
the assemblyman's words like this?
Go quickly! Go quickly! Go!
No matter how hard you try,
I'm stuck to you like chewing gum
and won't separate from you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
You are here?
How are you?
I heard from Secretary Sim;
Did you get a call from BH?
This Sim Dong Cheon...
By the way, Aren't
you really going?
Why am I going there?
Is it more strange that you
are not going? That is
the position that everybody
else is anxious to get.
Assemblywoman Hong. I will go to
the end with our Assemblyman.
He was right.-Pardon?
Someone said that Choi
In Kyung is the only
person for whom the word
comrade is appropriate.
I admit it.
Who is the someone?
The person who can die for Choi In Kyung
more than Assemblyman Jin... Baek Do Hyeon.
Anyhow, Choi Doube-O, you
sometimes look cool.
Is it because you are older
than me by one year?
Is it proper manners that you address
a year older person as Choi Double-O?
Just bear a little bit more.
After taking the badge off,
I will call you "Unni."
Unni?
Since I don't have many friends, I try to
be a friend. But you said you are older.
I can't help it.
Assemblywoman Hong.
It hurts.
I am strong, ain't I?
Say to give a punch.
Say honestly. It's a little regrettable
not to go to the BH, isn't it?
Kind of... A little...
Yes, So Min. Why?
Assemblyman looks strange.
What do you mean strange?
He went to the press conference.
All of sudden, he said to
us "Sorry" then he left.
What?
What happened?
As an Assemblyman who
leads Bae Dal Soo's bill,
I can't acknowlege this
reality at all, that.
Bae Dal Soo's bill
was vetoed and
can't be reconsidered
in the Assembly.
I got to know that the Assembly
is where the laws are made.
And the Assemblymen are the
people who make the laws.
If the law we make
with difficulty
becomes trash easily,
we should not be
the Assemblymen.
That's why I...
will resign
from the position of Assemblyman
at the end of this week.
Oh my god.
And I beg my last favor to the
leaders of the negotiation
groups from the ruling party
and the opposition party.
My last favor, only one favor.
Within this week,
please reconsider Bae Dal
Soo's bill in the Assembly,
whether it will be
passed or rejected.
Please allow me to cast my last
vote in favor with my own hand.
This is my last favor to
ask as the Assemblyman,
and my wish.
Wow, Is Jin Sang Pil a
suicide blackmailer?
How can he quit the position of Assembly
because of not reconsidering his bill?
How is the reaction
of the press?
Right now, it is fussing.
Not only one or two articles appeared,
saying to reconsider Bae Dal Soo's bill.
Chairman, let's reconsider it.
Anyhow, it will be rejected.
Assemblyman Baek, please work
hard this time, too.-Pardon?
I ask you to do the press conference
in opposition to reconsideration.
I clearly told you that I am
not interested in this matter.
This is not asking,
but ordering it as a leader of
Emergency Measure Committee.
Assemblyman Park.- Do it.
Both of Bae Dal Soo's
bill and Jin Sang Pil are
from the seeds that
Assemblyman Baek sowed.
Let's stay low for a moment.
It is irrational to challenge Park Choon
Seop before being reconciled with the VIP.
That's enough.- There
is still some suspicion
left in the Chief
Secretary Lim's case...
Please Stop it!
Hey.-Please!
Let's stop it!
Do whatever you want.
Lim Gyu TaeI already spent all
the living expense you gave.
Prepare five big denomination
bonds as I requested.
If not, your political
life will be over.
Even though the bill can be
reconsidered, the number of the
opposiition party members are not
enough to bring it to a vote.
We need at least 151
assemblymen to attend to vote.
There are only 150 seats even
if all of our opposition
party members and
Indifferent-BH members attend.
This means, if there is one
more member, we can vote.
But, who will come into line
with you from the Gookmin Party?
For a moment, excuse me.
Joo Hee's mom.
Wait.
Honey, when you quit the assembly,
what are you going to do?
There is an ironwork place that Hyung
Seong Gi saw in Kyeongje City.
We want to work there together.
That's good. You are
very good at welding.
You did Assemblyman better.
If you go to Gyeongje City,
Joo Hee and I will follow you.
Kyung Ah.- If you
are okay with me,
let's start again.
Mom, Dad! We have a camera.
Mom, Dad, let's have
a picture taken.
Gyu Hwan. Come here. Let's
have picture taken together.
Oppa, come here. Let's have
picture taken together.
So that Bae Dal Soo's Law
can pass, please help.
It will be better for you to go
and prepare to go to the BH.
No. Unless the Bae Dal
Soo's Law passes,
I will not be going to the BH.
I can cope with Baek Do Hyeon
as a corrupt politician but
I am not confident I can handle the failure
of a politician named Jin Sang Pil.
It sounds like you want
to leave politics.
Even for your sake, the Bae
Dal Soo bill must be passed.
Why is that?
It is the second chance
for Baek Do Yeon
to be reborn as a human being
out of the power from slavery.
Choi In Kyung, I will not live as a person
without power but as a slave who has power.
Now, please go.
To Assemblyman Baek, .. even
though you disappointed
me a lot, I can still
say there is one thing
that I am sincerely
thankful for.
What is that?
You asked me to serve as
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's aide.
Thanks to that,
I, who had been a trivial
political engineer,
I got to taste the
real joy in politics.
Then...
It's Baek Do Hyeon.
I won't wait any longer.
State your opposition at the
press conference this morning.
Aren't you going to be
in Yeoido next year?
I understand.
You thought well. Bye.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
I am Baek Do Hyeon from the Gookmin
Emergency Response Council.
The Bae Dal Soo bill...
should immediately be re-presented
in the plenary session.
With the assemblymen who agree
with me from the Gookmin Party,
I reiterate that I will vote in
favor of the Bae Dal Soo's Law.
Until recently I opposed the law
so I suspect many of
you are puzzled about
today's explanation
of my position.
Citizens.
Until now, I deceived
the citizens
and I deceived myself.
I am resigning from all positions
including the emergency council.
Also, I will not run in
next year's election.
Also with regards to Im Gyu
Tae, I will turn myself
into the Prosecutor and
reveal the entire truth
about the matters alleged
in the pending court case.
I've become a
completely new bird.
Citizens. Until now, I have
been there in this place...
Assembly.
I lived oblivious
of the fact that
this is the place where the
representatives of the people assemble.
To Bae Dal Soo's law that reminded me
of my original intention of politics
and those who led the
struggle for the law,
I express my deep appreciation.
Baek Do Hyeong... has
completely self-destructed.
Issue a mobilization
order for all members.
If he does that,
Bae Dal Soo's Law can
be reconsidered?
Yes.
Of course, it will
be reconsidered.
Now it looks like there is a possibility
the Bae Dal Soo law will be enacted.
Assemblyman, the members of the
Jinjimo have come to cheer you on.
Oh, is that so?
Assemblyman Jin! Hurry
up and go outside.
Why? What is the matter?
But, you guys...
How did you guys...
- Assemblyman Jin.
- Hyung Sang Pil.
I'm sorry. Not
understanding what your
intentions were, I just cursed you.
Forgive me.
Before you resign, I thought I
really had to apologize to you.
I am sorry for all this time.
What are you saying?... I'm
the one who is sorry...
Assemblyman Jin...
I am so sorry.
Forgive me.-Hyung Sang
Phil.- You came well.
I am really grateful.
Someone said this. If one person
dreams, it is just a dream, but
when more than one dreams
together, it becomes reality.
All of us together,
going forward together,
let us dream
the Bae Dal Soo law together.
Jang Pil. You are our hyung.
Chairnan, there isn't a
thing to worry about.
Even if the sky is split into two
pieces, the bill will be rejected.
Why hasn't Jin
Sang Pil appeared?
Did he already come in?
He's arrived.
What is that? He tries to threaten someone?
Why does he bring so many?
I'll be back.
Let's go.
Will the house come
to order please?
The bill to provide support for a second
chance to the bankrupt and the unemployed
which was submitted to the President is
being introduced for reconsideration.
Because there has been a request
for debate on the issue
we will start the debate now.
Assemblyman Park Choon Seop,
you may give your statement.
I am Park Cheoon Seop.
There are people saying that
the president's veto was
an infringement of the
Assembly's authority.
The veto is a legitimate right granted
to the President by the Constitution.
The government is a guard
protecting the lives and property
of the nation's people, not a
lending institution banker.
If there are many people who, blaming
their own failure on the government,
come to the government
begging for favors under
the speciously named
second chance law...
if many people ask for favors
from the government...
I guarantee this country
will have no future.
I, Park Choon Seop, with the
blood drained from my heart,
beg my fellow assemblyman.
Today... make this the memorial service
day for laws based on emotion...
thank for your attention.
Assemblyman Park Choon
Seop is in a big rush...
He has personally stepped forwardto
launch a pre-emptive strike.
Yes, the Gookmin party members
are wrung out and drained.
Next, Assemblyman
Jin, please speak.
Okay.
Yes, I'm Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil.
Looking at your expression, it
seems like you are rather anxious.
You don't need to do that, Assemblymen.
Don't get anxious.
The person we fear is
not the President,
nor Party Leader, but the citizen.
Citizen.
Just say what you
have to say quickly.
Shut your mouth and
listen to him.
Assemblywoman Cheon,
stop butting in.
Chairman. Please apply a
proper sanction against
the Assemblyman who
is picking a fight.
Here. Here. All of you be quiet.
Assemblyman Jin,
please continue.
Okay.
Before I speak,
just as I promised last time,
when this session ends,
my position as an Assemblyman:
I will resign from it.
I will keep my promise.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Do not lower your head.
As his secretary,
let's stand with our chests
high and see what happens.
Through some process, I did
become an Assemblyman but
as you know, I was a welder.
I really like welding.
The reason is that
welding puts things together.
Whatever the kind of metals,
we melt them and
put them together.
I would like it if
politics was like welding.
Bind Kyeongsangdo and Jeollado together.
Bind the rich with the poor.
And bind the winners and losers.
Binding them together,
creating that kind of a country,
I wish politics would do that.
In regard to Bae Dal Soo's Law,
I believe it is that
kind of politics.
Assemblyman Park Choon Soep,
a little while ago, you
said the government is not
a banker, didn't you?
Then, what about the citizens?
The citizens are the financial bankers?
Are they the financial bankers?
You see, our citizens work
themselves to the bone.
They keep our country.
And they pay taxes. That is
because the law says
that it is their duty.
Bae Dal Soo was like that.
All his life, he worked hard to build
ships, went to serve in the military,
and he paid his taxes without missing
a beat. However, suddenly one day,
he was thrown out
onto the street.
Who is going to help
him get up again?
him rise again?!
It's the government!
The government!
To make the citizens happy
is the government's duty.
The citizens are not pushovers
nor financial bankers.
The citizens are the
owners of this country.
That's why I...
want the citizens to believe
that the government
never abandons them.
"Even though I fall down,
the government gives a helping
hand to make me get up again."
So, I... I...
in this proud Korea, I...
I will become happy
in the future.
I, the leader of Indifferent-to
BH, Jin Sang Pil,
JSP, am clearly saying...
If the citizens do
all of their duties,
the government has
to do its duty and
the citizens have to
demand their rights.
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil!
Now we conclude the debates and
start voting on this matter.
April 2016.
Sang Pil.
Aide Choi asks you
to come quickly.
She is very upset. Stop
doing this and go quickly.
Noona Ae Ri, fire Hyung Seong
Gi and hire someone else.
Whenever he makes things,
all of them are inferior.
Hey. I am the boss, you punk!
The boss is higher or the
boss's wife is higher?
The boss's wife.
Okay. You are a match
made in Heaven.
Respectable citizens!
As candidate ♪8, I Kang
Sang Ho greet you.
Kang Sang Ho! Kang Sang Ho!
Kang Sang Ho!
Your avatar, Kang Sang Ho...
Now, I want to be the real
avatar for my hometown
and work hard.
Avatar. Avatar.
Please save me. I want to return
to the Assembly after I survive.
Everyone, please save
Assemblyman Park as well!
If you save me one more time, I will
be a real avatar for my hometown.
Early 20's... Strategy for victory in
the Gyeonje City general election.
This is everything for
election strategy?
It's a bit of the same things...
This is all?
It's okay.-It's okay?
Aigoo, this is about
the Bae Dal Soo Law...
You are still milking it.
I did this you know.
I don't think is going to do. You are going
to become unemployed like Assemblyman Jo.
Assemblyman!-Why?
So, are you going
to do it or not?
I stayed up all for days so my
throat isn't all that good and...
I had decided not to do anymore
political campaigning.
Why did you use a picture like this?
Should have used a good one.
Who picked the picture?
This looks good.
If I could tell you about
candidate ♪1, Choi In Kyeong,
Yes.
She gained a lot of experience from
the Assembly to the Blue House.
And the best point about
her is that she's smart.
Although in the picture she
came out a bit prickly,
in truth, her personality
is soft as a silk.
I know this because I personally
experienced. But because she nags a bit,
it can be tough. But because she
has so many good points about her,
I am completely certain that
candidate ♪1, Choi In Kyeong
is the fittest Assemblywoman
for Gyeongje city, everybody!
Thank you. And...
I am afraid there is
no fun if I talk about
only politics and sing
the candidate's praise.
During an intermission, I want
to give good information.
Former People's Truth, JSP
is working at the JSP Ironworks.
Our specialty was doing
welding and sheet metal.
This time, we invited the expert
who does laying a pipe from Seoul.
We are leaping into a new area.
Get this business card. To people
who bring the business card,
I will give 20%
discount for 2 months.
If you use ten times, I
will give one free service.
Yes. Take only one business card... Yes.
You can have two.
I want to give someone else...
Ah... Yes... Thank you.
Now, get back to the
main topic again.
In order to give the support to
Candidate ♪1, Choi In Kyeong,
Well, I will shout out.
Candidate ♪1, Choi In Kyeong!
Ironwork place is at JSP!
Ironwork place is JSP!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki.
Assemblywoman, congratulations
on your entering the.
National Assembly. I will
assist you sincerely.
Congratulations.
Assemblywoman Choi,
congratulations.
Thank you.
Assemblywoman Choi.
Congratulations on your entering
National Assembly. Best of luck.
Thank you, Sunbae.
Unni, so do I...
Yes. Thank you.
You don't have to
come like this.
Wow, of course I have to
come when the person who got
the highest vote is entering
the National Assembly.
It's almost time to enter.
Go now, please.
Ah... Yes.
Assemblywoman, let's go.
Yes. Let's enter.
Ah. I thought I was late.
I have a little time.
Have you been well?
Secretary General Baek, you look younger.
Assemblyman Jin, you look good too.
Assemblyman.
I knew it. From the first
day, you look like a novice.
A novice? Why? Do I look strange somehow?
Do you want to enter
without wearing a badge?
Omo. I forgot about it.
As a secretary, what did you
do without taking care of this
kind of thing? You'd better start
working as an intern again.
Huh. You told me to keep quiet
because you would take care of it.
When did I say that? You are a strange guy.
That's enough. Be quiet.
Give it to me. I am late.
Wait for a moment, please.
For this kind of stuff...
Sunbae has to... like this.
Ahh. It's good.
Congratulations,
Assemblywoman Choi In Kyung.
2nd Leader of Indifferent-to-BH, fighting!
No matter what, make many
members of Indifferent-to BH.
Yes.
Assemblyman. I think I am a little nervous.
Are you scared?
It seems like that.
Ahh... Why are you scared?
All of the people here
are your comrades. Am I right?
Enter now.
Yes.
Aide Choi.
Do well.
Thank you to all the
volunteers on The Assembly Team.
Thank you to Channel Managers
reclan_411 and LACruiser.
THANK YOU TO SEGMENTERS:
Signs of Serendipity,
pillar_velasquez,
recclan_411, amyPun,
THANK YOU TO SEGMENTERS:
leogregory, rocsanna,
bjohnsonwong,
themonsterasiatico, Wafaahs.
THANK YOU TO SEGMENTERS:
cgwm808, Robertases,
walter_casa, and
eileenloveskdramas.
Thank you to Korean to
English subtitlers:
Baritaggie, hermoine77,
awesomeharry, changhuh,
Thank you to Korean to
ENGLISH SUBTITLERS: Cgwm808,
SignsofSerendipity, SL3388,
alpaca123, and wanbyeokhan_yeoja.
THANK YOU TO THE EDITORS:
Cgwm808 (CHIEF),
baritaggie, SignsofSeredipity,
changhuh, and pey_288.
Thank you to all the
moderators and subtitlers