All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
And also... Oh, I will give my
warning to the party leadership
and to the Pro- and
Anti-BH factions.
I can look there
and do it, right?
From now on, when the
party decides something,
make sure to discuss it with
the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
If you look down on us
because of our small number,
and as you have been doing thus
far, if the Pro- and Anti-BH
factions engage in hanky-panky
and do shoddy work...
You just try that and
see what happens...
In that event, the same
party color or whatever,
I will just kick your
ass, all of you!
If you want to sanction
me, sanction me.
If you want to expel me,
just try expelling me, huh?!
Ugh, what should I do
to that wet blanket...
Me, Jin Sang Pil, the big boss of
the Indifferent-to-BH faction!
JSP! I will never get scared!
You better be prepared, huh?!
Do you read me, huh?!
"Jin Sang Pil's Declaration
of Indifference."
Episode 11
Jin Sang Pil, bouncing off
the walls again. Until when?
Response from the Pro- and Anti-BH
Factions. He does not merit any response.
-Jin Sang...  -
Enough already.
Instead of articles from the internet,
are there any articles in the newspaper?
Oh, today, the politics
sections of the dailies
are wallpapered with
the articles about
the President tongue-lashing the Prime
Minister in a cabinet meeting about
the inadequate measures to
stimulate the real estate market.
- There was a column in the Jo
Gook Daily.- What did it say?
Gag Concert PD, cast
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil...
We somewhat expected
this kind of response.
Now, this is only the beginning.
Let's cheer up and work hard.
- Yes.-Yes!
The 335th (SPECIAL) Session of the
National Assembly Full Agenda
Is this all for
today's schedule?
Yes, there were a few scheduled
intra-party meetings and appointments,
but everyone cancelled.
Are you nervous?
No, well, this was expected.
Still, I feel a bit... you know...
With my term ending soon and all...
But is Secretary Kim ill or something? Why
did he ask for a day off all of a sudden?
He said he was going to go somewhere
so I told him to rest for a day.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Bae Dal Soo
That I, this Bae Dal Soo,
am not a piece of trash.
They use me as they please and
they throw me out in the
street as they please.
I am not that kind of
trash but a human being.
That I didn't live a wanton life to
be treated like a piece of trash,
I am confirming that.
Is that enough?
What's so wrong to
live like trash?
JIn Sang Pil is trash.
He's trash because he betrayed
you and got the nomination!
Father. What do I
have to do now?
What should I do?
Gookmin Party Assemblymen's
Meeting Forum on
Measures to Revitalize
Real Estate Transactions
Even though I am an
Anti-BH assemblyman...
this time, I cannot help but
be on the Blue House's side.
Our real estate market is in a
brain-dead condition right now.
Transactions are halted.
In a word, it has gone batsh*t,
that's what I'm saying!
With the paltry policies that the
government is fidgeting with right now,
do you think we can revive
our real estate market?
A snowball's chance in hell!
Prime Minister, you have to be
ashamed of yourself and wake up!
A while ago, the President said
if you're going to do
something do it right.
Since when has the Prime
Minister been a government
officer to be always on the
civil servants' side...
Agreed!
Assemblyman Avatar... Dear
God, give me patience.
Damn.
He must have drowned his sorrows all
night long. I know that feeling.
Is this a defective
product or what?
Aide Choi, do I have to stay
still and not do anything?
Not right now. Hold it in.
But, you know, that Avatar
of the Anti-BH faction.
He is strange today. He's
being a Pro-BH copycat.
Since it's a policy
discussion, they are voicing
various ideas, irrespective
of the factions.
For today, zip up your mouth and
just listen no matter what.
This isn't right.
As for me, I have
a different idea.
We should not just gripe
to the Prime Minister
but also think about
why he is doing that.
Real estate, this thing... If
we touch it half-heartedly,
the market may overheat
and cause speculation.
Agreed!
Fostering speculation
Real estate transactions, this. We
can't unregulate them too much.
Even now, there is an uproar
over rising key deposits
for long term leases and if
the housing prices soar,
that's like forgoing next
year's general election.
I understand that the Blue
House is obsessing over its
track record but this is not
the time to touch this.
Agreed!
Not studying the
BH's countenance...
Now, isn't there any other
assemblyman who wants to speak up?
Yes. Let's go eat.
Let's do that! Let's go!
Let's go eat!
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
- What?- You are jotting
things down really hard.
If I give you a chance,
will you speak up?
Why behave in a way
so unusual for you?
Didn't you ask the party
to discuss things in
the future with the
Indifferent-to-BH faction?
Indifferent-to-BH my butt.
Stop wasting time and
get out of the party!
Are you playing
around right now?
I don't have anything to say.
What a goof-off.
If you don't know, just say you don't
know and don't feign indifference.
Now, then, we will conclude the
Gookmin Party general meeting.
Aigo, let's go.
What? Put your
assemblyman on the show?
Yes, I have to raise him to
be on a national scale, too.
That "One to One Debate"
show you're making...
It seems a lot of
people are watching.
This kid is trying to zap
it when I've finally
managed to push up
the viewer ratings.
PD Park, that's because
you don't know this.
My old man... He is,
unbeknownst to others, pretty
good with words and very
sensible, you know?
Really?
Your assemblyman is a no-go
because of low recognition.
He also has a severely
dislikable image, okay?
Hey, hey, hey, that's why he has
to be on TV to get recognized
and to change his image, too?
Huh, friend?
Since I'm your friend,
I'll tell you something.
Hey, friend, snap out of it.
Indifferent-to-BH? Try its grandfather
(SOMETHING A LOT STRONGER).
Assemblyman Jin, rat's ass.
What can he get done?
A partial amendment to the Framework Act
on the Juveniles will be put to a vote.
Secret Voting Machine
Yes
Have you all voted?
VOTE RESULTPRESENT: 217; Yes:
213; NO: 0; Abstention: 4
I will now tell you the
results of the vote.
Among the 217 present,
213 voted yes and 4 abstained from voting.
I declare that the bill passed.
Next, a partial amendment
to the Fair Subcontract
Transactions Act will
be put to a vote.
Please vote.
I declare that the bill passed.
Yes.
What is that?
I spoke to my acquaintance
in the Blue House and the
conflict between the
President and Prime Minister
is a lot more serious than
assumed by outsiders.
From now on, we don't know what
might happen so start studying.
But this issue... I saw
other assemblymen objecting
to it and doing well in
the general meeting?
- Let's do something else instead.-What
do you mean something else?
You know those issues where
the Pro- and Anti-BH go for
each other's throat and things
go to the dogs and such...
- Assemblyman.- But,
aside from visiting my
constituency, I haven't
gotten anything done today.
If we pass one, two days like this,
that's all just wasted time.
Wait. The popular opinion
is cool, as it is,
because of your declaration
of indifference.
If you just poke around
anywhere out of a sense
of urgency, you'll end
up a laughing stock.
So I have to wait
no matter what?
If you wait, you will
be given a chance.
How long do I have to wait?
Chapter 5 - Expenses
I'm back.
Ah, did you take care
of your business?
Yes. I'm turning in.
What is it? Is something up?
- No.  - There
isn't something?
I see it written
all over your mug.
- That's not so.  - Hey,
tell me what's bugging you.
What did you take a break for?
It's none of your business.
Hey, you're acting cocky again.
Whoopee.
Why are you harassing me?
Harassing?
Are you dissing me now because
you've done some martial arts?
I was also into
boxing before, punk.
Swoosh! Do you think that sound
just came from my mouth, now? Hey.
Phooey, huh? Take this, punk.
That's what I was aiming for, punk.
Why are you just standing there?
So you can't let down
your guard, punk.
How was that, huh? Hey.
Go for it. Hey.
Hey Punk.
Hey, now...
It was sparring but
really, this...
You should loosen up sometimes.
Young kid.
You always have a
frown on your face.
Turn in and relax.
-Assemblyman.  - What is it?
You want to
go for a round? Huh?
Want to do that?
Will I be drafting a bill also?
Bill? Which bill?
Can I?
If you insist on working but,
do you know how to do
something like that?
I will try.
By the way, Assemblyman.
What else?
- Assemblyman, your boxing...
- Yeah.
is garbage.
Hey. You come over here.
Hey, let's go at it properly.
Aren't you coming? Hey!
Hey, quickly go buy
headgear and mouthguards.
After you don't give the
nomination to me, do
you really think you can
handle the aftermath?
For a person who is
worried sick about a mere
Assemblyman Jin defecting
to another party...
Assemblyman Park!
I think tomorrow's Gyeongje District
meeting will be very interesting.
If he's faced with a vote of no confidence,
how will Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil act?
Were you looking for
me, Secretary General?
Among local party chapters,
give me the status sheets
for those areas overrun
by the Anti-BH faction.
May I ask why?
The chapters without much activity
and existing only in name...
I will either revoke their charters
or sanction their presidents.
At a minimum, more
than 10 of them.
Schedule a meeting with
the Audit Team Leader.
Yes, I understand.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Big trouble!
What do you mean big trouble?
This is what I heard from my straw (SOURCE)
working in the party administration office.
As soon as this special
session ends, Baek Do Hyeon
is going to audit the local party
chapters all over the country.
This, for sure, is revenge
for the local party
members' general meeting
we pushed in Gyeongje
City the last time.
This dude is countering with
a super powerful move...
If it is to this extent,
shouldn't we also enter
into war preparations?
Should I issue a DEFCON 3?
Auditing local chapters,
does that make any sense?
Secretary Kim, what's going on?
... then, "hey punk, how can
you manhandle an assemblyman?"
Saying that, you should break
through and strongly demand...
Push through no
matter what, okay?
If even that doesn't work,
then, I will come and just...
Write it down. I won't accept
anything not in writing.
Please summarize the common and
different points between the
President and Prime Minister over
the real estate market policy.
- Since it is going to be used
as the Assemblyman's study
material, make it as easy as
possible to understand.- Yes.
But the Anti-BH
faction's core people
were flocking to Assemblyman
Kang Sang Ho's room.
You don't know what
their agenda is?
No, I asked a hoobae of
mine in a roundabout way,
but he said he did
not know either.
Oh? The middle bosses of
the Pro-BH faction were
swarming at Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi's office too.
Have you seen who were going in?
Yes, roughly.
Not to provide a pretext for
the Anti-BH faction to resist,
we have to show them our active
participation in the audit.
It is a call from
Assemblyman Heo Dae Il.
Yes, Assemblyman. Why
are you not here?
Oh, yes, Assemblywoman Hong.
Today, I am feeling
under the weather.
But what have you gathered
to talk about today?
The Secretary General is performing
an audit of the local party chapters.
We are discussing
ways to support him.
Oh, really? If that is the occasion,
I should have made it somehow.
But my health is so poor...
No, Assemblyman. I will let you know
later, so take care of yourself.
Aigo, thank you.
You did well.
But, then, the Pro- and Anti-BH
factions are now fighting?
Unless some variable interjects
itself, that is how it will play out.
Then, we have to hurry
and make a statement,
in the name of the
Indifferent-to-BH faction.
That they shouldn't engage
in turf battles but
look out for the
livelihoods of the people.
Let's go quickly.
Oh, what is it, this time?
It's combat between whales
(GIANTS).(Korean saying:
"When whales fight the
krill's back is broken.")
If a krill makes a
public statement,
it can't influence the
current of events.
Am I a krill?
But, then, what is this? Are you
saying we should wait yet again?
In order for the
Indifferent-to-BH to show its
strength, the Pro- and Anti-BH
factions should be one
rather than split up.
Why are you saying
such nonsense?
How can those kids
play nice like that?
You must wait.
Aish, stop saying wait and
come up with some strategy!
It seems like you don't
have any strategy.
At this rate, what if the people forget
about the Indifferent-to-BH and what-not?
The more they forget, the better the
chance that will come your way.
Lay low as much as possible
and until your adversaries have
forgotten about your existence,
quietly lie in wait.
I'm going to die, really. How
can I lower myself even more?
I have conveyed your requests and
messages to the assemblymen.
You worked hard.
So impolite... What
are you doing?
Is it true that you are going to
audit the local party chapters?
Stop smirking and say something!
Yes or no?
It's true.
With the next year's
election coming up,
checking on the status
of local organizations
and disciplining
them, if necessary,
isn't that what a secretary general
should do, as a part of his duties?
Now, if your curiosity is
satisfied, why don't you leave?
We can't leave empty-handed.
Guarantee that you will
not target our Anti-BH
faction and audit
the hell out of us.
In writing!
Why don't you talk sense.
Where is an audit that excludes a
specific subject even before it starts?
What?
If you keep obstructing a proper exercise
of the party rights in this manner,
I will no longer just
sit still and watch it.
Then, do you think
we will just sit still and
watch, Secretary General Baek?
VIP
Yes, Elder.
What?
Whose call is that for
him to be like that?
Welcome, Secretary General Baek.
When you must be busy...
what brings you here?
There is a matter about which
I need to consult with
you. There is also a matter
I should thank you for.
Thank me?
Didn't I learn a proper move from
you just a little while ago?
So,
I heard that you were
preparing a gift to repay me.
Didn't you ask for this meeting
in order to declare war?
No, I'm here to
suggest an armistice.
The Elder at the Blue
House must not like the
measures the government
has come up with
in order to stimulate
real estate transactions.
Isn't it about time that the government
workers start disobeying him?
The day before yesterday, the polls showed
the administration approval ratings
went down even farther
than last month's.
The Elder wants
the measures that he likes to be
carried as our party platform.
In the eyes of the people,
it may come off as the ruling party
fighting with the Prime Minister.
That armistice...
I will decline it.
You'd better accept my offer.
Auditing of the party chapters... I'm
not afraid of that sort of thing.
Go ahead with it if you want.
And you are not afraid of standing
up against the President?
For a person who is as
important as the President,
he should not hold a grudge just because a
policy was not made into a party platform.
Why don't you tell him to just
bring around the Prime Minister?
The Prime Minister...
will spend his last
day at Sejong City
(KOREA'S SECOND ADMINISTRATIVE
CAPITAL) today.
What?
When the President's
will is this strong...
will you still decline?
Prime Minister Lee Seung Hwan has
expressed his wish to resign promptly.
Prime Minister Lee, in the statement
announced by his office moments ago,
expressed his keen sense of remorse
at not having risen to the
challenge of economic recovery,
the people's fervent wish,
and announced his resignation.
The Blue House, in a promptly
released comment, said it was
regretful but Prime Minister Lee's
decision would be respected.
With the voluntary resignation
of Prime Minister Lee, who has
been cautious about the
government-led market manipulation,
the Seo Dae Han administration
is expected to pursue
- a more aggressive economic
stimulus package...-
Is the Prime Minister
thrown out, then?
This has been Jeong
Min Hee of KBC News.
The armistice...
Let's enter into it.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Now.
Notice of Gookmin Party
Emergency General Meeting
Tomorrow Morning 9 a.m. at
THE MAIN HALL; AGENDA: Prime
Minister's Resignation and Status
of Current National Affairs
Tomorrow morning, there will be
an emergency general meeting.
Umm, I saw it too.
The Prime Minister... it was the
President who fired him, right?
Obviously. Seeing this,
I guess the President
is powerful, after all.
An assemblyman can't
hold a candle to him.
Yes, Aide Choi.
You've received a text message about
tomorrow's general meeting, right?
Yes, I just did.
Finally, the chance
you've been waiting for is here.
A chance is here?
Yes.
Today's General Meeting is in
camera (CLOSED TO THE PUBLIC)
As stated, this bill
minimizes the unnecessary
regulations that restrict
real estate transactions.
Not only by aggressively reducing
the transaction fees, but
also by enacting into law the
bases and rules upon which
the government can implement various
measures to catalyze transactions,
it aims at injecting
lifesaving oxygen
into the depressed economy.
With that, I will conclude
my introduction of the bill.
Next, Party Leader Yoon Jung
Soo will come up and speak.
Aide-nim.
So unlike you, why
are you so nervous?
Yeah, I will say...
I'm a bit nervous because the
coup d'état is about to go off.
I am thinking about becoming
the sponsor for this bill just
introduced by Assemblywoman Hong
and getting the signatures
of all Gookmin Party members
to present it as the
official party platform.
What are your thoughts,
Assemblymen?
What thoughts? What need
is there to ask and stuff?
Of course, everyone is for it.
Isn't that so?
Agreed! Agreed!
Let's make it a party platform!
Then, I will think that there is
no objection to this bill and...
Just a minute.
I do have an objection.
No way he'd just let it go...
Just leave me out of the list of the
assemblymen supporting this bill.
What did you say?
What are you saying? We are presenting
it as the party's unified platform!
Don't you understand
there is no exception?
Is this the military? If
it's a party platform,
do I have to accept and gorge myself
whether it's dung or doenjang (SOY PASTE)?
- What?- And, also,
a bill just needs
10 to support it.
Why must all 151
people support it?
Are you showing off the number
to the opposition parties now?
I don't want to be included, so just
get it done amongst yourselves.
Look here, Assemblyman Jin.
I'm busy, so...
Aigo, that wacko, that thing...
I should just!
Look here, Assemblyman Jin!
Hey, over there, grab
Assemblyman Jin!
But, Assemblyman Jin,
why are you doing this?
You're asking me why? Huh?
I jotted down everything that came
out in the last general meeting.
Shall I look at what you two said?
Huh? Oh, it's right here.
Objection to the real estate market getting
overheated and fostering speculation.
Housing prices soaring,
not studying the BH's
countenance! You two said
the exactly same things!
At that time, you two were
so fired up, objecting.
If you look at this bill,
those measures you opposed
at that time... Those
are all in here, now.
But why are you two
so quiet, today?
Wiping your mouths like this. Did you
eat some honey (LIPS GLUED TOGETHER)?
And in yesterday's general
meeting, surely one half
was opposed while the
other half supported it.
But why is everyone supporting
it today, all of a sudden?
Yes, of course, I understand that you
are scared of falling out of favor
of the party higher-ups and
not getting nominations.
But still we are
so-called, so-called assemblymen,
national assemblymen!
It looks as though
we let down our guard too much.
Ladies and gentlemen of the Assembly,
let's please live with some guts, okay?
Just, just! Are we some employees of the
Gookmin Party Incorporated Company?
Are you an employee?
Executive Baek!
- Look here, Assemblyman Jin.- Oh ho,
let me go. I've done some martial arts.
In the blink of an eye, really.
You'll be surprised.
Seriously, that is a king-sized
wacko, that thing...
Assemblyman Jin!
It sounds as though you are
opposed to the party platform.
Please give us a comment.
It seems like you have an
objection, just one word please.
Assemblyman Jin!
It's okay if I talk, right?
Ah, yes.
Ask me questions.
Are you objecting to making the real
estate bill into the party platform?
I, as the leader of
the Indifferent-to-BH
faction, am telling you
in no uncertain terms.
This bill, absolutely
NEVER! I can't put my
seal of approval to it.
Everyone who needs Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's press materials, take one from here.
Yes, take all of these and distribute
them to those who are not here.
Take many! Yes, the
person over there!
Will the real estate bill
become the party platform?
It seems as though Assemblyman
Jin is objecting.
Please one word, Assemblyman!
Never!
It sounded like Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
was objecting. How did the meeting go?
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Never, never!
You've done well holding it in
all this time, Assemblyman.
Now, we are just running
with it, right?
Yes, you'd better bring
nerves of steel.
Of course I should.
Jin Sang Pil has caused proper trouble.
The Indifferent-to-BH faction?
Really amazing.
Just say what your business is.
You know that in my party there was a
clash over the real estate policy.
Thanks to Jin Sang Pil, I think the
house will soon come to order.
If you present the bill, then we,
as one party, will object to it.
I mean when even a ruling
party member objects to it,
how can a wise political
party like us agree to it?
Please tell him that the Socialist Party
has already decided to oppose it.
Assemblywoman Cheon says the Socialist
Party is dead set against it.
Have I thumbed my nose too much?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil is
fighting alone against 150 people.
We need to keep watching.
Whether he will go till the end
or he will surrender.
You can't do this,
Assemblyman Jin.
Assemblyman Jin, you're doing something
that will cause you a big problem.
No matter what you say, I won't
waiver in my conviction.
Do you think we here don't have any
conviction to toe the party line?
What will become of the
nation if all 300 members
of the Assembly act according
to their own whims?
Right, what Assemblywoman
Hong says is the truth.
A unified party position is
absolutely not an evil thing.
And politics should
be predictable
and also have some
efficiency to it.
Party politics is a necessity.
It has many positive functions as well.
However, in
order for a party platform
to possess legitimacy,
it must be the product
of fierce discussions
and negotiations
among the members.
Like this time around, the top-down demand
by the party leadership to follow it
is an act that violates the
national assemblyman's independence
and autonomy guaranteed
by the Constitution.
Wow, simply so much better than some
spokesperson of the Gookmin Party.
Be quiet! The assemblymen
are talking right now!
So impertinent for an aide...
Just be still, stay still, okay?
Look here, this person is
an aide in name only. But
we are on rank-insignia-ignoring
(EQUAL) terms, okay?
- What?- If you don't want to
listen to her, just leave.
Assemblyman Jin, you are such a wimp,
using your aide as a shield...
You luckily avoided it
when you objected to
the supplementary budget
bill the last time.
But if you stand up against
the party platform
again this time, you will
be severely sanctioned.
I think there is some
sort of an error here.
Our Assemblyman is not standing
up against a party platform,
but is opposed to making
it into a party platform.
Of course.
It does not fall into
the sanctionable cause
category and even if
you sanction him,
he will promptly commence legal proceedings
including a suit to nullify such sanctions.
What?
You heard her, right? This is our
Indifferent-to-BH faction's position.
He didn't buy it one bit!
This Jin Sang Pil person
seemed like a dead mouse,
but in fact he was just
waiting for a chance.
It was my fault. All my attention
was on the Anti-BH faction
and we fell into Jin
Sang Pil's trap.
He's acting up like that
because we have only
two more seats than the
opposition parties.
Why don't we accept one person from the
independent assemblymen and kick him out?
I am just breathless with
the wish, but weren't
the majority of the
independent assemblymen
kicked out from their respective parties
for causing all sorts of scandals?
And the few who are okay are
just balancing our party
against the Korean
Democratic Party.
This is really a big problem.
If it does not become a party
platform at this rate,
there will be fire and brimstone
from the Blue House...
Secretary General, what do you
think about using broadcasting?
Broadcasting?
Yes, In Kyung.
Your old man... Can he
appear on the debate show?
Why? When was it when
you talked about
zero-level recognition
and dislikable image?
It's an item the higher-ups decided on.
That real estate policy thing.
Will he come or not?
An item from the higher-ups?
Hello. I am Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi.
The real estate market
must do its part to
give the economy momentum.
Momentum...momentum...mo-men-tum...
I think it is a tactic to make you into
a tongue-tied dummy before the people.
They will try to make you
feel small and then pursue
making the policy into a
party platform again.
But do you think I can do well?
If you want to appear, we will do
our best to prepare you for it.
But you don't need
to overtax yourself.
Because the one in the corner right now is
not us, but Secretary General Baek's side.
Let's just try it,
what the hell.
When we finally got to hit
the road, we can't hit
the brakes merely because
of this sort of thing.
Let's just drive
on and get ahead.
Yes, okay.
Aigo, loosen up a bit. Are you protesting
right now? Relax your facial muscles.
Straighten up your
shoulders like this too.
- Cool.- Da Jeong, his
face is too shiny.
Aigo, I don't need
things like this...
The most important
thing in a debate is
planting an impression
of honesty.
If your opponent asks you
an unexpected question, you
must not gloss over it or
pretend false knowledge,
but reinterpret it from
your point of view
and answer it with your own
confident logic, okay?
Confidence...
- Dong Cheol!- Yes.
They are sure to
ask this question.
Here, under LTV and DTI, write
the meanings in Korean.
Yes.
Hey, Kim Gyu Hwan!- Yes.
- You know the real estate market value
data from the Ministry of Land?- Yes.
- Prepare that quickly.-
Okay, I will.
As you, Assemblywoman
Hong, said that...
I'm not opposed to the intent
behind it, but... okay?
If the economy can be revived...
Assemblyman Jin, you look
far better from the side
of your hair parting, so
from the left side...
No, Assemblyman.
From the right side.
- Then, the economy, this thing...-
Not that, but your shoulders
turn them slightly left and tuck in
your chin and stare into the camera...
Yes, that's right.
Then, the economy... This
is weird, it's awkward.
All those poses are no go.
Yes, then...
That is, then... Refrain
from using them.
If you... look at this data...
Don't use saliva to turn pages.
- So I'm saying...- Don't
use these expressions.
It won't do. "That..."
Refrain from saying that.
Now, let's go again
from the beginning.
Thank you.
Today, just pat it down it a bit.
The other time, it was too oily.
Yes.
I didn't think you'd come, but
you are here, Assemblyman Jin.
But isn't an assemblyman someone
who goes anywhere he is called?
I consider this your
fault, Choi In Kyung.
Why so?
Because being on air is
a really scary thing.
Not just one or two
assemblymen, who got on air to
get more recognition, were
embarrassed or ruined.
But if you do well, you
win a jackpot, right?
Aish, I'm going crazy, really.
Thank you.
Please stand by, we are
about to go on air.
Aish, did this kid go to take a
dump and not find the toilet paper?
Why is he taking so long?
One-to-One Debate
Gyu Hwan, what is DTI, DTI, huh?
Yes, it's the
debt-to-income ratio.
Oh, right, right. It's here.
It means the percentage of
a borrower's annual income
that goes toward making
residential mortgage payments.
Oh, okay. Then
it's not this LTV.
That's the maximum you can borrow
when the house is used as collateral.
- Right?  - Yes.
And what is it that Aide Choi
said you absolutely must know?
That... what is the reason why
owners and landlords prefer monthly
rent more than the key money
deposit system for leasing homes?
Monthly rent more
than key money?
Prime rate... because of low prime
rates or something like that.
Yes, that's right.
What exactly is the prime rate?
Is it interest?
I think so?
Jeez. Find it already!
If I'm wrong on this,
I'll never live it down!
- Where is it?  -You're
making fools of yourselves.
Rather than interest, it's
about the interest rates.
Aide Choi, when I'm screwing up,
after you write it big
on something like a
sketchpad, show it to me.
Otherwise I'm a goner.
Assemblyman, although you
said you'd never get
scared, are you running
scared right now?
No, I'm not scared but
it's a live broadcast...
a bit... yes.
Give me the notes.
Why?
W-What... What are
you doing right now?
You're a wimp because you are going head
to head against Hong Chan Mi with this.
Forget this now,
Assemblyman, and fight with
what you have heard,
seen and felt so far.
Climb into the
four-sided ring now.
You can never beat the opponent,
relying on something else.
You can only count on yourself.
But, even so, if you
ripped everything up...
Now, ten seconds to go.
Ten seconds.
Now, then. We hope for a good
debate between the two Assemblymen.
Oh, yes.
You look very tense.
Not at all.
Cue.
Good evening, Viewers. I'm
One-to-One Debate's Hong Seung Beom.
We have brought in today
two assemblymen involved
in the current Gookmin
Party controversy
over whether a bill to facilitate
real estate transactions
should be a part of
the party's platform.
First the Gookmin
Party's spokesperson
Hong Chan Mi is joining us.
Hello, I am Assemblywoman
Hong Chan Mi.
Who is the opposition
on the issue within the
party? Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil joins us.
Ah, yes, hel—
Jin Sang Pil .. he
hit a wrong note.
Hello, I am Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil.
Then, we will reveal
the projected winner of
today's debate on the issue
as predicted by one hundred
randomly selected viewers.
JIN SANG PIL: 6
HONG CHAN MI: 94
Look at that!
Oh, this... the result
is a bit surprising.
For One-To-One Debate
the size of this disparity
is an all-time record.
The more we debate, the
less I understand.
The bill is to restore
vitality to the real estate
market, especially for
residential housing,
by streamlining
excessive control,
and I can't fathom any understandable
reason to be opposed to the bill.
Yes, that is, this... the
intent is very good, right?
But the gist is, that is, in the
end that the National Assembly
should unregulate re-development, taxes and
things like that and the government...
what... what thingamajig? That LTV
and DDT should be increased...
But, why are your
bringing up DDT here?
Are you thinking of spraying
pesticide on real estate?
Yes, I ah... DTI...
So now...
Do you really think that the
measures repealing reporting duties
for residential transactions and
easing up housing subscription
eligibility requirements as
well as sales of housing
purchase options will trigger
real estate speculation?
Yes, of course, they will. You're
proposing to unregulate everything.
If we control the real estate-related
taxes including the purchase,
recording and transfer taxes
with an equalization rates chart
and curb the demand
I think we can prevent
overheating of the market.
Yes, an equalization chart?
Yes, so, according
to my research,
this... equalization chart
must be controlled,
but how much should it be
controlled, that is...
Why don't you own up?
About what?
That you don't know the contents
of this bill very well.
What do you mean not know well?
Why wouldn't I know it well? It
is because you keep butting in
when I'm talking and
keep blabbing with
difficult terminology,
that is why I keep...
Emcee, check Assembly
Jin's words.
Um, Assemblyman, I would
appreciate it if you refrain
from using crude words
during the broadcasting.
Oh, yes, did I? I am sorry.
That is an item that
we went over together.
It's because he keeps
answering her questions.
He has to assail her
with questions.
At any rate, how much Assemblyman Jin
knows about this issue to oppose it...
I believe the viewers are making
a good assessment of that.
After all is said and done, do you
think a debate was too much for him?
No, it's not time to
get discouraged yet.
Assemblyman, if you have
no further response,
maybe we can move on
to the next topic...
Yes, about this, I
did not come as well prepared
as Assemblywoman Hong.
Because I don't know very well.
In fact, I didn't study enough.
I was studying
even just now, but
I am sorry about that. Even the notes
I had, my aide tore them apart.
Yes, I do not know very well. But about
this one thing, I am positively sure.
What is it?
Lately, there is this
youngster that I am fond of.
That fellow receives a monthly
salary of barely $1000
and used to pay $400 for a
hole of a room in a goshiwon.
Let's say this bill gets passed
and revitalizes the
real estate market.
To that fellow, there
is nothing beneficial.
And there is no hope for him.
Nowdays, these friends
are called the Chilpo
generation for the seven
objects they give up.
Courtship, marriage, childbirth,
personal relationships,
home ownership, and
along with that
dreams and even hope
have all been given up.
(CHIL=7; PO = BEGINNING
SYLLABLE FOR GIVE UP)
Assemblyman Jin, this is outside
the scope of this debate.
This occasion is to debate the ways to
revitalize real estate transactions...
Why, why is this outside
the scope of the debate?
I am speaking up about the reason
why I am opposing this bill.
As for me, I never told you
not to introduce this bill.
If necessary, go ahead and introduce
it, even right this moment. But,
just don't say that I have to, I
must be forced to sign off on it.
I hate that idea
to death, really.
I won't do it, even
if you kill me.
The bill that I, I really...
really want to support is
not a bill that facilitates
purchases and sales of
houses costing hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
As for me, those youths with their
whole lives to live ahead of them,
when they work themselves
to the bone and later
when they grow old and somehow own even
a small house, at least that one thing!
That they can have a dream
of buying it at least,
that they can have that hope...
I want to put my seal of
approval to that kind of bill!
Right now, you are uttering
slyly loaded words.
But the intent behind
facilitating real estate
transactions is to
revive the market and
in the end to
revive the economy.
The economy has to be
revived for the younger
generation to grow dreams
and hope, isn't that so?
Right, yes, the economy has
to be revived, of course.
Yes, the economy has to be revived.
I have heard those words
since I was a wee little lad
until they stuck in my ear!
The words I've heard are
revive the economy.
But when will it come
alive, the economy!?
Everyday you say let's revive it, but
when will it come back to life!?
But still, still
we must revive it.
Yes, we must try to revive it.
But that is work cut out
for Assemblywoman Hong
here, who is all that.
- What?- As for me,
people who, like me,
cannot even dream of
borrowing money because
of their poor credit,
okay?
Because the key moneys are
rising more than the pay raise,
people who keep looking for
housing in the outskirts.
The only possession
is just their house,
so people who have no thought
whatever of selling and buying it!
I will just...
yes, I will just
help those people.
Satisfied?
Yes, Assemblywoman,
are you satisfied?
Let's move on to...
the next topic.
Okay.
The next topic is related
to redevelopment.
Apartment complexes or villas
of 20-30 years of age...
Now then, we will look
into the final evaluation
of the viewers who have
tuned into today's debate.
Please show us the result.
JIN SANG PIL 53 :
Hong Chan Mi 47
Yes. The results are out.
By 53 to 47... Manse!
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil has
come from behind to win it.
There was the biggest pre-
and post- change of votes
in the history of the
One-to-One Debate show.
But I think maybe Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
moved the hearts of the viewers a bit more.
Thank you very much for taking time out of
your busy schedules, Assemblywoman and man.
Hong Seung Beon's One-to-One
Debate will say good-night here.
Thank you, Viewers.
No, but if that... that
happens, isn't the party
platform thing completely
out of the question now?
Yes, Assemblyman Park.
Let's quit putting it
on the party platform.
That's as much help as
you're getting from us so
cancel the party audit
of the chapters.
If you go ahead with it,
then there will be a real war.
You've worked hard.
At any rate... yes, good job.
Good job, Assemblywoman.
Sang Pil!
Aigoo, why are you doing this
again, making my flesh crawl...
Let me go please.
You did well, well!
All right, all right.
How was I? Was I okay?
Of course, WHOSE assemblyman
are you, after all?
But, how can you talk about me all
you want, without my permission?
Hey, are you the only kid
living in a goshiwon hole?
Then, don't go around saying that
person is me. I'll be embarrassed.
What, punk?
Let's go. I'm famished.
I will buy you something yummy.
- Really?- Yes.
- Huh? So unlike
you...- Let's go eat.
Really? I got it.
You'd better leave for today.
The VIP does not
want to see you.
Please relay to him that I
will contact him again.
Secretary General.
Do better.
How can someone like
you, Secretary General
Baek, not handle Jin Sang
Pil, that one person?
Chief Secretary...
I think you've become a bit flippant,
assisting the Elder from his side.
In the future, please refrain from
speaking to me in an imperative tone.
Secretary General.
There is only one person in Korea
who can speak to me that way.
The Elder is the only one.
Do you understand?
Please pass this on to the Elder.
Without fail I'm going to get Jin Sang Pil.
Teach you how to draw up a bill?
- Yes.- What winds of
change blew on you?
That's not in your character.
I am thinking of changing my character.
Drawing up a bill is just
a matter of technicality,
the true issue is the item.
What is it? Tell me.
First, teach me the steps.
When it's completed, I
will show it to you then.
Why are you looking like that?
Because I'm a bit proud of you.
Aigoo, our Kim Gyu Hwan
has all grown up and...
Don't do this. I'm not a kid, okay?
I'll gather up all the information
you need. So just escort
the Assemblyman to make a
round in the constituency.
Okay.
But, really, can't you
not treat me like a kid?
But a thirty-year-old is a
kid, seriously, really!
Then we will introduce
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Organization of a Gathering of Gyeongje
Citizens Who Support Jin Sang Pil
Aigoo, really, I...
Because of you, I really
feel energized.
Aigoo, really, a gathering of Gyeongje
citizens who support Jin Sang Pil...
Who came up with the name?
You did a good job.
Yes, I really will work very hard.
I will really not let you down
and do my best in the future.
Even though there are not many of us now,
one will grow into ten and ten will
grow into a hundred, isn't that so?
Cheer up, Assemblyman!
Yes, cheer up!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Hey there, excuse me for asking.
Yes. Go ahead.
You're Bae Gyu Hwan, right?
- Who are you?  - Don't you know me?
Room 3, 6th grade, Kim Jeong Im.
You and I were even partners.
I wasn't sure because
of the glasses, but...
You are mistaken.
But, isn't it Bae Gyu Hwan?
Bae Gyu Hwan?
No, I'm not.
I'm right. Isn't it?
Yes, the Jin Ji Mo (SUPPORT JIN GATHERING)
meeting went off without a hitch.
I had such a tough time
holding back the tears.
Don't forget that feeling from today.
- I'm going to grow the Jin Ji Mo
on a national scale, okay?- Okay.
If Secretary Kim is next
to you, tell him to
hurry and send the pictures
to Secretary Song.
Huh? Secretary Kim went to Busan.
Why to Busan?
Is he someone who would answer if
you asked him? Brushing you off...
Hang up because I have to eat.
- But Sang Pil,- Huh?
You are walking down a street
and say hi to someone
you recognized as Kim
Cheol Soo, but if that
guy is not Kim Cheol Soo
but Bae Cheol Soo, isn't
that a bit suspicious?
What are you talking about?
I mean, earlier at the Jin Ji Mo,
some woman asked Secretary Kim
whether he wasn't Bae Gyu Hwan and
Secretary Kim said no and left.
But Secretary Kim is Kim Gyu Hwan.
- Is that right?- Isn't that strange?
Did he change his family name in midstream?
You're curious about so many things.
After eating,
a bit later stay in a sauna or something.
- Why, you have business
to attend to?- Yes.
You took off a day to go somewhere a while
ago and why are you in Busan today?
Is there a problem with your family?
No, not a problem, but...
I'm visiting my father for a while
because today is his birthday.
Is that so? Okay. Be a very
loving son before coming back.
Yes. See you tomorrow.
Bae Dal Soo
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Preview
We must confirm the newly
appointed prime minister.
The approval rates for
the party will plummet.
At this rate, how can we win
in the next year's election?
I will try to catch Jin Sang Pil.
I am sorry.
I never knew I would some day witness a
filibuster that I had only heard about.
By now, Baek Do Hyeon's butt hole must
feel like it's sitting on a burning fuse.
This is tyranny of the minority
masquerading as a lawful act.
Is this really politics for
the sake of the people?
You should have been prepared at least
for that. How are you doing your jobs?