All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama are
fictitious creations .
Episode 4
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
D E M O C R A...
DEMOCRACY
Democracy
Society
Theory of Modern Politics
Leadership Oh, Ae Ri...
Your expression is so grim
from the first day at work.
-Hello.-People would think
you're going into a battle.
Do you have an overreacting
personality to begin with?
You know I am a serious person.
I wasn't overreacting but
making a firm resolution.
That is overreacting.
Resolution is for a person
in a responsible position.
And alertness is
reserved for the staff.
Future overreacting is
prohibited, understand?
Yes.
Good morning, Aide Choi.
How refreshing...
Hello.
Get in, what are you doing?
Oh, you came all
spruced up today.
When did you come in?
Oh, you are here?
Since there are eyes in the
Assemblyman Center,I think
it best to refrain from
sleeping in the office.
We have to save at
least the motel
fees.There are so many
expenses to be paid.
Did you stay up all night?
Well, I think so, but
I don't know what I did at all.
It's not something you
can learn by cramming.
Society. Culture
-Take it easy.-Then,
I'm a thief.
What?
Are the people paying
me to study?They're
paying me to hurry
up and do something.
That should be right.
Continue, then, your cramming.
What is she saying?
Eh, also, a secretary
does not have a mouth.
And what does this mean?
In the future, both of you
cannot go outside and
spout without permission
what you've seen and
heard in the office, OK?
-Yes.-Yes.
This is not some National
Intelligence Service...
He means watch your tongues.
There weren't just one or
two assemblymen who had
suffered because of their
tongue-wagging staff.
There were even assemblymen who
had lost their heads (SEATS).
Politicians are people who walk
the fine line of the prison wall.
Keep in mind that the aide
staff, on that dangerous path,
are guides who lead the
assemblyman to the right path.
Yes.
Gyu Hwan, why aren't
you answering?
Yes, I will keep that in mind.
Okay, then start the day.
I will work hard.
Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan... seems
like a bit gloomy person.
Father, watch me...
Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan, let's work
well together in the future.
Let's work hard.
I am totally disappointed
in you, CEO.
-Why?-Didn't you say you would put
on the (ASSEMBLY) badge later?
You said politicians survive
not on food but on pride.
And you become Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil's aide?
Someone slid into the
nomination because of you!
Don't nag me but just answer.Are you
going to come to our office or not?
Our office?Are you
nice or spineless?
Don't rub it in and just
give me a quick answer.
Why will I go there? Under an assemblyman
who is not even like an assemblyman,
it's clear that I will just work like a
dog and after a year become unemployed.
Hey, Song So Min!
Aide!
Oh, what brings you here?
Aide Seo asked us to buy
some office supplies.
Gyu Hwan, hello.
Yes, how are you?
But are you working for
the National Assembly?
Yes, I have ended up working in
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's office.
Oh, by the way, Aide Choi. Thank you for
that compilation of interview questions.
What do you mean a compilation?
You know what So Min
gave me before.
She said you ordered
her to do it.
Oh, why bring up what's past.You
have such a meticulous personality.
Go on and continue
with your business.
Aren't you going to work? Go!
Such undisciplined newbies...
Did you use me to hit on him?
I have a personal
taste too, you know!
I was just considerate toward
him because it's commendable
that a young person tries
so hard to make it.
-Recite it.-What?
You told me to
take charge of the
promotion.Recite a list
of the papers you need.
Oh really...
Go in please.
Gookmin Party General Meeting
for Emergency Policies
What did you say this now is?
That is, it is a Gookmin Party's general
meeting to discuss emergency policies.
So, exactly, what is this about?
Oh, that is, as I was saying...
It's a neighborhood meeting...
amongst assemblymen.
This is the first time we're meeting
each other face to face, right?
Oh, yes, I am Jin Sang Pil.
I'm Park Choon Seob.
Let's eat together some time.
Ah, yes, a meal.
How is our economy right now?
The citizens have
closed their walletsand
businesses are not
making investments.
Then, shouldn't at least the government
pump in money and stimulate the economy?
We have to come up with an
immediate modified budget
and increase
government spending!
Here! Here!
The government came up with a
modified budget a long time ago.
So why hasn't it submitted it
to the National Assembly yet?
Is it because they are afraid
of the opposition parties?
It's because they are scared
of the Anti-BH faction.
When it comes to stimulating
the economy, where
are the differences between
the Pro- and Anti-BH?
This assemblyman will give
firm support this time.
So, the government better submit the
modified budget to the Assembly right now!
That is all.
He is making a display to get some of
the budget money for his constituency.
Hello.
Secretary General, look where
Assemblyman Jin sat down.
It's nice to see.
Now, if there is no other
assemblyman who wants to speak,
I am about to
dismiss everyone...
Just a minute, moderator.
Yes, Assemblyman Park.
Isn't this Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's first general meeting?
Let's welcome him and
hear his greeting words.
It's okay with me
if I don't speak.
Oh, I didn't think about that.
Assemblyman Jin!
Ah, yes... Please come out.
I didn't need to speak up.
Then...
Is aiding him bearable?
The rumor is that he is
such a trouble maker.
He's a good person.The problem
is that he is incompetent.
Hello, I am Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil.
-Assemblyman Jin?-Yes?
Since the session will start
soon, please hurry up.
Oh, yes...
But what do I say now?
Oh, well, things like your
resolve or determination
regarding participation in
the legislative activities.
Just a brief comment would do.
Oh, determination... briefly...
Yes, to the best
of my abilities,
fight!!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil Expression of
OPINIONUNEXPECTED EXPLOSION: FIGHT!!
If a similar occasion arises again in
the future,you can say it like this.
I will put the party before all
personal interests and work hard.
I beg a lot of guidance
and instructionsfrom
senior and fellow assemblymen.
Yes, that party
first me second...
But, what they were yelling
about at the general meeting...
Modified budget?
What is that exactly?
Pursuant to the National Financing
Act, in the event a war, natural
disaster or great depression occurs
or is in danger of occurring...
in order to respond, the
government, in addition
to the already approved
national budget,
sets a modified budget.
Wow, you're a computer.
Wow, then, that modified budget,
that thing is a very
good thing, right?
There are many adverse
effects as well.
Especially at times of serious
tax revenue decrease like now,
a fiscal deficit through issuance
of government bonds is unavoidable.
This leads to an increase in the national
debtand worsens the financial health.
Yes, so, this has
nothing to do with me.
Depending on which standing
committee you're assigned to,
it may have something
to do with you.
Oh, I've heard that word
earlier, standing committee...
Which one?
Strategy and something...
Oh, Strategy and
Finance Committee!
SFC?
But that is a major league...
What?
We'd like Assemblyman Jin's
standing committee to be changed.
Sunbae-nim, please put in a
good word to the floor leader.
Why? It's a major
standing committeethat
everyone else is just
antsy to get in.
The SFC is too much
for Assemblyman Jin.
How come?
It's a committee where they deal
with the national budget of
trillions, all sorts of pension
funds, taxes and monetary policies.
Even economic experts
have hard times.
Do you think Assemblyman
Jin can even understand?
Probably... that's why
they sent him to the SFC.
What?
If he doesn't understand, then he
has no choice but to stay quiet.
Then he won't get
himself into trouble.
Just accept it.
For Assemblyman Jin, too,
that must be the best thing.
How about the best thing for me?
What should I do with an assemblyman
whose lips are glued together.
Must you... do something?
What?
No one in Yeouido expects Assemblyman
Jin to accomplish anything.
As I have told you
here, In Kyung, you
just have to help Assemblyman Jin
to smoothly adapt to the Assembly.
After massively messing up the
national economy for the first half,
are you saying Deputy
Prime Minister and
Minister of the Ministry
of Strategy and Finance
won't utter a word of
apology to the people?
Because, as I have repeatedly
told you, I cannot agree to
- your expression of messing up...-
Look here, Deputy Prime Minister!!
Don't you even look at the
basic economic indices?
Everything is 0%.
They are somewhat lacking but...
You didn't mess up, but
just a bit lacking?
What I am saying is...
there is a need to look
at the overall picture.
What are you going to do about the second
half?Things are not looking up, right?
The government is devising measures
to stimulate the economy, but...
in the face of continuing
difficulties, we...
The speaker asks
you not to doze.
are very much concerned.
What use is being concerned,
you should be working!
I sympathize with
what you're saying...
You just spoke of a broad policy
strengthening the finances.
You will set a modified
budget, right?
Yes, including an
additional budget,
we are in the middle of
considering various measures.
Don't set a modified budget.
Just from the first half,
there was a massive amount of
shortage in tax revenues.
When the state
coffers are empty,
this kind of suggestion
to create a debtto
increase spending
is irresponsible.
Come out.
In my judgment,
- What did you say?
- Please go out.
-Come out.-... the dangerous
threshold has been long crossed.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
I guess you left things like know-hows and
flexibility back in your constituency.
What?
If you're so sleepy, why
don't you take some
time outside rather
than sitting it out?
You know the people dislike the
politiciansleaving their seats empty.
The room was almost
empty as it was.
And there are people who
like dozing (ON THE JOB)?
I could understand the
political questions a little
bit, but when the economic
issues were brought up,
it was like a foreign
language to me.
How are you going to participate
in the SFC like that?
Ah, that's what I'm saying.
I'm in big trouble.
-Assemblyman Jin.-Yes?
I know a very good policy aide.
Shall I recommend you to him?
Oh, really?
You're telling me to move to
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's Office?
Since Assemblyman Jin
okayed it, please do so.
I do have... reasons.
Right, I know you've
worked hard all this time,
but connections from the assembly
are not lifelong anyway.
Go to Assemblyman Jin
and assist him well.
Assemblywoman...
Why are you like this,
making me feel sorry?
Am I kicking you out to
the streets just now?
It's just that I'm thankful.
Thank you, Assemblywoman.
Wow, really, thank you!
Thank you.
Aide Seo, just a moment!
Have you, by any chance, heard
about me moving into there?
Oh, I just heard
from the old man.
Wow, a jackpot event!
Oh, I thought Madame
Hong had lied again.
Oh, Dear Lord, I thank thee!
Hallelujah!
Oh, Lord!
I'm going to remove
my stuff right away.
Oh, hey, punk! Stay put!
The atmosphere is not
like that right now.
Why not?
Secretary Shim Dong Cheon
is not acceptable.
Why not?
He has no experience with the SFC
andhis work ethics are problematic.
But he has an impressive resume and also,
supposedly, outstanding abilities.
Assemblywoman Hong would not give
up help with outstanding abilities.
I don't know, the bus
has left already.I've
already promised
Assemblywoman Hong.
Buy her a meal and cancel it.
So frustrating really...
As an assemblyman,
how can I break a promise
that I've already made?
It's not a promise but you've
been taken for a ride!
-Well, let's just
go with it.-No way!
Ah, you're really
being too much!
No matter who comes, he
will be better than me.
That's why we cannot
use just anybody.
Would I do this with
another assemblyman?
Well, that is the truth. You must
be acting like thisbecause it's me.
I am sorry. It was a
slip of the tongue.
Aigoo, no, that's okay.
What verbal mistake...
Assemblyman!
Secretary Sim... what is your
reason for rejecting him?
Because he is not a suitable secretary
advising on the SFC policies.
He is going to ignore the courtesy
of a colleague like that?
I know that you are going to run from
your hometown district next year.
And that you intend to
let secretary Sim go
to replace him with a person
to work on that district.
So, an aide is commenting about
what the Assemblymen decided?
You are very
impertinent, aren't you?
-Assemblywoman Hong. -Do I
still look like the person
who was under you in the
Presidential election
running around campaigning?
You should talk only
about Secretary Sim.
He is not my secretary anymore.
Whether Assemblyman Jin takes
him or not, let him decide.
With all due respect,
may I say something?
As much as you want.
If you are a lawmaker,
please act like one.
That's similar to what I
wanted to say to you.
If you are an aide,
then act like an aide.
Don't take an assemblyman who knows nothing
and play Princess Pyonggang (famous
historic figure who turned her "idiotic"
husband into a great general) with him.
Leave.
Asssemblywoman Hong Chan Mi
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
Let's take in Dong Cheun. He's been
intimidated by Hong Chan Mi so much but
originally, he was a
smart working fellow.
He also likes to be treated
by government agencies.
Without that kind of fun,
what would we, ephemeral
workers, live for? Even if
it's only to save my face,
please bend your stubbornness.
At that rate, that kid
will end up like a forlorn
duck egg by the Nakdong River.
Tell him to move his belongings.
Oh, thank you.
Oh right...
I am saying this for your sake.
With your skills, I don't know
how long you'll stay here but
while you are here,
don't overdo things.
What are you saying?
About our old man, no matter
how hard we aides try,
there are assemblymen who
simply cannot make it.
Aide Seo.
Don't make people around you pointlessly
suffer as well, but roughly
just kill time and leave.
I'm Sim Dong Cheon.
I'm Kim Gyu Hwan. Let's
work well together.
I can speak informally right?
Oh, yes of course.
I wasn't like that when
I was an intern but...
Excuse me?
Over there.
Oh yes.
That's it.
Ms. Park Da Jeong?
Yes?
One cup of green tea. Iced.
Yes.
Thank you.
Oh, Sunbae. My place is there.
Must you... do something? There is
no one who expects Assemblyman Jin
to accomplish anything
here in Yeouido.
If you become an Assemblyman
who is applauded by people,
then, I'll come down.
Yes, what is it?
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
What's this?2015
Supplementary Budget Bill
Assemblyman, hello.
Who are you?
I am a senior vice minister of the Ministry
of Strategy and Finance, Oh Yeong Ha.
Oh...
-I am the budget department head.-I
am the tax department head.
Oh, yes.
The government has
submitted a supplementary
budget bill to the
National Assembly.
Regarding the supplementary
budget bill of about $15 billion
that the government has
submitted, the National Assembly
plans to convene the appropriate standing
committee and start a review next week.
However, the opposition parties including
the Korea Democratic Party are opposing
it as a pork barrel bill created with
an eye to next year's general election.
It will face substantial obstacles
before passage. Next on the news...
Even this year, if we
don't reach the economic
growth that we promised
in the election,
the public sentiment will
totally turn against us.
We can't let that happen.
I'll relay the VIP's
instructions.
In regards to the
supplementary budget,
no matter what, he says to make
it pass by end of this month.
What do I owe this honor
to, Assemblyman Park?
I thought I wanted to have
a cup of tea with you.
Can you make time?
This time, too, the review
of the supplemetary
budget bill will
not go smoothly.
The opposition parties
are expected to home in
and latch on to the issue
of government bonds.
Isn't that their favorite card
to play in every review of
a supplementary budget bill?
Government bonds are debts.
The national debt
should not increase.
At any rate, government bond
issuance is the business
of the SFC (STRATEGY &AMP;
FINANCE STANDING COMMITTEE).
Our Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho, who is the
head of the SFC, will have many headaches.
Assemblyman Kang's words at the
general executive meeting,
to support it irrespective
of different factions...
I am very appreciative of them.
Give and take...
Politics is not about
paying empty lip service.
There is some money within
the supplementary budget
earmarked for SOC (SOCIAL
OVERHEAD CAPITAL) works.
I will talk to the Budget
Committee chairman and,
for your and Assemblyman
Kang's constituencies,
pay extra attention.
Look here, Secretary General Baek.
I am not called
the acting head of the
Anti-BH faction for nothing.
You cannot, by any chance,
mean to look after all
the assemblymen in the
Anti-BH faction, right?
Please pay more attention to the
(ANTI-BH) assemblymen from...
less developed areas and constituencies
with strong pro-opposition tendencies.
To care for all those people,
the budget has to be enlarged.
It should be enlarged,
if necessary.
Being in politics,
I've seen the budget
stretched like a rubber
band numerous times.
- Assemblyman Park!- We,
the Anti-BH faction...
Aren't we the people pushed
to the bottom rung of the
party for having gotten
behind the wrong candidate?
Please let us at least
get a little money to
go back and be praised
by our constituents.
An increase is difficult. The extra budget
does not come from already collected taxes.
Isn't the country
incurring new debt?
Debts or whatever...
in the end, that money goes round and round
and ends up in the citizens' pockets.
Since we are doing it,
let's do it boldly.
So we can help you boldly too.
He says to pass the supplementary budget
by end of this month no matter what.
If you have an excellent
idea, I want to hear it.
Tell a pro-BH assemblyman
sitting on the SFC
to call for an increase
in the budget.
If he just sends the signal, Assemblyman
Kang Sang Ho will take care of the rest.
At a time of close scrutiny from
the opposition parties and media,
would there be an assemblyman with such
steely nerves to make that kind of call?
People with nerves of steel
are not the only brave ones.
Because of a change in the plan
to sell bonds we're in a bit of a
difficult position to secure the
budget size we had planned originally.
If you look at this diagram, the
2014 budget and 2015 one...
are shown like this. Please
look over this closely...
and if you also look at...
The ignorant also
tend to be brave.
Bottom line, this is very
popular, here too.Expenditure...
I'm going to get
cramps in my brain.
Hey!
Where did everyone go?
Send an information request first
to the SFC and its organizations.
They are really bad about
giving information...
-Kim Gyu Hwan, support
policy and when Secretary
Byeon is not available,
escort the Assemblyman.-OK.
I told you to print out the materials
before the meeting.Where are they?
Let's get a move on.
Here, this is...
What does this mean?
Have you seen the vice minister
going home totally drained?
Of course he'd be drained.
He had to lecture to a person who does
not even understand for over an hour.
Was that a lecture and not
chanting a mantra to a cow's ears?
For a man like him... what does he
mean by playing an assemblyman...
This is why the
Assembly gets reviled.
Hey Jin Sang Pil,
You, don't be a scaredy-cat, huh?
Understand?
I said don't be scared, punk!
Why are you scared?
I called you just in case that
something might be said of this.
Did the Assemblyman
cause any trouble?
It's not that.
It's just that over there.
I see that the voltage was too high.
You're an an amateur at welding, right?
Well I...
Next time when you
do this, call me.
I'll give you my phone number.
Okay, Assemblyman.
Why don't you take him now?
No, just let him be.
I'm sorry for being late.
I am Song So Min...
It's as cheap as it gets...
Office manager, are
you kidding me?
When did I ask for the information
for you to be still getting it?
I think this is the
perfect place to hang it.
What event was that?
-You call this congratulatory
message?-I'll rewrite it.
Can it be done?
Hello?
Who do you think you are?
What time do you think it is?!
I'm sorry. There
was a traffic jam.
From the first day...
Why is this so difficult? About
the world surplus money...
Hello, Assemblyman! I'm a 6th-grade
secretary, Song So Min...
This world surplus money...
where did you say it is used?
Just a moment... Yes, then...
This is perfect. Can
I nail it here?
If I raise it any higher,
it'll be hard to nail...
Secretary Song will open
your blog and SNS accounts.
Now, I think you
would need this...
Wow, you shouldn't have...Your
circumstances are not that great...
Ah, you must have done this because of
that slip of the tongue you made at me.
I purchased it with the
office expense money.
When my phone is perfectly
fine, why would you
use the office money to
buy something like this?
Hello? Hello?
Chief Secretary Lim Gyu Tae is here from
the Party Secretary General's Office.
This is an important favor the
Secretary General is asking for.
What is this?
It's a bill to expand
the government bond
issue to fund an increase
in the SOC budget.
Social Overhead Capital -
money to support indirexctly
industry through roads,
ports, power, etc.
and to support health,
education, research and culture
Chief Secretary Lim, are you...
asking Assemblyman Jin
to make this proposal?
To boost the economy, we have to expand SOC
projects which maximize short term effects.
This will be a big help to create jobs
and to increase the national income.
Ah, the people's income...
Chief Secretary, just a moment.
- What?- That proposal
is too dangerous.
If things go wrong,
Assemblyman Jin will be
bombarded by the opposition
parties and media.
Just pretend ignorance. The Anti-BH faction
demanded this from the Secretary General.
Are you calling the Secretary
General right now?
- What are you doing?- I should ask
you what you are doing, Aide Choi.
Aide Choi, weren't you on
Secretary General's side?
Why are you playing the part
of Jin Sang Pil's right arm?
What? Look here,
Chief Secretary Lim!
Do me a favor and be loyal
just to one person.
Million, billion, trillion, quadrillion...
It's quadrillions we're talking about...
The Importance of SOC (SOCIAL
OVERHEAD CAPITAL) projects
Come in.
Assemblyman, I have finished
drafting the questionnaire.
Oh really? Thank you.
I prepared it using all my care and 19
years' experience as an assembly officer.
I don't know if
you will like it.
Oh~(Questionnaire re:
Supplementary Budget
Bill (MINISTRY OF
STRATEGY AND FINANCE)
It's easy to understand.Cut SOC
Funds to Establish Balanced Budget
Very good work.
Wow, it just stands out...Is
it because of my mood?
Aigoo, Aide-nim...
- You said you were Officer
Park, right?- Yes, Aide-nim.
Here you go, the questionnaire.
Aigoo, thank you, Aide-nim.
Well then.
Goodbye.
Hey,
is it okay if I go to
Gyeongjae City for a bit?
Why, did something happen?
Ae Ri closed her coffee shop.
- Why?- What do you
mean why?It went
belly up because
of slow business.
She's not answering my calls, so
I want to go see her personally.
While I'm there, I will go see if our
local office is running properly as well.
Okay.
What's that?
It's a questionnaire
Aide Seo prepared for me
Questionnaire?
Why?
Well, earlier, Aide Seo
was secretly passing
something to a
ministry official...
He called it a
questionnaire as well.
Pass what?
What's up with this mood?
Customary practice!
What does that mean?
Assemblyman, I am
telling you the truth.
But that means the Minister already knows
what I'm going to ask him at the meeting.
How can that bullsh*tty thing
be customary practice!
It is customary, Assemblyman.
- What?- Strictly speaking,
it is a custom tacitly practiced between
government agencies and legislative aides.
Then, are you saying Aide
Seo did the right thing?
It is definitely not
a right thing, but
I am telling you that Aide Seo
did not do it for some kickback.
Assemblyman, I only hoped that
your proposal would go smoothly...
Why! Because you thought I would not
be able to even read this properly?
- No!- Did I make
you that nervous?
Huh? Do I seem so laughable?
I feel ashamed, Assemblyman.
Assemblyman... You can go.
We are sorry. We will make sure
that this never happens again.
I have something to ask
you too, Aide Choi.
Go ahead.
Do you know what
Aide Seo wrote here?
In order to secure financial
health or something,
he says the size of the extra
budget has to be reduced.
But
The proposal Secretary General
Baek sent for me to read...
It's the exact opposite.
No matter how dumb I am,
I've seen and heard things.
Secretary General Baek's, this
one, is problematical, right?
It's just that they are perceiving
the situation differently.
You cannot say that it is...
problematical.
Neither has a problem?
- That is right.- Then,
which one should I read?
Aide Seo's or Secretary
General Baek's?
I'm asking you which one!
I will read the one you tell me to.
Because I trust you.
Tell me frankly. Which
one shall it be?
If I were you...
I would read Secretary
General Baek's.
You mean it?
Yes.
I will be outside.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
I am sorry.
I should have consulted
with you first.
Assemblyman...
I am going to use this tomorrow,
so please send it to the SFC.
Everyone, go home.
Kim Gyu Hwan, aren't you going
to escort him?Get ready quickly.
Oh, yes, okay.
Just a minute.
Proposal to Boost Economy through Increase
of Government Subsidies for SOC Projects
(SUGGESTING INCREASE IN
GOVERNMENT BOND ISSUE SCOPE)
But who wrote this proposal?
What are you doing?
I will escort you during
Secretary Byeon's absence.
Didn't you come to the Assembly to
learn rather than to drive? It's okay.
Why are you like this again?Are you
going to do some martial arts again?
I will drive.
- Please allow me.- Why do
you work so aggressively?
When you are going
to get fired anyway.
Do it, then.
Ms. Choi In Kyung told me you passed all
the way to the police job interview.
Yes.
So, why? Why didn't you
hang in there to the end?
I have something that I
want to do in the Assembly.
What thing do you want to do?
- What, be an
assemblyman?- No.
I want to be the chief of staff
trusted by an assemblyman.
Then, are you going to keep
living separately from Sang Pil?
Since he became an assemblyman,
somehow he feels like a different person
and my heart goes out to him even less.
Your husband even made it big.
Just live with him!
What fallback do you have
to play so hard to get?
- My beauty?- What
is this girl saying?
- Unni, you know once I was
the hottest babe in the
KSR Accounting Department.-
That's right, I guess?
By the way, what are you
going to do in the future?
I don't know...
All my savings are gone.
How is working in a restaurant?
Is it doable?
I'm bearing it and
working for Joo Hee, but
- I think it will be hard for someone
with your temperament.- I know, right?
Why did I retire early? I
should have been brazen faced
and sat out my career
flicking abacus beads.
I'm saying this sincerely.
Unni,
what do you think about getting
it on with Oppa Seong Gi?
- What the hell are you
saying right now?-
All his kids are grown
up and on their own.
And Oppa Seong Gi was such a loving
husbandwhile his wife was alive.
I should just...! Do
you want to die?!
- If you don't want to, don't.
Why shout?- This wench...
Go and get some rest. I will be
there as soon as I'm done here.
- Okay.- Be safe
on your way.
Department head Oh!
Sang Pil...
You're asking me to
be your secretary?
It is not just a secretary, but
an administrative secretary...
It's a job that manages
schedules and political funds.
My aide tells me that I should
use a trustworthy person.
Are you giving me alms because
I've become a beggar?
What do you mean alms giving?
I am asking you for a favor.
You even worked as the head of
KSR's accounting department.
Sang Pil,
I guess you took me
for a mighty lowlife.
But I, even if I
starve to death,
can't be a secretary to
a person who put on the
badge after stabbing his
friends in the back.
Department Head Oh...
Please help me.
I will do good.
How will you do good?
Do you have education
or are you rich?
At the most...
you'll be a lackey to
the high and mighty.
- Department Head Oh, I...-
Stop building an air castle
and mind your own family.
What politics when you can't even
cover your own ass.Forget it.
Department Head Oh...
Department Head Oh!
Aide Choi, weren't you on
Secretary General's side?
Why are you playing the part
of Jin Sang Pil's right hand?
Be loyal to just one person.
Which one should I read?
I will read the one you tell me to.
Because I trust you.
Why is this open?
Didn't you go home yet?
The questionnaire that General
Secretary Baek sent...
Are you really going to
interrogate tomorrow?
I told you I would do.
- Why? - Pardon?
That you will get into
trouble If you interrogate,
have you already guessed.
Whether I get into
trouble or not,
when you told me to do,
there must be a
reasonable reason.
Of course, there is a reason.
I am close to General
Secretary Baek.
That's why, no matter what,
I have to stand by General Secretary
Baek's side. Don't you know that?
Am I a fool that I
don't know that?
Why are you going to
do if you know that?
Would you like to
eat this together?
Would you like to eat together?
This chicken tastes
good with much flavor.
Answer me. Why are you going
to do if you know that?
- Why are you asking? You are
scary.-Don't fool around with me.
Hurry and answer me!
Whether you are close to
General Secretary Baek or not,
I trust you unconditionally.
Do you think that makes sense?
Yes. For me, it makes sense. I
will trust you no matter what.
Why? Why do you have to
believe me unconditionally?
You really have a
lot of questions.
Let's eat chickens.
Here.
Don't you want to eat?
No one can make me a
proper assemblyman,
except you.
If I don't trust you,
whom will I trust?
If you are not here, I
can't be an assemblyman.
Assemblyman Jin.
Why, again?
Let's re-write the
questionnaire.
- Pass me.-Yes.
2015 Supplementary Budget Bill
Everyone, pay attention.
To one of assemblymen at
Strategy and Finance Committee,
ask him to insist on
increasing the budget.
would there be an assemblyman with such
steely nerves to make that kind of call?
People with nerves of steel
are not the only brave ones.
Ignorant ones also
tend to be brave.
Since it constitutes a quorum,
in the 345th Special session,
The first Strategy and Finance
Committee meeting will be opened.
Concerning the finance
ministry's agenda, paragraph 1.
The first supplementary budget bill in
2015 will be presented for discussion.
First, Deputy Prime Minister and Minister
of Strategy and Finance, Woo Tae Hyun,
please come out and
explain the bill.
Respectable SFC Chairman
Kang Sang Ho and Committee,
Chairman! I have a
proceedings comment.
Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu, let's hear
the explanation of the bill first...
The explanation of the bill
is not important right now.
Go ahead.
I have examined the supplementary
budget bills several times but
I have never seen such an
insincere bill like this.
It is said the amount
of $ 15 billion of the
budget will be funded by
issuing government bonds,
Where is such an irresponsible
attitude like this?
Assemblyman Jo, let's talk about it
at the general discussion meeting.
Even though we have to
examine, from Deputy Prime
Minister, who is in charge
of this poor and hasty bill,
we should hear an expression
of his regrets first.
Skip that part. I
don't have much time.
What are you saying now?
The public are watching us.
-The fighting cock wouldn't
let it go without a fight...
What on earth did Deputy
Prime Minister do wrong?
Did Assembly Jo act like
that in his school?
Then, what did you do well?
You are going too far!
Deputy Prime Minister! What are you doing?
Hurry and express your regrets!
From now on, we will start the
discussion of alternatives.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Phi,
ask questions first.
Deputy Prime Minister
Plan for Economy Revitalization through
Increasing the Support of SOC Business
Yes.
Yes...Ye.
I am Assemblyman Jin San Pil.
I will have a question to
the Deputy Prime Minister.
- Th...- Assemblyman Jin, relax.
You have prepared well.
Yes.
Kang Sang Ho, he is too blunt.
Did you write the questionnaire
easy to be understood, right?
Yes. General Secretary.
Before posing a question,
to Deputy Prime Minister,
I want to tell the story
of a small businessperson.
What is he talking?
I am calling and telling you
that you'd better watch TV.
Would you turn on the Assembly
channel at the cable?
After she graduated the commercial high
school, she got the job at a big company.
She was promoted to the
head of department.
She did her job very well.
Whenever the company reorganized
to lay-off, none let her go.
But she thought
that if she quit,
she would save the jobs of her two junior
clerks. So she retired by herself.
Excuse me. Assemblyman Jin.
Please have a question only
about the budget bill.
My aide told me that I can do
whatever I want to during this time.
Please don't interrupt me.
I forgot what I wanted to tell.
Please take out
this from my time.
So, with her retirement
fund, savings,
and the bank loan, she
opened the coffee store.
Then, next to her store, a big
franchise opened the business.
Ultimately, to pay her loan,
she took out the second
loan, used the credit
card loan, and did
everything she could do.
Still it didn't work out, her
store was put up at auction.
Assemblyman, I am sorry but I don't
get your point what you are talking.
You don't know my point?
Assemblyman Jin!
Aicham! Seriously! My point is..
the debt is very dangerous
to the common people.
Ye.
You must pay back. If you don't pay
back, you will come to an end.
That is my point.
Now, I will have a question.
I agree the object that the
sluggish economics can be pepped up
by putting the additional budget.
But the additional budget makes
the nation get into debt.
The people who have to pay the
debt are our people in the end.
Therefore, we have to make
the additional budget
as a minimum and put it
only as a necessity.
This committee thinks
that the whole budget for
Social Overhead Capital
(SOC) needs to be cut, and
the present $15 billion worth
of government bond issue
needs to be reduced.
Deputy Prime Minister,
please state your opinion.
We will sincerely consider your opinion.
Wow, he handled a thorny issue well.
When he can handle that he won't be
a problem to the party leadership.
Yes. Sunbae-nim.
I am a little disappointed
in you this time.
I am sorry that I didn't
tell you in advance.
Didn't I tell you what is
the best for Assembly Jin?
I am sorry but...
This is the best for him, what I chose.
Whose decision is right,
you will know little by little.
I understand.
Aide Choi, Assembly Jin
holds the microphone again.
What?
Don't tell as like a snake
climbs over a wall.
Say clearly that you will
do what I said or not.
As I said a little while ago,
Aigoo, I am getting nervous.
I will sincerely examine this.
Examine a lot.
I will tell you my posiiton exactly.
If this committee,
doesn't do what I said,
regardless of whether I belong
to a ruling party or not,
I will vote against the
supplementary budget bill.
No. Assemblyman!
Even if someone threatens
my life with a knife,
I will oppose, absolutely oppose.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
AssemblyPreview
I want to know the reason
why you don't like me.
It is not that I don't like you.
It's that you are not a kid who fits here.
Of course, if you ruined the business,
it's obvious that you should
take the responsibility.
We thought he was our side but
he is x-man. What should we do?
I will watch the situation a little more.
Did Baek Do Hyeon screw you again?
The garbage dumping ground
where the human trashes live.
What did you say?