All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
For Assemblyman Jin and for you...
this is the best I can do.
Take it.
Assemblyman Jin.
Announcement of Intention Not to Run
in Next Year's General Election
Not run?
You should sit down first.
Is this the last task
assigned to you, Aide Choi?
This is a misunderstanding.
I will explain.
No. I have nothing to say so go outside.
- Assemblyman.- I'm not
your assemblyman anymore!
What is it that you want?
When you made the strategic
nomination to pick me, did
you do it so that you can
run in Gyeongjae district?
When you said that I should go to the
Assembly and represent the weak...
was it all bullsh*t?
Why don't you tell me quickly?
Even if it was a conspiracy as you say,
do you really have to get mad about it?
-What?-Take a look at yourself.
On the body where you once wore
a vest while demonstrating,
now, you are wearing a
golden badge on a suit.
-So what?-Regardless of whether
it was a conspiracy or not,
you were the one who benefited the most.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil!
-What did you say, you son of a
bit*h?Assemblyman, please calm down.
Dal Soo Hyung died, okay?
Because of your shit*y
ploy, Dal Soo Hyung died.
If you insist on finding the
reason why Bae Dal Soo died,
it's because you accepted my offer.
Go and think about why you are in
this position and think about that.
You must be thinking about my
withdrawing from being a candidate.
Wishful thinking on your part.
I am not forcing you.
Just as last time, the choice
is up to you, Assemblyman Jin.
Listen carefully.
Even if I am a person who lacks things,
I am not going let things
happen as you wish.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Assembly~Episode 9~
I know that you could have easily
misunderstood the situation.
However, as your Aide, on my honor,
I did not do anything
that violated that role.
Aide Choi, you knew, right?
What?
The reason that he
strategically nominated me.
Why can't you answer?
That matter happened before I
started to serve you as an Aide.
So you didn't know?
Just tell me honestly...
that you can't tell me because you are
on Secretary General Baek's side.
You didn't tell me because
you are on his side!
Yes, I knew. Is that enough?
Now do you feel better
after spitting that out?
Yes, I do.
Knowing that, in spite of that
you've been playing with me.
Right? Was it fun seeing me do
whatever you told me to do?
Fun? Is it fun to suffer in silence?
Do you have the slightest idea how I feel?
Because I thought you were having such
a tough time, I couldn't say anything.
I was hoping you would
always remain unaware.
Nevertheless, no matter what you say...
it won't reach my ears.
In Gyeongjae City, which
is the true birthplace of
National Party Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon,
who is not running for his current
district in the next election,
Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon
is gaining momentum.
Gyeongjae City's leaders and over 30
community associations are behind him.
"Come Baek Home," a Baek Do Hyeon
fan club, has been organized and,
in actuality there has been a formal
declaration urging him to run.
With respect to the activity of the
Gyeongjae City voters, everyone
on Baek Do Hyeon's and
incumbent Jin Sang Pil's sides
is refraining from making
any official statement.
Hey, turn that off!
The focus of attention is on the future.
Ah, Jeez. For fangirls who
have as much sense of
loyalty as a baby chick's
teardrop, what? Fan club?
What bullsh*t infection
have they succumbed to?
Ultimately there's going to be a
face-off with Secretary General Baek.
Assemblyman Jin, aren't
you going to eat ramen?
He needs to eat.
If you insist on finding the
reason why Bae Dal Soo died...
it's because you accepted my offer.
Kim Gyu Hwan
- What is it?  I'm calling
about the news report.
I guess you must be very concerned.
It's the Assemblyman, not me you should be
concerned about. Take good care of him.
Nevertheless, no matter what you say...
it won't reach my ears.
-How are you?  - Yes.
Hello.
Yes.
Umm, for today... do I have
anything scheduled in my district?
There is a meeting with the merchants
from the Gyeongjae market cooperative.
Ah. Aide Seo, isn't there anything special
happening at the National Assembly?
There isn't, Assemblyman.
Assemblyman, please talk briefly with me.
I must leave for the district.
Let's go.
See you later.
Well. As I said yesterday,
everyone get busy with calling and
text messaging the new harbor
Support Committee members.
Secretary Song, you're
assigned to prepare a survey.
Yes.
From now on the top priority is blazing
a trail through my constituency.
Grasp the fine details from
Joe Schmoe's puppy's name
to the number of spoons in
his kid sister's household.
Understand?
Yes.
But why are you like people sentenced to
be executed? Don't you want to do it?
No way!
I'm going to observe you
without advanced warning
so don't even think
about playing hooky.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Assemblywoman.
A story about Aide Choi In Kyung
has appeared on the scandal sheet.
- Choi In Kyung?- Yes.
If you act cocky one more
time, when they were
ranking the proportional
representative candidates
you sought me out and begged
me, crying and sniffling,
to schedule a meeting with
Secretary General Baek.
I'm going to distribute
flyers about that episode!
Oh, noes!
What's up with this kid?!
TITLE: Assembly Hall Scoops: Assemblyman J
Choi 0 0, a political consultant
with a Blue House background,
after a business venture failure,
becomes Assemblyman J's aide
through her political sponsor DH's help.
When DH declares not to run
in his current constituency,
in order to offer up Gyeongjae City to
DH, Choi 0 0 is leading a double life,
spending her days in Assemblyman J's
office and her nights by DH's side.
It's just a rumor in a private tabloid.
Why do this among professionals?
- Assemblywoman Hong.- Ms.
Choi In Kyung...
She has great acting skills.
Even I was completely fooled.
I said it was just a rumor...
Didn't I?
Whether it is a rumor or not, the only
thing left is to be kicked out...
for Ms. Choi 0 0.
That may be for the better, after
all.When are you going to quit?
Stop this prattle and just do the poll.
You were already wronged
when you got passed up for
the Gyeongjae nomination
because of the assemblyman.
Do you still want to work,
being called a spy?
Didn't I tell you I'm going to
kill you if you reveal that?
Aide Choi, you fool. Are you, by any
chance, in love with Oppa Sang Pil?
Secretary Oh, I'll be back in a little bit.
Could you get ready an accounting summary
of the political funds for when I return?
Secretary Oh?
Yes.
Isn't she that woman on the scandal sheet?
Assemblyman Jin's Aide. She was
a rather good person before.
The Assembly has corrupted a person.
Please send a due diligence
team to Gyeongjae
City in connection with
the new harbor project.
Yes.
Thank you, Minister.
- Yes, it's me.- The scandal sheet...
I have read it.
It must be Chief Secretary Lim Gyu Tae's
work. He's close to the government-men.
Do you want to criticize
it as a cowardly tact?
Do you think it was an honorable way?
Before engaging the head of the
enemy, eliminate his think tank...
I think that is an excellent tactic.
That tactic... it will fail.
Because I will continue to remain here.
Well, would Assemblyman Jin be
able to continue to trust you?
He will.
If I have not judged him
wrongly, for sure he will.
Choi In Kyung, come to grips with it.
No matter how hard you struggle,
you won't be able to beat me.
We've never fought properly.
The result will be different
from what you expect.
1. Is Aide Choi 0 0 (FEMALE) at
Assemblyman J's Office DH's Mole?
2. To offer the district of Gyeongjae
City to DH, a political guardian of Choi,
she works at J's office on daytime, and
at night she stays at the side of DH...
Which newspaper carried this article?
Not a newspaper, but
it's called a scandal sheet.
What is Aide Choi going to do now?
Should you fire her?
This is just a wild rumor.
- Aide Choi is absolutely not
that kind of person.- Hey,
I don't want to talk behind
Aide Choi's back, either.
But what Ae Ri said
yesterday does make sense.
Frankly, in this situation,
there is no reason for
Aide Choi to be all loyal
to Assemblyman Jin.
Right?
But why are these people not here yet? Huh?
Assemblyman Jin!
Oh, yes, Chairman.
Forget about today's meeting.
But why?
The members say they are
busy and cannot attend.
What?Since when was this scheduled that
they are pretending to be busy only now?
- Ah, well...  -It's so obvious.
They must have gone to
Baek Do Hyeon's fan club.
If only you had made confirmation
calls to these people,
the Assemblyman would not
have wasted his trip.
How can you do such lax jobs?
I am sorry.
Please make sure that
this never happens again.
But, Aide Choi,
are you asking us to keep
doing this nonsense?
What do you mean, nonsense?
This is not an election time. How
can we keep doing this every day?
Even if we do this, the popular
opinion will not turn back, you know?
Aide Seo...
Aide Seo. Is that something
an aide should say?
What?
Look here, Aide Choi. Even
if you're the senior aide,
aren't you being too much between
the same 4th-level aides?
What are you saying I'm
being too much about?
- Why are you doing this? Please stop.
No matter how messed up the hierarchy is in
the Assembly Hall, still this is not right.
And when you first entered
the Assembly Hall,
I was the vice president
of the Aides Association.
If you are a veteran, you
should act like one!
Aide Choi, it's you who
should act properly.
How did you comport yourself normally
to put your name on the scandal sheet!
- Aide Seo!- I am telling
you in no uncertain terms!
This, text messaging, di di di di
di di, this. I am not doing it.
No, I will not do it!
Why, so unlike you, did you do it?
You used to tell me that
a useless spirit of
resistance is the shortcut
to an early demise.
I did, right?
But I'm a right-winger.
I can't forgive spies.
Secretary Oh.
Is the accounting summary finished?
Is this all?
Yes.
You have to give me
details together with the
receipts so I can report
to the Assemblyman.
In the future, I will report
directly to the Assemblyman.
What did you say?
When I asked other assemblymen's offices,
there are more where the administrative
secretary does the reporting.
Do it again.
I can't do that.
Secretary Oh!
Why are you two like that?
What's the matter?
There was a little dispute over who
reports the accounting summaries.
Secretary Oh, you do it from now on.
Assemblyman.
Does an aide have to know even
how an assemblyman uses money?
What are you doing?
I want just one free glass.
Why?
You want to console me in your way?
Isn't that allowed?
Just one glass.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Timing and
Subtitles by The Assembly Team @ Viki
New Harbor Project Support
Committee Member List
He needs to work closely
with the authorities...
I cannot trust Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil...
Go into the district and
meet the local residents.
Engage them in conversations and
watch how they live day-to-day.
That faction is like a thorn
attached to a beautiful rose.
If you become intoxicated
by the sweetness a
faction brings, you can
lose your soul to it.
Use your faction, but you
cannot let it enslave you.
What are you, staff members,
doing to the Assemblyman?
Are you, by any chance, in
love with Oppa Sang Pil?
You were already wronged
when you got passed up for
the Gyeongjae nomination
because of the Assemblyman.
Do you still want to work,
being called a spy?
... already wronged when you got passed
up for the Gyeongjae nomination.
What are you going to do in the future?
In the future?
Do what?
The Assemblyman's office...
Are you going to keep working for him?
Enough with that chatter. Just study this.
The other side will surely spread rumors
or weak points about the Assemblyman.
Don't get flustered.
And you have to respond according
to what's written here.
I...
can never understand you, Aide-nim.
When we visited you because you were
ill, I saw an incomplete resignation.
Why do you keep hanging in there
when you're having such a hard time?
Even the Assemblyman treats
you now like you're a spy.
Human beings can briefly hesitate.
- But I trust the Assemblyman.- No.
Your judgment was wrong.
Our Assemblyman...
is not such an amazing person as you think.
Let's stop. What use is this talk with you?
I wish you'd be more at ease.
I said let's stop.
I would like to give you
a strategic nomination
to run as our Gookmin Party's candidate.
What are you doing right now?
Let's talk later. Wait outside.
- Sunbae-nim!- In Kyung!
Wait outside.
What are you thinking about so hard?
Umm...
did you drink?
A little.
Why drink and then come to work?
From now on, events in the constituency...
I will personally manage them.
Meetings not taking place at the
spot like today will not happen.
In the case of the new harbor project,
all sorts of events and power
brokering will continue for now.
But we must refrain from
direct confrontation and wait.
When time passes and the fever subsides,
we will counterattack with
your own development strategy.
My development strategy?
Gyeongjae City's sustainable
development model
that preserves the environment and
the working class's livelihood.
In a few days, I should be able
to at least present a draft to you.
Assemblyman.
As much as you trusted me,
I know your shock is also great.
But you have to trust me.
I am not on such great terms
with Secretary General Baek
as you think.
What do you mean by that?
Because I...
proclaimed war by saying that I would make
you into Gyeongjae City's next assemblyman.
Why did you do that?
This is my fight.
This is...
yours and mine, our fight.
Before being your aide, I...
am your comrade, Assemblyman.
This is unfair. Really.
Ahew, I almost got duped again.
But...
are you asking me to believe those words?
Am I a dummy?
- Assemblyman...- Go
out and ask people.
Stop them on their way and see if even
one of them believes those words.
Just look at Gyeongjae City now.
Everyone is screaming for Secretary
General Baek, Secretary General Baek.
And, the closest person
to Secretary General Baek
will be on my side?
Are you really...
going to disappoint me like this?
Who's disappointed in whom?!
I'm the one who's disappointed!
Because I was hoodwinked!
Now, I'm really sick and tired of
both of you. So let's stop, okay?
Let's stop.
There should be a limit to
toying with another person.
Why? Why are you looking
at me like that again?
Why? You're going to act again? Huh?
I...
I guess I...
overestimated you a lot.
Your office...
I am going to quit.
Yes!
As it was, I was worried about how I
could sack you with everyone looking on.
But since you're offering
to leave on your own,
that worked out great. I'm
thankful, very much so!
No.
I'm the one who should be thankful
because you're showing me
your very worst like this.
Ms. Choi In Kyung.
Don't do any useless thing and be
loyal to Secretary General Baek.
So you can wear the badge next time.
Oh, that's a really good idea.
Yes, I will do that.
Without fail, I will do that.
Constituent Response Manual
Welcome Government Due Diligence Team
Gyeongjae Citizens Love Baek Do Hyeon.
Oh, he's coming!
Here he comes.
Yes, thank you.
Baek Do Hyeon! Baek Do Hyeon!
Ah, yes, yes, thank you.
Baek Do Hyeon!
What you asked me the last time
about shortening the bus
waiting time to 30 minutes...
I've settled at 45 minutes.
That will be across the board...
If you can endure it until then...
I heard that there is a
big event at the City
Hall today. Aren't you
going, Assemblyman Jin?
I had a prior engagement here today.
I will go after this.
But, that Baek Do Hyeon guy seems
to be a somebody, after all.
He coughs a few times
and government workers
are coming out in droves.
Gyeongjae City has
produced a public figure.
I heard that he was born in Sangwon-Ri.
Assemblyman Jin, where in
Gyeongjae City were you born?
My hometown is not here.
Huh? Not here?
Aigoo!
What use is a hometown nowadays?
Where you live is your hometown.
Isn't that so?
Still, it is not like that.
Don't you think the citizen
response nowadays is a bit tepid?
I've heard that those
Come Baek Home weasels
are chewing you out so much,
calling you an outsider.
No need to worry about that. What day
and age do we live in for that to work?
This kid, this kid... How
can you be so naive?!
Just a moment!
Oh my, isn't this the Assemblyman?
That's right! It's him!
Yes, I'm Jin Sang Pil,
Gyeongjae City's servant
who is always sweating and doing his best.
We are Jin Sang Pil. Here...
Umm, let me ask you a question.
When you vote,
do you consider the
candidate's hometown or not?
- Aigo, Hyung, why do you ask so
useless...- Of course we consider it.
If they are about the same, of course
we should take care of our own first.
Why would we let outsiders have a ball?
That's right! Aren't we one big family?
Right!
If you have any civil matter,
I will take care of it if you
give me a call at that number.
Yes.
Call us.
Assemblyman, take care!
Goodbye. Thank you!
- Oh my, that was a national
assemblyman.- Goodbye.
Hey, you saw that, right?
They say they'll take
care of their own first.
But you don't have a competitive
edge against Secretary General Baek.
I'm saying you are screwed, punk.
Of course, yes.
I run into you often in
Gyeongjae City nowadays.
Because I don't like law that much,
I try not to do as it says normally, but
doing this in another's constituency...
isn't this a violation of the election
law prohibiting premature campaigning?
Do I look like I'm campaigning right now?
A person who has nothing
to do with Gyeongjae City
is making a big scene with a
government due diligence team.
If that's not campaigning, what is it?
I guess your aides are not
working properly these days.
A few days ago, I was appointed
the chairman of Gookmin
Party's Special Committee for
National Land Development.
So, today, I am here not
as the Secretary General,
but as the chairman of
the special committee.
How can a so-called assemblyman
not even know that, unless he's really
indifferent to his constituency?
Wow...
When we had Aide Choi, nothing
like this happened. Hey!
If they act like that, what do we do now?
All sorts of events and power
brokering will continue for now.
But we must refrain from
direct confrontation and wait.
So, once the result of the
field investigation comes out,
we are planning to start negotiation
with the proper authorities.
But we must refrain from
direct confrontation and wait.
But, Secretary General Baek,
what is your opinion?
I am a bit hesitant in saying this,
but we, the Gookmin Party, too,
are thinking among ourselves
that this is very feasible.
Team Leader.
Team Leader!
I have a question.
Yes, Assemblyman.
Team Leader, we have met a few
times in Sejong City (Korea's
second administrative capital
city after Seoul), right?
Yes.
At those times, you told me the
project had no feasibility.
What?
Why is he doing that?
Ah. Really.
Because there are many big harbors
nearby and the inlet is narrow,
you told me it was hard
to build a new harbor.
Was that a lie, then?
Since such opinions exist too
we have to carefully evaluate it, I
think that's what I meant to tell you.
Government workers are said to be soulless.
But, Team Leader, your
soul is highly developed.
It changes drastically
depending on the situation.
I demand as the National Assemblyman
of Gyeongjae City District,
that the government stop
being swayed by politics.
And the ruling party stop filling
the citizenry with hot air.
Hot air, it's a bit awkward to hear that.
What are you saying? It's a bad check.
Assemblyman Jin! What do you
think you're doing right now?
Are you saying Gyeongjae City's assemblyman
will go against the citizens' wish?
Look here!
Are you the only people
living in Gyeongjae City?
Huh? Are you people here the
only citizens of Gyeongjae City?
I've walked around in my sneakers.
There are tons of people worried at
the mere mention of a new harbor,
because the real estate prices will
sky-rocket and rents will go up too.
They've lived by fishing and
running small stores for tourists.
There are a lot of people
who have lived like
that and are worried about
future livelihoods.
I have also met a countless
number of people worried
about possibly harming our
city's beautiful environment.
Even though they have no
power or organizations,
aren't they, aren't those people
also residents of Gyeongjae City?
Those people are Gyeongjae citizens
just like you! Don't exclude them!
Hey, from just listening to this
person, isn't he totally a spy?
Right now, are you trying to
spoil an all-finished dish?
Is this an all-finished dish? Huh?
I'm asking you whether this is a done deal!
Since they're coming and going
with a due diligence team,
it looks as though it's done, right?
No way in hell!
Saying yes, yes, they will fill you up with
hot air and once the election is over,
it will be all back to square one!
Wake up and smell the coffee, please!
Get out! How can there be such a jerk?!
Don't talk down to me! Why
are you talking down to me?
I said don't talk down to me!
- What if I do?- What?
Okay, so?
Let's say a new harbor is built. How
many ships do you think we'll see?
Do you think ships will
just overflow it, huh?
Didn't you see the next door
neighbor with a new airport?
If only a new airport is built, do
airplanes flock to it, flock in?
There are tons of airports all over the
country that can't even make ends meet.
The new harbor will end up like
that, too, okay? It will go down!
Are you going to play an
origami ship game, now?
Huh?! You cannot do this.
- You cannot work willy nilly
like this!- Get the hell out!
No, you must not!
Huh?!
We declare that...
we cannot acknowledge Assemblyman
Jin Sang Pil, who has ignored
the Gyeongjae citizens' long cherished
wish, as Gyeongjae City's assemblyman.
Moreover, we solemnly
swear that we will start
a community-wide movement to
oust Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil!
With regard to Assemblyman Jin
Sang Pil's inappropriate behavior,
our party cannot suppress its deep
concern and sense of disappointment.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil,
before the Party, and citizens
of Korea and Gyeongjae City,
kneel down and beg for forgiveness.
- Office of Jin Sang Pil...-
I am a Gyeongjae citizen.
-Put Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
on the phone.- I'm not getting
angry but if you have
something important to say...
Well, the Assemblyman is really not here.
Stop just being angry and...
I understand what you are saying, but...
Sir, umm...
- Aish, why are you cursing at me?
Do you know me?- We'll contact you.
Do you know me so you are cursing...
But what are you doing, so
rudely, to a voter right now?
Yes, please tell me. I
will lend a listening ear.
I am an aide.
Yes, I understand what you are saying...
Don't curse!
Hey, punk, how old are you? What?
You called a wrong number, punk!
Everyone, hang up.
Jin Sang Pil, get out!
Get out! Get out!
- Jin Sang Pil, get out!- Get out!
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
- Jin Sang Pil, get out!- Get out!
Get out!
You can't do this here.
Get out! Get out!
- Jin Sang Pil, get out!- Get out!
Get out!
The fan club and Support Committee will
start collecting signatures on a petition
to oust Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil starting
tomorrow in Yeouido and Gyeongjae City.
The local media in Gyeongjae
City are pumpingout
critical pieces aimed at
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
I will try to make the central
media join the bandwagon as well.
It cannot end as a one-time whirlwind.
Assemblyman Jin will try to hang in and
wait for the popular opinion to subside.
There has to be a knock-out punch
to make him throw in the towel.
I have searched through the
Party's ethical code but could
not find a serviceable reason
for disciplinary actions.
There is a more effective method
than disciplinary actions.
What is that?
Baek Do Hyeon is using the
influential people of Gyeongjae City
to corner Jin Sang Pil as in a rabbit hunt.
He must want to finish him up quickly.
Because the popular opinion
may change at any time.
Assemblyman Park.
Jin Sang Pil is right now like a
godforsaken sailboat in a boundless sea.
Should we help him out a little?
Let him be.
What use is resuscitating
an almost dead person.
I guess,
we are not the 911 emergency rescuers.
Secretary General Baek, what
do I owe this honor to?
Leaving an old nest and
trying to build a new one...
How is it going? Not easy, right?
So it is.
At any rate,
this time, I marveled at
your strategy once again.
While tightly holding on to the
local leaders with a new harbor,
and making the natives turn their backs on
Jin Sang Pil for being an out-of-towner...
For distressed Assemblyman Jin
there is no other way than
to make a suicide goal.
Getting complimented by a guru
like you, Assemblyman Park...
This is a great honor.
But I don't care for clever moves too much.
There is a baduk saying that three
clever moves will cost the game.
So this time, I think I will engage the
standard tactics instead of a sneaky move.
Is there something you want from me?
More than 70% of the party
members in Gyeongjae City
belong to the Anti-BH faction.
Please use your influence on them.
If I do that,
how will you pay my wages?
I will enable you to focus
only on the election campaign
without having to worry
about the party nomination.
Gookmin Party Members'
Gyeongjae City Local Office
So, that is, oh, it's right here.
If the members demand convening a
general meeting, then it can be done.
Right.
We don't have time, so just start
circulating the sign-up sheet first.
Okay, don't worry.
Jin Sang Pil, this punk, can he do this?
Motion to Subject the
Head of Gyeongjae City
Party Members' Committee
to a Vote of Confidence
Why are you guys just sitting around
like people whose lips are glued shut?
We must come up with a plan, too,
and do something to reciprocate, right?
Aide Seo, while working
here for over 20 years,
you must have gone through a lot
of similar situations, right?
Ah, that is, as for myself,
I've worked mainly specializing
in the policy area and...
Aigoo, seriously, I'm about
to blow my gut and flip!
Then, are you saying we should
just sit still like this
and silently watch Secretary
General Baek gobbling up
Gyeongjae City, huh?
Enough already.
It's the fault of the troublemaker,
not the staff members.
We are back.
Serves you right, after
labeling an innocent
person a spy and
kicking her out...
Notice
Secretary Song.
- Yes?- What is this?
Give it to me.
TITLE: Emergency General Meeting of
the Gyeongjae City Party Members
What is it?
Work after eating.
But, Assemblyman.
The Gyeongjae party members
are holding a general
meeting to put the head
to a vote of confidence.
What?
When the head of the members
is Assemblyman Jin,
by whose permission are they saying they
are holding a general meeting, huh?
The party members have
demanded a general meeting.
Until the general meeting is
held, don't let down your guard
and carefully watch over the
situation in Gyeongjae City.
Yes, I understand.
But, Secretary General,
about Ms. Choi In Kyung...
Oh. how is it going with her move
to the Secretary General's office?
That is...
Ms. Choi In Kyung is declining the job.
New Harbor Objection Scandal
Jin Sang Pil, in Danger of Getting
Expelled from his Constituency
Sunbae Jo Woong Gyu
Yes, Sunbae-nim.
I'm sorry, Sunbae-nim.
There was a traffic jam.
To see your cool sunbae,
if you are late getting all
prettified, then I forgive you.
Right, getting prettified.
- Hurry and sit down.- Okay.
Did you wait for long?
Why didn't you order first?
- One more chap is coming.- Who?
The busiest punk in the Republic of Korea.
Long time no see, In Kyung.
Yes, have you been well, Sunbae-nim?
Why so awkward like broken-up lovers
running into each other again?
Did you two fight?
No, what do you mean a fight...
Do Hyeon said we three musketeers
should get together, so I took it on.
I did well, right?
Yes, you did well...
By the way, from the
news, it seems like
you've almost got Jin
Sang Pil in the corner?
Yes.
But Jin Sang Pil looked
like he could take some
beating. How are you
going to knock him down?
There are two ways to win in a fight.
Either knock him out or
get him to surrender.
Surrender?
I have selected only the ones with the
right kinds of resumes and experience.
Do you think you might like any of them?
Resume Before being your aide,
I am a like-minded person with you.
There isn't.
Assemblywoman Hong Chan
Mi wants to see you.
Haven't you hired a successor to Choi,
the lolling star of gossip rags, yet?
Why? Do you want to recommend to
me an amazeballs person again?
You are so greedy.
How can I find a person of better
ability than Secretary Sim Dong Cheon?
I can easily imagine. What is your agenda?
- I came here to deliver Secretary
General Baek's proposal.- What is it?
Announce your intention not to run
in next year's general election.
-Hello.- Whether you call out
"Hello" or not, Assemblyman Jin!
You have no one to turn to for help.
You'd better
take the practical benefit
instead of your pride.
The practical benefit?
As soon as you announce it,
you will get back into the
Pro-BH faction, under the
banner of Secretary Baek.
That means, even if you are not
serving in the Assembly next year,
you may get a director's-level
position at a large public company.
Go and tell him not to say nonsense.
I can imagine you are
searching around for a
job at the iron foundry
with your resume.
Secretary General will
wait for you one more day.
Consider it carefully.
What's the reason you perversely engineered
this occasion through Sunbae Jo?
We have met over official
matters in the meantime. Isn't
it good we can chat about old
times after a long time?
I am uncomfortable because your changed
features overrides your former image.
I didn't change but just
got in step with reality.
You succumbed to the reality.
Now, why don't you transfer to
the Secretary General's office?
Is it really necessary for
you to give a favor to me?
In Kyung, you are my comrade
of 20 years and the best aide.
I want to prove I am right.
I hope you watch over me.
Let's go for karaoke.
Scumbag punk!
Have you seen Assemblywoman Hong?
What about? Announcing not to run
in next year's general election?
Ah. You have not heard it yet. I asked
her to tell you not to say nonsense.
You have to have the
courage to admit defeat.
I am not defeated yet.
I can't be defeated by a
corrupt person like you.
Is that so?
As you said, let's consider
I killed Hyung Dal Soo.
But, if I lose to you, I will
kill Dal Soo Hyung a second time.
That's why I must not lose to you.
Understand?
Excuse me, Aide Choi. I am sorry.
Have you been well, Choi In Kyung?
Yes.
It is good that you have been well.
In Kyung.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Assemblyman.
Declare your intention not to run
in next year's general election.
Hey, Assemblyman Jin, since we
can't get caught like this,
let's see Aide Choi once with the view of a
drowning man aiming to grasp at a straw.
We can make a good excuse to see her.
Just make an excuse of asking about
the maintenance fee for this house.
It seems we made a mistake to Aide
Choi, no matter how we think.
We didn't make a mistake. Just let it be.
Who is Aide Choi?
Joo Hee!
Hey, Dunce! How did you get here?
How? I searched the
address in the computer.
Ta da! Pickled mustard kimchi!
Aigoo. How come Assemblyman
drinks every day?
Hey. This is the first time I'm
drinking since I drank at that time.
I came home.
Ahwoo! A big dunce came, too.
Hey, why do you come home so late, punk?
I met friends.
Hello.
Hi!
It's the right time.
Secretary Kim, we have to discuss
a kind of serious matter.
Would you take Joo Hee and play with her?
Yes. Of course.
Do you want to go to an Internet café?
Cool! Oppa, you don't work but play games.
If you work at an Internet café for a few
years, you are able to do this much.
Did you attend school while working?
Yes. Why?
Nothing. But you look like
a son from a rich home.
By the way, you're speaking informally
from a while ago, young kiddo.
Aihee! We have the same
situation of getting older.
There is no way.
Even I will go and meet her.
Why would you do that? Why?
Why even you?
We have to do something!
Are you going to finish your term stupidly
while your soul shrivels like this?
Seriously. Leave Aide Choi
alone no matter what.
She is pitiful if you know.
What about?
Why is she pitiful? Because
she got fired by you?
Hey. To my eyes,
you are more pitiful and stifling, punk!
You don't know! If I were not there,
Aide Choi...
If it were not for me...
Aide Choi...she should have worn the
Assembly badge for Gyeongjae City.
What? Assemblywoman?
Oh my! What are you saying?
The nomination that was
supposed to go to Aide Choi,
it came to me with a detour!
How can I make her my Aide? How?
Can I make her Assemblywoman?
Just, she should stay with
Secretary General Baek, now.
Let's leave her alone, huh?
Just leave her alone with Secretary Baek...
Did it happen that way?
Somehow, I feel like...
even if I try something and fail
at it, with that assemblyman,
I won't get hurt.
Kim Gyu Hwan?
You drank a lot?
Today, I have to admit it.
What are you talking? What do you admit?
Our Assemblyman, Jin Sang Pil.
Kim Gyu Hwan!
Only today, I will admit what you said.
Our Assemblyman.
What on earth happened to you?
Ah. I got in big trouble.
Aigoo.
I am in big trouble. I have to
go to the constituency today.
Ah, my stomach!
Hyung Seong Gi!
No... I can see an apparition. Wake up!
Hello.
Oh.
What brings you here, so early?
I come here to apply for the position
of Aide in your Assembly office.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Assembly~Preview~
I want to be a real Assemblyman who can
honorably stand in front of the people.
Don't relax your guard.
At the slightest slip,
the support of the people
in Gyeongjae City,
may turn to Assemblyman Jin.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
will make an important
announcement this evening
at the press conference.
I know you have an eye on
Secretary General Baek.
If he gets a vote of no
confidence, what will he do?
If I have to die, I will die
together with Secretary General Baek.
The General Assembly meeting
will be held as scheduled.
Then I will defect.