All characters, party
names, and incidents
appearing in this drama
are fictitious creations.
Oh!
Episode 10
What brings you here so early
in the morning, Choi In Kyung?
Because I heard that your
office is looking for an aide,
I came to apply.
What are you talking about?
I do lack many things but
if you look at the resume and my work
experience, you might want to hire me.
Resume
SPECIAL NOTE: 2015 Candidate for
Gyeongjae District Assembly.
I sent you away, so why
are you doing this?
You have to wear the
badge next time.
If you come to me, you know
there will be nothing for you.
Are you a dummy, Choi In Kyung?
Now, I'm going to
try to be a dummy.
Just like you, Assemblyman.
Sang Pil! Aide Choi's car...
A while back, Secretary
General Baek Do Hyeon
taught me something.
Even if you lose 99 times,
the one last victory
will decide everything.
Even if you have lost many times thus far,
don't you think you should win next time?
Please take care of me.
Yes.
Let's make sure we win.
Yes, Assemblyman.
Oh, I'm late. Late. Oh, Aide.
What time is it now?
I'm sorry. I had an alumni
meeting last night so I drank...
Oh, my insides.
What did you eat
for side dishes?
Why are you late?
- I'm an aide.  - What?
Assemblyman Jin Sang
Pil's number two.
Two.
I admire you.
Please go in.
I apologize for causing concern.
From now on, I will turn over a new leaf,
so for Assemblyman and this office,
I'll do my best.
As the saying goes, the ground
becomes sturdier after the rain.
Now, Aide Choi comes back and
joins our team. Therefore,
let's be energized. Fighting!
Fighting!
The atmosphere feels good.
I expected an atmosphere
of deep mourning.
Who is this?
Hello? I am a newly hired
aide for the Assemblyman.
What brings you here?
I don't even eat with aides,
so why don't you leave?
I promoted her to the Assembly-level
treatment. So, don't mind her.
Just tell us why you are here.
I came to hear your answer regarding
your entrance to the election.
I told you I was going to
wait until today, right?
I THINK I TOLD YOU LAST TIME:
when hell freezes over.
I just can't understand you.
I told you yesterday.
It's a proposal that includes enough
compensation for not running.
Is a director's-level
position at a large
public company just a
run-of-the-mill position?
I told you that I have no
interest in that kind of thing.
-Just go.-Assemblyman Jin.
You must be thinking that something
will pop up if you persevere.
If the vote of no confidence
passes at the Gyeongjae
City Gookmin Party
Members' General Meeting,
you will lose the nomination
for next year's election.
Which party is going to be so irrational
as to nominate a censured person?
For Assemblyman, there
will no case of
being censured.
-How so?-Beats me.
Showing off...
I understand. Work hard.
Okay.
Both of them are showing off!
How vulgar!
By the way, Aide Choi. Is there
really a way not to be censured?
It is impossible within
the regular procedure.
The members who are trying to convene the
meeting belong to the Anti-BH Faction.
That means Park Choon Seop allied
with Secretary General Baek.
Once the general meeting is held, there's
a 100% probability that you will be out.
A few minutes ago, you
said I would not be out.
That means you just showed off
when Assemblywoman Hong was here.
There is only one way! We prevent
the meeting from ever being held.
How?
You would have to cause trouble.
Trouble? What kind?
Why do we help Baek Do Hyeon?
We're on the same team,
but why do we always fight?
We sometimes need
to help out too.
You might be able to trick some
people, but you can't trick me.
Assemblyman Park, why
don't you speak honestly?
What did you receive
from Baek Do Hyeon?
Nomination for the
next election!
What?
He said he would give it, so I
accepted without hesitation.
Does an assemblyman exist in Korea who
wouldn't want to accept the nomination?
Assemblyman Park, you are
betraying your hoobaes!
Why have we confronted Baek
Do Hyeon all these times?
Because if we don't want to get
slaughtered at the next nomination,
we have to take him down from the
Secretary General position, don't we?
But now, if you alone,
as the annointed one,
receive a bulletproof
vest and wear it,
does that make sense to you?
You're really... simple.
What?
Do you think this Park Choon Seop only did
it because he lacked a bulletproof vest?
Then why are you doing this?
I'm trying to take
down Jin Sang Pil.
Indeed, Baek Do Hyeon made Jin Sang
Pil half-dead by stepping on him.
Why do we have to help him?
Jin Sang Pil has to be
in a desperate position
so that he can cause trouble.
Trouble? What kind of trouble?
Leaving the party.
- Leaving the party?  -Yes.
You want me to leave
the Gookmin Party?
Lea... Leaving the party?
If Jin Sang Pil leaves the party,
the problem becomes serious.
I mean retaining the
ruling majority.
But, we now have 151 seats.
The opposition have 149 seats...
One hundred fifty to
one hundred fifty.
The Gookmin Party ruling
majority will be lost.
If you switch your party affiliation,
Secretary General will have to take the
responsibility for losing the
Gookmin Party's ruling majority.
Oh, that will be the case.
He will really have to abdicate
his Secretary General's position.
Not only that but because he will
be shunned by the Blue House,
he will have to relinquish his leadership
position in the Pro-BH faction as well.
In other words, he'll
become a paper tiger.
But are you saying
that Secretary General
Baek is not aware of
those things right now?
It would make no sense if the top person
in the Gookmin Party didn't know that.
The price of your not running
in the next election:
that he will get you a director's-level
position at a large public company
is the very reason for that.
Now, I know. He was saying
that I should take the
carrot that was thrown
to me and be on my way.
Secretary General Baek
might have seemed calm on
the outside but inside,
he must be very nervous.
You say that Assemblyman
Jin absolutely refused?
Yes.
But do you have a concern?
You don't look very well.
-Even so, I can't leave
the party.-What?
The citizens don't like that.
Did I become who I am
because I was so great?
I was elected at Gyeongjae City because
of the strength of the Gookmin Party.
What will happen if I leave the party?
They will call me a traitor.
Assemblyman, stop getting so worried
and just do what I tell you to do!
Aide Choi, how could
you say it that way?
I am regretting
hiring you again.
In Kyung went back to
Assemblyman Jin...
Yes.
What was she thinking?
I want you to assure me,
as a person who works hard
and doesn't want to get
disappointed, of one thing.
Choi In Kyung is out in
the cold now, isn't she?
She is not just out in the cold,
she is now in Antarctica.
To what do I owe the honor of
this call, Assemblyman Jin?
Could I see you briefly?
Would you cancel the party
members' general meeting?
I will refuse.
Before coming here, I
left something with
Aide Choi In Kyung. Are
you curious about it?
I am not sure.
Withdrawal from the party.
-You want to leave
the party.-Yes.
If I get a vote of no
confidence, I will immediately
hold a press conference
to declare my defection.
Well, let me hear the reason why
you want to switch parties.
Because you manipulated
the party members so that
you effectively removed
me from the party.
I was wronged.
Just over that, you think the
citizens will sympathize with you?
All you are going to do is
shorten your political life,
which hasn't got much life
left in it to begin with.
Whether I die on the
fifth or sixth of April,
because I'm going to die
anyway, I am thinking about
dying together with you,
holding you tightly.
If I switch party affiliation, I know
that the party's majority will end.
I also know that if that happens,
it'll be the end of you as well.
You're scared, right?
That kind of empty
threat won't work on me.
Just announce that you
won't run as a candidate.
I don't want to.
The Gyeongjae local party meeting
will proceed as scheduled.
Then, I'll defect.
What happened?
Secretary General Baek did shove back a
bit but he also seemed a bit afraid.
I really don't know.
Is that so?
Now, you and Secretary
General Baek have
started the game of Chicken.
What -- a game?
Chicken?
It means the one who is afraid.
Once upon a time, young Americans
used their cars to play this game.
In it, they face each other
and drive towards each other.
The one who succumbs to his fear and
turns the steering wheel loses.
If both of them never turn their
steering wheels, what will happen?
They'll crash and both will die.
You have to make Secretary General
Baek turn that steering wheel first.
But will the Secretary
General Baek who is
so full of hot air turn
that steering wheel?
It will be him. As the
person who has the
most to lose, he will
be the most afraid.
Yeah, like the rich person who's
looking out for his well being.
As the general meeting day
gets closer, the person who
gets more anxious will be
Secretary General Baek.
Until then, you go
around the district and
you have to make an advantageous
situation for yourself.
I think that will be fun.
Dang, let's just do it.
That Chicken game.
(IN KOREAN)
The Chicken
game.(IN ENGLISH)
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
is a stumbling block in
Gyeongjae City's development.
Fellow Gyeongjae citizens,
how long have we
waited to bring the new
harbor infrastructure here?
We have to expel
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
to secure the new harbor project
and save Gyeongjae City!
Don't get fooled!
- What the hell?- Fellow
Gyeongjae citizens!
The new harbor is a mere
ploy that will be discarded
once next year's
election ends, everyone!
A mere ploy!
The new harbor is literally a mere
empty shell, an empty election promise
that dinosaur
politicians cooked up,
just hoping that you would
distrust me, everyone!
Everyone, it's an empty promise!
What do you mean it's a lie? I'll go
and visit you...Handle this for me.
Okay.
Da Jeong, take a look at this.
I will get back to you, yes.
Oops, sorry!
Gyeongjae City
Development Strategy
Here it is.
Okay.
Aide Choi, where
should I stick this?
Right next to it over there.
Yes.
ASSEMBLYMAN JIN SANG PIL: Gyeongjae's
new harbor is pork barrel politics!
Gyeongjae New Harbor Areas
To Be Intensively Managed
Hello, don't be fooled by
the new harbor project!
Yes, it is an election fraud.
Attracting a new harbor
infrastructure, it is a lie!
Don't believe it.
Don't be fooled by the
new harbor project!
It's a bold-faced lie.
Don't believe in the
new harbor project!
Hello.
Yes, don't be fooled by the
new harbor project, everyone.
We are Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil!
Invens Sky Apartments
The new harbor is...
a mere ploy that
will be discarded
when the election
ends, everyone!
It's just rubbish, everyone!
That can never fit the situation
in Gyeongjae right now!
Everyone... Fellow
Gyeongjae citizens!
Considering the
conditions at the site,
a new harbor is not appropriate!
It can soon turn
into a calamity!
Please, I beg for
your wise judgment!
My highly respected
Gyeongjae citizens!
The first assemblyman to confront
and contest an election promise
to develop his own constituency...
On Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's
next move, everyone's
interest is focused.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil is
arguing that the election promise
to build a new harbor in Gyeongjae City
is impracticable pork barrel politics.
By suggesting a sustainable development
model in place of castles in the air,
he is stirring up a breath
of shockingly fresh air.
Gyeongjae citizens... Nature and
man have to harmonize
and create a really smart
and beautiful city, we
have to aim for that!
That's why...
Oh, shucks!
The signatures supporting your
expulsion that we gathered
just today and only at the
five road junction location...
it's this much.
Okay, keep trying hard. We'll
keep trying hard as well.
No matter how much you talk,
the people of
Gyeongjae won't move.
That's right.
Assemblyman Jin,
look over there.
Fellow Gyeongjae citizens,
please participate and give
us your signatures to oppose
the new harbor project!
Please give us your signatures!
Everyone, please sign up.
Let's conserve the environment!
What participation! Let's go!
Driving me bonkers, seriously.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Everyone, let's preserve
the environment!
Please sign up!
Assemblyman Jin.
Dead set against a new port!
Dead set!  Dead set!
Ah...really.
We kept knocking to death...
and it does open up after all.
Gyeongjae citizens, everyone...
What is this?
People opposed to a new
port have organized.
By the people's own will?
Yes, they are usually
from internet cafes.
Two of them have already
started petition drives.
How is the movement to oust
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil going?
Your fan club and the Support
Committee for a new harbor
are holding a large-scale
campaign, but
the citizens' favorable
response is down a notch.
Secretary General, you
can't get careless.
One mistake and the
Gyeongjae citizens' popular
opinion may turn favorable
toward Assemblyman Jin.
-Secretary Im.-Yes.
In the name of Gookmin Party's
Secretary General's Office,
distribute press materials
about the general meeting
to be convened at the Gyeongjae
Gookmin Party Chapter.
I understand.
It's a battle of
wills, after all.
No matter what, the general
meeting will be held.
We have to show our resolve.
General Meeting of the Gyeongjae Ruling
Party Chapter to Convene in 2 Days
What do we do now since
Secretary Baek won't budge?
Did the Secretary General
look like a person
who would back off under
this circumstance?
Do you really think what
we are doing will work?
My blood is about to run dry.
Yes, Secretary Kim showed
me the news so I saw it.
I guess Secretary General
does have some guts.
It's just psychological warfare,
trying to push you over the edge.
It's hard but never
look crestfallen.
Just as you are doing, all you
have to do is keep it up.
Oh, I'm a person who pitched a tent
and fought layoffs for over 4 years.
I can do this for 40 years.
Don't worry.
Yes. Yes. Bye.
- Hyung, buy us a meal.- Oh?
You guys!
If one keeps going around,
he'll run into old friends.
Ah seriously. I haven't seen you
in a long time. How are you?
Yes, we're living stuck in a rut, Mr.
Assemblyman.
If you haven't eaten yet, why don't
we have a meal together, huh?
I'm sorry but I have a
rather weak stomach.
My stomach doesn't feel very
well, either, Assemblyman.
- Mine isn't good,
either.- Neither is mine.
Don't be like that.
Assemblyman Jin is having
a hard time these days.
Turning assemblyman
after being a welder...
I can understand how you
may want to enjoy it more.
But if you have something
called a conscience,
it's about time you
clambered down.
Section Head Kim.
Hyung Dal Soo is howling from
the nether world, you scumbag!
Why are you bringing
up Hyung Dal Soo, huh?
Why talk about
Hyung Dal Soo now?
Assemblyman Jin, there are ears listening.
Turn down your volume.
When Hyung Dal Soo was
beaten up and hospitalized,
you used that timing to
settle with the company
and pocketed that party nomination. Is
that something a human should do, huh?
So I'm paying the price
right now, aren't I?
I am doing this right now so
that Hyung Dal Soo won't wail.
Don't delude yourself. You
quitting will be more helpful.
Do you know, you piece of crap?
Do you guys know?
Do you really know what
Hyung Dal Soo wants?
Do you guys even know?
Hey, I don't think this will do.
You guys go. Just go.
Let's go -- let's
go -- let's go.
Go! Go away.
Leaving a bad taste in my mouth...
Let's go.
Hey.
Can I ask you a question?
What is it?
That...
It's about Hyung Dal Soo.
What?
What he really wants...
do you know, Assemblyman?
Why do you want to know?
I'm your secretary, Assemblyman.
- Is there a reason you can't tell me?
- What, kid?
Please tell me.
He said to take care of the...
earth.
The Eagle 5 Brothers (MANHWA
CHARACTERS) have left the earth.
Forever.
Satisfied?
Hyung Seung Gi, let's go.
We have to go. Get up.
Hurry up and get up.
Dang, let's go together.
I'm sick of this chicken.
Aide Choi, why do you
only order chicken these days?
Aide Choi.
- Aide Seo.  - Yeah.
Take this and go out with
Secretary Sim to get a drink.
Alcohol?
Are you saying that out
of your sincere heart?
Yes. It doesn't matter
how many rounds you go.
Assemblyman Jin is no joke.
He won't be able to win
against Baek Do Hyeon.
Soon, he will waive a
white flag and surrender.
I really don't think
this is right!
Aide-nim, aish, shouldn't he
really refrain from this?
It's not even a sure thing yet,
so why are you doing this?
What if someone hears us?
Then let them hear it!
What? Defecting?
Muffle your muzzle.
After all, how was he
elected in Gyeongjae City?
There, if you only have the
Gookmin Party name tag...
Even if I run, no, no, no...
Even if our youngest Park Da Jeong
runs, she will get elected there.
And he's leaving the party?
No matter how wet a blanket
he is, if he's a human being,
he shouldn't do that, right?
Let's stop. Let's go.
Aish, why do you keep
saying defect and defect?
Hey, Jin Sang Pil...
No, I mean Sim Dong Cheon,
how can a young guy
like you have such low
alcohol tolerance?
Do you think you can
manage defection?
Let's go.
Defection?
Assembly Jin Sang
Pil is doing it?
What are you talking
about, Reporter?
Who's defecting?
Those are all rumors.
Yes, I swear I
will never defect.
Yes. Yes.
Is it a reporter again?
Yes, I wonder where he
heard these things.
It's strange.
Why aren't you eating? Eat.
Eat a lot.
Hey, can't we stop eating
this damned chicken?
Secretary General!
Reporters are investigating the talks
about Jin Sang Pil's defection.
I know.
They're not reporting on it yet,
but it's just a matter of time.
We have to delay it
as much as possible.
Please utilize all the capacity you have
in the Spokesperson's Office and stop it.
Yes.
Even I got a call
from a reporter.
If Jin Sang Pil really defects,
wouldn't that be a big disaster?
That will never happen. Do
not worry, Party Leader.
But there is such a thing as a
one-in-ten-thousand chance.
One little slip, and even
I might be on the hook.
That will never happen.
Didn't I tell you?
Secretary General!
I'm sorry.
Yes, Chief Secretary
(FOR THE BLUE HOUSE).
Why on earth is there a buzz of talk about
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's defection?
That was just a rumor.
I will take good care of it,
so you need not be worried.
Since the regular parliamentary
session is just around
the corner, let's stay
quiet for the time being.
Please cease any and all behavior that
may provoke Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Chief Secretary! Are you
going to keep interfering
with the party matters
in this manner?
Well, this is not my opinion.
It's the VIP's opinion!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Did you stay up all night?
I'm not sleepy.
-You should go in and sleep
more.-I'm done sleeping.
- Aide Choi.  - Yes?
For your return to work...
I'm slightly grateful.
Me too.
Yes. I'm Choi In Kyung.
It's me.
Yes.
This time...
I think you have won.
Yes.
What kind of phone call was it?
Hello.
What happened?
What?
Did you really say...
that Secretary General
Baek waved the white flag?
I will relay to you Secretary
General Baek's exact words.
"This time, you have won."
Assemblyman, you have
been through a lot.
What do you mean I suffered?
All you guys have
worked hard too.
- You were really
tough!- Good job!
You hung tough!
Thanks.
Assemblyman, when are
you coming back?
In the afternoon I have a
few places I have to go to,
so I'll go back
right after that.
Today, you should
go home and rest.
Don't worry about us.
Yes, yes. Because you've
all worked hard, go home.
Great job!
Go home!
Wow!
We did Aide Choi's bidding and Secretary
General Baek surrenders to us!
That's right. Aide Choi
is an amazing person.
Assemblyman Jin, are you okay?
What?
- Are you crying?-
Who's crying?
You're crying? He's crying!
Wow, you're shedding
tears of joy.
Calling off the general meeting?
Yes.
From inside and
outside the party,
there are voices of concern
calling an impeachment of
the head of a local party
chapter a bit too harsh.
How do you propose
to call it off?
The members who had demanded
the meeting can send
a revocation to the party
administration office.
- Party members are not kids, and
I can't order them around.- What?
Only yesterday, the party even
distributed press materials to convene
a general meeting, and we're to
call it off this late in the game?
Because I'll feel ashamed, I
can't do those kind of things.
If you act like this, I will not be able
to keep the promise I made a while ago.
Look here, Secretary
General Baek,
even until now, I have never
begged anyone for a nomination.
I did it with my own strength, and
I will do that the next time too.
As for me, I am different than the
ones that you have dealt with before;
if you are going to be like this, you'll
face unfortunate circumstances for sure.
Will it really happen?
After you don't give the
nomination to me, do
you really think you can
handle the aftermath?
For a person who is
worried sick about a mere
Assemblyman Jin defecting
to another party...
Assemblyman Park!
I think tomorrow's Gyeongjae District
meeting will be very interesting.
If he's faced with a vote of no confidence,
how will Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil act?
These past days, all of you
have been through a lot.
Aide Choi, no matter what others
say about our victory this time...
isn't it because of
our combined work?
Acknowledged.
- Then, give us a reward vacation or
something like that!- No.- Why not?
There you go again! How far off is
the regular parliamentary session?
Just make thorough preparations
for the inspection hearings.
- Yes.
- Now, we've only turned one corner.
From this point on,
let's work even harder.
Secretary General Baek.
A problem arose. The
Anti-BH faction acted up.
I thought you were on Secretary
General Baek's side.
I was surprised that you
were on the other side.
So, what is it that you want?
I wish for you to cancel the
general meeting tomorrow.
Such a bold person, you are.
Assemblyman Jin will leave the party
after a vote of no confidence.
Then, the majority government will be
lost and you, Assemblyman Park, will
not be free from blame, either.
I'm already far out of favor with
the Blue House or party leadership.
even if I get pushed out
more, I don't care.
I know you are out to get
Secretary General Baek.
Because of Assemblyman Jin's untenable
situation with the Secretary General,
if you can stop the general
meeting for him, Assemblyman
Jin can stop Secretary General
Baek for you in Gyeongjae.
I guess you intend to have Assemblyman Jin
re-elected in Gyeongjae City next term.
That's correct.
If you do that, what's there
to gain for yourself?
- What?- Close aides
are, to begin with,
people who survive on
breadcrumbs from their bosses.
I'm asking what is
your breadcrumb?
I haven't thought of that yet.
Because my idea of a close aide
is a bit different from yours.
If that's the case,
my answer is no.
You should leave now.
What is the reason?
I can't trust you.
I seem untrustworthy?
I don't believe in people. I
only have faith in their greed.
Greed makes predictions
and controls possible.
For people who have no greed, I
don't know where they will end up.
Just like you and the
assemblyman whom you serve.
Assemblyman, I beg
of you sincerely.
As an aide, I want to, at
the very least, prevent
my assemblyman from having
to leave the party.
Factions aside, as a senior
member of the party,
I wish you would give Assemblyman Jin
a chance to work within the party.
The bus has already left.
The last one, at that.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Eat slowly! You're going
to get indigestion.
-Yes.-Chew your food.
You have to eat it with stew.
-Awesome.-Is it good?
Yes, thank you, Oppa.
Eat it well.
Jin Joo Hee, be honest.
You came here because you
got in trouble with your
mom for not studying.
Not at all! I came here to
play with Oppa Gyu Hwan.
With me?
You're going to play
with me, right?
Oh. Sure.
-Thanks, Oppa.-Playing
around, I see.
-Assemblyman.-Aide.
Aide Choi, come and
have some with us.
Yes. Come here.
I think the general
meeting of the Gyeongjae
local party members will
be held as planned.
What does that mean?
I thought Secretary
General Baek surrendered.
Park Choon Seop is being stubborn and even
Secretary General Baek cannot control him.
Then what will happen?
There is no other way than to attend the
meeting and to plead its injustice.
What if I still get impeached?
Do I then leave the party?
Yes.
We are going to prepare
Assemblyman's speech for the
general meeting and a plea
to the party members.
Secretary Kim, you search
the Assembly intranet and
find the materials I'm going
to dictate to you now.
Yes.
First of all, we are going to point out the
impracticality of the new harbor project
and the evils of
politicians' indiscriminate,
oversubscribed election
promises of development.
The basic data of the current status
of general matters in Gyeongjae;
the history of former
assemblymen's and governors'
promises of development and
whether they were carried out;
large-scale construction
projects halted in the
middle anywhere in the nation
during the last decade;
cases of projects that
were completed only to
turn into eyesores. All
of them, understand?
-Yes. I got it.-Read it.
Umm, first, the new
port project...
Enough. Get that
organized, okay?
Park Choon Seop, you bastard.
Order all Pro-BH members in
Gyeongjae City to mobilize.
They are to attend the general meeting and
cast votes of confidence for Jin Sang Pil.
I understand.
But the number of
Anti-BH members is
overwhelming and we need
some special measure.
Under the circumstances, it's hard
to come up with a countermeasure.
For now, it's enough that we
make sure of this one thing.
Never forgetting today's
ignominy and humiliation.
Plea to the Gyeongjae
Party Members
If I find even one typo, I'm going to make
you run laps around the Assembly Main Hall.
Don't worry.
Aish, should I have gone with
a more stoic-sounding title?
It feels too self-deprecating,
or maybe not?
Aide-nim, are you aware that
you're very elated right now?
-Me?-Yes.
We're in an emergency situation
but you're enjoying it.
You see, I am the type that enjoys the
atmosphere of an emergency situation.
You know the political
field entails endless
EMERGENCY SITUATIONS: much
like a war without guns.
Aide, do you really like
politics that much?
Yes, it's one of very few
jobs that can change
the world, whether in
a big or small way.
The way I see it, I think everything
is turning for the worst.
That's because a person
like you contributes to it.
Be honest. How many
times have you voted?
Except for the absentee voting I did while
in the military, I never voted even once.
How pathetic you are.
What's so pathetic about me?
In this unfair world,
the vote is one thing
that you and a conglomerate
son have in common.
You threw that away?
There has to be a person
that I want to vote for.
If there's no one good, then
choose the lesser evil.
That way the most
evil won't win.
The one who isn't so bad is still a
bad person. Why would I do that?
Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan. Engrave this
saying of Plato on your mind.
"The price good men pay for
indifference to public affairs
is to be ruled by evil men."
If you become an assemblyman
that people applaud,
then, I'll come down.
Let's meet then.
Gyeongjae City Gookmin Party
Members' Emergency General Meeting
MOTION: To Put Jin
Sang Pil, Head of the
Local Party Chapter, to
a Vote of Confidence
Head of the local party chapter
Jin Sang Pil did not stop
at disappearing and causing
hit-list related disturbances.
He also committed an
unpardonable act of opposing
all Gyeongjae citizens'
long cherished wish,
namely securing a new southeast
regional harbor infrastructure here.
We can no longer acknowledge
Jin Sang Pil as our head
when he has dishonored Gyeongjae
City and Gookmin Party members.
Don't you think so everyone?
Don't be nervous.
Republic of Korea Parliament
Just read what it says here.
Aide Choi...
can I just say what
I want to say?
Do it that way.
Thank you.
Next, we will hear
President Jin Sang Pil's
refutation.
Please come up.
Yes, I am the current Assemblyman
representing Gyeongjae,
and President of the local
party chapter, Jin Sang Pil.
Well, because I am not
really crafty with words,
I'll briefly say a few words.
Actually, things like
votes of confidence...
I really am not afraid of that.
However,
the thing that really scares me
is that the people of Gyeongjae
may be fooled about
that absurd...
new harbor project.
Who is being fooled?
He's saying nonsensical things.
Even more scary is that new harbor
being built in our Gyeongjae City
by some illogical insistence.
Into that irrational project, without
any economic feasibility at all...
for sure, there will be poured from
a few tens of million of dollars...
to a few hundreds of millions.
That money belongs to the people of
Gyeongjae. It's the people's money.
Yes, of course, the
government and politicians...
will get behind us a lot
in the beginning...
granting special benefits. Because
they can't let the truth be known.
Even forcing ships headed to another
harbor to turn around toward our harbor...
They will make a big fuss,
doing whatever it takes.
So let's say that our
Gyeongjae City...
becomes a wealthy town,
with money to burn.
But is our Gyeongjae City
the only town in Korea?
Even if we have to suck all the
marrow out of other townspeople...
if only we can eat well and live
well, then is everything hunky-dory?
Is that something a local
assemblyman should say?!
Look here!
I'm not a city councilman.
I'm not a ward councilman. I
am a national assemblyman...
who must think of the whole
of the Korean people.
My Aide Choi In Kyung said this.
When you become
an assemblyman...
there is an oath you take.
Yes, I stammered a lot at that time.
It was very difficult
because everything was written
in Chinese characters.
What is written there...
is the people's liberty,
promoting welfare, putting
the national interest first,
conscience!
These three things are the gist.
I...
will not be a marketing
agent who makes a pitch...
for regional self-centeredness.
I! A real national assemblyman
who thinks of the whole country
and the people all together!
I!
I want to be a true
national assemblyman...
who can stand tall and proud...
before the people.
I truly want to be
that kind of assemblyman
of the Republic of Korea.
That's all.
Dead Set Against
New Gyeongjae Port
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Now we will vote.
How did it turn out?
Oh, really, okay. Good job.
Did the results come out?
By a 52% share of no confidence,
the impeachment succeeded.
Since they barely made it, I guess Jin
Sang Pil put up a pretty good fight.
Now, if Jin Sang Pil
just leaves the Party,
we can get Baek Do Hyeon.
Secretary General, you have to communicate
immediately with Assemblyman Jin.
Stay still.
We have to stop his
defection by any means.
-If Assemblyman Jin
defects...-For God's sake!
Stay still.
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki
You don't have to be
listless like this.
It's like you lost a battle,
but you won the war.
I did the right thing, right?
You were the best.
Then, it's enough.
If Aide Choi said I was the
best then it was the best.
You did well.
I know that.
Why is he acting like that?
Assemblywoman Cheon.
It was a moving statement,
Assemblyman Jin.
Not at all.
But what brought
you to Gyeongjae?
Are you here to offer him
your party membership?
Well, if he wants to
come, I will not oppose.
The reason I came here is,
I wanted to apologize for
past troubles I caused you.
I've been following you since the
new harbor breeze started to blow.
Assemblyman Jin,
I'm sorry.
No.
Kim Gyu Hwan!
After praising a person whom you called
a son-of-a-bi*ch when you were drunk,
are you feeling awkward?
But why would a person like that, in
order to become an assemblyman...
betray the laid-off workers?
So off the wall... Why would
you bring that up here?
Yes, Sunbae-nim.
My beloved hoobae, In Kyung,
this time, I'd like to
take advantage of you.
What do you mean?
I've just heard the news
from Gyeongjae City.
Let my party recruit
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
You called him a scumbag.
Why all of a sudden?
What do you mean why? He's
going to defect anyway.
Belonging to the Korean Democratic Party is
a lot more snazzy than being independent.
For us, too, if we secure the
Gyeongjae City District,
we can pride ourselves on
the fact that we are a
national political party in
fact as well as in name.
Our Assemblyman is
a bit expensive.
How much are you going to
pay for the signing bonus?
I'll call him the
best assemblyman.
Wow, the terms are not bad.
But I don't think I can make our assemblyman
into a migratory bird (pejorative term
for politicians who change political
affiliations whenever that suits their needs).
- In Kyung.- I'm sorry.
I am busy so...
Humph, this rascal...
The Korean Democratic
Party has informally
invited you to join their
party, but I declined it.
Wow, that defection thing...
is, I guess, scary indeed.
Even Secretary General
Baek surrendered.
And the opposition
parties are courting me.
What is this?
A defection statement for
the press conference.
You want me to defect?
I'm not that happy
about it, either.
But this is the
only way for now.
Defect for now and
stay independent
until Secretary General
Baek resigns from his post.
And then you can
return to the party.
But the party is not like a
bathroom you go in and out of.
Right, but the Gookmin Party will have
no choice but to accept you back.
Because you have
the casting vote.
What is a casting vote?
That one vote which resolves a
deadlock and decides the outcome.
That is what you are holding
right now, Assemblyman.
Not only can the majority government of the
governing party with its ratio of 151:149
be changed to a tie between
the parties, but also
in a deadlock situation between the
ruling and opposition parties,
your one vote can
change the landscape.
Still, I can't
allow a defection.
Just until Secretary
General Baek steps down.
Just a very brief
period will do.
After that, somehow, I
will get you Gookmin
Party's nomination.
Assemblyman, my goal
is to make you the next
assemblyman of Gyeongjae City.
Please concentrate
on our conversation.
What is that for you to be
fidgeting with it so much?
This?
It's the reason why I
became an assemblyman.
What?
Listen.
What is this for you to keep
telling me to listen...
Sang Pil, it's me, Dal Soo.
My original wish was just
to get back to work.
But now I have one more.
That is for you, Sang
Pil, to do well.
That you become an assemblyman
who gives hope to
people like us.
When you become an assemblyman
who is applauded by the
people, I will come down.
Aide Choi, what I
really want is...
to be applauded by the people.
A party nomination,
I can do without.
But a thing like defection...
I will never do it.
Assemblyman, then let's do this.
Secretary General, Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
will hold a press conference this evening
and make an important
announcement.
They are going up!
I am Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
I will read my statement
for the press conference.
For me, getting the Gookmin Party's
nomination for the next year's election
has become virtually impossible.
As such, I will tell you
about my next move.
From Gookmin Party, I...
Stop that cliff-hanging and just
spit out that you will defect.
I will not defect.
- I will not get hung up on a party
nomination, either.- Secretary General!
- I won't accept it even if they give
it to me.- What the hell was that?
Yes, I won't accept it even
if they give it to me.
I won't because it's so filthy.
Right, never.
Instead, I will remain in the
party and take on another task.
As you know, in our Gookmin
Party, there are two
FACTIONS: the Pro-BH and
the Anti-BH persuasions.
You all know, right? They fight day in
and day out, engaging in turf battles.
They are pundits when it
comes to back stabbing.
Two factions like that...
Pack-tions (Korean
pronunciation is gaepa,
where gae can mean dogs).
In order to stand up
to these rotten packs,
I have decided to
form a new faction.
Forgetting all selfish interests and
greed, only on the side of the people,
according to the people's will,
doing what the people want, that
is what the faction is about.
Even though I am the
sole member right now,
yes, I'm sorry, no one
has joined yet...
I'm alone.
If there are assemblymen
who share my thoughts,
I will welcome them any time.
What my faction wants
is just one thing.
And that's their fellow countrymen's
warm encouragement and applause.
That is all.
A faction, all of a sudden...
What did that person just say?
Within the ruling party,
he means to play the opposition party.
- What?- Assemblyman Jin
is right now saying
that he'll use his
casting vote as a weapon
and form a one-man opposition
party within the ruling party.
I'm sorry.
When you came back to get me re-elected...
I failed you.
That is okay.
Right now, I have a new goal.
Because of the people's
overwhelming support,
a true people's assemblyman to whom
the party has no choice
but to give a nomination.
Assemblyman Jin, what is
the name of that faction?
Name?
The name my aide supports is...
Gookmin (PEOPLE'S) Faction.
Gookmin Faction, but
for a mere faction's name, I dislike
using that sublime word, "people."
So I don't like that much.
So our faction name is...
I like neither Anti-BH
nor Pro-BH.
I will just go by Indifferent-to-BH.
Indifferent-to-BH?
That idiot. He's an idiot.
Yes, I will choose Indifferent-to-BH.
I like the sound of that.
That is all.
Oh, I will give my warning
to the party leadership
and to the Pro- and Anti-BH factions.
I can look there and do it, right?
From now on, when the
party decides something,
make sure to discuss it with
the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
If you look down on us
because of our small number,
and as you have been doing thus
far, if the Pro- and Anti-BH
factions engage in hanky-panky
and do shoddy work...
You just try that and see what happens...
In that event, the same
party color or whatever,
I will just kick your ass, all of you!
If you want to sanction me, sanction me.
If you want to expel me,
just try expelling me, huh?!
Ugh, what should I do
to that wet blanket...
Me, Jin Sang Pil, the big boss of
the Indifferent-to-BH faction!
JSP! I will never get scared!
You better be prepared, huh?!
No, that...!
Do you understand?!
Subtitles ripped by bozxphd Subtitles
by The Assembly Team @ Viki