Subtitles - English :
(as spoken in english audio)
Britain, 420 AD
The Roman Empire has called all its troops
home .. .
when it ended the occupation of the country,
leaving it in turmoil.
In every province of Britain,
the local tribal chief has declared himself
king of that region
and each king wars with
another for more territory.
Now, the Saxon Barbarians have started
invading the shores
trying to conquer Britain for themselves.
A Dark Age in Britain has begun.
The time lost in history.
The time of legends, violence, and bloodshed.
Magic and mythical creatures.
and of a great wizard named.
MERLIN.
MERLIN   "The War Of The Dragons"
That's right.
Push!
Push.
A message sir.
Reads: Kill the child.
Killing is the safest way.
But not the wisest.
This child
If the offspring of a demon
can be called a child.
I believe your daughter...
that no man, but rather an evil spirit come down...
and second advantage is of the basic goodness
and purity.
Nor, do I confess the  nature of her .....
... only the nature of the spirit.
which must have been evil
to fire herself.
One  needs  look no further at the chaos
in the Heavens of Pyra, My Lord!
To see basic evil ...
Quiet!
I'm tired of your words.
I... I'm tired of yours...
The pupil should not challenge the Master.
I've counselled you
so ...I did to your father,
and his father and his ..
and many other kings of Wales and Britain.
.. over these many years ..
Healing the plague and the famine.
Kept the Roman legions in proper fear ...
... of invading these lands.
Yes... You and your Druid priests...
.. took their pains and sacrifice when you need it.
Did you not ?
I want the child !
More! More !
I have seen a vision of the Oak tree...
associated with this child.
So you say this child's father is the...
... spirit of the underworld?
Evil spirits.
which is why, it is better
and safer to kill the child.
to have no evil spirits here.
Or would it be better not to risk ...
the wrath of dark Gods, by killing it !
20 years later...
Merlin, let me see.
Good.
One last lesson .
What would you like to learn ?
I would like to learn how to read minds.
A simple preposition...
To read a person's mind...
you must know heart.
Study them.
you must understand what it's like to be then.
Only then you'll be able to place yourself
in the minds of the eye.
and you will be able to read their minds.
But that is not magic.
Yes, but it also equally as well.
One should not think first of magic...
if you can
accomplish the thing  in other means.
Merlin, what would you like to learn ?
I would  like to learn how to create light.
The spell you  seek  is an ancient.
I rarely use it.
In dark places...
it would call attention to me ..
as much as it one's vision.
Let me try again.
That's what I would call
attention to one's ......
Has he ever shown you that book?
The Book of Spells?
No.
Hasn't he shown you ever ?
I doubt you  could even read it
And you could?
Ofcourse.
I have studied ancient scripts.
This 'Book of Secrets', handed down from one
..to the next.
One thousand years of knowledge.
we change
back into the Hiboriaanse Ages.
Everything we need is in that book.
He must have his reasons.
He's afraid.
You and I ,the power we have  is within us.
It was his ....from these pages .
I don't think we are so different from him.
May be hiding something from you.
Like what?
Has he ever told you who your father is?
We are orphans.
If he knew who is our father
he would have told us.
You're naive.
There are spells in that book,
that you can read the past.
Show you where you came from.
He is hiding  not from you.
Do not you want to know who you really are?
Use your spell.
come along
to me.
It is enchanted!
-...keep watch !
abracadabra
How did you get ?
I do not know.
It .. just ... by itself.
Ask it something.
Show Merlin his father !
His father.
Focus on that.
Claus.
Merlin.
Vendiger, put it down!
Paira ..Release him!
Release him ..
Release him... Paira
abracadabra
I've failed...
all  What I ...telling you
I cann't see now.
Has great power .. in this book.
Neither you nor Merlin are ready.
I disagree.
If you wish to remain under my guardianship,
Master Vendiger
... you will adhere to the time and honour the traditions.
I trained you as I was trained.
and show  the magicians before me.
Now, Come on.
Let us fix what is needed.
Merlin needs our help.
So, is about Merlin, isn't it?
I have no favorites.
Really?
If it were I ,
call from the ground like a crying baby?
How can you say, I am worried ?
I left him there to attend to you.
You  came for the book.
You and Merlin're like sons to me
You're not my father.
Come.
There are things to do.
Merlin needs you
There is still time to undo the damage
which you have done
You're making a mistake.
I have failed you too.
I need your help.
Bless the gods and...
I would not finish, if I were you.
Will you help me?
Is this the great Merlin?
Rest, Merlin.
Merlin , Good morning .
I would like you to introduce to the Lady Nimue.
Hello.
Where am I?
My sanctuary.
Private study.
Deep within the earth, beneath the Oak Tree.
Here one can work undisturbed.
Well, it is the home of Lady Nimue
What happened to me?
Vendiger's spell put you
in contact with your father.
That thing...
That could not be my father.
I'm afraid so.
I am no child of a demon.
Your vision...
was not about an Oak tree?
We need more proof than a mere birth mark.
Turn it over and one can see an Oak tree...
... yet this way, See something entirely different.
Who you are, does not come from your father or mother.
Not even your status or your family.
Who'll be...
comes from you within.
You're the offspring of God.
But how much of these powers lying in you...
... and for what purposes you would use them,
only you can determine
What is she?
- One such ...can be powerful allies
... otherwise the enemies.
There are many Gods...
Still about in this world...
if you choose to see them .
Not what you expected, huh?
EMPIRIA
to me!
Dragon! Dragon !
Dragon! Dragon ! Dragon !!!
Fight!
Please, every one...
I'm just a traveler passing through...
I only ask  one thing...
That we shall celebrate this night together.
that we can share this water .. for victory!
Drink.
We should attack before
the spirits weakened
Every day, people  leave our ranks.
Hengest, has taken us this far, perhaps you know ?
We should take the kingdom for ourselves.
Instead of protecting these fools...
..from our labour.
I wish to join your army.
What skills could you possibly have ?
100 of your finest men...
can not kill me.
Naive Ling, I'll crush you right now.
May be, sir.
Aren't you curious that why I
would make such a claim ?
What is it you want?
I want what you want.
Are you not Hengest...
..who hated Vortingen, and the Picts
drove in securing the kingdom ?
Same, if I am correct.
which was rewarded by being expelled...
from the very large .. spell  bloodhood.
I want the same as you.
Take back what is mine.
Well, Tom !
the verdict remains the same.
The Gods are telling that evil is approaching ...
Evil that threatens the foundation of your kingdom.
Evil, that has been brought about a dark spirit,
that took human form
and has now reached adulthood.
His power...
strengthens Saxon
and is back to this land...
... to over run it, to become his servant
and
to kill all who stand in his way.
So you  must kill him.
It's Merlin.
Before he means death for us all.
Mage!
We've come for a guy called Merlin.
Come on, now.
No!
But... No!
You must have some idea.
For the hundredth time... No!
I see you never wearing gun.
My weapon... is up .. here!
I'm sorry to hear that.
Is it your magic, that protects you?
Show me something.
What do you like to watch ?
Make something.
How about ??
Supper !
Magic is not something that is use it on whim
He can not do it.
He thinks not.
INMRI Hira
You first.
smell that?
Picts.
This is nuetral territory.
.. Come and leave as they please
You wish you have  a  weapon on you now .
It is he... the evil one.
I know nothing.
I know the terror agencies of the evil spirits.
They bringing down troubles upon us.
Now... shall be slain.
And your blood will be scattered
around the castle grounds....
...to appease the gods.
This is the only way that the Gods...
... will realize our committments to the task
to relieve this land of all evils.
I think its worthy that the Gods
help
to defeat Saxons.
You'll destroy yourself only hope...
in defeating Saxon?
Mage.
I have seen visions of the one
who bears the mark of Oak Tree.
He will bring ruins on us.
death and destruction.
It is your ...life to be
so wrong in your vision.
Voltinger ..
Why do you create a storm...
... so low over the ground rages
and to reach the sky
What do you see?
A Dragon.
A White Dragon.
What?
I see it too !
There!
Dragon!
Archers, Take the wall.
We may not be abe to destroy .
At least we should try.
We must  work together.
Who sent you?
Mage!
We now have a chance to escape to the beast.
Kill him!
My Lord, this man saved my life.
He predicted the dragon.
Your own counsel, this has not seen.
He comes back.
He brought the dragon to us.
We have to kill him while we still have time.
In the forest!
Thanks.
Casualities ?
Only one.we were forced them down .
We are forced to withdraw.
Voltinger, we're not the enemy.
We can survive only if
we work together.
I suspect a wave of attacks , soon.
My outposts have  seen
no such invaders.
Did you...the fine, of these dragons?
You should not forget whom you are talking to.
I will never forget who you are, Sir.
'll Follow the dragons back to their masters.
I want to go with you.
Teach me how I can transform into a hawk
and I will follow you.
No.
You go to Linn Augin, bring Excalibur.
Excalibur?
You must get it from a lady Vivian.
Vivian?
Nimue's sister.
How do I find her?
Go to Linn Augin.
She will find you.
But remember...
the gods have little in common with the
mortal men.
You must not let her...
detain you.
Now go.
I can't help here.
Bring Excalibur.
Prepare youself for an attack.
I would set up defensive positions
and keep out of the open.
How dare you tell me
how to run my army?
If you want to survive ,yes ..
I would dig in.
I do not think that attack
was the worstof it.
Does he know who you really are?
No.
Wise to keep that.
Gods ..speed !
Vivian!
I seek...
the Lady Vivian!
Mage sends his regards.
What we really need right now
is your help !
So that if you kindly show yourself !
and I should...!
You be  ...the Lady Vivian.
And you be...
the famous Merlin.
Are you  not talking ?? ??
The Mage has sent me to ask you...
.. for Excalibur.
Yes.
I ....I give it to you ...the same offer
... I gave to Mage
I will give you something...
You must give something back to me.
What do you want?
I want to ...
what is in here.
You are not going to find a lot .
ou don't think yourself much less .
What can learn a hell of God in me?
Excalibur!
Forged in the Hiboriaan Age before ..man ...
It can catch  the hide of a dragon.
The blades with special light,
to blind the enemies.
The scabbard, however simple it may be ,
has powers as well.
While  wearing  the scabbage,
one can suffer great injuries, yet...
... it will heal.
A word of warning...
While this blade has great powers,
it is not suitable for all .
It rewards the virtuous, the righteous,
and the pure heart.
It destroys the unworthy.
To remove it from its scabbage,
it will reveal to you who really are .
Excalibur will exactly .. price ,
If you are not... worthy.
Thank you.
You can not keep Excalibur.
It must be returned to me,
you,
shall bring it back.
I shall take this.
I would not do that if I were you.
Why is that ?
Excalibur rewads only the worthy
... you're worthy?
The Bastard son of a whore mother...
and the demons from the underworld?
.. slay with this blade
Merlin?
What are you doing here?
I had a vision.
Vision?
Who did this?
Vendiger
What are you looking for?
I fear my "Book of Secrets."
Lost its way.
Did you find it?
No.
That's good.
Where did you hide it?
So you're the Dragon Master.
You're losing your sense.
I suppose I have ...
I selected...
... such a poor candidate for schooling,
I knew it was a risk,
to take you in ...
knowing where you came from.
You...
... had so much promise .
But if proved to have little
talent.
Feel it !
The Book of Secrets.
Where is it?
That...
I invested thousands of years of knowledge...
your hands.
Feel it .
Feel it!
Mage !
No, no, no, no!
It's lodged in my heart.
My time of death is now.
No.
No, you can not!
You're the only one...
whom I would much trust...
my faith.
for you has always .
You closely look like my son.
Listen to me...
To combat dragons...
... it is written in the Book of Secrets.
You take my body  .....
to the lake Augin.
It will be the only way...
Lady Vivian...
will  show way to you .
But remember....
The gods have lttle in common...
with  mortal men...
It's...
the truth.
Mage!
You see that?
Hengest.
The tables have turned.
I, once the servant...
'll soon become a master.
It is inevitable.
It's up to you to decide...
How painful the transition shall be.....
You replace the centry by the mountain side.
What is this battle plan?
All in the open...
The men who gathered here today...
... are the finest fighting men of Britain.
You have served me and your crown well.
Today, I ask you
one more sacrifice.
Lay down your arms...
... and Hengest has guaranteed
me your survival.
Throw down your weapons
and walk away from this field of the battle...
... and you will be able to return
to your farms ..
and villages.
Hengest has guaranteed that you
families ...
will be spared if you do this.
If you are disobeying... you will be destroyed.
Men of Britain.
If you lay down and walk away..
you will not be free.
Voltigan wants to take away what
he has never possessed.
Your souls.
If you give them today,
you will be vassals...
... servants for a new king.
Vortigen will certainly be rewarded...
... for the success of your capitulation.
But you, each and every
one of you ...
who go back to your families ...
not as free men,
but slaves.
because I was angry, these
Saxon men of not their words.
Do not think they will be afraid
from  attacking  your villages...
... slaving your children,
taking your women...
Look what they've done so far.
Imagine what they would do again...
We will not ..go down,
without a fight.
Are you with me?
How can we defeat their army and their
dragons?
only offering me the brave words.
a sure death for us all.
Death in battle is a good death,
and think about this...
Though the chances are same ,
we may prevail .
We have more allies than you may know.
Our people go home, many of
Saxonca 3 to 1...
if we give it today, all hope
will be destroyed.
If you give it today, you lose your soul ,
and  man without a soul is dead !!
Are you ready !!?
Are you with me?
Yes!
How dare you speak to me  this way?
Inciting me in this direction ..
I shall execute you for treason.
No, its you  will be executed.
You committed treason
long time ago when you killed my father.
Umbanish Ambrosis ia an eye in your kingdom ...
.... and you have committed treason today...
... by forcing our people into slavery.
But I will avenge  this treason.
Voltigen!
I told you that he would not
surrender without a fight.
Shall I?
Not yet. Send the infantry.
Soldiers...
Attack!
Send your dragons,
Master Vendiger.
But our men are still on the battlefield.
... what about our men ?
These are now God's men, now .
Fly, my children.
Fly.
He is to be taken to Avilon.
Avilon?
Avilon.
The resting place of the gods.
And now...
from the Mage.
There are no ones that have gods as their patron.
so, those are keen, who earned his patronation,
his knowledge of the secrets of magic.
Which is by way the reason
I have come here.
That is Mage's The Book of Secrets.
I.
The Book of Secrets.
Thank you.
You can not take it from here.
The Mage made me promise to do,
it never...the world of the man again.
Whatever you need from it ,
you'll scan it here.
But he never told me how to break the ......
No , I .
Do we have new information for the troops?
Not yet. But that  will come.
Word?
Word, word, word?
or phrase may be .
If you have tasks I keep you from ...
No.
Instead of going to spell after spell
in your mind ...
Would not it be more helpful to them
saying them aloud?
Perhaps can  I hear something familiar.
Or.... ...
I can learn from you.
You and your ploy have failed.
... our army lies intact,
but my battalion  ... dead.
Have the Dragons moved down ?
Yes, moved on to our families and homes.
Nobody to defend them.
Had we listened to Vortigen's wish ...
... many men are still alive,
to fight again.
Do you know , things would have
happened if thrown down weapons...
Hengest... you'd have to live?
He would have you butchered like dogs.
Yet,we are butchered like dogs, Uther.
Do you want to help?
Everyone here is working
Take an axe.
Your words are tiresome.
I can see no hope for you.
You're wrong.
As long as we still alive, there is hope.
And I also have hope in other,
Soon will return.
Who?
Merlin.
Merlin? He has probably fled... to another
region.
He will not be seen here again .
He'll return.
No doubt  he faces life ... in danger ....
do so, even now.
Merlin, you must leave here.
... If you do not leave ,
Lady Vivian will imprison you forever.
Why would she do that?
It's a cat's play for a mouse .
... You   have count  .. interest of her.
And the last time for you,
if the movement doesn't start .
She gave me the Excalibur.
And she made you to get it back, is it not?
I can not leave now.
Not until I get the knowledge
I seek.
Tell her you're leaving now...
and see what reaction you must get.
You... are a prisoner...
... and she will kill you
once you show access to the book.
We Gods have little in common with mortal
men.
It's... the truth.
The Gods have little in common with mortal...
men.
It is
truth.
True.
Thank you so much for...
your help.
The truth...
Will be...
In Veritas
Show me the spell
to slay a dragon.
Any luck ?
No.
I think I'll give up.
....  by  this book ,
is beyond me.
I have to join the battle before
what all is lost.
You may leave ..
any time you like.
May I suggest you,
try a little longer.
Think...
Think which you can gain...
... if you can get access to this book
If one drinks the blood of the dragon...
... one can become like him.
You're a tricky one .. Merlin
.. pretending you had not solved the riddle
I think I'll be going now...
If you please , return me to the surface.
You promised you'd hep me in learning ...
... the secrets of magic.
in ... the working of nature.
I would love to stay and help...
but,I have to join my people
so if you please .....
You're one of us...
... we are your people, Merlin .
I'm only half your kind.
and if .... you  care not for others,
I would  cut how myself ........
to Ocean.
Merlin,
I did not think that I will not help you.
Abracadabra
Thank you. You were right.
Do you have the book?
No.
I left in the room.
She can not access it.
I learned everything that I need
fnow.
We need the book.
If you kindly return
me to the surface ...
No, you'll never leave !
Not until you show me ..
... how to access it ?
You Go!
I'm sorry I did not trust you.
We shall see each other again.
And you...
shall make it up to me.
I'll return it .
I see you've managed ...
what I expected.
Yes.
The Dragon Lord and Hengest
want them ...
... on the run.
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
Who is the swiftest rider?
This sword, how easy it looks, also has powers
while wearing this scabbage,
one can suffer great injuries...
... yet it will heal
Are you sure this spell will work?
If you take it out of free will...
... I can change it back ....
free will.
What if you die in battle?
You change back into a human as well .
..just like Vendigers dragons will do.
Only  we need are dragons keep
long enough for...
to go and kill their masters...
and then the victory is ours.
I will do it !
and I .
Are you really sure ..... ?
Definitely.
Merlin!
Attack!
Reinforcements it with the archers.
Leave this wizard to me.
Closer will not come.
You're not the only son of Paira.
It does not have to be like this
Merlin !
Join me.
And together we can rule Britain.
Never!
Look at the sky...
your dragons dropping like stones
unable to defeat mine!
Tell me where is the book, Merlin.
A quick death is better than
.. I need to pull from your mind.
You speak as if you've won already.
I'll win, Merlin.
I was always the true power behind
Hengest.
If he falls, the Saxons will follow me.
Its my dragons,
who inspire them .
Its my magic that will conquer Britain
and rule, as the God .. I am.
Now Merlin, you'll see the truth.
Our birthright ...
the power of dark gods inside us.
Merlin,
It would be wrong not to embrace it.
No.
He taught me more  important things....
this sword can slay a wizard
just as can any man.
but now you will all die!
This Britain will not die that easily.
You're free!
I can get used to it.
See here , Uther!
...  your new king!
As I  knew...
... you would return .to me
For today only .
Today,
or may be a few days.
We shall see.
End.
Subtitles-English
by  srjanapala