Mr. Back
In the blue Tumen River...
A boatman is rowing a boat.
A lover from my past is riding on it.
Where did the boat that left go?
Father.
My lover I miss so much.
My lover that I miss so much.
When will she come back?
Who are you?
- Stop singing that song.
- What is it?
I said stop singing it!
I know I saw him.
Where did he go?
Choi Shin Hyung.
What are you doing out here?
You should have come inside.
Why would you stay out here?
I was just passing by.
I didn't want to
interrupt your conversation.
Come inside with me, will you?
- Let's go.
- Well...
Eun Ha Soo, step away from him.
Director Choi, what's the matter?
Because he's someone who is
eventually going to leave soon.
Don't fall for him.
What do you know to say that?
I think I have a good idea who you are.
- What?
- Chairman Choi Go Bong.
Father.
What nonsense is that?
The reed pipe.
You won't say you learned that
from my late father, too, right?
I learned it from him.
Why do you doubt that?
As to who you really are...
- That you could be my father...
- Does that even make sense?
Of course it makes no sense...
but then how can I explain
this strange feeling?
Stop the nonsense. I'm leaving.
Come on, why are you doing this again?
I thought you two were
becoming close lately.
You give me no choice. Here.
Hold each other's hands.
Leave together, okay? I'll get going.
Goodbye.
[Episode 9]
Dae Han almost figured it out.
He was so close.
Then just tell him
that you're his father.
Why can't you say that?
That's because...
Hey you, where are you taking me, huh?
What are you doing?
I asked what you were doing!
Thanks to the creature who claims
he was in his 70s and is now in his 30s
we now see the possibility of
discovering the fountain of youth.
No! No!
Let go of me! Let go!
What are you doing? Let go of me!
You bastards! I will kill you all
when I get out of here.
If people find out what happened to me
they'll try to do experiments on me.
What kind of imagination is that?
You've become quite weak, haven't you?
What I was saying is that
you're still his family.
You should tell him one day.
The family I used to know has changed.
I'm looking into this as
Choi Shin Hyung, not Choi Go Bong.
You scared me.
I left you two alone so you could talk.
Why are you here?
How flustered must it have
made Choi Shin Hyung?
How could you possibly say that
he was someone already deceased?
I don't know what it all
might sound like to you...
But he resembles him so much
that I had to say it.
But still, how could you possibly
land on such an absurd conclusion?
Forget it. I'm hungry,
so let's just go and eat.
Have you ever been to
a pojangmacha before?
Of course, I have.
I really like places like this.
Don't they have a menu here?
- Here they have...
- Oh my.
Chicken feet, stir-fried cartilage,
chicken gizzard, stir-fried eel, and cockles.
Today, I can recommend
the fresh cockles.
Other than that, we have healthy items
like ginkgo nuts, steamed pupa...
If you are hungry,
there's udon and ramen.
What do you think?
Will you drink with me?
Slow down.
No one is hurrying you.
I see that you can drink.
I'm just like my late father.
- No one has ever beat me in drinking.
- Is that right?
Then should we bet on it?
I'm Chairman Choi Go Bong's son, too.
What's wrong? Not feeling confident?
Fine.
I'll fix your drinking habits tonight.
- Please stop.
- Come on.
Drink some liquor and work it out.
Bring more liquor!
You still have some here.
There's something about me
that you should know.
I'd drink from my late father's
hard liquor cabinet
without him knowing
when I was in middle school.
I'd fill the empty bottles
with barley tea afterward.
I bet my father never knew
about that until he passed away.
Our late father knew about that.
You drank three bottles of
hard liquor he treasured.
Those were 30-year-old liquors.
He also knew that you even
consumed a bottle of wild ginseng wine.
Father...
Are you my father?
Father. I think you're my father.
Father, Father! Father!
Father, I've missed you.
Father, Father.
Father.
I'm... I'm your father, okay?
Don't be ridiculous.
My late father, you see...
he was very cool.
He was very intelligent, too.
And his nose was pointier than yours.
He didn't have deep wrinkles
around his mouth like you do.
Well, he had a nasty temper...
I'm the one who's crazy
for thinking that you were him.
Father.
How did he figure it out?
Could it be that he can
recognize his father or what?
[Choi Go Bong, you have 22 days
to return on your payment.]
The days... have dwindled again.
Does this mean that
I only have this long to live?
If not...
My youth will last...
48 days?
What does this mean?
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
How did I get home last night?
Man, why did you drink
so much last night?
Here it is. Catch.
Shin Hyung gave it to me.
It must be yours.
Hello there.
Oh my.
He's just like my late father
who puts on too much toner.
He looks like he's in his thirties.
It's completely nuts.
Step away from Choi Shin Hyung.
Because he's someone who is
eventually going to leave soon.
Don't fall for him.
He's going to leave soon?
What did he mean that
he's going to leave?
I have no idea what he meant by that.
This week
we'll be evaluating you based on
the comments from our guests.
Try your best to keep the guests happy.
- Smile.
- Smile!
Now, things we should
never say to our guests.
Shout out three things we never say.
'You cannot do that.'
'We don't have it.' 'I don't know.'
Three things that
all employees should do!
Smile on our faces,
kindness in our hearts
- and satisfaction for our guests.
- Good, now back to work!
Thank you.
What do I do?
If we receive negative feedback,
we won't be hired as full-time employees.
That's completely up to chance.
Let's hope to get nice guests. Fighting!
- Fighting!
- Let's go.
Welcome.
How may I help you?
Are you certain that Manager Sung
helped him in changing his identity?
It seems that way.
Why would he have
to steal someone else's identity?
Shall I have lunch with my brother?
I'll have the same thing, please.
Isn't it enough to see you at home?
Now you want to eat with me here?
Can you imagine how jealous
others are of us?
Don't you think so, Manager Hong?
- Then...
- Stick around for a bit.
One of the branch hotels
of our resort...
I'm talking about Seohae Hotel.
If you let me take it over
- I'll revive it.
- Do you even know what it is?
It's a headache that has pulled in
no profits for the past three years.
It's not profitable,
but a waste to abandon.
It's our late father's inheritance.
- Don't even think about it.
- How come?
The Cruise Hotel from our late father
wasn't enough for you?
To revive Seohae Hotel,
you need a special team.
Did you have anything planned?
About Seohae Hotel...
It may look like a headache
and a lousy hotel chain...
but actually, it was
our late father's hidden card.
I thought I told you not to
butt in on my business again.
And Seohae Hotel is not
something for you to talk about.
Seriously.
Hey, Choi Dae Han.
A premium outlet where
Seohae Hotel is located?
- Push forward with it.
- Are you serious?
Bravo. Great. Good decision.
As expected, your hegemony
is smart and elite.
Honey, why are you suddenly
in speaking English lately?
Was my pronunciation okay?
Yi Hye humiliated me because of it.
I decided to speak in English
from now on.
It's great that you two think alike.
Of course.
If anybody works like we do,
there's nothing they can't do.
No problem. You can do it!
Enough.
Director Jung, I hope things will
work out with Manager Hong.
- Is there anything I can do to help?
- No, it's okay.
Manager Hong? Wait a minute.
She seems to have feelings
for Dae Han, though.
No. Don't act like an amateur.
Anyway, the bottom line is that
we have to make this work, right?
That's right.
No problem.
Mission Impossible.
Miss, can I talk to you?
- Yes, ma'am.
- About this resort...
I designed this resort myself.
How do you like it?
- Did you really?
- Yes, I did.
- Can I have an espresso?
- Yes.
This espresso isn't hot enough.
- Did you expect me to drink this?
- I'm sorry. I will bring another one.
And what's wrong with this blanket?
- Don't you have cotton?
- Pardon?
Also, how come my name isn't on here?
I'm the one who designed this place!
How come my name isn't in here?
Did you do that?
- How come my name isn't on it?
- Please, ma'am.
I designed this place.
Why isn't my name on it, huh?
- Tell me why my name isn't on it. Why?
- Ma'am.
- Why not?
- What are you doing now?
Let go of me!
Go Bong.
Go Bong. You're Go Bong, right?
- What's going on?
- Ma'am.
This is Chairman Choi Go Bong's son.
What do you mean?
I can tell that he's Choi Go Bong.
You may fool other people,
but you can't fool me.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
Can you let go of me?
- Do something, will you?
- Go Bong.
It's me.
It's me, Go Bong...
Go Bong.
Hi there.
Director Choi, no, President Choi.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Can I ask you something?
Yes. What is it?
There's something I can't throw away.
But if I had to throw it away
what should I do?
Well, I'm not sure.
If the reality is different
from what you pictured
shouldn't you make
the reality work for you?
You're an idealist, aren't you?
Could I also ask you a question?
Everyone is worried because
of the guests' evaluation.
I want to try my best
to do a good job...
but if a person doesn't know what
my intentions are, what should I do?
That must be very upsetting.
Then you should let the person know.
No matter what it takes.
- You're a realist, huh?
- Am I?
What was that about?
Should we pick and choose
the guests from now on?
What are you mumbling about?
Let's go. Hurry.
Do you have a different plan
for Seohae Hotel?
The only way for President Choi Dae Han
to persuade the board of directors
is if he proves himself in
handling Seohae Hotel.
When did you start to have feelings
for him, Manager Hong?
I understand it was an order from
the late Chairman Choi, however...
Could you take this away?
He doesn't eat peanut sauce.
Aren't I right?
Chairman Choi Go Bong.
I saw Director Jung earlier.
I think he was asking Kang Gi Chun
to do something in secret.
Do you have any idea what that might be?
There will be a lot of people
coming to see you soon.
Pardon?
In preparation for that day,
I'll write something for you.
What will you write?
You have a gallstone.
- Gallstone?
- Yes.
Can you see it over there?
Inside the heart artery
there's something that
looks like a small rock.
A small rock?
Why would it be in there?
Could t be the meteor?
Meteor?
What should I do then?
You can get it surgically removed,
or use other non-surgical methods, too.
Would you like me to schedule
the surgery then?
No, I'll come by again
at a later time.
How come Dr. Kim hasn't
called from Africa yet?
It may take a long time.
He said he'd definitely win
the Nobel Prize this time.
- I have sweet potatoes!
- Great to have them here!
- Ta-da.
- Hey.
Don't eat them here
Move them away!
How picky is your customer this time?
He's as picky as the late Chairman Choi
I met at Silver town.
Oh my.
But he didn't have Alzheimer's.
- Alzheimer's?
- Yes.
- He was close.
- It's coming along.
Eun Ha Soo, what are you up to?
That's fine.
I'll eat some later.
I'm not an idiot, am I?
What kind of moron am I?
Why would you call?
Did you mean to ask
what I was up to?
Did you understand that?
How could someone not able
to text in this day and age?
Well, I just never had
a reason to text.
I'll make sure to teach you
when I see you tomorrow.
Oh, will you?
Did you text me wondering
what I was up to?
Well...
If you're free tomorrow,
will you go somewhere with me?
Sure.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo!
Wow!
Wow. For me, too?
- Get in!
- Let's go!
What is this place?
Just come down. Hello.
Are you two a couple?
Yes, but we prefer to get
our massages separately.
Can I check your skin types first?
Sir, please come this way.
I can't do that. I won't do it.
Seriously. Sit down.
I don't want to waste the coupons.
A lot of men come to places
like these nowadays.
- Don't they?
- Of course.
That's amazing.
This is it.
Here, go in and have a good time.
This is so wrong.
Are there any male employees here?
How long do I have to be here for?
- What's the matter?
- What?
- It's nothing. I'm okay.
- One second. I'll be right over.
No way. Don't come over!
Don't you come over!
I feel like I've just
experienced the afterlife.
Your skin has become
all plump and rested.
What am I supposed to do?
Why does she keep getting more beautiful?
- What is this?
- You don't know what this is?
This is what a date should be.
It's the main menu at a cafe.
An herb tonic tea with egg drops.
I see. A herb tonic tea
with egg drops...
But I'm not so sure about the yolk.
Shh. Just try some.
You may not have tried it yet...
but you can never stop with one sip.
That's what this herb tonic tea
with egg drops is all about.
Oh, it's tasty.
See? What did I say?
By the way, about the woman
from yesterday...
she said she designed
Daehan Resort herself.
What? Did she?
She said she designed the building
and asked if I liked it.
She was mad at me because
her name wasn't in the pamphlet.
Was she Designer Park then?
Then did she really design the place?
Come to think of it,
she does resemble her.
But she seems to have dementia.
She walks around the hotel barefoot.
I might have heard that
she had Alzheimer's.
My word. She was so
smart and pretty, too.
- How could she have dementia?
- You knew her well?
- No, I heard about her from my father.
- I see.
She must have been confused
since you two look so much alike.
Seeing her act that way, she must've been
very close to the late Chairman Choi.
No, she wasn't.
She was just a business partner.
I have a feeling that I'll like
this herb tonic tea with egg drops.
You will, right? I thought so.
Seohae Hotel?
If you spend tons of money
in renovating the place
- Do you think it will revive itself?
- Director Jung.
Don't you know that
we're in a financial crisis?
It's supposed to be a busy season now.
But the profit isn't even close
to 30 percent of what it was last year.
We'll find more investors.
How much damage will you bring upon
again using someone else's money?
Why would you act this way
when you want me to fail so badly?
What?
I haven't even started
any kind of construction yet.
Why? Because if I borrow money
from the resort
you think you'll be the one
to suffer the consequences?
President Choi.
Bring me something innovative
instead of this hideous business plan.
Since that's the only way
you'll receive any funding.
This is how anything gets started.
Don't be discouraged.
If my father were here...
What would he do right now?
I'm telling you that's not right.
The characters for Choi
for your name is over here.
- You add this dot here.
- Okay.
- What is this?
- How can you not press it properly?
I won't do it. I won't do it!
I'd rather not do it.
You're impossible.
Here, look at it.
If you want to add something,
press this, okay?
I know that.
I told you I knew that.
Gosh, what is this?
Choi Shin Nyeo?
You wouldn't listen to me
and are so impatient.
How mean. Give it to me.
I'll learn it by myself.
- Give it to me.
- Don't bother.
- I'll do it by myself.
- You're so stubborn.
Listen carefully now.
This is the last time
I'm going to teach you.
- Okay, then do it slowly.
- Okay.
If you want to write Choi Shin Hyung,
you have to press here...
There you go! Then continue
with the other dot.
There you go again. And then?
S, right?
That's right.
I knew you would be good at this.
And then? Keep going.
O. You're so good!
You're a quick learner!
Next...
Oh my.
Ma'am.
- How are you feeling?
- Oh, you're the one from last time.
By the way, where is the entrance?
It's that way.
That's right. I came from that way.
I'm so forgetful these days.
I don't know if I was being rude
to you, by any chance.
No, you weren't.
Ma'am, please take this.
You dropped it last time,
and it was ruined, so I made a new one.
I don't know if you will like it.
Oh my, it's so pretty.
Thank you.
Hello there.
Designer Park.
I'm Choi Go Bong.
Oh my, what a bad man you are.
Do you know how long I waited for you
at Seoul Station that day?
I told you not to wait for me
because I was seeing someone else.
How pretty was she for you
to reject someone like me?
Oh my.
Designer Park.
It was good seeing you.
I thought you were dead.
I just stopped by to confirm.
I have no regrets now that
I've seen you before I die.
I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings.
At the time...
I didn't know much about all this.
I know how you feel. I know.
For as long as you live
I wish you a long and healthy life.
Thank you.
You two look good together.
Don't let go of this hand,
and care for each other.
live happily ever after...
until the very end.
You don't have to help me.
Two heads are always better than one.
How were you supposed
to finish this on your own?
Thank you.
Unlike your appearance,
you do have some designer sense.
I'm good at picking the pretty ones.
- Does that include me?
- What?
Does it sound like that to you?
No, I was asking if
I dressed this up well.
Well, it's bearable.
- Be careful.
- Don't worry.
I'll make the best Christmas tree ever.
Whee...
We need to hang this in order
to complete this tree.
Hold on.
What is this? Is it a back scratcher?
- Will you hang it, too?
- You're so old-fashioned.
This is not a back scratcher,
but a selfie stick.
- What stick?
- Since you've worked hard
we should take a selfie together.
Here, hold this for a second.
Put this on.
Here we go now.
Smile, will you? Tree.
- Tree.
- That's amazing.
- Isn't it?
Let's take one more.
Get closer to make us seem close.
Here. One, two...
Where have you been?
What is this? Did you buy it?
Why do you care?
What is he up to, huh?
Is he really dating or what?
Oh my.
This is the photo we took earlier.
If you click the photo,
it will enlarge.
Oh my.
How can we look so young?
She's so pretty. So pretty.
It sounds like you two
went out on a date, huh?
What do you mean a date?
How long has it been
since you met him?
How many days? I don't know.
Women are supposed to
keep track of those things.
That way, you guys can celebrate
your 100th day of being together.
- 100th day?
- It will be here before you know it.
There are lots of couples who break up
even before their 100th day.
Gosh, why are you
talking about break-ups?
It won't happen.
What is that?
You're so into him, aren't you?
- You're falling in love, aren't you?
- What are you talking about? Go away.
How far did you go with him, huh?
What do you mean how far
Go to bed.
- You did, didn't you?
- Go to bed.
- Something happened, didn't it?
- Go to bed now!
Are you seeing Eun Ha Soo these days?
- What nonsense.
- You're not dating, right?
Okay.
Why does he keep poking me like that?
Congratulations on being chosen
as the employee of the week.
Thank you.
If you become a full-time employee
which department would
you choose to work at?
A full-time employee?
Oh my, I'm not sure.
- How about the Management Support team?
- Pardon?
If you do dispatched work for
the Management Support team now
you'll receive a higher score
to be hired on staff.
I think it's a good idea since
the salary is good and the job is secure.
You're going to send her to work
for the Management Support team?
Yes, I was considering that.
You'll be working on accounting.
Is that okay?
I truly appreciate your consideration...
But I think it will be better to give
that opportunity to somebody else.
It's a good opportunity.
Why not take it?
I actually have something else in mind.
If possible, I'd like to try to pursue it.
What kind of work is that?
So what did you tell them?
A job where I can make people
happy and smile.
You should have become a comedienne.
When it comes to comedy,
Nam Chul and Nam Sung Nam are the best.
- Pardon?
- Well...
If you want to make people laugh,
that's what a comedian does.
It's not about making people laugh...
What do you call it, someone who
creates memories for other people?
What are you saying?
Women shouldn't act cheap.
Why would you want to create
something like that for some man?
That's not what I meant.
Gosh, forget I said anything.
Anyhow, you chose
your dream over money, huh?
I envy your youth.
Choi Shin Hyung, do you have a dream?
My dream?
I can't even remember
the last time I've had a dream.
Is it your dream to make money?
It can't be, right?
My dream, huh?
Ta-da. I have movie tickets.
This is the prize for being chosen
as the employee of the week.
Wow, you are doing really well.
Congrats.
By the way, who would you
go to the movies with?
I have someone to go with.
Are you done?
What is it? Are you disappointed?
What disappointment?
So who are you going with?
Oh, I have a call.
Hi, Woo Young.
You want to go to the movies with me?
No.
I've already decided to go
with Choi Shin Hyung.
A movie...
With me?
When will we go?
Tonight.
I got it.
See you later.
Do you have a dream, Choi Shin Hyung?
Is it your dream to make money?
It can't be, right?
Welcome.
- Any flowers you're looking for?
- Well...
This is my first time buying flowers...
I want to give them to someone.
A present for a lady, right?
We should know what she might like.
What is she like?
Well, it's hard to describe her
in one word.
She's very slender...
But she's very full of energy.
She's cheerful, tough,
and energetic...
so she makes others feel good
just by watching her.
She's plain-looking...
but I can somehow spot her
right away in a crowd.
She's quite cute, too.
I don't ever get tired
of looking at her.
She's one pretty woman.
What do you mean?
Why would I help steal an identity
for Choi Shin Hyung?
What is this?
How did you get a hold of this?
There will be a lot of people
coming to see you soon.
Of course you could misunderstand.
The late Chairman Choi
asked me in such a hurry...
I hope that no one suspects my son,
Choi Shin Hyung's identity.
Even if I wasn't the one
who took care of him
he was in a difficult position
to live in hiding for my reputation.
I don't want anyone
to ask questions about that.
After Choi Shin Hyung
lost his mother in an accident
he had his identity stolen.
He was living wandering around
for a while and had a tough life.
What are you doing?
No need to know. It's nothing.
Are you writing your bucket list?
You bastard.
By the way, why 48 days?
It's not like 49 days when
a dead soul can wander afterward...
48...
- By any chance...
- What is it?
Four Noble Truths, Eight Sufferings?
- Eun Ha Soo.
- You scared me.
I heard you were chosen to be
the employee of the week.
Can we have some tea and celebrate?
I already have plans for tonight.
It won't take long.
Really? What is it?
It's just this and that, you know.
Eun Ha Soo.
I told you this would help
make a dream come true.
Why give this to me?
You said you'd become someone who
will create memories for others, right?
I hope it comes true.
But this is a keepsake
from your late mother.
- I can't accept this.
- Don't take it off.
If it's too much, then wear it
for one week and give it back.
You can't just give it back now.
Get out of the car, so we can talk.
What's up with him?
What do you want to talk about?
- Eun Ha Soo...
- What about her?
Do you really like her?
Why are you asking me that
all of a sudden?
Do you like her too?
- I asked if you liked her.
- Yes.
I think I like her.
I don't remember being loved much
so I didn't know how to
love someone else.
I suddenly felt like
being sincere to someone.
I want to fix things for her
and I want to treat her well.
If that's what people call
to like someone...
it might be true then.
I understand.
But why would you ask about that?
What is it? What's wrong?
What's wrong, Choi Shin Hyung?
Choi Shin Hyung.
The Four Noble Truths,
Eight Sufferings...
According to the sacred book
there are eight sufferings
that humans go through.
Birth, aging, sickness, and death.
These are the four of them.
No. Don't.
Why do you keep saying no?
I'll go get her.
- I'll go get her!
- Who will you go get?
- Manager Sung.
- This is crazy.
I will go get her!
Gosh, seriously!
I've arrived here and
am waiting for you now.
You say goodbye to your loved ones.
The pain of saying goodbye
to your loved ones.
The pain of not getting
what you want.
- I will start the anesthesia.
- Okay.
The pain of not getting
what you desire.
- What happened? Did he go into surgery?
- Yes.
He shouldn't have surgery.
We should stop the surgery right now.
And the pain you get from your desires.
It's the pain you get from
such restless greed and desires.
When you add these four sufferings
they become eight sufferings.
Subtitles by DramaFever
It will be better if he disappears,
but what if he comes back?
Are you okay? I'm not okay.
Why did I live like that?
He can't be my father,
and he said he wasn't my father.
It's driving me crazy.
I hope you can help out.
In my eyes, you're just like
the late Chairman Choi Go Bong.
I wish your earnest wishes
would come true.
Let's put them inside the lanterns.