Mr. Back
Eun Ha Soo.
What are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
Actually, about who I really am...
What do you mean who you are?
You're Choi Shin Hyung.
On the day when the meteor fell
I was involved in an accident here
with the late Chairman Choi Go Bong.
Funny thing is...
I don't know if
it's because you're his son...
but it was amazing that your pain
stopped when I was with you.
If that's the case...
I could be of your help.
Thank you for holding his hand
at that time.
I think that was the reason
why I was able to survive.
And...
That Choi Go Bong is...
What is it?
Who are you? Go away!
- Choi Shin Hyung.
- I said go!
- What is it? Are you okay?
- I said go away! Go!
- Choi Shin Hyung.
- Go away!
- I said go away!
- Are you okay?
- I still have time!
- Choi Shin Hyung!
What is it all of a sudden?
- Are you okay?
- What?
Yes, I'm fine.
What did you see?
- What was that about?
- It's just that...
I felt dizzy...
Can you drive?
Yes, I'll be fine.
This is where the late
Chairman Choi's accident took place...
[Episode 15]
I'm saying I'm fine now.
Gosh, now that I got some cold air
I feel much better.
Did you buy that for me?
I'm not good at coming up
with long answers...
but I'm good with short answers.
So don't try to beat around the bush,
but just tell me yes or no.
- What do you mean?
- You're very unwell.
It's because you have a meteor
in your heart, isn't it?
Was it Manager Sung
or Dae Han who told you?
If it made you see hallucinations,
it's quite serious.
Why are you being stubborn
when you need surgery?
'Shik Ja Woo Whan.'
It means, 'the unknown is the cure-all.'
Don't you know 'Yuk Ji Sa Ji' if you like
four-character proverbs that much?
- What?
- That means, 'put yourself in my shoes.'
If I were that sick
would you be able to not care?
Would you be able to
just let me take care of myself?
Why would you be that sick?
I'm worried sick right now!
I... no matter how much
I try, I can't sleep.
Even if I manage to fall asleep,
I wake up in nightmares.
Do you have any idea how scared
I am because of you right now?
Eun Ha Soo.
I was... scared, too.
Wondering if something would go wrong...
I didn't want to hurt anybody.
Wonder if even that wish
will leave a scar...
I was afraid of that.
Choi Shin Hyung.
You told me to answer
yes or no, right?
Can you ask me again?
Will you have the surgery?
Yes.
I will have the surgery.
Now... can you relax
and sleep at night?
- Would you like to try this?
- Sure.
Here it is.
[The results confirm that these two sets
of fingerprints belong to the same person.]
How can this be?
How can this be possible?
What do you think about my offer?
It's not bad.
Chairman Choi received a promotion
that day of the sinkhole accident.
Why did he have to get into
an accident on such a nice day?
Wait.
- Is that?
- That is...
someone putting money in
Director Cho Young Dal's car.
He was taking it out,
not putting the money in.
The one who took the money
from him that day...
put the money in
the late Chairman's car.
- Is that perhaps?
- Jung Yi Gun?
We need solid evidence.
Wait, what is this?
Isn't he Prosecutor Yang?
Why was he there?
- Where is this place?
- It's the street near the sinkhole.
If you look at the time
that's right before the accident.
Then he was waiting there
expecting an accident?
No way. It was a natural disaster.
Wait a second. Does this mean...
that he knew there was money in the car.
He was already waiting
for my father there.
We don't have much time, so hurry up.
Bring Choi Shin Hyung in for questioning.
I can't bring him in
without any charges.
I can't start an investigation
just because their fingerprints
are identical.
It's likely that he stole
the late Chairman Choi's fingerprints.
He may have needed them to
get access to the Chairman's safe.
- When is the deal finalized?
- Soon.
When they sign the contract
for the buyout
it will be Daehan Group's foundation day.
Are these all the reports?
President Choi will bring
more evidence soon.
You do look very much like
the late Chairman Choi.
Do I?
I appreciate you working to find
the truth about my father's case.
With his position, malignant people
are usually nearby.
Director Jung is close
to Prosecutor Yang.
No wonder.
- I'd appreciate it then.
- Don't worry.
As for the case involving
the late Chairman Choi's five billion won
we'll find a lead soon enough.
- What is this?
- Do you know Prosecutor Gu?
Choi Shin Hyung asked to gather
the evidence on him and go see him.
He's saying we should pressure
Director Jung with evidence, huh?
Then Director Jung will end up
having to give up his takeover.
But we still don't have
definitive evidence yet.
We have to find it.
That way, we can clear my father's name.
We should.
What's up with you?
What business do you
possibly have to call me?
I can't believe your nerve for calling me.
What is this?
The records of the money
I've received from Director Jung so far.
When we went to
the casinos in Las Vegas
I have the recorded phone
conversation from then, too.
Why did you decide to hand this to me?
Would I hand it over for free?
Ask Choi Shin Hyung.
Wow, really?
I'm pissed off at Jung Yi Gun, too.
Ever since the photo incident
I haven't been paid.
So how much did you get offered for this?
That's a secret.
I'm leaving tomorrow,
so I wish you luck.
Hey, hey!
Live a honest life out there.
How rude.
Okay, I got it now.
What are you doing in here?
Get up.
You asked me to wait.
Yet you announced your engagement?
You sure know how to
backstab people, don't you?
That was for the business.
You really think you've got
Hong Ji Yoon's heart?
No way.
Do you even know that
she's Choi Dae Han's spy?
It doesn't matter.
It'll be all resolved
once the resort is sold.
After I added your name as a joint owner
for the New York department store
now you'd sell it off without
even consulting me first?
Are you trying to end things
with me now?
I'm saying that's not what it is!
What happened with this article?
I guess she had no idea either, huh?
- Could you excuse us?
- You underestimated me.
Do you think I'm going to stand idly by?
Can we talk about it later?
Please retract the engagement announcement.
- Ji Yoon, it was about...
- And about the terms for the buyout
will you reconsider them?
- Is that because of the employees?
- Of course.
The damage would be too great.
Stop worrying about other people.
I secured your position...
so can't we set the date
for our engagement first?
- Yi Gun...
- I...
I don't want you because of work
like somebody else does.
Don't you know how I feel?
I'm sorry, Yi Gun.
I didn't want to hurt your feelings.
But I'll make things clear.
About Daehan Resort...
I know that you've contributed
a lot for Daehan's growth.
But don't try to take it over
in the wrong way.
What?
Even if you were to get your way,
it still wouldn't satisfy you.
You acting this way...
speaks to your sense of inferiority,
not your ambition.
Hong Ji Yoon.
Why don't you quit now?
I haven't even gotten started yet.
- You might end up really hurting yourself.
- Who do you think will get hurt?
- I guess we'll know when the game is over.
- Sure about that?
Who would have put five billion won
in my late father's car?
Did you get some advice
from Choi Shin Hyung?
- On this and that.
- Funny.
He's not even Chairman Choi Go Bong.
But he has that kind of ability...
Wait and see who's going to stand
on stage at the foundation ceremony.
Would you mind taking a photo of us?
- A photo?
- Yes, please.
- I'm such a good photographer.
- Thank you.
Here we go. Where?
Get closer together.
One, two, three.
It came out well.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- They look good together.
- Not as good as we do.
Oh my. Are you okay?
- Gosh, I almost fell in this skirt.
- Oh my.
What happened all of a sudden, huh?
Choi Shin Hyung.
Huh? He was here a minute ago.
Man, where did she go?
- Boo!
- Jeez.
You scared me!
You scared me.
It's cold, isn't it?
Give me ten thousand won.
- No, I won't.
- Seriously. Please just give it.
Gosh.
Wow.
Put it all in.
- Pardon?
- I'll be fine with this one bill.
Do you really want me
to put it all in there?
I'll be right back.
Seriously, what are you doing?
No wonder why people aren't coming over...
You should shake this bell
up and down hard like this.
Let's help the less unfortunate!
Let's help the poor! Thank you.
You should shake
this bell loudly!
Thank you.
Shake it hard like this.
We don't need a lot of money
to be happy.
Thank you.
Blue mountains...
You made a fuss about
going somewhere important
and it was a bathhouse?
Water in blue stream...
Gosh, it's too noisy.
Stop moving.
- You haven't been scrubbed off yet.
- You're going to scrub me off?
I take showers in the morning
and at night.
Showering a hundred times won't be
as good as taking a bath.
No matter how often
you take a shower
they say one scrub is better
than hundreds of showers.
Then do that as much as
you want, by yourself.
You said there were a lot of things
you wanted to do with your father.
I did, too.
I wanted to sit in
a warm bathtub with my son.
I wanted to sweat it out,
and scrub each other's backs.
Your father wanted to do that, too...
What's the big deal?
Usually the trivial things build up
and they stay right here.
So you can never forget them.
Blue mountains...
It's hot.
Wait a second.
Why are you scrubbing so hard?
What's all this, huh?
Are these thin noodles
or thick noodles, huh?
You might as well
open up a noodle shop.
Let's switch! Change!
Take it easy, kid!
Come over here!
That felt good.
It was nice, wasn't it?
Let's do it again.
Scrubbing each other's backs.
I'll go easy on you next time.
Let's do it again.
Oh my.
Wow, it's a Christmas tree!
- It's so big.
- What do you think?
Wouldn't it be really nice
once it's finished?
It was my dream to decorate
a tree with my father.
Was it?
What kind of man
has such a small dream?
Wow, there's a star, too.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make a wish.
Tomorrow's Christmas.
I wish my father wouldn't leave.
I wish I could decorate
a tree with him next year
and the year after that.
Gosh, man.
I'll have to make another wish.
This necklace is said
to make miracles come true.
To my father...
I wish for a miracle for my father.
On the day of the next meteor shower
take this to where the accident took place.
- You're okay, right, sir?
- Yes.
Now Christmas... is only two days away.
Yes, by the way...
should we set the surgery date now?
- Manager Sung.
- Yes, Chairman Choi.
- What Chairman?
- Well...
To me, you're always Chairman Choi
whether you're dead or alive.
I've worked for you for thirty years.
Thirty is only a number.
It seems to have been
much longer than that.
- Have a seat.
- Yes, Chairman Choi.
What is this?
Manager Sung, now...
With your wife and kids
you should all live happily together.
Return to your wife.
All this time, because of me...
you had to live your life
according to mine.
It must have been tough for you.
Why are you saying that?
You're making me nervous.
Come on.
You should let me go now.
You should be mentally prepared.
How am I supposed to do that?
Even if everyone can do that...
I won't be able to.
All this time...
you've been separated
from your family...
I'm sorry for not understanding
how it was for you.
Chairman Choi.
I'm sorry that I made you
worry about me, too.
Sung Gyung Bae was
Choi Go Bong's best partner.
Where would I go without you?
I will protect you until the end,
Chairman Choi.
Okay.
Truly...
- I'm grateful to you.
- Oh my, Chairman Choi.
Oh my, Chairman Choi.
What are we going to do?
What are we going to do
with Chairman Choi, huh?
Shouldn't we try to do something, huh?
He won't listen to me.
I just don't understand why
he won't have the surgery.
Can you go and try to
talk him into it again?
I don't think he'll listen to me,
Manager Sung.
According to the text messages,
the 25th is the last day.
We'll go ahead and
request surgery for that day...
and we'll drag him in, and force him
to have the operation.
We should at least do that...
We can't just let him go like this.
Let's try to do everything we can.
Please help me, Manager Sung.
I'll try everything I can think of.
Gosh...
What are you doing when
you're supposed to be working?
Well, my hands are
so chapped these days...
- Should I get one of these?
- Go ahead.
Really?
- They come as a set, too.
- I said go ahead.
- Buy it for me then.
- What?
We can use it together.
Move over.
What am I doing...
Sir. Sir.
Gosh, rumor has it that
there will be a staff layoff.
Is that true?
If our resort gets sold
to a foreign corporation
it may be true.
The resort is being sold
to a foreign corporation?
Then we can't just sit around
and let that happen.
How about we petition the employees?
Young Dal.
Did you get a call from the
prosecution's office too?
I did.
Son of a bitch.
We have no choice.
- I'll go and see Director Jung.
- Wait.
Can you hold on a bit?
He's talking with your sister-in-law
about a business deal...
So let's wait a bit, shall we?
Do you still trust your wife?
What is this?
It's the account ledgers
she sneaked out to Germany.
What?
What's all this, huh?
That damned woman.
She set this all up for
her family under my nose?
You said I was tricked
when I got married...
What kind of married couple are you two?
I won't leave her alone.
Young Dal, you can't get worked up now.
What do you want me to do then?
We should first find a way to survive!
- What brings you here?
- Can you two help me?
I'll help you, whatever it is. Tell me.
It seems that you're both victims.
Us? How come?
In your case, it's because of your wife.
And aunt, it's because of Director Jung.
Who's saying that?
What did I do?
You should find a way to survive
before it's too late.
Don't you think?
This should be enough.
Please clear my father's name.
Bringing Director Jung down...
It won't be easy.
We know that.
That's why we've brought
all these documents to you.
I'll review them and be in touch.
Why did you get out?
It's cold. You can go.
Thanks for being by my side.
Don't mention it.
I'm just doing my job.
No, when I think about how hard
it must've been for you because of me...
Gosh, it gives me chills.
I'm sorry.
Things aren't over yet...
so you can't relax just yet.
You know that, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Happy Christmas!
Today's Christmas Eve.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
Merry Christmas.
He worked for Daehan Resort
for thirty years.
He didn't get a proper retirement ceremony.
It bothers me that
he had to go like that.
I see.
The late Chairman Choi was
always in the back of my mind.
So I'd like to make him
an appreciation plaque.
I want my brother
to receive it on his behalf.
That's a very good idea.
Then how about a video clips
to show his accomplishments?
Wow, that would be great.
Thanks, Eun Ha Soo.
[Appreciation Plaque]
Hello?
I'll send you the word file for
the appreciation plaque in an hour.
You can make it
by tomorrow morning, right?
Okay. Thank you.
- They're coming.
- They're coming!
Statement, please.
Can you just say one statement?
Do you have anything
to say about the investigation?
Do you acknowledge
the embezzlement charges?
Why didn't you bring my car?
Does it matter who picked us up?
Why did I get in this car?
How was it?
Prosecutor Yang must have
been after you aggressively.
He tried to accuse me of frivolous charges.
I thought my blood pressure
would drive me to the edge.
I didn't understand why he'd go over
my family's bank accounts.
You dare to say that in front of me?
Why can't I say that
when everything's out in the open?
How noisy.
Can't we leave in silence?
This is all because
you were played by Jung Yi Gun.
If you committed a crime,
you should pay for it.
Hey, can you help us?
There has to be a way, right?
Can you help us with Dae Han's help?
Gosh, how can you ask for help now?
I'll think about it
after I see how you behave.
What do you need to see?
We'll be on our best behavior
from now on.
Can you take care of
my matters first?
Things aren't going well.
Choi Young Dal, Lee In Ja...
On top of it, Choi Yi Hye stepped up, too.
- They even submitted evidence.
- What evidence?
For Choi Young Dal
it was the premium outlets.
For Lee In Ja, it was a video file
of the late Chairman Choi's will.
Choi Yi Hye must have submitted
the New York department store then.
Yes, sir.
Things are getting complicated.
Furthermor, Prosecutor Gu is investigating
into the five billion won case.
It might be better to give up now
and wrap things up.
Quitting now would be
to admit to the crimes.
Continue with it.
Hello. We're collecting signatures
as a petition to retain Daehan Resort.
You know what's going on, right?
Thank you.
Hello.
We're against the takeover
by a foreign company.
Can you sign here?
Choi Shin Hyung, can you sign here?
How did you come up with this idea?
I thought it could help a little
if we worked together.
The employees have changed
their minds about President Choi.
He helped revive Seohae Hotel, too.
Everybody seems to be counting on him now.
If he overcomes this crisis,
he'll do even better in the future.
Wait, are you free tonight?
Of course.
[Terms of Takeover]
- Did you get all the paperwork ready?
- Yes.
I can't believe we're doing this
on Christmas Eve.
If everything works out,
it'll be a very memorable day.
How are things on their side?
It seems to be a good side that
they've agreed to meet with us...
I'll know for sure when we meet.
I'm afraid I won't be able
to see you today.
Something urgent came up.
I'll call you again.
What is this?
Can we talk now?
- Let's talk later.
- Come on.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Who are you?
Your fingerprints match those
of the late Chairman Choi.
Shall I call the police to look into it?
Now you're performing
a background check on me?
How can you possibly do this to me?
After your parents passed away...
I thought of you like a son.
I supported you financially,
and even helped you go study abroad.
So you repay grace with evildoings?
Who are you?
While we were managing Daehan
how many places did we go
together all these years?
I wanted to teach you many things.
Didn't you work so hard, too?
If I had known that
you'd turn out this way
I don't know why
I spent all that time with you.
What's the use?
The bottom line is that
I was never his son.
I could never become Choi Dae Han!
I understand how you feel.
Enough!
That's enough.
Please check this document.
- It's for me?
- It's very important document.
We will wait for your evaluation.
Our agreement...
Just pick one.
I'm okay, so buy one for yourself.
But still it's your birthday.
This color's pretty.
What do you think?
- It's pretty.
- Okay.
Can you gift wrap this?
- Ha Soo, do you want to try that?
- What?
On a day like today, you can
get a complete makeover
- and go see Choi Shin Hyung.
- It's okay.
Why not?
Everything is ready.
Wow.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Eun Ha Soo.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
Happy birthday to you.
Wow.
What's all this?
Unbelievable.
Once upon a time...
there lived a very rich old man
with a lump in his face.
The old coot thought he was living
a good life compared to anybody else.
Okay.
I guess you can say that
I succeeded in life.
Of course.
One day...
there was a storm with
strong winds and thunderous rain.
He was hit by lightning.
He passed out.
Oh no.
Oh no, please help me.
Help me.
I want to live longer.
The old man thought making money
meant living a successful life.
It was only at death's
door did he realize that
he wanted another chance at life.
Oh, save me.
Somebody help me.
Just like that, when he was about
to breathe his last...
All of a sudden...
an angel came down
from the sky.
Sir, sir!
Yes...
Hold my hand.
Who... who are you?
Do you still think
you've lived a good life?
No.
I... didn't live a good life.
I didn't know what happiness was.
I didn't spend a lot of time
with my family, either.
I never really said that I loved anybody.
What a pity.
What have you been doing
all these years then?
I don't even know.
I don't know why I lived like that.
It's the angel's birthday today.
What do I do?
I don't...
have much time left now.
I might not be able
to see you ever again.
Then...
we should say our farewells first.
I don't know
how to say farewell, though.
Then I'll teach you how.
Repeat after me.
Even when I'm gone...
Take care of yourself.
Make sure you don't skip meals.
This is annoying,
do the rest on your own.
Even when I'm gone...
make sure you don't skip meals.
If you eat the spicy ddukbokki
make sure that you're the winner.
When it's cold...
don't wait outside too long.
When you're not feeling well
say this spell, 'Koong koong da.'
Make people happy and smile.
Make sure you that
you achieve your dream
of creating memories for others.
And...
Meet someone and fall in love, too.
Live happily ever after.
I sincerely wish that for you.
Oh no, you can't cry.
Your pretty nose will turn red.
And...
I wish you a happy birthday.
Thank you for being born.
I am happy to have met you.
I still didn't tell you
my final wish yet.
Okay.
Tell me.
Let's not break up.
No matter what happens.
Do you understand?
I love you.
[Dec. 24, 2014. 11:59:38]
[D-day.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
- I'm sorry that I hurt you.
- Choi Shin Hyung!
- I may not be able to keep my promise.
I'm sorry I fell in love with you.
Choi Shin Hyung.