Mr. Back
What's wrong with me?
This is so wrong.
Is it okay to do this? Me?
I'm not suddenly getting old again, am I?
[Episode 7]
Come on, hurry.
I'll see you later.
Woo Young, wait up.
- Are you off to work now?
- Yes.
Wow, are you going somewhere?
I'm  meeting someone.
Man, seriously...
Make sure it's straight, will you?
Make sure it's pretty.
There you go.
What are we having for dinner today?
Well, what would you like?
Well, anything.
Make me something
that you're good at.
All right, I have to go
because I'm running late.
She's pretty.
- Choi Shin Hyung.
- Yes?
Welcome, everyone!
We're going to have
an enjoyable time today.
Before we do that, let's welcome
Director Choi Dae Han
who organized this event.
Welcome to the Red Day Festival,
which kicks off the winter season.
The color red represents
heat and anger.
To those who often encounter
angry situations in modern society
this event could relieve some stress.
Starting now, release all of your stress...
and that feeling of dislike
towards others...
We can be completely free from it.
I hope that this will be
a great opportunity for all of us.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
Think of a person you hate the most.
And then throw it.
What are you doing there?
Come on out.
No way. I'm going home.
- You came all the way here.
- I'm going home!
- What is this?
- Take this!
What are you doing?
- Director Choi.
- Why are you here?
How rude!
How dare you say that to a customer?
Come here. Get him!
Shin Hyung.
I told you that
I didn't want to do this!
Look at the state of me!
Nonsense. You were having the most fun.
Let me see.
I'll wipe you off.
Over here, too.
Wipe it yourself.
Next to your nose there.
- Man, you were having so much fun.
- Director Choi.
Manager Hong.
I think it's better to have
that man move back in.
Why all of a sudden?
I don't know.
I just think it's better that way.
How itchy.
Where did he go?
Thanks for your hospitality.
I'm leaving. Choi Shin Hyung.
What is this?
How can he just leave
without saying a word?
How have you been?
Why does he keep changing his mind?
It's annoying.
- Come this way.
- No, my room is that way.
- What's your deal?
- I felt bad you being homeless.
Plus, it doesn't help my image, either.
You should have done this sooner.
I'll have dinner first,
so set the table.
A glass of vegetable juice, please.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Can you bring over the documents
from earlier and come by the house?
Right now?
Yes, I need to go over them tonight.
There's something my late father
used to say all the time.
'Those who don't work, shouldn't eat.'
I have a suggestion for you.
You can work at Daehan Resort.
What do you think?
I don't have any interest
in management
but you seem to have
great interest in it.
So I'm giving you an opportunity.
I appreciate it.
That's what I wanted.
There was another thing
my late father used to say.
'No matter what kind of work,
always start from the bottom.'
Start from the bottom.
You can do it since you're his son.
If you can't do that,
then get out immediately.
What? You don't think you can do it?
Fine. I'll do it.
But the thing is...
Our late father said this, too.
'Don't live life without a goal.'
What goal do you have in mind
to suggest that to me?
Goal, huh?
I originally wanted to be
a professional dancer
But I couldn't pursue it because
my late father was against the idea.
He said a child who doesn't listen
to his parents aren't human.
But since he isn't around anymore...
I'm thinking of taking it up again.
- What?
- Why not? It's cool.
You haven't seen me dance.
Want me to show you?
No, I have no interest
in seeing you dance.
Why don't you act like
a human being first?
What a rotten kid.
What brings you here?
- Director Choi invited me.
- At this hour?
It's fine, so you can go home.
How could you leave
without saying a word?
Huh?
You asked me to make dinner earlier...
I did, didn't I?
What do you think you're doing?
She's my guest.
Can you get lost?
Director Choi. Director Choi.
Wait...
Director Choi, the document...
Don't go hanging around
Choi Shin Hyung again.
Why not?
You started to change my life
by one percent.
Well, here.
- Then I'll get going.
- Wait.
- What is it?
- Don't go out yet.
It seems that your conversation
is becoming quite long...
- Would you like some tea?
- No, I'm coming right out.
You two seemed to be living together.
Are you guys dating?
- No...
- Wait a second.
Jujube tea, mulberry leaf tea, and
quince tea. Which one do you like?
- Answer.
- Gosh, quince tea!
Oh my god!
Excuse me.
Wow, leaving already?
It's kind of late now.
By the way, why did he
call you over at this hour?
He asked me to run an errand.
What a rotten man.
How dare he asks anyone
to run errands at this hour?
- Then...
- Wait a second.
I'm sorry I didn't say goodbye
before I left.
Could you talk to your mother for me?
Since you've decided to stay here,
make the most out of it.
And you two.
Stop arguing, please.
I'll go now.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't harass and manipulate her
because of me.
Who the heck are you
to tell me what to do?
Do you have feelings for her
or something?
- Looks like I'm right.
- It's not like that.
Isn't it about time for you
to come to your senses?
Don't go around and hurt people
if you're not serious.
What can I say?
I like her.
Why?
Is it odd for a young man
to like a young woman?
I'm not married and
I don't have a girlfriend.
Why do you think
I'd end up hurting her?
On what grounds?
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
You started to change my life
by one percent.
Let's go to bed.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
Hey, do you know of
the Choi Go Bong Dance?
It's the dance that's taken
the country by storm.
How fast can you run 100 meters?
I've been feeling great lately.
Why are you doing this?
Go away!
Still, those two seem to have
grown much closer, don't you think?
I'm not so sure.
- They're on fire.
- Are they? Where?
We should put it out.
No one can possibly
put that fire out.
'The prince of Daehan Group,
Director Choi Dae Han'
'has made good on his name.'
'The sensational response
from the Red Day Festival...'
If we leave him be
then he'll come and
take you down in no time.
Do you want to be dismissed by your family?
And go back to be being known as
the invisible man in this company?
Would you disappoint me again?
Let's show them something.
Okay?
Put out the notice immediately!
- What's going on?
- Oh my goodness.
[Personnel announcements]
What is this?
They're everyone who closely worked
with the late Chairman Choi.
How could this be?
[Hong Ji Yoon: Fired.]
- Oh my god.
- What do we do now?
[As of November 26,
you have been terminated.]
What are you people doing?
Leave everything and go.
- That's enough.
- Enough of what?
I told you to leave immediately. Sir.
I had expect this to an extent.
Nonsense.
Do you think this is why I handed
that title over to my uncle?
What do you suggest we do then?
- I will handle it myself...
- What can you possibly do about it?
Manager Hong.
There isn't anything
you can do about it.
I chose the wrong person to work for.
Why would they tell us to clean
the pool on such a cold day,?
Gosh.
How long are you going
to abuse me like this, huh?
What's going on with
Director Jung Yi Gun?
It seems like he's working on it,
but it's easier said than done.
The company is a mess after
Chairman Choi passed away.
Who would buy out the company?
If Choi Young Dal starts stealing
from the company
it's only a matter of time
until the company is ruined.
If you were really Chairman Choi
you would use your brother's
weakness and fight back.
As expected, you're definitely
someone I need!
You only say that
when you need me!
Over there. There.
What brings you here?
I came to check up on the cleaning.
I'm supposed to check up
on it this week.
By the way, you got rehired?
Yes, it turned out that way.
What happened to the workers
that Manager Sung would be...
Ji Yoon.
Congratulations on your promotion.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Thank you for thinking of me.
You don't believe me?
Why would you interfere on my behalf?
I don't want it
to backfire on you.
Ah, seriously.
- Not there, but over there.
- Where?
- Here?
- No. You already cleaned that.
- Over there.
- Where?
- Where is it?
- Over there!
Gosh.
Here?
You're good at this.
How is it that you're so bad at this?
I usually don't do things like this.
Knowing how to do this is a given.
Follow me.
She's bragging because
she was good at it, huh?
Let's race.
- How tiring.
- Let's go.
- Oh, my butt.
- Are you okay?
How tiring was that?
It's been a while
since I worked up a sweat.
Oh my.
Why are you packing
something like that?
It's my snack. Here.
- Try some.
- No, thanks.
Just try some.
Food you eat after working up
a sweat always tastes better.
Try some.
Wow, this is delicious.
But this makes me thirsty.
I'm thirsty.
Here you go.
It's good.
How did you get rehired?
It's just that, Choi Dae Han...
If he wants you to come over
or meet up, just say no.
- Never!
- Why not?
You just shouldn't.
Do you know how many women's
hearts he's broken?
- How do you know that?
- What?
My late father told me.
Back when he was in school
girls would come over
bawling their eyes out
just because he wouldn't see them.
Wow, so he was popular?
What do you mean, 'popular'?
Some girl jumped in front of a car
because of him.
Do you know how much money
was spent for that?
How does he know about that?
- Are you serious?
- Of course.
I wasted billions of won
because of that.
I mean, my late father did...
But...
Are you interested in him or something?
No.
Don't ever fall for him.
Got it?
- He's an irresponsible man.
- Seriously, that guy...
Hello.
Actually...
Ha Soo.
- Ha Soo?
- What is it? What's wrong?
I've just been just that
all the interns will be fired.
What?
Where did he disappear off to
after calling me over here?
Why did you come here?
I'm just exercising.
What's the matter?
I like it because it's thrilling.
How long are you going to wait?
Don't you know how careless my brother is?
Kicking Choi Young Dal is easy.
It's because we can't buy up
Dae Han's shares, is all.
His shares, huh?
Don't worry.
I've already got
a plan in motion.
Crazy bastards...
- You asked for me?
- Yes.
About the Red Day Festival...
Thanks to you, it was a success.
My reputation improved greatly.
- Good job.
- I was only doing my job.
About Choi Shin Hyung...
You know he's working here again, right?
Yes.
You might run into him often
while you go about your day...
No matter what he says about me...
Don't listen to him or
believe anything he says.
Pardon?
He's going to speak ill of me anyway.
What the?
Has he already said something?
No.
No, huh?
- I'll excuse myself.
- Wait.
You heard that the interns
would be fired, didn't you?
I'll take care of it,
so don't worry about it.
What is it?
You don't trust me?
I'm capable of at least
doing that much.
I'll get going.
Young Dal, you bastard.
Going to fire the employees?
Cruel bastard.
Who spilled coffee in my hotel, huh?
- Chairman Choi.
- What?
Why don't you answer your phone?
What is it?
Seriously, Director Jung Yi Gun...
- With Yi Hye?
- That's what I'm saying.
My heart was pounding, and
I ran around looking for you.
You weren't answering
your phone, either.
Are they firing the interns or not?
It makes me so nervous...
Director Choi said he'd handle it,
so let's trust him to do it.
Do you trust what that guy says?
He's a troublemaker who's incapable
of taking care of himself.
Jeez, let's just go home.
How come this is in here?
- Are you treating today?
- Where are we going?
I'm sure somewhere nice.
- Thanks, man.
- Let's go.
That man, seriously...
The company is on the brink of ruin
and he's still hanging out
with his friends?
Does he have his head on straight or what?
What are you going to do?
What can you possibly do about it?
There isn't anything
you can do about it.
You upset over your half-brother
who showed up out of nowhere?
Is this the time for you to be dancing
and drinking at a place like this?
What do you care whether
I go out dancing and drinking?
Wait, aren't you Dae Han's brother
who was the talk of the town?
- Hang with us.
- Let's have fun.
- Come this way.
- Hey, hey!
Don't mind him and continue.
Come out.
You're stubborn and shameless, too.
How can you be so much
like our late father?
You've never even lived under
the same roof together.
Genetics is a powerful thing, isn't it?
- You punk...
- You're going to act like my older brother?
It seems like you want to try
and change me or something.
Don't bother.
Our late father gave up
trying a long time ago.
If you go around badmouthing me
to Eun Ha Soo like that...
- Isn't that a foul?
- A foul?
Is having feelings for someone
some kind of a game to you?
I don't know what you heard
from our late father.
That girl from my past
got into a car accident
I went to get my father's money
because I felt bad for her.
What did you say?
Look at her.
Does she look like someone
who would jump in front of a car
just to try and win me over?
She doesn't, right?
- She's that girl.
- What are you talking about?
Then...
You lied back then to obtain
that amount of money?
What a rotten punk.
How could you fall for a woman that hard
that you'd take money your father
worked so hard to make?
But she's still the girl
who made me seaweed soup
on my birthday after
my mother passed away.
My father didn't even
remember my birthday.
So I did it because
I was grateful towards her.
I did it because I hated my father.
You immature child.
So you'd better not tell Eun Ha Soo
what you heard from our late father.
None of it will be accurate, you see.
Why didn't you tell him the truth?
Not even once!
Because... he never believed me.
Not even once.
Gosh, it's cold out.
What brings you here at this hour?
Gosh, you scared me.
You didn't get kicked out again, did you?
Excuse you.
People might think that
I get kicked out all the time.
It's because you two always seem
to be arguing whenever you meet.
It's because Dae Han won't listen to me.
Can you imagine how upset
the late Chairman Choi would be
to see you two fighting like this?
How much could he have
possibly hated his late father
that he would hate me this much?
I can believe that.
Director Choi may need some time.
After he's finished
hating his late father
Director Choi will start to miss him.
Will he really do that?
Do you know what my father was like
when I was in grade school?
I wanted to wear pretty clothes
but he'd make me clothes out of leftover
fabric rather than buying me new ones.
I was so embarrassed
to go to school in those clothes.
I really hated my father back then.
But...
I find those memories
so precious now.
Of course, our situations
are very different.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
Thank you.
It's cold out, so go on in.
Try to wear more layers.
Goodbye.
Koong, koong... da.
Koong, koong, da.
Koong, koong.
What's going on with me?
Koong, koong, da.
Koong, koong... whoa!
- Aunt.
- Ah...
Where is Dae Han?
Can we talk for a moment... please?
You went out of your way
to drive me out that night.
Since then, I've learned and
come to realize many things.
What is it that you wanted
to talk to me about?
I'm saying this as a member
of this Choi family.
About Director Jung Yi Gun...
Director Jung.
It seems that Choi Shin Hyung
might have forged his identity.
- What?
- Here.
He may have used
that man's identity.
- Who is this guy?
- I'm not sure yet.
I'll look into it some more.
It rather seems like he's trying
to push our family out
and take over Daehan for himself.
What do you mean by that?
I'm just worried that
we might end up...
getting my late father's entire
fortune taken away from us.
It seems like you don't know
what you're talking about.
Despite my brother offering Director Jung
the CEO position and stock options...
He didn't take it.
You don't know anything.
Why didn't he accept the offer, though?
It was such a tempting offer.
Probably because...
He's very proper and
has a clear conscience.
He probably didn't want to work
with someone like Young Dal.
Are you sure you're willing
to exchange this for that?
My father left me with some
very important business when he died.
The Cruise Hotel.
From the planning, funds,
staffing, and construction...
Everything is already complete.
You can see it as the prime jewel
of my father's life.
If we're trying to achieve the same goal
we have to make it
a win-win situation.
It's up to you on whether
we can switch it or not.
Okay. You trust me, right?
After you asked me last time...
I did my research to find
any other similar cases.
Africa...
He's the head of the village in Zimbabwe.
In 1984, he was in an accident
at the age of 78.
He was about your age.
But one day, he woke up...
and suddenly found himself
transformed into a young man.
The villagers believed that
he'd been by the gods.
So they celebrated for
three months and ten days.
Gosh, and our chairman
became homeless.
Shut it. So?
A doctor from America presented
this amazing case at a conference.
He was completely ignored.
It was called pure nonsense
without medical reasoning.
But the more surprising truth...
Do you know what happened
near the scene of the accident?
A meteor.
There were a lot of falling stars, huh?
At that time, near the village...
a mysterious giant hole appeared.
The head of the village
fell into it, didn't he?
The same thing happened to you, sir.
So...
What happened to him, huh?
- We have no idea.
- What? How come?
That American doctor couldn't
withstand the ridicule...
and left the medical world.
- Manager Sung.
- Yes?
Book a ticket to America.
- To Africa, too.
- Will you go there yourself?
How can I possibly go
without my passport?
Dr. Kim should go instead.
Of course, I should go.
Me?
If you write up a thesis
on what happened to me.
you're sure to earn a Nobel Prize.
No, no way.
- Nobel Prize in Medicine?
- Yes.
Besides, I really need to know.
Whether I'll suddenly
become an old man again
or if I have to continue
living in this body.
What would you prefer, sir?
What do you mean?
Do you wish to go back
to being an old man
and take back your title and fortune?
Hurry up and get on the bus.
- Hello.
Are we going for fun?
We're going for work.
- Just try this.
- Gosh.
Let's go.
Wait up!
Open up.
Gosh, I almost missed it.
Isn't that Choi Shin Hyung?
- You're here, too.
- You're coming with us?
Of course. I'm an employee, too.
I can't miss a day like this.
- Can't you get up?
- What?
Don't you see that
I'm carrying a bag, young man?
Here we go!
Gosh, I'm pretty hungry.
- Want something to eat?
- What?
You always carry snacks
with you, don't you?
Try some.
But your taste seems
to be similar with mine.
Mung bean pancakes
sweet potatoes, boiled eggs...
You're an old soul.
My taste in food is usually
like an old person. Here.
Would you like this one, too?
What is it?
It's a peppermint candy.
Look.
Do you give these out
to just anybody, huh?
What do you mean?
Such spineless woman...
Spineless?
Have you been giving out candy
to any man out there?
You're being ridiculous.
How can you go around
giving candy, huh?
What's wrong with giving candy, huh?
Don't bother.
If you don't want it,
just give it back.
Don't bother!
Seriously.
It's your first time here, right?
That's right.
This is where I met the late
Chairman Choi for the first time.
You see that over there?
I even washed his hands there.
Why don't you just wash
your hands at least?
Don't bother.
Stay still, will you?
Hands!
There you go.
He was a bit grumpy that day...
but he held out his hands.
Considering he did everything
that I asked of him...
he seemed to have a soft heart.
Hurry up and get the food ready.
Let's get going.
What brings you here?
What do you mean?
Here. Open it.
[Application for Wrongful Termination]
How did you do this?
I ran around to put that together.
We can't just sit back
and suffer like idiots.
I'll see you at work then.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to work.
I'm going to see Chairman Choi Young Dal.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
There no galbi.
Bring some more here.
Please enjoy.
We have galbi here.
Hello.
You didn't have to prepare this much.
Let us know if you need anything else.
- We will.
- Isn't it tasty?
Enjoy.
Here it is.
- What brings you here?
- I just stopped by.
I wanted to see you, too.
- Me?
- Well...
I came by because I wanted to see you.
Something wrong with that?
Well, you might want
to start working, too.
What?
You told me to trust you that
you'd take care of the interns.
You're being just another chairman, huh?
Do I have to hear something
like that from you?
I'm just worried.
You don't know much about
employment instability, do you?
Gosh, employment instability?
Seriously.
Did you just hit me?
- Did you just give me the look?
- Hey.
I blocked it, didn't I?
- Did you just duck?
- Hey.
What are you doing?
What is it?
Seriously.
What were you doing back there?
What do you mean?
We were just talking.
Talking? Please.
Why are you doing this to me?
Do you like me, by any chance?
What are you doing here?
Go on. Go back to work.
- Why did you come here?
- I came to work.
Chasing after a girl is work?
And you didn't come
chasing after Eun Ha Soo, huh?
Nonsense.
Forget it then.
How wrong is this, huh?
Oh my, I'm sorry.
Ready, set, go!
One, two. Slowly.
What are you doing? Hurry up.
You're a young man.
I'm coming.
Oh my, I've got a leg cramp.
We have to be in sync
to get something done.
Then shall we try to be in sync?
I have a secret accounting ledger.
Shall I talk about it while
the reporters are here?
What do you mean
a secret accounting ledger?
It's the ledger you used
as an emergency fund.
What are you?
Let's go before we're too late.
Oh my, Chairman Choi.
What is he doing when
he was so athletic with me?
We should keep going. Let's go.
What is it that you want?
Do you really have it?
How could that possibly
be in your hands?
Why don't you give it to me now?
The Cruise Hotel that my brother
worked on as his final project.
Amazing.
As expected of Go Bong.
Why so important about
how I acquired it?
My life is pathetic,
but so is yours.
Both your sister and your wife...
What are you talking about?
Give it. Give it!
How much money did you
steal all these years, huh?
For building Silver Town, you took
the entire construction cost, huh?
I'll go public with this.
Don't do this, and
tell me what you want.
What do I want?
If you give up all your shares
and step down as chairman...
- I'll hand this over.
- What did you say?
Give it. Now.
Here we go.
Ma'am, you're tired, aren't you?
I'm almost done, so you can go ahead
and enjoy your dinner later.
Oh my. How can you be
so pretty and kind?
I'm a bit pretty and kind, aren't I?
You're so pretty, ma'am.
All the men must have been
chasing after you when you were young.
I heard this song on the radio.
It goes like this.
'When I was young,
I didn't know about youth.'
When I was in love, I didn't see love.
- That's the one, right?
- That's right.
That's what getting older is like.
Only after time passes
do you learn about
so many things in life.
So if there's anything
you'd like to do, do it all.
If you meet someone you like,
fall in love and live happily together.
If you live that way
when you're young
you won't come to regret things
when you're older.
I will. I will keep that in mind.
Why did Chairman Choi Young Dal
step down as CEO?
- Who is going to take the job now?
- Are you going to take the job?
- Did you do it yourself?
- Look this way, please.
- Please look this way.
- A comment, please.
I will be in charge from now on.
I will be in charge of Daehan
and move it forward.
Wait a second.
Look.
What brings you here?
What do you mean?
- I came to talk to you about something.
- About what?
Do you want to get in first?
- Get in.
- Okay.
What is it?
I...
It's just that...
How frustrating.
- What is it? Tell me.
- Well...
Remember how you asked me
something yesterday...
At Silver Town.
I... wanted to give you an answer.
Ah, I see.
Actually...
I don't know if I can do this, but...
So what I'm trying to say is...
To be honest...
Look over there.
[Director Choi Dae Han
demands sex from lady named A]
- That's his car.
- That's right.
Hurry, take pictures.
How do you know her?
Did that take place?
Are you going to sue her?
- Please answer.
- Make a comment, please.
The man in the picture...
Is me!
It wasn't Choi Dae Han!
But me, Choi Shin Hyung!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Why on earth would he protect Dae Han?
We have to worry about you right now.
That's not what we were looking for.
Choi Shin Hyung is toying with us.
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
I was thinking about
going along with the blue sky...
to get to the Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.