Mr. Back
It's already Christmas Eve tomorrow.
Yes, that's right.
It's finally tomorrow.
Ah, that's right.
Here you go.
- What is it?
- It's an invitation.
We have a Christmas event at
our resort the day after tomorrow.
My proposal was chosen.
Really?
Congratulations.
One who creates memories...
I did well in all my training classes
and I did my best preparing for it,
so you have to come.
Sure.
Christmas...
I'll wait for you there.
I should come.
[Final Episode]
On the day of the next meteor shower
take this at where
the accident took place.
'Gu Bu Duk Gu.'
'The pain of not getting what you want.'
[Choi Go Bong, you have one day
to return on your payment.]
I wonder whose son he is.
He's so handsome.
What do you think you're doing?
The buyer wants to postpone the date
to sign off on the contract.
I had no choice.
Selling the resort to
a foreign company isn't right.
It's not too late to change your mind.
You, seriously...
I'm busy preparing for tomorrow's event.
I should go now.
What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing?
People are watching.
You shouldn't be doing this here.
You get your entire family involved
and even use my weaknesses.
What did you hand over
to the investor?
- Who you really are.
- What?
I let them know what would happen
to the resort if they let you run it.
I explained that to them in vivid detail.
What is it?
A hiccup in your plan?
I can handle that
on my own just fine.
If you keep this up, it'll be dangerous.
- What's dangerous about it?
- Hong Ji Yoon...
As for what you're working on...
put everything back
in its original place.
What are you planning to do?
So did everything go well?
Of course. You know whose son I am.
He said he would either
postpone the deal or think it over.
I guess he realized who
Director Jung really was.
- Anyway, you're okay, right?
- Of course.
You know whose father I am.
Don't worry about the text messages.
It just adds more stress,
so it won't be good for your health.
- Okay.
- I'll just throw it out.
What kind of cell phone is that?
- Nothing will happen, so don't worry.
- Okay.
I hear there's a Christmas event
at the resort tomorrow.
That's right.
I have to step out again because of that.
Sure. Don't worry about me, and get to it.
Eun Ha Soo worked on it, so you have
to come no matter what, okay?
Okay, I understand.
Choi Shin Hyung!
Excuse me...
What were you doing there?
You could've been hit by a car.
It's just that my meteor bracelet
fell off, so...
Where were you headed?
I had to do something
for the event tomorrow.
I'll go find the bracelet
so go about your work.
All right then. I'll go.
Hong Ji Yoon.
Can I help you?
You worked on the Cruise Hotel project
with the late Chairman Choi, correct?
Yes, I did.
One of the contractors
has filed a lawsuit against you.
Since Chairman Choi passed away
there hasn't been any progress.
We will need to ask questions
on the charges of dereliction of duties.
Merry Christmas.
What brings you here at this hour?
Santa Claus who even gives toys
to crying children is here.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
No, just continue.
What will you be doing then?
I'll just watch you work.
Have a seat.
You set the date for the surgery, right?
Yes, I did.
The next program is called,
'Walk For the Mind.'
Ever since I met you...
I feel like I can walk in
a dark road without a lamp.
I feel like I can cross the ocean on foot.
I feel like I can fly without wings.
Ever since I met you...
I feel like I have everything
I've ever wanted.
Oh man, I'm so tired.
I can't help yawning.
By the way, aren't you
going to open my present?
Open my present first.
Ta-da.
Eun Ha Soo.
They say even a kitchen-hand working
for three years can cook ramen.
I'm don't even come close
to my father's skills.
But I made it myself.
I've always been on the receiving end.
I wanted to get you something, too.
Try it on.
I made it according to your measurements
from the last time.
I wonder if it will fit well.
Wow.
The model is good,
so the clothes fit so well.
[Choi Shin Hyung]
What is it?
Is it hard to move around in it?
In all my life...
I've never received any present
that's more special than this one.
Well, it's not that special, you know.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Marry Christmas, Choi Shin Hyung.
The same to you.
Merry...
Christmas...
[Choi Shin Hyung]
Ha Soo, see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow. Good night.
- You too.
Wow.
I'm sorry that I made you sad...
and I'm also sorry that I won't
be able to keep my promise.
I'm sorry I fell in love with you.
I wonder if you'll like
my Christmas present.
[Choi Shin Hyung]
Redirecting your call...
[D-day.]
Open the door, Choi Shin Hyung!
Why are you doing this?
Open the door.
Please open the door.
Why are you doing this?
Open the door!
Open the door, Choi Shin Hyung!
Why are you doing this? Open the door.
Choi Shin Hyung. Choi Shin Hyung!
Why are you doing this?
Please open the door.
Let's talk face-to-face.
What is it?
He won't open the door.
I think he's inside.
Something isn't right.
I'll go get the key.
Choi Shin Hyung!
- It was my father's.
- I know.
These are the glasses I fixed for him
and the mint I gave him.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
I'm sorry I made you sad...
and I'm sorry I won't be able
to keep my promise.
I'm sorry I fell in love with you.
When rain stops on the long hill
green from the pasture
is more noticeable.
As I send them away
a sad song comes to mind.
We add tears of farewell
to the blue ocean every year.
By getting to know you
I realized things in this world
weren't so irrelevant.
I learned to appreciate
being born into this world.
As I love you with all my heart
I love the world where people live.
When I see a wild flower on the street...
the days of when
you were there with me...
and the day when
I put my head on your shoulder...
Just like the sun sets on the ocean
we were very happy together.
Go home.
I'll come to the event tomorrow.
[Eun Ha Soo]
Redirecting your call...
Manager Sung, have you seen my father?
- Where is Chairman Choi?
- Nowhere.
He wants us to come home.
Father...
Father.
Have you now returned
to the way you were?
Father, let's go to the hospital.
Let's go have the surgery now.
Let's do that, Chairman Choi.
What if something goes wrong
tomorrow morning like Dr. Kim said?
What do we do?
Let's go to the hospital now,
Chairman Choi.
- Please.
- Okay.
- Let's go to the hospital.
But...
- Just one more day.
- Father.
I made a promise.
I promised to come to the event tomorrow.
After I go there...
I'll go to the hospital immediately.
Chairman Choi.
Tumen River...
in the blue water...
The boatman is rowing a boat.
He's rowing a boat
with my lover from the past.
The boat has left...
Where did it go?
Father.
My lover that I miss so dearly.
- Could you clean up the table there?
- Sure.
- It's so pretty.
- Really?
Ha Soo, how do we look?
You two look good together.
It's so pretty.
I'll finish up here.
Choi Shin Hyung, you're really okay, right?
You're coming to today's event, right?
I wonder what time
the event will end.
It would probably
take about two hours.
What are you so worried about?
No, I'm not worried.
It's just that...
You still have the medicine
that Dr. Kim gave you, right?
Yes.
What are you going to do with it?
Will you take it?
If you're going to take it
you have to go to where the sinkhole was.
It's better to go there and wait...
Then I'll go in.
I'll wait in the car then.
If there is anything,
call me right away.
Okay, I will.
- Where did Choi Shin Hyung go?
- Who knows?
Whether he disappeared
to the sky or to the ground...
Gosh, I thought he'd save us.
We have no choice
but to stick to Dae Han.
How is he able to save us?
Like Choi Shin Hyung said,
we can all go to prison...
or we can do community service.
We will just have to wait for
the court's decision.
Oh my god.
If I had known this
I'd have taken out more money
and flown to Germany.
What? You still haven't
come to your senses, have you?
How much did you sneak out to Germany?
Why would you want to know that?
Why don't you reclaim
the New York department store?
Gosh, how about you two?
How much of the secret funds
did you take out?
- Oh my! What's happening?
- What's going on?
- Please wait.
- Press the emergency button.
- Emergency button.
- Emergency button?
Yi Hye, you're closer.
- Where is it? Where?
- Right there.
No way! No way!
You half-wits.
Brother.
If you don't get your act together...
I'll show up every day...
and I'll haunt you!
Please save us.
- I was wrong, brother.
- Please don't do that.
Please forgive me.
I won't live like that again.
- I was wrong, brother.
- Kill me, brother.
I was wrong, brother.
I won't do it again.
- Are you okay, Yi Hye?
- Yes.
- How about you, honey?
- I wasn't the only one who saw him ,right?
I wasn't the only one
who saw him, right?
I can even smell the cologne
my brother used all the time.
That was so weird.
Did everything go okay
at the prosecution office?
I was sued for obstruction to
perform duties by our contractor.
Yesterday Choi Shin Hyung
said this could help and left it.
What is it?
We did terminate the contract
with them in the past.
We did it in secret,
so we even got rid of the document.
He said this would help
since we need the documents now.
So Choi Shin Hyung gave this document
with my late father's signature, huh?
But I'm not sure what I should do with it.
- This will do.
- Pardon?
Prosecutor Yang, how did it go?
We have a problem.
Everything has been exposed.
Prosecutor Gu is on his way there now.
Is he?
Okay.
I'm grateful that I get to share
this special event with my loving parents.
Mom and Dad.
Thank you for raising me.
Don't be sad that your daughter
of 27 years is getting married.
I'll live a fulfilling and happy life.
Thank you.
This is our final event for the night.
The last applicant is the most
handsome man at our resort.
President Choi Dae Han.
The one I wanted to give
my best Christmas memory is...
my father, the late Chairman Choi Go Bong.
He spent all his life at Daehan Resort.
He loved his employees
more than anyone.
Compared to him, I have so much to learn.
I realized that as I rose
to lead Daehan Resort.
He taught me that the best leader...
is someone who works next to
the employees, not above them.
I want to send him
my appreciation and respect.
[Appreciation Plaque]
Eun Ha Soo.
These are the ones
I've been working on.
Because they are well organized into files
it will be easy to look over them.
Yi Gun.
Jung Yi Gun.
Regarding the case involving the late
Chairman Choi's five billion won
a warrant has been issued for your arrest
for defamation and embezzlement.
Please come with us.
I will.
Hold on a second.
I almost forgot something important.
And this is something you worked on
with the late Chairman Choi.
It's the business plan for Cruise Hotel.
Take care.
Take care of Hong Ji Yoon.
Next news is...
November of last year
the late Chairman Choi Go Bong
passed away in defamation
due to the case involving an exploding car
containing five billion won.
The truth of the case
has just been revealed.
Director Jung wished to bring down
the Choi family from management.
It has been confirmed that he had
placed the money into the chairman's car.
Thus the late Chairman Choi's
reputation should be restored.
Redirecting your call...
Why isn't he answering the phone
when the event's over?
Where did he go?
- Manager Sung.
- Yes?
Do you know where
Chairman Choi might be?
No, I can't get in touch with him.
It's crazy.
Did he go to where the
accident took place?
What?
First, get in the car.
Anyway...
If the time is up and
something happened to him
he asked us not to look for him.
Since there’s nothing we could do now.
He said we should just accept
the situation as it is.
- That's what he said and he left.
- Seriously.
He didn't go to the hospital.
Where could he have gone?
If he isn't at the location
of the accident
what are we supposed to do?
It's a mint.
Do you go around
giving it to everyone?
Actually, I am...
The day when you were in
the sinkhole accident...
- Yes?
- Did you eat one of these?
Thank you for holding his hand
at that time.
I don't...
have much time left.
He's not at the hospital.
If he's not at the sinkhole,
where else could he be?
It's almost time now.
Father.
[Choi Dae Han]
[Sung Gyung Bae]
My dearest son.
My son, Choi Dae Han.
You've grown up to be
a fine young man.
I regret so many things,
but grateful at the same time.
Whenever you face
difficult situations in your life
I hope you won't lose your beliefs
and live accordingly.
I'm sorry, but could you go
a little bit faster?
Choi Shin Hyung!
You're Choi Shin Hyung, aren't you?
I thought maybe, but...
How?
Chairman Choi Go Bong...
Choi Shin Hyung.
Can you explain this to me
so that I can understand?
I never wanted to deceive you.
I wanted to tell you everything.
But I didn't have the courage to do it.
I'm sorry.
Lies.
Where are you trying to go
if you feel so bad?
If you disappear like that...
what are people left behind
supposed to do?
An old man like me...
Forget me.
Time will do that for you.
No.
I don't want to forget about you.
I won't give up either.
You are Choi Shin Hyung in my eyes.
There has to be a way.
Let's find a way together.
Please don't give up, Choi Shin Hyung.
Eun Ha Soo.
Don't do that, Choi Shin Hyung.
Please.
I'll wait for you.
And I'll pray, too.
Until you come back, Choi Shin Hyung.
We cannot sell off Daehan Resort
to a foreign company.
Now I will present the new management
strategies to the board of directors.
I will explain the screen presentation.
It's our business nature to get influenced
by the market economy.
The business recession
that lasted a few years now...
is effecting Daehan Resort negatively.
Moreover, due to an increasing number
of competitors in the resort business
it's the truth that Daehan Resort
is being threatened.
Especially, as the business recession
influenced the global economy
there has been a hiccup in our plan
to expand overseas as well.
For that reason, we need renovation
for our second wind.
Especially, as the regulations have evolved
an idea of combining medical service
and a hotel
a project called Meditel has been allowed.
We can see this as
an opportunity for Daehan Resort.
I did a good job, didn't I?
I want to be praised today.
I have a letter for you.
[Eun Ha Soo]
- What is this?
- You'll know when you read it.
It was my first time.
The way I felt about you...
Is it your first time?
for Choi Shin Hyung?
I. Will. Not. Tell. You.
Gosh, that's not fair.
[One year later]
Smile.
Father, today's the foundation day,
so I have a lot of events to attend.
I'll be late tonight.
I'll see you later.
- Manager Sung.
- I've found him!
I've found him.
After I received your order...
I've been looking for him
all year long.
- I didn't get to go to Canada.
- Are you sure it's him?
- Last time it was the wrong person.
- I'm 100 percent sure this time.
He was found on Christmas Day last year.
It's the same day when
Chairman Choi disappeared.
His description matches, too.
Do you think there was a mysterious force
in place so he wouldn't disappear?
Maybe you wanted to have him
around so badly...
that they heard your prayers.
There might be someone else
who prayed more earnestly than I did.
By the way, there is one problem.
When he was found...
they said he couldn't remember anything.
His age or name or anything at all.
Then he's been like that ever since?
They couldn't find who he was,
so they let him stay here.
He's so diligent and nice
that he helps other people.
They treat him like his own family here.
Chairman Choi is not someone
who would do such hard work.
- Let's take him home.
- Manager Sung.
Yes?
Chairman Choi Go Bong of Daehan Resort...
He's already dead.
President Choi.
My half-brother from Canada,
Choi Shin Hyung...
Like how you helped my late father...
you will assist my brother
in the same way, right?
It will be my honor to work
for two generations.
Who are you here for?
You can request to see someone
at the office over here.
I came to find my brother.
Your brother's name is...
Choi Shin Hyung.
Choi...
Hello.
I'm Eun Ha Soo who organized
the Christmas event last year.
Then now we will start a presentation
on how to plan Christmas events.
This is the most important part of our event.
Excuse me for a second.
- You came.
- Thank you for inviting me.
No problem.
Your seat is over there
around the corner.
- Over there?
- Go ahead.
Sure.
Choi Shin Hyung.
Everybody here calls me by that name.
Saying it's my name...
What happened?
Don't you know who I am?
I'm sorry.
I learned my real name just now, so...
Are you okay?
No, it's just that...
I'm not feeling well...
Well, then try to repeat after me.
It will calm you down.
Koong koong da. Koong koong da.
I know that one.
I taught you that one.
- So you are...
- I'm Eun Ha Soo.
- Ah.
- I'm The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
You must know a lot about me then.
The stories behind these photos...
Can you tell me about them?
That will take a while.
I... have a lot of time.
I also have lots of questions.
Do you really want to know?
What is it that you want
to know about the most?
I...
Was I...
in love with you?
If you earnestly wish for it
a miracle could happen.
In the name of love...
Subtitles by DramaFever
Shit. Shit. Shit!
Oh my, good work.
This is for you, Uncle,
and this is for you, Aunt.
Choi Young Dal, Lee In Ja, Choi Yi Hye...
What is this?
I wish this precious moment
would last forever.
My name is Cha Do Hyun.
28 years old.
They say I have
dissociative identity disorder.
Shin Se Ki. Mr. X.
Nana. Ahn Yo Seop.
Ahn Yo Na. Perry Park.
I still don't know
how many people live in me.
A strange show with
seven personalities.
Kill Me, Heal Me.