Mr. Back
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
To the one who's given me
such precious memories
Again, I'm very grateful to you.
Thanks to Choi Shin Hyung,
I'm very happy now.
I wish this precious moment
would last forever.
[Episode 11]
- Manager Hong.
- What brings you here?
Well, I just wanted to get some air.
How about you, Manager Hong?
They asked me to leave them alone
so they could talk about work.
Why do they look so serious?
See you around.
- Are you looking for someone?
- No, it's just that...
- Are you looking for Eun Ha Soo?
- Yes, I wanted to thank her...
As a token of my appreciation.
- It's just that she is...
- Where is she?
It's just that...
The interns are gathered
to receive their evaluations.
Why do they have to work this late?
I'll see you at the conference
room at 8 a.m. tomorrow.
Sure.
Excuse me...
Tomorrow morning...
What are you doing there?
I was just telling you to come to
the conference room by 8 a.m. tomorrow.
I got it.
When it comes to men...
it's all about their bodies,
not their money, huh?
Was that your favorite movie?
Yes, it's my favorite one.
The movie was in celebration of
two actors' engagement in real life.
Wow, that's romantic.
But they called it off.
Maybe there is no such thing
as happily ever after...
You and I can be happy forever then.
Forever?
Is there such a thing
as forever in this world?
Every moment adds up to become forever.
If we cherish this moment
it could last forever.
This is nice.
What is it that you wanted
to talk to me about?
It's okay, so go ahead.
I'm all ears tonight.
Then what you are about to hear
you should forget about it
immediately after you hear it.
I got it, so tell me.
And go.
- You like Eun Ha Soo, don't you?
- What?
Ah... you found out.
How much of your heart
has gone to her now?
Not sure.
What if you get hurt?
I already know that
she likes Choi Shin Hyung.
By the way, what do you think
about unrequited love?
If the other person doesn't
accept your feelings...
you'll just end up hurt
and broken-hearted.
If one is still okay with that...
then one can't stop those feelings.
Don't worry. I won't end up
with a broken heart or anything.
How do you know so much
about this topic?
Did you study about love through
textbooks or something?
- Pardon?
- I'm just kidding.
You're kidding?
Why do you think that I wouldn't
have those kinds of feelings?
Well, I-I'm sure you do.
You should have those feelings.
You're a woman.
I know that.
Did you know about my feelings
for you this entire time then?
W-what's wrong?
Are you pretending not to know,
or do you really not know about them?
You knew, didn't you?
N-no, I really had no idea.
I'm sorry.
You didn't know?
I'm sorry, but I'll get going now.
Please forget what I said tonight.
Aren't you tired?
I'm okay, but you must be, right?
No, I'm not tired.
- Then shall we play a game?
- A game?
Starting now, we can only say sentences
up to five syllables long.
Do. You. Like. Me?
- Oh my, what do I do?
- 'Oh. My. What. Do. I Do.'
It's my turn now.
What. Do. You. Like. About. Me?
What? Very informal, aren't we?
Very. Informal...
you're good at this.
You. Are. Good. At. This.
You lose.
You. Should. Be. Happy.
Of. Course. I'm. Happy.
What. A. Great. Relief.
I. Don't. Have. A. Reason.
Why. I. Like. You.
Neither. Do. I.
I. Just. Like. Everything. About. You.
I. Have. Never. Felt. This. Way. Before.
Thank. You.
I. Feel. The. Same. Way.
Guess. It's. Not. Your. First. Time.
For. You. Choi. Shin. Hyung?
I. Will. Not. Tell. You.
Gosh, you're too much.
- Are you sleepy?
- No, I'm not.
I know that you are.
- What wish did you write down?
- Me?
- Well, that's a secret.
- A secret?
- I'll go and find out.
- No, you can't!
- Here we go.
- No, no, you can't!
It's over there! That one!
No, you can't!
So did you have a good time?
- Was the movie fun, too?
- Yes. You did well.
Of course, I did a good job.
Do you think I'd ever imagine
doing something like this for you?
By the way, what's with the face?
Did something happen?
I thought you would be overjoyed by now.
Overjoyed...
I'm so happy that I'm so scared now...
I feel like I'm standing on thin ice,
not knowing when it might crack.
Don't be so anxious.
Why worry about something
that hasn't happened yet?
Time is too precious even if
you were to live happily every day.
Is there really such a thing
as forever in this world?
Each moment adds up to become forever.
If we cherish this moment
it could last forever.
[Movie ticket]
We watched a movie.
How do I look?
Don't I look like Alain Delon?
Well, let me see...
you look nothing like him.
Nonsense.
Fine then.
Actually, Choi Shin Hyung...
is far cooler than Alain Delon.
- What is it?
- What?
No, I was just wondering if you
got back home okay last night.
- Of course.
- Ah, did you?
This won't be enough.
We may need something more special.
Didn't Choi Shin Hyung say last time...
that my late father prepared
a hidden card for Seohae Hotel?
Yes, he did.
Then he came to me...
and asked what demographic
we should target as potential guests.
So did you come up
with any answers?
We have prepared a folk dance lesson
to better serve our guests
here at Seohae Hotel.
I want you to learn how to do the dance.
I'd appreciate it if you could be
a reliable partner for our guests.
Please hold each other's hands.
Relax and...
One, two, three, four...
From this pose,
five, six, seven, eight...
Again. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
Dae Han is surprisingly
working hard, isn't he?
It's the same here,
but if you do a half-spin...
He's even teaching the dance himself?
Put your hands out and cross them...
Like this, one, two, three, four...
Right here, to the side.
Five, six, seven, eight...
Whatever she does is beautiful.
One, two, three, four...
What am I supposed to do, huh?
- Thank you for your time.
- Don't mention it.
How can I just ignore it when
it's my late father's hotel?
Furthermore, so many employees' families
depend on this job.
How many employees
do we have in this hotel alone?
We all have to work together
for everyone to make a living.
To switch to Meditel
it will require a tremendous
amount of money right away.
If we spend the money and
there aren't enough guests...
We need a shocking headline.
One way to appeal to the elderly
is to make them feel like
they're at a cultural center.
You're saying to open up
our facilities to the public, right?
What's the point of properly
setting the table?
The food will go to waste
if no one will come and eat.
About my late father's
business plan for Meditel
I'll hand it over to Dae Han.
Have him go over it thoroughly.
It looks as if President Choi
revived Seohae Hotel.
It would be impossible
by Choi Dae Han's own efforts.
It seems that Choi Shin Hyung
is helping him.
Since when did they start
getting along with one another
that they would team up like that?
Isn't there a way to make them
turn against each other again?
It's men who conquer the world.
But it's women who move those men.
I'm saying that we can handle them
if we use one woman.
- You're saying that's Eun Ha Soo, huh?
- Bingo.
Wasn't it suspicious ever since
she applied to work at Seohae Hotel?
When no one wanted to go
she even convinced
her co-workers to go with her.
Well, among young people these days...
there something called,
'How To Win Over A Rich Man'.
- 'How To Win Over A Rich Man'?
- Yes.
The first step is to get a job
where the rich guy works.
She sure did get a job, didn't she?
Second, whereas everybody
is crazy about him
she's the only one
who ignores him.
Wait a second.
Who are you to ignore me?
- Thank you.
- That's attractive.
Then the rich guy falls for her
that refreshing quality about her.
You're the first woman
who has treated me this way.
Starting today, you're mine. Got it?
Third, the woman always
slaps him in the face.
Take that filthy hand off of me!
How refreshing.
You're the first woman
who treats me this badly.
From that moment, the rich guy...
Eun Ha Soo, Eun Ha Soo, Eun Ha Soo...
- I'm sorry.
- He becomes her slave.
Oh my, that's how Eun Ha Soo
seduced him then?
She looks so innocent,
but she's totally wicked, isn't she?
So what do you suggest
we do with Eun Ha Soo then?
We don't have to do anything.
If we just let her do
whatever she does
the brothers will turn against
each other on their own.
We'll just sit back and watch.
No, we should make her work for us.
- So we can use her as our spy.
- Will she go for that?
She'll find it easier to turn her life
around by picking one of the two men.
No, no, no!
President Choi.
Why is it so hard to track you down
to say thank you?
- Thank me?
- Yes.
I wanted to thank you for persuading
the other employees to come and work here.
Not at all. It's my job.
It's disappointing when you say
you were only doing your job.
You refused my necklace, too.
Actually, I...
those feelings that were
at one percent have grown...
I'm worried that they may become
100 percent one day.
I'm sorry.
But I hope that you would
get over your feelings for me.
Are you turning me down?
Actually, I like Choi Shin Hyung.
With Choi Shin Hyung...
I don't know how serious
it is between you two...
but I just wanted to let you know
that I have feelings for you, too.
I'm nobody...
I appreciate that
you think of me that way...
but President Choi, please consider
the other person's feelings as well.
You once told me...
When reality doesn't go along
with your feelings
you can make the reality work for you.
- About that...
- I can just make it work for my feelings.
Man, I'm hungry.
The first assignment out of five is...
- going fishing.
- Going fishing?
Actually, I like Choi Shin Hyung.
Honey!
Come on, wake up. You'll be late.
Give back the teddy bear.
Can you put it down?
Now can you change your clothes?
You're a good boy. How good.
Here is your jacket.
- You should come home early.
- Of course.
There's such a pretty flower
waiting for me at home...
I have never seen such a pretty flower
like yourself before.
You'll be late. Hurry up.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Brother-in-law, breakfast is ready.
Come and eat.
No, no way.
No way. Absolutely not.
- Where are you going?
- No need to know.
Are you going out on a date,
by any chance?
Are you going to see Eun Ha Soo?
Why did you want to go fishing?
I told you to think it through
and pick five things.
I did think it through.
- This is what I did with my late father.
- Ah, I see.
I wonder if Dae Han
has anything like that.
Oh my, what are you doing here?
Of all the fishing spots,
you picked this one?
I agree. What a coincidence.
- It's freezing.
- How can a young man think it's cold out?
Man, it's been a while.
By the way, who's better at fishing
between the two of you?
Of course, that's me.
What can he possibly know?
He only knows mackerel and cutlass fish
when they're on the dinner table.
Don't underestimate me.
I usually have no interest in this.
My late father never took me with him.
The rod is moving!
- Pull it.
- How?
- How, how?
- Move away.
- Let me.
- Wow, it's big!
Once you pull it,
you need to lift slowly.
Otherwise, it will escape.
- Oh my, this guy is strong, huh?
- Be careful!
- Wow!
- Jackpot!
- Here it is.
- Wow, it's a big one.
By the way, who caught this one?
- I caught it.
What do you mean?
I held the rod right here.
If you held on, it would
have already escaped.
Oh my, then let's say
that I caught this one.
Carp!
Wow, that's amazing.
Okay then. Shall we taste it now?
It's so good.
It's delicious.
It's good, right?
Have one more.
It's my fish.
What do you think?
We'll choose the best of the best
for the merchandise.
- What's going on with Seohae Hotel?
- Not sure.
Dae Han won't be able
to do it by himself.
Are you saying Choi Shin Hyung
is capable enough to pull it off?
He's not the late Chairman Choi Go Bong.
Not only does he look like
my late brother...
but is it possible to have
his exact DNA, too?
How can he make this possible otherwise?
Excuse me.
What do we do?
Director Jung is very angry.
- I'm sure there is a way.
- We have to find the way.
If we had known things
would turn out this way
should we have joined the team
for Seohae Hotel?
Seriously...
That is so wrong.
Hey, honey.
What are you doing in my office?
We'll see each other often from now on.
Manager Hong gave him this office
because he helped out with Seohae Hotel.
It's time for you two
to get along.
We're getting along just fine.
Don't you think so?
As for how you're going
to handle Seohae Hotel
go and get me the reports immediately.
Something is buzzing here
on the Internet.
[A premium outlet is moving into
Seohae Hotel's current location.]
- What is it that you want?
- President Choi. Let go.
Are you destroying the efforts made
by all those people overnight?
It's not what I wanted.
- It's what the board of directors want.
- What?
President Choi, please stop.
You shouldn't handle this matter this way.
The decision was made for
the sake of the company.
It's not what I want.
You know at least that much, don't you?
Jung Yi Gun is really
a cunning man.
Choi Young Dal, Lee In Ja,
Choi Yi Hye, Jung Yi Gun.
Find out what they are up to right now.
Do you want me to look into
all of them on my own?
Of course you should.
Did you expect me to hold your hand
and come with you?
- Go now!
- Jeez.
Why do you boss me around all the time?
You can't stand to see me
relax for a day, can you?
I'm going.
What am I doing here
without eating?
I'm not a detective. I'm starving.
Why aren't these people coming out
after going in to see a fortuneteller?
How could you ask me
to come to a place like this?
Excuse me.
Are you here to find out your fortune?
Do you have to do that now?
No, it's just that...
The women that were just here...
what kind of reading did they come in for?
Hey, hey!
Doctors must keep
patient confidentiality.
Like reporters who
protect their informants
We, fortunetellers must also protect
our clients in the same manner.
If we go yapping about their personal lives,
we're done for in this field.
What's with the face?
- You have a lot of worries.
- Pardon?
Tell me your birth date.
Yes, the name is Choi Go Bong.
He was born on November 5, 1945, at 6 a.m.
- What do you think you're doing?
- What?
Do dead people show up for
health check-ups these days?
How dare you bring information
of a dead man!
I don't want to see you. Get out!
He's already dead?
- Are you sure?
- Gosh.
What's the matter?
The mystery of the universe
is wrapped around his body.
He's been given a new life for free.
It's true that he came back
to life, isn't it?
It's a very precious time he should be
willing to trade for living 70 years.
However...
He should keep the time he promised.
What do you mean? Does that mean...
After the time he was given...
He'll die?
If he takes a rock from the universe
he'll return to looking like an old man
and die when the time comes.
If he doesn't do anything...
he's destined to die when
the time comes in his current body.
He doesn't have much time left.
What do I do about him?
Gosh, what do I do?
Why are you still here, huh?
Then...
There  must be some kind of
talisman to stop it, isn't there?
What did I say?
Gosh, why are you still here, huh?
You brought me information
about a dead man.
Get out now!
I was wrong, but...
- Give me an talisman to take care of it.
- I said get out.
- One talisman, please.
- Get out. I said, get out.
Just one talisman...
I said leave. Now.
How can he bring information
about a dead man?
What are you going to do?
I should let Choi Dae Han
handle it on his own...
even if he might end up
losing everything.
How can you say such nonsense?
If you're still around
at the crucial moment
as long as you don't collapse...
couldn't you take back
whatever it is?
Without me...
Dae Han has to learn to stand
in the ring on his own.
You've seen him all your life.
Don't you know that by now?
I know that you wanted
to raise him to be a lion
but he's not cut out for it.
He's too weak.
Even so...
He's getting stronger.
- And I'm getting weak.
- Don't say that.
And throw away the cell phone
and the texts.
- It's no use.
- What?
Do you know how nervous
I get every day because of those?
You don't know how I feel.
By the way, the fortuneteller said...
It's okay. I don't believe
in things like that.
Gosh, you're driving me crazy.
I never knew how precious
each and every day would be.
Aren't you done yet? Let's go.
Stop damaging President Choi's reputation.
Ji Yoon.
How could you destroy
what we started like this?
I told you that you'd get hurt.
- I was against it for your sake...
- Yi Gun.
Are you really going to do this?
It seems that Director Choi Young Dal
contacted the board of directors.
I had no choice but to
go along with the majority.
Please help us.
I'll do whatever you want.
[Choi Go Bong, you have 20 days
to return on your payment.]
Who in the world is
sending these messages?
[You have a message.]
[Choi Go Bong, you have 19 days
to return on your payment.]
[Please call me.]
Who are you?
Your second assignment out of five is...
to visit Eun Ha Soo's
favorite restaurants.
What a simple-minded woman.
What is this? Your favorite place to eat
is a measly spicy rice cakes place?
What do you mean a measly
spicy rice cakes place?
This isn't just an ordinary
spicy rice cake.
It's a super hot dish that
relieves all of your stress.
- Super Hot spicy rice cakes?
- Yes.
- Let me see.
- What do you suggest?
You have to finish this dish
within three minutes.
Get ready. Set.
Get ready, come on.
Go.
Spicy! It's so spicy.
How can anybody eat this?
You pay for something like this?
It's free if you finish it
within three minutes.
Hurry.
Gosh, why do I have to do this, huh?
It's hot.
The last one.
Ma'am, I did it.
What is it?
You ate here for free a month ago
and you're back again?
You finished it nine seconds
faster this time.
- You finished in first place.
- Thank you.
I was in first place last time, too.
But are you usually that extreme?
Why? I still had spice rice cakes
for free, you know.
You're one of those people who would
chew bricks if they were free, huh?
No way. Bricks aren't tasty.
I can still taste the spiciness.
Here. You went to that place
again, didn't you?
Yes.
- It's self-service here, by the way.
- You seriously.
Go ahead.
After you eat something spicy
you should have something
sweet to calm your lips.
Gosh, that's not it.
If you do this, the chocolate will melt,
and it becomes sweet.
- Go ahead.
- Wow.
It's amazing.
- Choi Shin Hyung.
- Yes?
- You woman!
- You look like Charlie Chaplin.
- Come over here.
- No!
Why are they doing that again?
Come here.
Oh my, they make me itchy.
Is it gone? No?
What are you doing here?
I was just looking at this.
I made a tree with my father
just once when I was little.
That might be the first time
I learned what a Christmas tree was.
Ever since that time, I never once
decorated a tree with him again.
If I made one with my mother
and waited up for him
he wouldn't even look at it saying
he was too busy with year-end business.
He must have done that
because he didn't have the time.
He was responsible for his family,
but also his many employees.
He must have been.
I hope the deal about Seohae Hotel
won't trouble the employees.
You handled today's schedule quite well.
You're more confident in front
of the board of directors, too.
It's not that I couldn't.
Once I do it, I do it well, don't I?
We have a tight schedule tomorrow.
I canceled your dinner appointment.
- Why?
- It's your birthday tomorrow.
Whose birthday? Mine?
How time flies.
I wish you a happy birthday
ahead of time.
Don't buy me anything expensive again,
like a watch or something.
I'm grateful enough that
you remember my birthday every year.
You don't know what day it is, do you?
Today?
Not really. Is it Wednesday?
- This smells good, doesn't it?
- Yes.
Hey.
It's very moist. It's good.
Wow, it's nice.
Hey, should we buy this whole set
and share it?
Deal.
I'll buy it.
Cool, aren't you? It's good.
[Pervert punk]
One second.
- Yes, President Choi.
- It's me.
- Are you done for the day?
- Yes, I left the office a little while ago.
Did you?
Can you come by my house later?
What is it about?
You asked me to be considerate
towards other people...
so I'll be honest.
It's my birthday today,
so I wanted to invite you over...
I worked up the courage to call you
because it's my birthday.
Please don't stand me up.
What is it? What did he say?
It's his birthday, so he wants me
to come over. What do I do?
What do I do?
You can't not go when he invited you
to his birthday party.
Is that right?
Hi, The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
What? Dae Han did?
Ah, he did, huh?
Come over.
I get to see you,
so it's fine with me.
What misunderstanding?
I won't do that.
I'd be grateful if you could come over
and wish him a happy birthday.
You're here. Have a seat.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming.
I was worried that
you might not come over.
By the way, why are you alone?
Oh my, who did you say came by?
Dae Han! Dae Han!
- Happy birthday!
- Let's go party. Congratulations.
How can you stop by
without any notice?
We wanted to throw you
a surprise birthday party.
- Isn't that right?
- You're no help at all.
- Shall we go out?
- No, I'll leave.
Where are you going?
You're a guest.
Did you say your name...
was Eun Ha Soo?
Yes.
What do your parents do for a living?
My mother runs a tailor shop.
- My father passed away.
- Goodness.
Oh my, you were raised by a single mom.
Why do you ask such things?
A tailor shop?
- Is that okay with you?
- What are you talking about now?
If she were the one
whom you would marry...
Oh my.
Did someone just make
a wedding announcement?
Still, an intern isn't quite
good enough, you know.
Wouldn't there be such a difference
between households?
If you're going to talk about that,
please just leave.
It's up to me whether
I date her or marry her.
Oh my, you're already making
an official announcement?
They might end up getting married
at that rate, huh?
Enough. Enough!
Get up.
What are you doing?
Good night.
Wait!
She is my guest.
Let go of her hand.
A war is about to break out
between them.
We have a problem.
I said let go of her hand, seriously!
I want you all to leave.
You may not know this...
But Eun Ha Soo is a sly woman.
I can sense that she's a golddigger...
- What did you say?
- Shin Hyung.
- Be careful.
- Of course.
Bringing in a wrong woman
will ruin the whole family.
How long are you
going to live like this?
- How long?
- Oh, shit.
Eun Ha Soo.
I apologize if my family offended you.
That's not it.
I'm sorry.
Oh my, I'm sleepy.
What is it? Did something happen?
No.
It seems that President Choi is
very serious these days.
He seems really into you.
- That's not it.
- Eun Ha Soo, I envy you.
You're having a happy dilemma
between two rich men.
What do you mean, happy?
When he showed interest in me at first
I thought he was playing around,
so I didn't take it seriously.
He might have been sincere.
Did President Choi confess
his feelings for you or something?
He did, didn't he?
What do you do?
It's good to see them
working so well together right now.
What if I come between them
and ruin everything?
You just focus on your feelings.
How can I only think of myself?
They're brothers, not complete strangers.
Gosh, what do you do?
I really enjoyed
my birthday dinner tonight.
The seaweed soup this morning
was a bit bland.
Can you add more seasoning next time?
- What is it?
- We didn't make the seaweed soup.
Then who made it?
Choi Shin Hyung got up
early this morning.
He prepared the seaweed
and made the soup himself.
Why did you come here?
It's just that...
I wish I were unconscientious,
so I could ignore how Dae Han feels.
Aren't I worse in that department?
I like someone like you
when I'm a nobody.
What are you talking about?
I'm not saying this just because
your family hurt my feelings.
What I'm trying to say is...
that we should stop here.
What is his deal?
Why did he make me the seaweed soup?
What is that?
'My wishes.'
'Be happy every day.'
What's all this?
'Try to email.'
[Try to parachute like my son.]
[Travel with my son.]
[Make seaweed soup on my son's birthday.]
'Make seaweed soup on my son's birthday.'
Is it because of Dae Han,
by any chance?
That's not it.
I'm not someone your family
would welcome.
I thought I'd been living a good life.
Somehow, I felt lousy.
They're not wrong
in their words, either.
And what scares me the most is...
you two have just gotten close.
I don't want you to grow apart
because of me.
Choi Shin Hyung.
I want us to stop seeing each other.
Even if everything about me may be false
my sincerity and the way
I feel about you is real.
Subtitles by DramaFever
I saw some notes inside the room.
There was one with
Eun Ha Soo's name written on it.
I have a strange boyfriend.
I wish him to be truly happy.
Eun Ha Soo is hiding her feelings
because of us.
I won't have reason to see you anymore.