Mr. Back
[Episode 13]
Gosh, I momentarily fell asleep.
I had a good time, thanks to you.
What is it? Are you tired?
No, I had a good time, too.
You don't look like you did...
It's just that...
you're not planning on going somewhere
without telling me, are you?
Ah, no.
Why are you asking me that
all of a sudden?
If you're not, that's fine.
I hope you don't keep secrets from me.
Because the time I spend with you
makes me happy
I might be worried for no reason.
I want him to get a thorough
medical examination.
He just won't want to
come to the hospital.
You said he had a heart attack
before the surgery, right?
Yes, when it was impossible
to breathe on his own
- it was like a miracle.
- Really?
And there was something strange.
There was something different about him.
- Like what?
- Well...
the blood was pumping
backwards into his heart.
And then it caused
the heart to stop.
It was my first time seeing this happen
at such an accelerated pace...
Oh my...
What is it?
You're not feeling well?
Let's go see a doctor today.
- What?
- Let's get a medical exam done.
No, thanks.
I'm fine.
I don't want you to collapse again like
last time and make things hard for me.
I won't make things hard
for you again.
Are you keeping something from me?
What if you are suffering
from a terminal illness?
Hi, Aunt.
T-the hospital?
Uncle is?
Oh, honey.
Enough is enough.
Were you trying to kill him
or something?
They said his blood pressure
is stabilizing.
I also collapsed because of him.
So this is your revenge?
How could you do this to him?
That's enough.
- Brother.
- Honey.
Why did you bring him here?
Shouldn't I be here?
I heard my uncle was about to die.
- I'm not about to die.
- Are you all right?
Can't you see?
Can you imagine how much
she tortured him
to make his blood pressure
shoot up like that?
He ignored all the warnings
and his liver shut down.
Why is that all my fault?
- He's just old now.
- Shut it.
Did Director Jung stop by yet?
If he shows up here
that would make him
a human being.
All he did was make us
fight amongst one another.
It was a fight between you two.
Why are you blaming Director Jung?
That's ridiculous.
Jung Yi Gun is the one who betrayed us.
Acting like he helped
revive Seohae Hotel
he was bragging about that
to the board of directors.
- As expected, he's a smart man.
- What did you say?
He took care of things
without getting himself involved.
He's responsible for a couple's quarrel
and caused trouble within our family.
- You want to live a long life, don't you?
- Yes.
It's not too late yet.
You'll live long only if
your organs are healthy.
Your liver is all swollen, and...
you have a dark mind.
How can you possibly live long?
How much longer do you think
you can live at this rate?
- What... what are you doing?
- What did I tell you?
'Too much is as bad as too little.'
This happens when you're too greedy.
Will you come to your senses
if you know when you will die?
- How arrogant...
- Honey.
- Send him out.
- Get out. Get out!
- Get out now!
- Why?
Wasn't it enough to damage
my father's reputation?
Why are you still living like this?
My father is watching us
from the afterlife!
Oh my, brother.
Why in the world did you
have to send him?
Honey, honey.
Yi Hye, get him out of here,
or your brother will die.
Get out! I said get out!
Get out. Get out!
Oh, my brother...
He's gone too far, seriously.
- My brother.
- Shut it. You scared me.
Won Jung Hyoi Go.
The pain of facing things you hate.
- Shut up!
- Quiet!
Eun Ha Soo.
Hello.
- Well...
- About my brother...
- About Shin Hyung...
- What is it?
- Go ahead.
- Well...
I was just asking you
to be nice to my brother.
By the way, what about my brother?
Is he going somewhere, by any chance?
Why? Did he say something?
No, that's not it, but...
I just got this sense he might be.
He's not sick or anything like that, is he?
- Well, about that...
- What is it?
Is he really sick?
No.
I'm looking into it,
so don't worry too much.
Okay.
He's handsome.
Why didn't I see it all this time?
What is it?
- How do you like this ring?
- It's pretty.
- What is this?
- What do you mean?
These are matching
couple rings, you know.
A couple?
I didn't realize it before
because we worked so closely.
But you're like oxygen to me.
I hope we start to notice
each other from now on.
I was thinking we could
start as a couple today...
Gosh, seriously!
Don't take it off!
I'll get my heart broken.
It's pretty.
How come you're not
sending me the final assignment?
Because that's not something
we can do right now.
Then when can we do it?
Wait and you'll find out.
Don't keep me waiting for too long.
Why not?
Well... no reason.
You're not going to leave me...
after you grant my final wish, are you?
Can we go see that movie
we missed last time tonight?
Really? Sure.
It shows another deficit
for this quarter.
If this continues, we won't even
have enough for maintenance.
Resorts three and four are
in danger of immediate closure.
President Choi should be
responsible for this crisis.
If we don't do anything right now
it will get even worse next year.
It's not impossible.
The late Chairman Choi's final project,
Cruise Hotel...
- About that...
- As long as we have the business plan
we can handle
the current financial crisis.
There are a good number of foreign
investors lined up for Cruise Hotel.
Then are you saying we should
bring in foreign funds?
There's no other way.
The offer will be gone
in a few days' time, too.
What's going on?
- We need the Cruise Hotel business plan.
- Why?
Did Director Jung ask you
to sneak that out, too?
- President Choi.
- What's your real objective?
- Ask Choi Shin Hyung to help you.
- What?
If you two work together
you may be able to overcome the crisis.
What is this?
[Buyout Offer]
Before Director Jung sells this resort
to the foreign corporations listed there
please hurry.
[Business report]
Why are you going through
all this trouble?
I misunderstood you
without knowing this.
Just focus on your work for now.
I'm here and just got the tickets.
Director Jung?
Hello, speaking.
Sure.
Why did you want to see me
on such short notice?
[Search and seizure warrant]
It's a search and seizure warrant
for Daehan Resort.
Before the police barge in with
the warrant tomorrow morning
I'm letting you know ahead of time.
For what?
Including Choi Dae Han, Choi Young Dal,
Lee In Ja, and Choi Yi Hye
asked for investments for Cruise Hotel,
the project the late Chairman Choi worked on.
The police have a reason to believe
they used the money for a private fund.
That's why they are trying
to investigate the matter.
You...
how long do you plan on
deceiving me for?
What do you mean by that?
I already know about
your ambition...
but there are plenty of other things
you can do on your own.
If you came this far
by your own strength
you should finish it on your own!
- Don't you think so?
- I appreciate your advice.
But I don't want to hear
anything like that anymore.
Redirecting your call to voicemail...
I'm here. Where are you?
Why can't I get a hold of you?
He's not reading it.
What's going on?
Is everything okay?
The late Chairman Choi Go Bong
once said this.
'When it comes to business,
it's all about profits or deficits.'
'It's not about right or wrong.'
What is it that you want?
Truth usually doesn't matter
in cases like these.
It will just weaken
the current management.
The late Chairman Choi
raised you to become a monster.
Then I will wait to hear from you.
Eun Ha Soo!
You fool!
Why are you out here?
Why didn't you just go home?
Why are you getting mad at me?
I'm the one who should be mad.
Ha Soo...
When it's this cold, you should have
been waiting inside where it's warm.
I thought you disappeared on me.
Your cell phone was turned off.
You said you'd wait for me here.
I'm sorry.
A sudden work meeting came up,
so I had to go...
How could you just go like that?
I was worried that you were sick again.
I was worried that
you disappeared again.
Koong, koong da.
You're feeling better now, right?
Yes.
Don't just disappear again
without telling me first, okay?
I'm here. Where are you?
Why can't I get a hold of you?
Are you sick again, by any chance?
Are you really sick?
I'm going crazy here.
Why did you switch off your phone?
Choi Shin Hyung, call me back.
Just don't be sick, okay?
Please.
You didn't go far away, did you?
Choi Shin Hyung, if you don't
call me back before I count to ten
I'll really leave!
Where on earth did you go?
- Please, after you.
- Yes, President Choi.
- You seem busy these days, huh?
- Of course.
I just couldn't stand the wrong person
acting like the owner anymore.
Let's go.
Hong Ji Yoon.
Don't stay with him anymore.
Take your hand off of her.
Isn't it enough to make her work to
the bone since your late father passed?
How long does she have to babysit you?
Gosh, you seriously!
President Choi.
All right.
You should have reacted
like this sooner.
[Choi Shin Hyung]
Don't you know that it was Jung Yi Gun
who started the premium outlets?
I know that.
We're the ones that
protected Seohae Hotel.
Then why are you sucking up to him?
Is that because
you think I'll fail again?
- No, it's not.
- Then stop working with him.
Don't do this because of me.
It's not entirely because of you.
I think it means Director Jung
gave me a chance.
What do you mean?
So I can let go of you from my heart...
I think he's given me a chance
to get you out of my mind.
I feel better.
I'm much better.
So please don't jump to conclusions again.
I'm sorry.
For making things hard for you.
That I couldn't like...
a nice woman like
Hong Ji Yoon like yourself...
I'm sorry again.
That I'm still trying to
hold onto you now.
I'm going to try really hard.
Trust me just this once.
So are you really going to
hand it over to Director Jung?
You worked on it with
Manager Hong for three years.
Take this opportunity
to kick your family out.
They're the ones who are just
taking your money any chance they get.
- You once said that my family was better.
- Did I?
It was a different situation back then.
You have some sort of plan, right?
Verify it.
You sure knew what I meant.
Like you said...
it's not about whether it's true or not.
I should put an end to it
before it gets out of control.
- This should be authentic this time, right?
- Instead...
don't try to use Choi Yi Hye anymore.
Don't break her heart.
That will be Choi Yi Hye's choice.
Don't worry about the resort.
Like you told me last time
it's a good idea that foreign companies
buy out the resort.
In exchange, in regards to
the terms for the buyout
keep the clause that
the employees keep their jobs.
I will. By the way, why did you
make this decision?
Because they're still my family...
What? Am I weird?
I hope you will understand one day.
Jung Yi Gun, this will come back
to bite you from now on.
I feel bad for you.
[Choi Go Bong, you have eight days
to return on your payment.]
Please don't try to fool me anymore.
I know everything.
Manager Sung.
As expected, you can't fool family.
You knew, didn't you?
Is he really going to die?
He's going to die on this day?
I don't know.
We'll only know when time comes.
How can a mere human
understand God's plan?
There has to be a way.
There has to be a way for him to live.
Meteor...
If we take out the meteor
he might be able to live longer.
These are the books
our late father read.
They will help you with
your work in the future.
There are books about management...
- and some about humanities.
- Why are you doing this?
What do you mean?
When someone's about to die...
I hear they do unusual things.
You won't see a doctor.
You won't have surgery, either.
Why would you make me
seaweed soup and buy me shoes?
Why did you go rock climbing with me?
Now you're even giving me
the books that our father read?
You want me to read them?
If you don't want to,
you don't have to.
I don't want to have surgery.
That's why I won't do it.
You don't have much time left.
[Choi Go Bong, you have eight days
to return on your payment.]
Look.
It's the text sent to our father.
Then why are you the one who's dying?
Nonsense.
This means nothing.
Some crazy punk keeps sending
these to our father as a prank!
So you stop worrying about it.
Please...
I wish I could do that.
I appreciate that...
But I don't think I'll have enough time.
Is Choi Shin Hyung going
somewhere, by any chance?
I don't want to have surgery.
That's why I won't do it.
Father...
Where are we going all of a sudden?
You should at least tell me, huh?
What is this?
Who is this? Manager Hong!
Good to see you.
I was waiting for you.
Are we going to go work somewhere?
- Just get in.
- Where are we going?
- Stop talking. Let's get him in.
- You should tell me where.
I said tell me where.
Get in.
What do you mean
a business trip on my day off?
Just follow me.
Manager Hong, how are you?
Good to see you, Eun Ha Soo.
- What is this about?
- I don't know.
It seems that he wants
to take us somewhere...
Get in. Just get in.
[Go on a trip with my son.]
Hold that side tightly.
Can you hurry up?
Gosh, I said to hold it properly!
I'm doing it right.
You worry about yourself.
- Eun Ha Soo. Eun Ha Soo!
- Are you okay?
Are you okay?
How can two men have trouble with this?
That's what I was saying.
He can't even do this right.
Who are you blaming
when it was your fault?
You should've held it straight.
- How could you suddenly let go?
- How crazy.
You've never done this before, have you?
You two stop fighting.
It'll get dark soon.
Why did I come along with you?
- Move. I'll try.
- It's okay.
I'll do it by myself.
What could I possibly do with him?
Two people have to click
in order to do this.
Leave it then. I'll do it myself.
Good then. You do it all yourself.
Gosh, hold it there again.
Make it straight.
Oh my, it's too heavy to hold by myself.
How did you end up coming here?
He wanted to surprise me, so here I am.
He didn't tell me.
- I was kidnapped.
- Then was I kidnapped too?
Gosh, those two are making me
into a kidnapper now, huh?
Oh my, I'm hungry.
Is it not ready yet?
- Here it is.
- What is it?
- You want me to do it?
- Of course.
Men are supposed to do this
when we're outdoors.
Okay!
I'm going to grill it to perfection!
Don't even lift a finger
and stay right here.
- Got it?
- Sure.
Please let me do that.
Let me see.
Try. Say 'ah.'
It's good.
Manager Hong, say 'ah.'
I'm okay. Give it to Manager Hong.
Dae Han is taking good care of her.
What are you doing?
Why are you eating mine?
Eat yours.
Why are you acting like a child?
- Let me. I'll grill it.
- It's okay.
I'll grill it again and
let's not share with them.
Try.
Manager Hong, can you
get the shrimp ready?
You'll do a good job.
There are people
who shine more...
when they're in each other's company.
While they live the rest of their lives
I hope they become great friends
who can help one and another.
Why would you take pictures?
No one would replace me...
but it's very fortunate thathe has such
a wonderful person like her by his side.
he has such a wonderful person
like her by his side.
Men are supposed to get this
for the ladies, okay?
Manager Hong, put this on.
Isn't he insensitive and rude?
Yes, he's like that in a way.
That's my charm.
I agree. When I'm with Choi Shin Hyung
I feel as if I'm with
the late Chairman Choi.
The late Chairman Choi
was like that, too.
Do you remember that time?
He misunderstood us and yelled at us.
He fired me right away that day.
That's how he was.
He would never hear me out.
But later on, he asked
Manager Sung to call you.
He was worried and
gave you your job back.
Did he?
He did...
I don't know much about my father.
But he was very good at his work.
Now that I'm in his shoes, I see it.
Of course.
There was no one else like him.
I still have deep respect for him.
Of course.
He was such a great man.
It's a good thing
that you guys know that.
Shall we try the sweet potatoes?
How done are they?
Let's play the Tact Game. One!
- Two!
- Three.
Four!
What do you mean four?
- No?
- Drink.
Isn't it right?
One, two, three, four?
Drink.
- Just drink.
- One, two, three, four...
- I said drink.
- Drink the coffee!
- Why?
- Drink up. Drink up.
What is it? Four comes after three.
Then is it five?
I'm so glad that you're by his side.
Please don't mention it.
You'll face a lot of difficulties
at work in the future.
I hope you can teach him and lead him
in the right direction when that happens.
He's already doing a good job.
Since Chairman Choi passed away...
and he met you,
he's changed quite a lot.
He gave up his dream.
Seeing him choose to follow
in his late father's footsteps..
I sometimes feel bad for him.
While you worked for
the finicky late Chairman Choi
you had to take care of Dae Han, too.
It was hard for you, wasn't it?
No, every moment of it
was very meaningful.
I have a lot of good memories, too.
If you still have feelings
for Dae Han...
wait for him a little longer.
He's still just immature.
But he's thoughtful...
and he's a warm-hearted person.
Shin Hyung, take this.
What is this?
You want me to sleep in the tent?
It's so nice in here.
You should try sleeping in
one of these. Come here.
- Will you be okay?
- Of course!
I'm a tough man, you know.
Hurry, go in. It's cold.
- We'll go inside then.
- Good night.
Good night.
You'll see her in the morning, gosh.
- Come over here.
- Go in.
What are you doing now?
Did you have to go this far?
Because of the case involving
five billion won last time...
Wasn't it enough that my brother's
reputation was ruined when he died?
Will you be happy that you take
every member of my family to the police?
Are you choosing your family
over money now?
What?
I'll make sure it doesn't
harm you, so don't worry.
How can I believe that?
Just hold onto the department store
in New York that's left for you.
Why are we suddenly
having wine, Manager Hong?
I hid it so that we could
enjoy it by ourselves.
If I get drunk, I might snore...
- I grind my teeth, too.
- Lies.
- I'm not lying.
- It doesn't suit you.
You're so graceful and stylish...
Please go around and tell people.
Don't keep it to yourself.
It's enough that
ne person knows, isn't it?
When it comes to sneeze and love
they say no one can hide those.
The problem is what happens next.
I can't find a way out.
I fell in love with him.
But I have this unsettling feeling.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I think I know.
I sometimes hate him. too.
You hate him so much
and get mad at him, too.
You know it well.
Is Choi Shin Hyung like that?
No.
I think you've just sneezed.
By the way, will the men be okay?
It's supposed to fall below
zero Celsius tonight.
That's right.
Gosh, it's cold.
I might become a frozen fish.
Do you want a couple
more hot packs in there?
Aren't you cold?
I went rock climbing in bad weather.
This is like spring weather.
You are one heck of an Eskimo then.
Can you turn that off?
What are you doing with it?
I didn't get to tell my father about this.
In my second year of high school...
I had to get psychiatric treatment
after my mother passed away.
Psychiatric treatment?
I was about to go crazy at that time.
When my mother collapsed
if only I had found her
five minutes earlier
No...
if only Father had shown up
at the hospital in time
then my mother wouldn't
have died like that.
Our father must have had a reason.
I know.
I could understand him
in my head...
but my heart couldn't let that go.
The psychiatrist told me backen then...
imagine that my father
was behind this light.
And say everything
I'd been keeping in my heart.
- Father.
- Yes? What?
What are you talking about?
Why did you leave me all alone?
More than your son and your wife
was money more important to you?
There were so many things
I wanted to do with you.
I wanted to go camping
with you like this.
At least, I wanted to toss around
a baseball with you.
On my birthdays, I wanted
to go out to eat together.
Was it that hard for you?
Dae Han...
Father, to me...
do you know what a large part
of my life you were?
What kind of son was I to you?
'I love you.'
'I trust you.'
You could've just told me that.
I... I mean...
Our late father may be...
It's too late now.
Father...
Mom...
I know that, too.
Even if I wanted to turn the clocks back
that it's too late now.
So...
even if your father leaves
for a far away place...
Remember this one thing.
You're my pride.
My one and only child.
Choi Dae Han.
No matter what others
say about you...
you're Choi Go Bong's son.
Be careful. There you go.
- Oh my!
- Are you okay? Are you hurt?
- What do we do?
- Gosh.
You're so impatient.
You can keep your balance
even if you ride at a slow pace.
- Aren't you going to believe me?
- I believe you.
If I don't believe you
who else would I believe?
Don't you think so?
Then rather than steering to go straight
let your body do the work.
It wasn't working because you wanted
to the keep your balance.
If you go straight, you will
keep the balance naturally.
- Good luck.
- Man...
My teacher is scary.
She's scary.
Get set.
Go!
Be careful.
There you go.
That's right.
All right.
- Am I doing it now?
- Yes.
That's right.
Hold my bike!
Hold on!
- Oh my.
- Are you okay? You're hurt?
- What do I do?
- Oh my.
- Oh my, I'm dying.
- Are you hurt?
It hurts.
Where?
- It hurts here, and...
- Your knee?
- It hurts here, too.
- Here?
It hurts here, too.
How could you just
let go of me like that?
Stop kidding around. Get up.
See? I'm good, huh?
Gosh, be careful.
Slow down.
Wow, this is nice!
- Hold on tight.
- I will.
This is great!
- I'll go faster.
- No.
- Hold on tight!
- No!
Why did you want to
go camping, by the way?
Maybe...
I thought this could be
our last trip together.
There doesn't seem to be
much time left for Choi Shin Hyung.
How was it? Was it fun?
Yes.
But why did you stay for two days?
- Were you two alone?
- No.
Five assignments? What is this?
Hey, don't look. No.
- Don't look.
- What is it?
He said he'll grant me five wishes,
so I wrote them down.
How could you ask a rich man
to do things like these for you?
If he asks about your five wishes
House, car, purse, shoes, and coat...
- Is that five already?
- By the way...
Talking about the end and that
there's no such thing as forever...
He's not well.
He's thinking about leaving.
Then what comes to mind?
He might be suffering from
a terminal illness?
- What?
- He's going to die.
He's terminally ill.
What is it? Who is suffering
from a terminal illness?
No.
No way.
What is this about?
Because of the illegal investments
for Cruise Hotel
we're investigating the matter.
[Search and seizure warrant]
Search the place.
You said something last time.
When Choi Shin Hyung is sick,
that I must be there for him.
What did you mean by that?
Why must I be there for him?
I don't know the reason, either.
Choi Shin Hyung told me that
he'd get better when you were nearby.
When you were involved in
the sinkhole accident
the late Chairman Choi Go Bong
was there, too.
It might have something
to do with that accident.
- Pardon?
- At the time...
you two almost died together.
That's probably why Choi Shin Hyung
needs you nearby...
to be able to get better.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Well, since they're family
there must be some effect.
How sick is he now?
It's about the same as the last time.
We don't know when he'll collapse...
When he had a rock in his heart
why didn't he want it
surgically removed?
It's just that surgery won't
promise a happy ending...
so he seems conflicted
over it right now.
I've just been to the doctor's office.
What's happening to your body, huh?
What's this?
Answer me!
I don't know.
I don't know what's happening.
Are you in pain?
Does it hurt?
I'm not in pain.
Hello?
Hello? Choi Shin Hyung.
Choi Shin Hyung. Choi Shin Hyung!
Choi Shin Hyung.
Choi Shin Hyung, what's going on?
Choi Shin Hyung...
Hello. Hello?
Choi Shin Hyung, what is it?
Father. Father.
You still have time left.
Let's have the surgery.
You should get the surgery.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my son.
Father. Father.
Father.
Father! Father!
Subtitles by DramaFever