Mr. Back
Why did Chairman Choi Young Dal
step down from his position?
- Who will be in charge now?
- Will you vote for a new chairman?
- Will you take over yourself?
- Look this way, please.
- Make a comment, please.
I will be in charge
from now on.
I will lead Daehan as chairman
and move it forward.
- Hold on.
- Can we ask a question?
The sum will be substantial
this time around.
Don't worry.
I'll be well worth the money.
What did you want to talk about?
Remember how you asked me
something yesterday...
at Silver Town.
I... wanted to give you an answer.
I see.
I...
To be honest...
How I feel is...
Look. Look over there.
[Director Choi Dae Han
demands sex from lady named A]
Director Cho. Wake up, sir.
What is it?
What's the matter?
Who's that?
What is this?
- Get out.
- Pardon?
- I said get out!
- Okay.
Manager Sung, check the CCTV.
Fine out what time it was
and the room number.
Who was that woman and
why was he in that room?
Call me back after you find out.
Manager Hong, where are you?
How do you know her?
Did that take place?
Did you really demand sex?
- Make a comment, please.
- Please give us statement.
The man in the picture...
Is me!
It wasn't Choi Dae Han!
But me, Choi Shin Hyung!
Are you saying that you are
the man in the picture?
[Episode 8]
That's me! Me, Choi Shin Hyung.
Just look at it.
It's clearly me, isn't it?
I have a habit of sleeping on my stomach.
Want me to show you my back?
Want to see?
I'm the one that was subpoenaed.
Why are you interfering?
Look, there must be
some kind of mistake here.
I'm the one who
slept in Room 3017.
Don't come forward, okay?
Never, don't do it.
It's you who shouldn't be interfering.
You're not going to listen to me?
Jeez, what are you doing?
- Choi Dae Han.
- Yes?
Where were you that night?
Listen carefully.
You slept at home that night.
All the CCTV tapes have been erased.
We have an alibi and eyewitness ready.
Don't worry, and just do as I say.
The one in the picture
will be Choi Shin Hyung.
At the resort. In Room 3017.
That's where I slept.
That woman is more than capable
of doing things like that for money.
I was drinking alone
in that room that night.
I got so drunk that...
I don't really remember who
came in or out of the room.
I said that's not true!
Why do you keep lying?
I'm saying that
I slept in that room.
Then did we sleep together, huh?
Why are you doing this?
That's our late father's resort.
Manager Hong charged my credit card.
But what does this woman want? Money?
Can I have your name and
identification number?
451105...
I'm a Canadian citizen...
and my name is Choi Shin Hyung.
When did you come to Korea
from Canada?
November 5.
On my late father's birthday...
Where in Canada are you from?
Vancouver? Montreal?
You remember your address there, right?
Are you pleading the fifth here?
If you keep this up, you could
end up in jail after questioning.
Got that?
What's your deal?
Why didn't you do as
you were told by Manager Hong?
Why are you doing this?
You're finally trying to do some work
after coming to your senses
you fell into a trap.
Am I wrong?
- Just listen to me.
- The truth will eventually reveal itself.
Listen carefully.
The truth doesn't matter when
it comes to cases like these.
Once this gets out,
people will talk.
And that will be your end.
Plus, you haven't been on
your best behavior all these years.
Who are you to tell me all this?
Who the hell are you?
How rude of you to speak to
your older brother that way.
Go on. I don't want
to see your face.
Seriously.
Gosh, I didn't think Choi Shin Hyung
would do something like that.
What could she possibly want
from Choi Shin Hyung?
He already cut ties with the family.
Is his current position
what's important right now?
Even if it was brief,
he was our previous chairman.
Even if he is illegitimate,
he's still late Chairman Choi's son.
It's obvious she planned this
to go after his money.
Whether it was Choi Dae Han
or Choi Shin Hyung
all she needs to do is get her money.
Don't you think?
Do you know why on earth
he's acting that way?
Did you go knowingly
go along with his plan?
It's more important to keep you safe
than to focus on
Choi Shin Hyung's intentions.
Please do as I say.
If you get wrangled into this issue
in such a crucial time
it won't be easy to recover.
Manager Hong, by the way...
aren't you curious as to
what really happened that night?
I don't want to know the truth.
What matters to me is that
you won't be charged.
You saw the CCTV, didn't you?
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
But were you really
the one in that picture?
I'm saying it is.
If you're lying, you could be charged
with perjury and obstruction of justice.
Don't interfere with the investigation.
Tell the truth.
Why do you think it's not the truth?
Probably because you planned it,
so you know better than anyone.
Director Choi has gotten himself
involved in such cases in the past.
Gosh, that punk...
You're getting aggravated, aren't you?
Handle this on your own.
Then I'll go meet with the prosecutor.
I will see if the charges
can be dropped.
Sure. Do that.
Why did you get yourself into this mess
and go through all this trouble?
Are you jealous of scandals now
just because you're young again?
What did you say?
I'm nervous enough as it is that
your cover might be blown wide open.
- What if it does?
- Then what?
How are they going to find me?
You really have no idea, do you?
Don't worry.
I won't trouble your nephew in Canada.
Don't do that.
Just throw a couple of
gold bars at her as a settlement.
What's the point of keeping them?
Not like you're going to give them to me.
Why would I want to settle?
I did nothing wrong, you punk.
What if something really happened
between Dae Han and her?
What would you do then?
I told you not to call me
before I called first.
Didn't I?
How could you handle matters like this?
The picture. The picture!
It was done thirty minutes ago.
The man in the picture is me!
Don't come forward, okay?
Never, don't do it.
How rude of you to speak to
your older brother that way.
Go!
Older brother?
Manager Hong.
Go look into the CCTV...
and find out when she came
in and out of the room.
and how long she stayed
in the room.
See if there were any eyewitnesses, too.
No matter how hard I try
I can't figure out what the deal
is with Choi Shin Hyung.
Why is he protecting Dae Han?
I agree.
They were going at each other's
throats not too long ago.
Hold on. Could Dae Han have
handed over his shares
and had Choi Shin Hyung
take the blame instead?
No way.
Even if that were the case,
he'd never do that.
Did they plot something behind
our backs, by any chance?
Excuse me.
Did something happen between
the two of them while we were gone?
What is it?
Tell me what happened.
They were in the heat of
the moment, and on fire...
- Fire?
- That fire couldn't be put out
even if the firefighters
were to come.
Isn't that right?
- What do you mean?
- They were on fire?
Then... by any chance?
- Those two?
- What is it? What?
- In love?
- Oh, shit.
Is that why he brought the guy back
after we kicked him out?
Oh my, they were bickering so often...
and became close in the end.
That's a perfect romantic comedy.
What are you all imagining?
No way.
Dae Han, that's not right.
Excuse me, Director Jung.
Choi Shin Hyung.
What is this?
Who sent her in here?
Your salary comes out
of my tax dollars!
Aren't you going to
do your job properly?
Don't do that.
I'll leave soon.
- Gosh.
- Aren't you cold in there?
Jail facilities are quite nice nowadays.
It's like a hotel.
I was going to bring some clothes,
but they wouldn't allow it.
When you are released,
I'll make sure to feed you.
They feed me well in here, too.
It's like a feast.
You're not sick, are you?
I was worried that you might
suddenly get sick like last time.
I'm glad I got to see you
even if it was for a moment.
I'll go now.
Hey.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
I'm a despicable man.
I talked a model trainee into
coming with me to a hotel room.
Anyway, I'm far worse
than you can imagine.
So don't worry about me.
I'm not sure about you being despicable,
but you're a terrible liar.
What?
You were surprised
by the news in the car.
You had no idea
what it was about.
That's because I was shocked
that it was on that big screen...
What was it that
you wanted to tell me then?
What do you mean?
You were trying to say something
right before the news.
You said you would
answer my question.
Ah, that...
It was about...
You said you would
make me some side dishes.
Hey, we're done here.
Can you show her out?
I believe you, Choi Shin Hyung.
As far as I know, you aren't
someone who would do that.
Gosh, you're such a frustrating woman.
You're not supposed to
trust people that easily.
I don't trust people easily.
I only trust those who can be trusted.
So why don't you try
believing in yourself, too?
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
For trusting someone like me...
This is the image of the woman
captured on the CCTV.
From the time she appeared in the lobby
to the time she came down
the elevator and exited the lobby
was exactly four minutes and 27 seconds.
How long was she in the room then?
As a reference, I tried walking through
the lobby and getting on the elevator.
I opened the door to the resort
and came back down to the lobby.
It took me three minutes
and 35 seconds in total.
If that's the case, she stayed in
the room for a mere 55 seconds.
It's enough time to sneak inside
and take a few pictures.
You can't do anything
within 50 seconds, you know.
You would know that as a man.
You walk in, set the mood,
take off this piece...
and take off this one,
and this one after that.
50 seconds just flies by that way.
Don't you think so, Prosecutor Yang?
And this is the document that proves
Choi Shin Hyung's Canadian citizenship.
That woman is lying.
That's right.
Someone I didn't even know
sneaked into my room...
took some pictures,
and then sneaked back out.
Since both parties' testimonies don't agree
we're looking into the victim as well.
Who are you calling the victim?
We're the victims!
Don't you think?
Manager Hong, good work.
No. I only did what I had to.
Choi Shin Hyung.
- Don't get involved in my business again.
- What?
- What? You punk.
- Let's go now.
- Don't even respond.
- Gosh.
Stop acting like my brother
and tell me the truth.
Why did you do it?
Everybody thinks that you sacrificed
yourself for your half-brother.
- You think I'm a fool?
- Gosh.
- You rotten punk.
- Why did you do it?
Tell me.
Because I suddenly feel like
trusting you, Choi Dae Han.
Why? Why would you?
Not sure.
You're were hurt far more
than I thought.
That's why you might have
tried to live a screwed up life.
Who are you?
- Who do you think you are?
- Me?
I'm...
currently the most popular guy
out there, Choi Shin Hyung.
Hey, Ha Soo.
- Look at this.
- What is it?
[Daehan Group Brothers
Scandal Breakthrough]
Wow, this is a relief.
Shouldn't we throw him a party
for getting out of jail?
Should we?
Hold on.
Hello?
I'm glad that everything was resolved.
About what happened yesterday...
do you really see me
as someone who'd do that?
I didn't think you would.
Why did my brother do that?
Do you know that you just
called him your brother?
What? I did?
When did I do that?
Nonsense.
His name is Shin Hyung.
I probably said that.
The reason why
I asked you out here is...
- When will you give it to me?
- Give what?
My pendant.
- I forgot. I left it at home.
- Did you?
Good then.
I'll get to see you again.
Hello, ma'am.
I heard you got the new coat.
Can I see it?
Well, there was only one
that came to Korea...
and someone else
is already trying it on.
What?
Wow, not too detailed
and it looks luxurious.
Oh my, are you trying
to buy that coat?
You're so fast when it comes
to something like that.
- Were you thinking about buying this, too?
- Yes.
What do we do?
I already decided to get it.
By the way, you're so greedy.
Isn't it enough that you came this far
after coming from the countryside?
Why do you have to try so hard
to act like you're rich?
It can't hide where you're from.
Sister-in-law.
Wrap this one.
And show me something else
that I would want.
We have the latest editions
for shoes and scarves.
- Would you like to take a look?
- Okay, I'd love to.
Let's see them.
Sorry.
What was she saying?
Is this how you treat
your VIP customers?
How can you text
an item to everyone?
- Who do you think I am?
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
- I'm very sorry, ma'am.
- Shit.
Honey, are you just going
to sit back and watch?
[Daehan Resort Business Plan]
What do you think?
Do you like my plan?
Not sure.
Daehan Suhae Hotel is...
I thought Chairman Choi Dae Han
was looking into it to revive it.
Just push that one away.
You should pull out of a dead project.
How is Dae Han supposed to revive it?
- Don't you think?
- Of course.
If we build a premium outlet
in that location
the sales will be three times
what it is now.
As you can see,
we've prepared everything for you.
All you need to do is show up
and cut the ribbon at the ceremony...
I'll think about it.
I have a meeting, so...
- What do you think he'll do?
- Don't worry.
He'll take the bait.
What is all this?
Do I have to lower my head to
a former subordinate like Director Jung?
If you don't?
Would you rather get kicked out and
be homeless like someone else we know?
Before Chairman Choi Go Bong
passed away
he had worked on something big.
The Cruise Hotel...
How did you know about that?
That's something only
he and I knew about.
I thought so.
You worked with him
in secret for everything, huh?
How did you know about that?
Choi Shin Hyung had the business plan
in his possession.
What?
- Yi Gun.
- Marry me.
I have something to tell you.
- It's about Choi Shin Hyung.
- Okay.
The late Chairman Choi was working
on the Cruise Hotel as his final project.
He seems to have its business plan.
Cruise Hotel? What's that?
Chairman Choi was
preparing for it in secret
and I was assisting him.
Since it was his final project...
I hope you can see it through.
Then how does Choi Shin Hyung
have that information?
I'll get it back, no matter what it takes.
It's always like this...
Ah, seriously.
Who dropped gum in my resort, huh?
Darn it.
You seem very dedicated.
Of course,
I'm following my late father's philosophy
in starting from the bottom.
But do you have business with me?
It's about the business plan
for the Cruise Hotel.
I worked on it with the
late Chairman Choi in secret.
It took us more than
three years just to plan it.
We were going to present the plan
at the end of the year and move forward.
So?
I think it's right for Director Choi
to be in charge of it.
Why is that?
Because he prepared it for
Director Choi Dae Han.
- If you steal it away like this...
- It's true that he prepared for him...
But didn't he also say he'd let Dae Han
be in charge if he came to his senses?
How did you handle it?
- What do you mean?
- This isn't what we were looking for.
- How is it not?
- That document...
It's a translated document of
the Meditech business plan in America.
What?
It can't be.
Choi Shin Hyung is toying with us.
It was odd that he came forward
on Choi Dae Han's behalf.
Are they working together or something?
About Choi Dae Han and Choi Shin Hyung...
It wasn't a war between brothers.
But it was love between two brothers?
- Love?
- No way.
He's his half-brother who
showed up out of nowhere.
About Eun Ha Soo...
Is she playing around
with both of them then?
Ha Soo isn't that kind of a woman!
How do you know?
They're both the late
Chairman Choi's sons, after all.
If she uses her wiles
it'll only be a matter of time
before she gets promoted.
Wiles?
What if she becomes my superior one day?
- Excuse me.
- You scared me.
If you're jealous, just say so.
Not everybody can become
Cinderella, you know.
What is she saying?
I'm going to be Snow White.
I will have seven rich dwarfs.
Gosh, I'm so relieved that
I'm not a dwarf.
Why are they doing this?
That was a nice bath.
I feel good now.
Oh, hello.
Mom, Shin Hyung's here.
Hello, everyone.
What did you bring?
I wanted you to each
enjoy a whole chicken.
Wow.
How have you been?
Oh my.
- She's changed her mind about you.
- It's about the scandal.
Even if it was resolved and all
it still makes me uncomfortable.
That's why I came all the way here.
Mom, don't be mad anymore.
- Wow.
- Wow, one, two, three, four chickens, huh?
Wow, there are four radishes, too.
You think I'd change my mind
over a chicken?
Good.
Men should always be careful
of women problems.
Of course.
Mom, it's not like he cheated
on his girlfriend or anything.
That's enough, Mom.
- Girlfriend?
- Here we go.
Try it with some sauce, Mom.
Have a bite.
Say ah.
It tastes good at least.
- Isn't it good?
- It's so good.
It's just been fried, huh?
It's really good.
It's so good.
You didn't have to do that.
I'm glad that your mother
liked the chicken.
Anyway, about what I didn't
get the chance to tell you last time...
You said it was about the side dishes.
Ah, I said that, didn't I?
But the thing is...
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
I guess it's a dish
that's hard to make, huh?
It is difficult indeed.
But even if it's hard...
If I don't tell you now
I think I'll regret it
for a long time.
So...
I'm working up my courage
to say this...
What courage do you need
to talk about a side dish?
Tell me. I can make it.
Migratory birds follow
the wind to fly home.
An ocean follows the waves
to get to the horizon.
Stars follow the moon
to get to dawn.
I was thinking of
following the blue sky...
and go to the Milky Way...
Can I do that?
What side dish were you
talking about then?
Think about it.
Come to think of it...
the DNA match is too perfect,
don't you think?
What nonsense are you talking about?
No.
Even his walk looks the same
as my brother's.
Even the way he talks...
Even if he's his son,
his tone is like an old man.
Even his tone and accent
are identical.
Then what does this mean?
No matter how much
medicine has improved...
It just can't be done.
Is it a face-off, by any chance?
Seriously. Stop talking nonsense.
He said he was from Canada, right?
If it's Canada, wait a second.
That's where Manager Sung's
wife and kids are, isn't it?
That's right.
After Go Bong passed away...
he's been following
Choi Shin Hyung around.
That's probably because
he wants to keep his job.
By the way, what about that?
No, I was just saying...
- What?
- What is it?
My stomach...
Why is my stomach hurting?
Gosh, seriously...
I have nothing to say.
What took you so long?
Were you slacking off?
Slacking off?
That's your specialty.
I don't know about anything else,
but you need to be on time.
Oh my, listen to yourself.
Come over here.
First, empty the trash can.
Look at that dirty floor.
Wipe it clean.
Well, this desk here...
Organize all the documents.
You said you'd start from the bottom
so that you can stay in the house.
A promise is a promise,
so don't be too upset.
Yes,yes.
Of course.
When my late father hired me,
this is what he made me do, too.
Can you imagine how hard
it was to rise to this position?
It was all because our late father
wanted what was best for you.
Give me your name and
identification number.
451105...
I'm a Canadian citizen, and
my name is Choi Shin Hyung.
These are the DNA test results.
100 percent?
- Boo!
- You scared me.
- Are you free after work today?
- Yes, I am.
- I'll cook for you tonight.
- Cook for me?
- What are we having?
- Eel soup.
It's my mom's specialty.
I got her recipe.
- Do you like eel?
- I do.
I really like it.
Please go about your work.
You came.
What do you have under your nose?
Since when you started
to grow a mustache?
Oh my...
Wow, you're not bad.
- Oh my goodness!
- What do I do?
Pick them up.
Can't you do something?
Oh my, what do we do?
Oh my, what do I do?
Ouch! That hurts.
Are you okay?
Can you get up? Easy now.
You seem to be in a lot of pain.
Let me see.
- Can I see it?
- Ouch.
You're such a crybaby. Here.
There.
- Ouch.
- You're faking it.
Can you lift it? Good job.
I always tell you
to be careful, don't I?
I said it was okay.
All done.
Here it is.
We end up having ramen.
Let me see.
It looks delicious.
It's hot.
Yes, go down further.
No, to the left.
Further down.
- Oh my.
- You missed it.
- Can I have more coins?
- I'm all out. Don't do it.
I really wanted to get
that stuffed dog.
This one is designed
not to let anybody win.
Let's go.
That stuffed dog...
Gosh, why wouldn't it work?
It looked like I was going to get it,
but it always drops at the end.
That's their business tactic.
You can never get it.
I'll buy you a truckful.
It's okay.
Here comes a taxi.
Get in.
River Tumen...
the blue water...
A guy is rowing a boat...
I will think about my lover
from my past.
The boat that left with
my lover on it...
Where did it go?
My lover that I miss so much...
Father!
Hello. What is it at this hour?
Dr. Kim came back.
He wants to meet with you right away.
Don't beat around the bush
and just get to the point!
How did it go?
Did you get to meet
the American doctor?
I did.
I listened and I learned.
So?
There is something I need
to confirm before we go on.
You said you took the pill when
you fell in the sinkhole, didn't you?
The pill?
Yes, I took whatever it was.
- Why?
- It might not have been the pill.
You may have consumed
a piece of meteor.
- Meteor?
- How is it related to him turning young?
When the accident took place
the head of the village
also fell into the sinkhole...
and he happened to consume
a piece of meteor.
Wait. Why is my cell phone in here?
[Choi Go Bong has 25 days
to return the payment.]
What is this?
[Choi Go Bong has 27 days
to return the payment.]
[Choi Go Bong has 48 days
Did you find anything
about Choi Shin Hyung?
There was nothing wrong
with his Canadian citizenship.
By any chance...
Isn't there a possibility of him
using someone else's identity?
Shall I send someone
to Canada to verify?
Do that.
Go find someone who might know him
and show them his picture to verify.
And find the graduation pictures
from his schools, too.
I will.
Hi, Eun Ha Soo.
Okay. What time?
Should I come by or
do you want to come over?
I'm not sure if it was captured
on the black box.
Play it.
It's ready.
- What on earth am I taking?
- Perhaps...
Perhaps was it really a meteor?
You took it. You swallowed it!
The power that cannot
be explained by modern science...
was hidden inside the meteor!
That's what the American doctor believes.
Man, I could have made a ton
of money selling those rocks then.
Shut it!
So what happened
to the village chief?
You're not going to hurry up
and give me an answer?
Do you want to see me out of breath?
Breath! He ended up dying!
He's dead?
On the morning of the 48th day
he turned young to be exact.
He couldn't wake up for good.
His physical appearance changed
back into an old man, too.
You said the village celebrated
for three months and ten days.
I was just exaggerating.
Seriously.
Anyhow, I believe the the power of
the meteor won't guarantee eternal life.
Wait.
How many days has it been
since you turned young, sir?
Then how many days
do you have left now?
- Dr. Kim.
- Yes?
I'll get you anything you need
in terms of expenses
for research and staff.
Can you find a way somehow?
I did receive the materials from him...
But I cannot give you a guarantee.
Look.
I... can't die like this.
I still have things left to do.
I found someone to take care of, too.
Please.
Please. I'm begging you.
Oh my, my sister is seeing
two men at the same time?
Man, she's good.
[Shin Hyung]
Hi, Shin Hyung.
My sister?
Where is she?
She's at the cafe.
Hello? Hello?
Gosh, I caused trouble again.
[Choi Shin Hyung]
- Here it is.
- Wow.
It finally made it back
into my hands.
How did you find it?
It was in my bag.
When I was looking for it,
it wasn't there.
It's enough that you found it now.
Come to think of it, everything
was going wrong while it was gone.
I should be the one to say that
everything went wrong after I lost it.
But it's that important to you?
This?
It's a keepsake from my mom.
Ah.
That's why.
When I got this
it was probably
the happiest time in my life.
My mom and I went to  see a meteor
shower together when I was little.
She got a piece of meteor then,
and made this pendent with that.
She said it would help my wish
come true or something.
And did you wish truly come true?
Not sure yet.
She really must be in there, huh?
It's amazing.
- Stop looking. You'll wear it out.
- What?
Here it is.
Shin Hyung...
What's gotten into you?
You asked me out on a date?
I was nervous that
you didn't give me an answer
when I proposed.
But I'm more nervous to see you now.
I'm sorry, Yi Gun.
Let's enjoy dinner first.
I'll get rejected later.
Yi Gun.
About the scandal involving
Director Choi Dae Han...
were you the one behind it?
I want to know what
your ultimate goal is.
You must have misunderstood.
I did that to find out who
Choi Shin Hyung really was.
- Choi Shin Hyung?
- He's using someone else's identity.
Is that true?
If he really was the late Chairman Choi's son
and Choi Dae Han's brother
I was curious how he would
handle something like that.
But he surprisingly acted like
Choi Dae Han's real brother.
I saw him for sure.
Where has he gone?
Choi Shin Hyung.
What are you doing out here?
If you came, you should've come inside.
I was just passing by.
You looked like you were
in the middle of a conversation.
Gosh.
- What is that?
- This?
It's a reed pipe.
Ah, a reed pipe?
When did you learn how to do that?
When I was in the army.
It was about fifty years ago...
- Pardon?
- No, nothing.
Director Choi is sitting inside.
Come with me.
No, it's okay.
Seriously.
You two are family now.
You just met your brother.
You two didn't grow up together
but you don't know how long
you'll be able to see each other.
Come inside with me, will you?
Eun Ha Soo, move away
from Choi Shin Hyung.
Director Choi, what's wrong?
He's... someone who will
eventually leave anyway.
Don't fall for him.
How can you say
something like that?
I have a good idea as to
who you really are.
- What?
- Am I right?
Chairman Choi Go Bong.
Father.
Subtitles by DramaFever