Mr. Back
[Episode 12]
You don't feel
all that great, do you?
Do this whenever you feel that way.
Koong, koong, da.
[Make seaweed soup on my son's birthday]
[Choi Dae Han]
[Eun Ha Soo]
What is this about?
What do you mean?
Why do you have these?
Are these also what
our late father wrote?
- Yes.
- Really?
Then why is Eun Ha Soo's name
written on there, too?
Why are you going through
my room without asking?
- Get out.
- About the seaweed soup...
I heard you made it yourself.
Was it for me? Or...
Was it on behalf of our late father?
I just tried it for fun.
- It was your birthday and all...
- Is that right?
I'm so grateful that I might cry.
But I just can't figure out
what those notes mean.
If they were written by our late father,
why was Eun Ha Soo on there?
I got the feeling that
the notes weren't finished.
Also that the notes
have yet to be fulfilled.
Stop your nonsense,
and go to bed.
I'd like to be alone.
[Eun Ha Soo]
- What is this?
- It's a present.
You got me that stuffed dog last time.
Oh my.
How am I supposed to carry around
such a big guy like this?
Sir!
Sir, are you okay?
Try to get up.
Wait, why is the soup so bland?
It's like water.
Why are these eggs so over-cooked?
Don't you have any soft-boiled eggs?
Oh my, what kind of vegetable dish
has this much water in it?
You should take the water out
before putting it on a plate.
- Okay.
- When it comes to vegetable dishes...
These go better with soy sauce.
Why aren't you eating?
Huh? I'm eating.
By the way, I heard you were invited
to a birthday party at his house.
Ha Soo, shouldn't I have bought you
a nice outfit before you went over?
How was his house? Was it nice?
Of course. It must be real nice and
bright since two rich men live there.
It must have been
a different world there, right?
You met his family, too?
Kind of.
Actually, my future son-in-law
was an illegitimate son, so...
it must not have been comfortable.
Did his family seem to like you?
It doesn't matter...
You should still be
on good terms with them.
Eun Ha, shall I go meet them?
What are you talking about?
It definitely won't happen,
so stop dreaming.
Why wouldn't it happen?
It seems soon enough to talk
about the wedding about now.
- Do I need to go, too?
- You should go.
In any case, it's not true.
It won't happen.
What's going on with her?
- Did something happen?
- They must have had a fight.
It's only natural.
What's taking you so long?
- Do you want some tea?
- No, thanks.
You don't seem well today...
What should we do
about Seohae Hotel?
If we don't do anything
the premium outlets preparations
will go underway.
According to 'The Art of War'
there is something called
'Sang Ok Chu Jae.'
We lure the enemy to the roof and...
we get rid of the ladder.
If we do that
The businesses that signed the contract
to move into the outlets will face damage.
When they want to
come down from the roof
we can give them the ladder.
- That means...
- Tell them we will support the decision.
Pardon?
Are you saying you'll support
the idea of the premium outlets?
Then what's going to happen
to Seohae Hotel?
You didn't have breakfast yet, right?
Have this.
I delivered the current financial
statements of Daehan Resort...
and the sales figures of all departments.
Terms for a buyout stay the same.
We really need a business plan
for Cruise Hotel.
We should get a hold of that
as soon as possible.
Without that
they won't try to push forward
with the buyout.
Will Choi Shin Hyung
hand it over easily?
We have to find a way.
Engagement?
If you aren't comfortable marrying me
due to the situation at work
let's get engaged first.
And resign from your position.
You come work with me
in the planning department.
- Yi Gun.
- Didn't you expect this?
I'll stay at my current position
and help you then.
Hong Ji Yoon, that's not how it should be.
What I want is for you to
stay away from Choi Dae Han.
Then does it mean that
we can get Seohae Hotel back?
Yes.
If you make up your mind
we can overturn the decision.
Without me, the deal won't go through.
Fine. Then let me be reassigned first.
About the engagement
A little bit later when
things calm down at work
Hello there.
- Are you busy?
- No.
How may I help you?
Well, on Dae Han's birthday
I'm sorry about the way I acted.
It won't take long, so have a seat.
By the way...
when did you and Dae Han
start seeing each other?
There seems to be some misunderstanding.
President Choi and I
aren't seeing each other.
You're not?
Then is it Choi Shin Hyung
you're seeing then?
- That is...
- It was Choi Shin Hyung, wasn't it?
Oh my.
Either way, you're involved
with men in my family.
So I wanted to apologize for
that night and make you an offer.
You said your mother
owns a tailor shop, right?
Yes.
I wonder if she'd consider
opening a store in our resort here.
I can arrange that.
I'm sorry, but we can't afford
that at the moment.
I'm saying that I can
arrange that for you.
You just tailor suits for our guests.
I'll cut the rent in half, too.
By the way, why are you
making us a special offer like this?
You'll eventually find out...
All you have to do is to meet
with me from time to time
and keep me in the loop
about Shin Hyung or Dae Han.
We can discuss things, too.
It's all good, you know.
No, I have no reason to
receive that kind of favor
and don't want it, either.
I appreciate your offer,
but I'll politely decline.
Wait.
Oh my, did she just say no?
Oh my, unbelievable.
What kind of woman is
that unyielding, huh?
Whoever decorated it
did an excellent job.
I'm sorry.
I invited you over for my birthday,
and you had to leave like that.
My family went too far, didn't they?
I shouldn't have acted that way
with Choi Shin Hyung in front of you.
I won't come between
you two from now on.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
I have to get back to work, so...
Did something happen?
I'm asking what happened.
Do you still go climbing?
I'm talking about rock climbing.
Oh my.
If you try what an expert does,
you'll end up hurting yourself.
Just go where beginners hang.
I've been doing this for ten years.
- I know that.
- You heard that from our father, too?
- Of course.
- You two were close, huh?
- You're quite opposite from me then.
- By the way...
do you have to do
something this dangerous?
If you fall off a cliff
your bone will shatter.
That's why I started this.
Whenever I went
rock climbing or sky diving
it was worth seeing
how my father's face changed.
I started it to add raise
my father's blood pressure.
You're so immature.
No matter how much
you hated your father
how could you rebel
risking your own life?
I found it fun once
I started to get into it.
At first, it was too difficult
to know what it was...
but I realized after falling
numerous times...
how and where to hold on and step on.
It works the same way in life, doesn't it?
The more you fall and get knocked down,
the easier you find a way up.
Shin Hyung!
It's okay.
If you need a coach,
I can help you out.
Thanks for the offer...
but I may not have enough time.
Why not?
That's that...
About our father...
whether you jumped off from a plane
or climbed the Himalayas
he would have been just fine
if it had been someone else's child.
But it's different when
it comes to your own.
Whether you're twenty or thirty years old
'Don't skip meals,'
'Watch out for cars.'
Your parents will nag you regardless.
That's what a parent's heart is like
I'm saying that's how
our father might have felt.
Gosh, it's too bad.
If he had seen
his two sons doing this
his blood pressure would
have shot up again.
He could have said it looked great.
By the way, did you guys fight?
Something didn't seem right
about you two.
I'm talking about Eun Ha Soo.
It's true that you two
are seeing each other, isn't?
We won't see each other again.
Why not? What happened?
Why did you call me over
here all of a sudden?
- I didn't get to buy you a birthday gift.
- What?
It's already passed.
Come on. If your brother
wants to buy you something
say thank you and accept it.
We want to buy some dress shoes.
Are there any specific items
you are looking for?
Is there anything
you especially want?
He's the one who is
going to wear them.
He'll have to run around a lot, so...
we want soft calf skin.
The color should be...
a dark brown that will go well
with business meetings.
And we'd want the round toes that
are most comfortable for his feet.
He will be doing something great.
I want you to pay special
attention, please.
Of course.
I'll measure his feet first.
Excuse me.
Why don't you get one for yourself, too?
I'll buy it for you.
- Get this bag.
- I'm okay.
Excuse me.
For him, I'll order
the latest design, please.
- Sure.
- Please measure him, too.
Come over here.
Try them on. Try.
Try this one. They're pretty.
Oh, they look good on you.
How about this one?
Try them both.
What do you think?
- You try this on, too.
- This?
Oh my, they fit so well.
- Do they look good?
- They look good.
See you.
Listen carefully to what
I'm about to say.
When it comes to business
First, persuasion,
and second, persuasion.
- Third, it's persuasion again.
- What are you saying?
In order to persuade someone
one needs to be certain first.
Once you're certain
guts, patience, sometimes you'll need
a desire to win, too.
- Follow me.
- Where are we going?
To persuade someone.
What is this?
It's five times your contract money.
Are you asking me
to take this money...
and convince the other investors
to pull out of their investment?
Yes, that's correct.
Does that make sense?
You shouldn't invest in
the Seohae Hotel location.
It won't last more than three years.
You think I haven't done my research?
You've only done your research,
but haven't checked it out yourself.
How can you sound so confident about this?
Why do you think
I brought this much money?
I'm sorry to say this, but it was pushed
through by certain people at Daehan.
So if it fails, it will be our loss, too.
If you, our major investor,
pulls out of your investment now
others will follow suit,
and pull their investments, too.
Instead, you can invest that money
when we're converting
Seohae Hotel to Meditel.
Don't bother.
Whether it's Seohae Hotel
or the premium outlets
- I can't trust either, now.
- Why's that?
Considering you brought
five times the contract price
isn't that obvious?
But it's still a lot of money.
- Would you reconsider?
- No need to.
Who knows what could happen
after taking this money?
I'm pulling out of
my investment immediately.
Oh no, you shouldn't do this to us...
How much is in here?
What is this? It's empty.
Carry it.
Not bad.
I have a very strange boyfriend.
Women are supposed
to behave with dignity.
He's a very special person.
Nonsense!
A woman who grew up well
was fooled by a bad man's lies.
It's clear who the bad person is!
How can I just sit back and watch?
His way of speech is a bit strange.
What are you doing, Eun Ha Soo?
He doesn't even know how to text.
He likes Mung Bean pancakes,
boiled eggs...
and herbal tea with egg drops.
He's old-fashioned
and unfriendly, but...
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
He encourages and acknowledges me.
He supports my dreams.
Most importantly...
he's always on my side
and wishes for my true happiness.
Choi Shin Hyung.
Whenever I see him...
I grow excited...
and I can trust him.
About Choi Shin Hyung...
I saw some notes in his room.
They definitely looked like they were
written by my father before he passed.
But Eun Ha Soo's name
was written on there, too.
- Eun Ha Soo?
- Yes.
My other family members
and your name were there, too.
Why was Eun Ha Soo there?
- My name was there, too?
- Yes.
Then...
Choi Shin Hyung must have
only added her name there then.
And your late father
wrote all the others.
The handwriting was exactly the same.
How could my father
possibly know about her?
Why couldn't your father know her?
They were in the accident together.
Ah, that's right.
But still...
Before he passed away
he may have wanted to do something
for the ones he knew.
Was that it?
That's why he saw it and
made you the seaweed soup.
One of the things
your father didn't get to do...
Choi Shin Hyung confuses me so much.
Why did he break up with Eun Ha Soo?
I don't know. He didn't say.
Anyway, if he collapses again,
we have a problem.
Funny thing is whenever he got sick...
he got better if Eun Ha Soo was nearby.
What is he going to do
without her nearby?
He got better whenever
Eun Ha Soo was nearby?
True.
How could it be even possible?
I don't know if it's the power
of love or something.
I'm really worried now that
they're not together anymore.
What if something awful happens?
Have the surgery.
Why wouldn't you want to get it done?
What if you really die?
As for those notes...
you wrote them out
yourself, didn't you?
That's right.
Now that I came here...
and have met my family.
I understood how our father
would have felt.
While I was thinking about what
I could do instead of my father...
I got to write them down.
I had to go through a lot
to be able to meet my family.
We should get along
and live in harmony, right?
What does that even mean?
Not living our lives hiding
our thoughts from each other...
but being able to open
ourselves up to one another.
It's been a long time.
My wife in Canada
wants a divorce again.
Again?
Go over there.
How can I possibly go now?
We don't know what could happen.
As if I would die in that time.
When I went to the fortune teller's place
that your sister went to...
I heard something.
The rock that's in there, the meteor...
If you remove it surgically
you can go back to your original state.
Are you telling me to go back
to the way I was?
If you go back,
you can live longer at least.
If you stay this way, it's good
being young and all...
but you're destined to die
when the time comes.
You don't have many days left.
You have to make a decision
between those choices soon.
What would you do
if you were in my shoes?
I would go back and live longer.
It's an era for living up
to 100 years old.
If you take good care of yourself
you can live for another
thirty years at least.
Only Heaven decides
what to do with our lives.
What happened to me
must be my destiny, too.
I'm okay.
What do you mean, you're okay?
Go see Eun Ha Soo.
I heard you wouldn't get sick
if you're with her.
I lost my father not too long ago.
Would you be happy if I lose you, too?
Why are you being so stubborn?
What if you get sick again?
What would you do then?
Sir, please get up and have this.
You have to have some
to regain your strength.
Please.
Leave it there.
You may go.
Make sure you have some, okay?
[Choi Go Bong, you have 17 days
to return on your payment.]
What kind of bastard are you?
Answer me.
Who is this?
[Choi Go Bong, you have 17 days
to return on your payment.]
What happened?
You broke up with Choi Shin Hyung?
You said you liked him.
I ended it because I liked him.
I didn't want him to become
unhappy because of me.
Why would he become unhappy?
I want him to get along with his family.
His family...
It was hard for him
to reunite his family.
It's all my fault then.
Choi Shin Hyung can't eat anything...
and he's very sick now.
I'm worried he might
collapse again, at this rate.
When he disappeared from the hospital
I know that you were
truly worried about him.
And this time...
I've felt... that he sincerely likes you.
Eun Ha Soo.
I like you, too.
But I know that you don't
feel the same way.
When you two like each other this much
you shouldn't do this
just because of me.
What am I?
Should I make you
a promise or something?
I'll get along with Choi Shin Hyung.
I want you...
to continue to see my brother.
Please.
Get well.
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
Do you think I've done anything
like this for anyone before?
You don't listen to me
about going to see a doctor.
You're so stubborn.
It looks like it's from Eun Ha Soo,
so check it.
Just leave it.
I'll get over her.
Eun Ha Soo is hiding her feelings
for you because of us.
I'll call her and tell her
to come over.
I said leave it.
You said you'd get better
if she's with you.
If that's true...
there won't be any place for me.
Not next to you nor Eun Ha Soo.
I don't want to lose you.
Call her now.
Hello? What are you talking about?
Why can't you tell me why
you changed your mind?
Hello? Hello?
How did this happen?
I have no idea.
Why are the manufacturers pulling out?
It looks like the premium outlets deal
isn't going to pull through.
We can't go forward anymore.
The construction is scheduled
to start the day after tomorrow.
How could everybody
do this all of a sudden?
Please stall them for a little bit.
I'll go meet with them
to change their mind.
No, no.
It seems that they've
already been persuaded.
Who do you think did that?
Who in the world pulled off
a stunt like this?
Choi Shin Hyung.
That's what my gut is telling me.
- Choi Shin Hyung?
- Are you sure?
- Choi Shin Hyung did this?
- Unbelievable.
What a bastard.
How could he do something
like this behind our backs?
How could he mess up
what was almost complete?
- Oh my god...
- Honey!
What are you doing?
How can you reassign her
without my approval?
I believe my report came to you.
- I submitted the report.
- What?
I'd like to work at the planning
department from now on.
What did you say?
Ah, now I understand.
You've been sticking
by my side long enough.
I didn't realize that.
Let him be.
I'm sorry.
I should have consulted you first.
Consult me?
Hong Ji Yoon.
Do you want to advance
in your career that badly?
That's why I told you to stick
with Jung Yi Gun a long time ago.
Yes, I plan to do that now.
Please let me do that.
I'm disappointed.
I was mistaken about you.
[The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo]
Please don't be sick.
[I miss you, Eun Ha Soo.]
I miss you, Eun Ha Soo.
Choi Shin Hyung!
- Did you eat yet?
- No.
I saw you two coming in,
so I'm leaving.
I'm so glad to hear that
you're able to run Seohae Hotel again.
Thank you.
But why do I get the feeling
that you were behind the
premium outlets deal?
Even if I deny it, there's nothing
I can do if you think that way.
You may have thought so
since I was often opposed your plans.
Now that you took Manager Hong,
I hope for the best.
You've given even more power now.
Then enjoy your dinner.
Let's go in.
Hong Ji Yoon.
I can't figure you out.
How have you been?
Same old.
I heard you were very sick.
I'm okay now.
After I asked to stop seeing each other...
I'm sorry I texted you.
It's okay.
I was so glad to see it.
After I told you that we should
stay together forever...
I'm sorry.
I only thought about myself...
I thought I shouldn't see you
because of my own selfishness.
But when we were suddenly apart...
it became harder to bear.
The time we spent together
wasn't even that long...
but I thought I was going crazy.
I'm sorry.
I haven't done much for you.
But you care about me this much.
Will you tell me what
the third assignment is?
The third assignment out of five is...
- to make matching bracelets.
- Matching bracelets?
- Oh, you're here.
- Here I am.
Let's go over there to see some.
Wow.
Are these all meteors?
Yes, aren't they pretty?
What do you want to make with these?
Just pick the one you like.
I like this one.
Wow, it's pretty.
Then I'll pick...
What do you think about this one?
It's unique and pretty.
Like somebody I know.
I wonder who. It's me, isn't it?
Thank you.
I didn't do anything.
It was all you.
It was. It was all me, wasn't it?
That's right. So stop bragging.
Honestly, you know how hard
I was working, right?
Trying the investors
to change their minds.
I had to run around
the entire country on my own.
Okay. You did a good job, okay?
Father.
Are you watching?
It's not much...
But if you knew, you would be happy.
You wouldn't praise me...
but you would be proud,
wouldn't you?
This must be why
you sent my brother here.
Sometimes, he's exactly like you...
so I can't help but hate him.
But in a way, I feel bad for him.
To you, who left your sons behind...
Honestly, I'm a bit sad.
I also get angry, too.
So even if I'm not that nice
to my older brother
don't scold me much.
How could he reverse our plan overnight
and stab us in the backs like this?
How?
Get out of there now!
Honey, calm down.
If you collapse for real, it's our loss.
How much more could we possibly lose?
I won't back down like this.
Seriously.
Honey!
Why did I marry you, huh?
Did I marry you to live my life
as number two?
Seriously. What do you want me to do, huh?
I did everything you told me to do!
Did I make you the number two person?
When it's your own destiny,
what am I supposed to do about it?
Because of you, I'm also living
my life as number two!
Oh my, listen to yourself!
Are you done?
Just because I've been patient with you
do you think I'm someone
you can just boss around?
Choi Young Dal.
Let's get a divorce.
Divorce? Fine. Let's do it.
You thought I wouldn't go for it?
Just sign the papers now!
Honey. Honey.
Honey. Honey!
The fourth assignment out of five is...
to go to a unique festival.
What kind of place is this?
- Cosplay.
- What?
- What is it again?
- It's a cosplay.
People express themselves
by wearing a costume and have fun.
Why wouldn't they just have fun
with the way they normally dress?
It's fun to be somebody else sometimes.
- You punk!
- Oh my!
Choi Shin Hyung.
- Don't!
- You punk!
Wow, are you the Beast
from Beauty and the Beast?
Wow.
What do you think about me?
If I leave you alone,
someone may steal you away.
That's not true. Let's go.
It's like the end of the world.
Isn't it time to get used to this?
What is it? Do you go to events
like this one often?
No, this is my first time here, too.
I couldn't because
I didn't have a boyfriend.
You haven't had a boyfriend
all this time?
What have you been doing
if you weren't dating?
I've been working hard to be able
to meet a beast like you.
- I'm glad.
- Pardon?
I'm glad that you met me.
Otherwise, you would only focus
on work, and become a grandma
You'd be full of regret as a grandma.
My looks aren't that bad.
True. You're not that bad.
Shall we go dance?
What do you mean a dance?
It's embarrassing.
When we did the folk dance last time,
I wanted to dance with you.
Did you?
I'm so grateful that I've made
such precious memories with you.
I will remember your beautiful heart
and pretty face forever.
You made me know what love is.
I will have you in my heart forever.
The Milky Way, Eun Ha Soo.
I'm sorry that I cannot
spend forever with you.
Still, Choi Dae Han's made it
this far, thanks to you.
You've done enough.
Seriously.
Do you want me to bring you a new one?
- Have a seat.
- Why?
Did you just choose me
because you like me?
No, you were chosen
because I didn't like you.
I'm Hong Ji Yoon, who will assist
Chairman Choi starting today.
So what?
You go assist my father then.
Why bother me here?
Chairman Choi put in a
special request with me
because you're rebellious,
spoiled, and audacious.
So he wants you to go out with me?
You're pretty.
Can you take off my clothes?
I hate this outfit.
This tie suffocates me.
Anyway, can you let me
get out of this outfit, huh?
Then I'll listen to you.
It's raining.
Can you drop me off over there?
- Are you not done?
- I'm done.
Oh my.
My cell phone...
- Where...
- Look carefully.
Oh, it's the wish he wrote last time.
Gosh.
Did you find it?
- Let's go.
- Sure.
Why didn't you buy a good one?
Why did you pick this?
Don't you like hearing the raindrops?
I wanted to hear this sound.
What's wrong? Choi Shin Hyung!
Choi Shin Hyung!
It was in my room.
What are you going to do with it?
It's a keepsake from my father.
I want to hold onto it.
[Choi Go Bong, you have 14 days
to return on your  payment.]
Choi Shin Hyung.
Are you really going to die?
I wish I could leave
without hurting anybody...
Subtitles by DramaFever