1
00:00:06,703 --> 00:00:28,323
Original Sub
<font color="#F87217">= s0c0labd =</font>
<font color="#F87217">= wanyad =</font>

2
00:00:36,821 --> 00:00:48,721
<font color = "yellow">Google Translate by Kakang.Brama</font>

3
00:01:33,060 --> 00:01:37,019
we arrived at the KTV just for
sing, is not it?

4
00:01:38,899 --> 00:01:40,059
Ji Won

5
00:01:40,901 --> 00:01:41,890
what do you think?

6
00:01:42,035 --> 00:01:43,900
Do you want to continue to love one another?

7
00:01:44,004 --> 00:01:46,063
you with him?!!
how her face?!

8
00:01:46,139 --> 00:01:49,973
end now, or keep in touch and you want
destroy their careers, so whether?

9
00:01:50,110 --> 00:01:51,873
But sir,

10
00:01:51,978 --> 00:01:53,969
we have to hear first
opinion of both of them ...

11
00:01:53,980 --> 00:01:54,947
No need!

12
00:01:54,948 --> 00:01:56,939
we only just met a few times

13
00:01:58,085 --> 00:01:59,985
This will not
repeated

14
00:02:05,892 --> 00:02:09,919
Ji Won. Kim ji won

15
00:02:16,103 --> 00:02:19,072
just because the little things
like this you have failed?

16
00:02:20,040 --> 00:02:22,008
I do not know anymore

17
00:02:23,877 --> 00:02:26,004
I think too much, about
how to become a singer

18
00:02:28,882 --> 00:02:30,941
This is very meaningful to me

19
00:02:34,054 --> 00:02:35,112
But I really do not understand

20
00:02:35,922 --> 00:02:37,981
This event is not
for personal

21
00:02:38,058 --> 00:02:39,958
Now concentrate was
for the show.

22
00:02:47,000 --> 00:02:49,935
Hyun-bete-now again,
I beg to play for time

23
00:02:50,003 --> 00:02:50,992
Please give him time

24
00:02:51,037 --> 00:02:52,902
No time for its

25
00:02:52,906 --> 00:02:56,967
This is not just a matter of time,
I will be telling her to a gig

26
00:03:00,914 --> 00:03:06,853
Glass screen is a television premiere in the World and the Hereafter
boy band 2008: Mr Children

27
00:03:47,671 --> 00:03:55,671
THIS SCENE DO NOT copied!
UNLESS YOU STILL THE SAME MASTER Limbad!

28
00:04:55,896 --> 00:05:02,961
Mr.Idol

29
00:05:15,949 --> 00:05:18,008
3 years later

30
00:05:20,954 --> 00:05:26,915
guide services, I will guide
you according to your desires.

31
00:05:27,027 --> 00:05:28,051
Through here

32
00:05:36,937 --> 00:05:38,063
guide services

33
00:05:55,088 --> 00:05:58,854
Welcome
Goo Joo Oh

34
00:05:59,092 --> 00:06:02,892
Tomorrow or the next day. Be prepared to
event held in TV.

35
00:06:42,969 --> 00:06:43,936
'Wonder Boys'

36
00:06:49,042 --> 00:06:52,011
1 2 3 Welcome,.
We are a boy band 'Wonder Boys'

37
00:06:52,979 --> 00:06:56,881
After this final selection.
The next contract will be ready to start work

38
00:06:57,083 --> 00:07:00,917
in the contest 'for the Stars',
eventually they too will be the only one.

39
00:07:01,855 --> 00:07:03,015
Disconnect the headphones

40
00:07:06,893 --> 00:07:07,951
chewing gum

41
00:07:10,063 --> 00:07:11,087
Then go is

42
00:07:11,866 --> 00:07:13,133
out

43
00:07:16,970 --> 00:07:19,939
We will be
'Wonder Boys'

44
00:07:26,946 --> 00:07:29,073
'Mr Children

45
00:07:29,916 --> 00:07:31,884
I think you're still there
 contract with us.

46
00:07:33,086 --> 00:07:37,045
Signs. He will be the manager.
He is also responsible for delegation

47
00:07:37,891 --> 00:07:41,884
'Mr. Children actual potential, three years ago,
But not now.

48
00:07:41,995 --> 00:07:47,956
Nepal at a glance the story or the Germans,
both can be taken as an example.

49
00:07:48,034 --> 00:07:50,969
Mr Children do not need to work harder

50
00:07:51,971 --> 00:07:54,030
Trying to help them
Only be in vain.

51
00:07:54,107 --> 00:07:56,905
Let me mengatuuurrr to their

52
00:07:59,112 --> 00:08:00,875
 said

53
00:08:01,047 --> 00:08:03,015
'Mr Children dropped
repository, right?

54
00:08:03,116 --> 00:08:08,385
Since he left, I ran back and forth alone.
wondering how to restore the reputation of the root

55
00:08:09,055 --> 00:08:11,853
Did you know, my 3-year bear
much suffering

56
00:08:11,958 --> 00:08:13,892
not accepted everywhere

57
00:08:14,461 --> 00:08:16,554
what they have they
has mengancurkan everything,

58
00:08:16,763 --> 00:08:18,560
Never
thinking

59
00:08:18,565 --> 00:08:20,125
But this is not all their fault

60
00:08:20,133 --> 00:08:23,400
So you think I do not need the money??
their contract meelanggaran

61
00:08:24,071 --> 00:08:26,764
Provide evidence that the
they violate the contract.

62
00:08:27,140 --> 00:08:29,973
and to 'Mr. Children ...

63
00:08:29,976 --> 00:08:30,965
... I'll take over.

64
00:08:31,077 --> 00:08:32,977
They are clearly in violation of
with expenditures exceeding revenues

65
00:08:33,012 --> 00:08:35,105
He wants to fill the gap, sometimes
will destroy itself

66
00:08:37,984 --> 00:08:39,849
I give this plan to his staff

67
00:08:40,954 --> 00:08:42,922
must follow the rules for immigrants
I could try.

68
00:08:43,056 --> 00:08:44,045
oh no

69
00:08:44,891 --> 00:08:46,085
I have a plan

70
00:08:47,026 --> 00:08:48,823
Do you want to
something from me?

71
00:08:48,928 --> 00:08:50,020
meaning ..

72
00:08:51,030 --> 00:08:52,964
... I'll start from scratch.

73
00:08:57,971 --> 00:08:58,995
You really want to go back

74
00:08:59,072 --> 00:09:00,937
then, what is your plan.

75
00:09:02,876 --> 00:09:05,936
First, set back,
he helped me find a gym

76
00:09:06,045 --> 00:09:07,910
hot, is not suitable for the stage

77
00:09:08,014 --> 00:09:09,982
He did it just to punish myself alone.

78
00:09:10,049 --> 00:09:11,846
Mother's boss

79
00:09:12,986 --> 00:09:15,113
He was no longer Sa Hee
once we know.

80
00:09:19,092 --> 00:09:21,117
I know, I go to work
is off.

81
00:09:21,928 --> 00:09:22,952
I would also go

82
00:09:23,062 --> 00:09:23,994
But it ...

83
00:09:24,063 --> 00:09:26,896
I still think ... I'm still
in need here ...

84
00:09:27,100 --> 00:09:28,032
Yo ..

85
00:09:29,002 --> 00:09:30,970
basic stubborn woman

86
00:09:33,940 --> 00:09:34,964
Thank you

87
00:09:37,043 --> 00:09:38,032
have a nice day

88
00:09:39,112 --> 00:09:40,079
have a nice day

89
00:09:44,984 --> 00:09:45,916
Whose is this?

90
00:09:48,855 --> 00:09:49,879
meneketehe.

91
00:09:50,123 --> 00:09:51,886
Why is there left?

92
00:09:52,058 --> 00:09:54,856
Reduce new problems, many
I have to do more than this one

93
00:09:54,961 --> 00:09:56,929
Bring home ane like ya drunk ...

94
00:10:22,088 --> 00:10:26,024
Problem, you are the spouse
wrong, do not fit the work in the water.

95
00:10:26,926 --> 00:10:28,086
Although the destiny can not be changed

96
00:10:29,028 --> 00:10:31,019
But the future can be changed

97
00:10:31,998 --> 00:10:34,899
So, want to change the future
must have the will

98
00:10:35,034 --> 00:10:36,899
And fully prepared

99
00:10:37,003 --> 00:10:38,868
Ready for what?

100
00:10:39,038 --> 00:10:41,871
Forgive me this business.
Do not know ...

101
00:10:42,075 --> 00:10:44,100
I actually have some ideas.

102
00:10:44,143 --> 00:10:46,111
Terusterang was Asolole.

103
00:10:47,013 --> 00:10:48,002
So ...

104
00:10:49,882 --> 00:10:52,043
Commercial Insurance

105
00:10:52,919 --> 00:10:57,083
This is the insurance
The most well-known basic

106
00:10:57,290 --> 00:10:59,281
waste of time,
like no other jobs

107
00:11:02,095 --> 00:11:04,086
Nunggak kindergarten costs a lot

108
00:11:04,897 --> 00:11:06,888
We will finish it for kindergarten
In addition, he will stay in school

109
00:11:07,000 --> 00:11:09,059
He needs to get a little, at least
children in day care centers

110
00:11:10,103 --> 00:11:11,968
You must immediately pay it off.

111
00:11:12,905 --> 00:11:13,997
The others let me finish.

112
00:11:14,974 --> 00:11:16,942
I'd nemuin suitcase.

113
00:11:20,423 --> 00:11:23,023
-What?, Then what is it?

114
00:11:23,116 --> 00:11:24,981
Why I should know,
I would mengembalikanya

115
00:11:25,352 --> 00:11:26,810
Open it,
greet tau valuable contents

116
00:11:26,820 --> 00:11:28,651
That will change our destiny

117
00:11:28,955 --> 00:11:29,922
Why

118
00:11:30,023 --> 00:11:32,014
I was not comfortable for
open

119
00:11:36,129 --> 00:11:38,893
Why do you open
suitcase, tuyul.

120
00:11:38,898 --> 00:11:40,024
Alo, alo

121
00:11:40,133 --> 00:11:41,896
I'm just curious
Just really.

122
00:11:42,001 --> 00:11:43,025
Turned out to open his own

123
00:11:43,136 --> 00:11:46,833
So Eun Han, Han Eun has not slept,
why you memperbolehkanya.

124
00:11:50,209 --> 00:11:51,210
Ooo ..

125
00:11:51,867 --> 00:11:53,687
He again sleep anyway,

126
00:12:32,919 --> 00:12:33,886
Hello Assalamualaikum,,

127
00:12:34,921 --> 00:12:36,081
Dimaling not stuff, right?

128
00:12:36,889 --> 00:12:37,856
Not

129
00:12:37,924 --> 00:12:38,982
I am not a thief

130
00:12:41,994 --> 00:12:43,894
He tells you to meet

131
00:12:44,997 --> 00:12:46,897
This is where the King

132
00:12:47,867 --> 00:12:49,926
Yoo Jin, the King was here

133
00:12:50,870 --> 00:12:51,928
Where are you?

134
00:12:52,004 --> 00:12:53,062
I just got here

135
00:12:53,740 --> 00:12:55,640
We will soon be gone

136
00:12:55,908 --> 00:12:57,000
I just came to return

137
00:12:57,143 --> 00:13:00,909
-Is that so?
tell where you are, I'll meet.

138
00:13:00,913 --> 00:13:02,873
I still do not see you

139
00:13:03,850 --> 00:13:05,010
I dah nyampe.

140
00:13:05,918 --> 00:13:07,010
Where are you?.

141
00:13:07,954 --> 00:13:10,081
Raise your hand, let me know

142
00:13:34,115 --> 00:13:35,513
Huaaa ...

143
00:13:35,523 --> 00:13:37,143
Suitcase magically fly

144
00:13:54,567 --> 00:13:55,659
Take lah.

145
00:13:57,103 --> 00:13:58,934
You want me to nyebur?

146
00:14:01,007 --> 00:14:02,896
yes no lazy,

147
00:14:14,921 --> 00:14:15,910
Please, Lontong!

148
00:14:16,989 --> 00:14:17,887
Save me

149
00:14:39,111 --> 00:14:40,840
You seem to be old,

150
00:14:41,147 --> 00:14:43,115
I have two children, of course, old age

151
00:14:43,116 --> 00:14:44,148
Emang who says the young

152
00:14:44,417 --> 00:14:45,475
I also, want to get married 2 times

153
00:14:46,386 --> 00:14:49,778
I do not want to get married again,
Will only increase spending

154
00:14:50,189 --> 00:14:52,956
Why? why?
you in touch with him, right?

155
00:14:52,959 --> 00:14:55,948
I'm now very busy,
Do not follow me anymore

156
00:14:56,028 --> 00:14:57,595
This makes it crazy.

157
00:14:57,897 --> 00:14:59,125
Ms. ae,

158
00:15:03,570 --> 00:15:04,559
Yoo Jin in there

159
00:15:05,972 --> 00:15:07,098
She looks fine

160
00:15:08,074 --> 00:15:11,100
He says,
there that makes you fall into water

161
00:15:20,920 --> 00:15:22,880
Oo,, Up,
This is it

162
00:15:50,049 --> 00:15:51,038
I know him

163
00:15:52,084 --> 00:15:55,815
He needed money immediately to the marriage,
so it's cheap.

164
00:15:57,022 --> 00:15:58,853
resting place

165
00:15:59,125 --> 00:16:00,922
Workplace

166
00:16:01,093 --> 00:16:03,061
Place of Entertainment Practice,
no problem

167
00:16:04,063 --> 00:16:05,052
no game

168
00:16:05,965 --> 00:16:06,932
memories of the past

169
00:16:09,000 --> 00:16:11,901
There is also the championship belt.

170
00:16:16,343 --> 00:16:18,870
He's also not a sportsman,
so do not like this place.

171
00:16:19,979 --> 00:16:21,139
No need to spend lots of money

172
00:16:21,448 --> 00:16:22,380
Monthly rental only.

173
00:16:22,749 --> 00:16:24,238
Save more money

174
00:16:34,601 --> 00:16:35,701
Agree ...

175
00:16:39,131 --> 00:16:41,998
This time we invited Ricky Jang
when he was 3 years old in 1986

176
00:16:42,068 --> 00:16:46,337
When received professional training in Canada

177
00:16:46,872 --> 00:16:47,099
Hello

178
00:16:47,940 --> 00:16:54,671
I know he was very young at the time, do c
t difficult, but if he remembers the details of r

179
00:16:54,713 --> 00:16:56,772
Please tell your learning process

180
00:16:57,984 --> 00:17:02,545
At 3 years, I passed by a
column in the back alley

181
00:17:04,090 --> 00:17:06,024
There are two children playing together

182
00:17:07,093 --> 00:17:08,990
A child that I know

183
00:17:10,696 --> 00:17:12,256
kai is a girl

184
00:17:17,537 --> 00:17:18,561
Goo Joo Oh

185
00:17:21,140 --> 00:17:23,836
Jang Ricky ...
Sit

186
00:17:38,358 --> 00:17:40,553
Back to the game, is P

187
00:17:41,261 --> 00:17:43,320
Now holding a child as well
pain throughout the body

188
00:17:44,964 --> 00:17:47,057
Baek Kon, room number 5 is completed.

189
00:17:48,034 --> 00:17:50,867
This, what is wrong.
Room No. 2 room no one moved.

190
00:17:54,907 --> 00:17:56,101
I want to try again

191
00:18:15,961 --> 00:18:17,053
Stop, Jang Jio

192
00:18:18,064 --> 00:18:19,998
I've had quite a lot of trouble.

193
00:18:26,005 --> 00:18:27,063
We're broke!

194
00:18:31,110 --> 00:18:32,941
Cah ngganteng,

195
00:18:40,752 --> 00:18:43,386
Welcome,
Please log.

196
00:18:50,896 --> 00:18:51,920
How are you.

197
00:18:53,065 --> 00:18:54,032
Want to exercise.

198
00:18:55,134 --> 00:18:56,965
Of course not.

199
00:18:57,870 --> 00:19:00,896
Can we practice here while
Including dance

200
00:19:00,973 --> 00:19:03,432
The main theater where?
We do not have a vocalist?

201
00:19:04,910 --> 00:19:06,901
Do you think okay, sooner or later
only to fail again.

202
00:19:10,015 --> 00:19:11,880
Failure. That is ...

203
00:19:13,119 --> 00:19:16,811
Left, not everyone gets this opportunity,
This is not bad at all

204
00:19:17,123 --> 00:19:19,887
Previous manager Su Yin Huang, remember?

205
00:19:19,992 --> 00:19:22,984
Now it will be replaced,
others who will be responsible here.

206
00:19:24,063 --> 00:19:25,826
So, he has not contacted?

207
00:19:25,998 --> 00:19:26,965
Yet.

208
00:19:27,133 --> 00:19:29,931
A few weeks ago I met to him or her,
Perwakila in charge of Java Garden.

209
00:19:31,003 --> 00:19:31,935
Representative?

210
00:19:32,104 --> 00:19:33,036
Who?

211
00:19:33,906 --> 00:19:34,873
I?

212
00:19:35,074 --> 00:19:36,974
I will help her to recommend titles.

213
00:19:39,044 --> 00:19:41,103
Taman Sang Sik You dare ...

214
00:19:42,982 --> 00:19:43,914
Representatives ...

215
00:19:57,062 --> 00:19:59,895
Yesterday I had no other way

216
00:20:01,033 --> 00:20:02,091
Thank you

217
00:20:04,003 --> 00:20:06,995
So I will not go home again

218
00:20:08,040 --> 00:20:09,098
Very noisy!

219
00:20:11,110 --> 00:20:13,078
Do not know why I say this?

220
00:20:16,015 --> 00:20:18,006
This Saturday, Auditions begin.

221
00:20:19,051 --> 00:20:21,019
Just relax about it!

222
00:20:22,955 --> 00:20:26,015
This is my dress rentals in Parkland Auditions later,
Pretty cheap too!

223
00:20:26,959 --> 00:20:29,894
If the money is still a little,
it would be nice to go for it!

224
00:20:31,030 --> 00:20:32,054
Why is that?

225
00:20:32,865 --> 00:20:34,958
So money is not worth, what?

226
00:20:35,100 --> 00:20:36,889
Try it first sleeve,
ngebacot new.

227
00:20:36,902 --> 00:20:38,862
Money is an additional award,
such as John Kennedy!

228
00:20:38,904 --> 00:20:40,796
I still do not understand you.

229
00:20:40,873 --> 00:20:41,965
100 large and small clothing dong

230
00:20:42,375 --> 00:20:44,603
I told him
to mengembalikanya intact.

231
00:20:46,912 --> 00:20:47,936
I listened mbok in!

232
00:20:48,047 --> 00:20:49,844
His style is in stark contrast?

233
00:20:58,013 --> 00:20:59,413
-Word-Utina

234
00:21:04,776 --> 00:21:05,896
-Adul-

235
00:21:07,043 --> 00:21:08,243
-Rido Roma-

236
00:21:08,766 --> 00:21:09,886
-S.I.D-

237
00:21:09,951 --> 00:21:11,351
-NEUTRAL-

238
00:21:12,325 --> 00:21:14,145
Gymnastics-The-

239
00:21:15,639 --> 00:21:17,459
Mariah Carey--

240
00:21:18,996 --> 00:21:20,816
-Bambang Pamungkas-

241
00:21:22,982 --> 00:21:23,949
We are only looking for men only!

242
00:21:24,684 --> 00:21:26,310
-Dancer-sadistic
please refer to the first and commentary!

243
00:21:31,789 --> 00:21:33,609
-Toufik Hidayat-

244
00:21:36,260 --> 00:21:38,080
-Ben Jo (Timlo) -

245
00:21:41,626 --> 00:21:43,446
Budi do-re mi-

246
00:21:44,136 --> 00:21:46,001
Why do people
look the same?

247
00:21:46,872 --> 00:21:47,930
'Dream motition'

248
00:21:49,041 --> 00:21:50,941
Start of us, at the same time!

249
00:21:52,419 --> 00:21:53,539
-Afgan-

250
00:22:07,927 --> 00:22:08,894
Are you a singer?

251
00:22:09,128 --> 00:22:10,857
My fans!

252
00:22:31,083 --> 00:22:33,017
Why are you here?

253
00:22:34,119 --> 00:22:35,108
Group you want to play?

254
00:22:36,021 --> 00:22:37,818
-I am his sonnets guitarists bang Roma

255
00:22:38,891 --> 00:22:40,017
"Why did not protest '"

256
00:22:41,026 --> 00:22:41,993
Start!

257
00:23:22,204 --> 00:23:24,024
yo,, asked for time

258
00:23:43,856 --> 00:23:44,880
Want more slowly?

259
00:23:45,891 --> 00:23:46,858
Or faster?

260
00:23:47,126 --> 00:23:48,821
Play alone!

261
00:23:52,865 --> 00:23:53,889
My view would be no problem!

262
00:24:58,997 --> 00:25:00,123
His respiration is stopped!

263
00:25:05,371 --> 00:25:07,031
This song takes a little effort!

264
00:25:07,973 --> 00:25:09,099
I can only say that this is tiring

265
00:25:09,975 --> 00:25:12,000
Chaotic, tasteless,
makes people sick

266
00:25:12,144 --> 00:25:15,113
You're the only singer here

267
00:25:16,014 --> 00:25:17,879
Other less popular

268
00:25:20,052 --> 00:25:21,883
But I can accept

269
00:25:22,288 --> 00:25:23,448
but not all

270
00:25:24,490 --> 00:25:25,650
Just sings it

271
00:25:28,927 --> 00:25:29,985
Just me?

272
00:25:30,062 --> 00:25:31,996
Was not this an audition for the group?

273
00:25:33,065 --> 00:25:34,862
So, why only me?

274
00:25:35,033 --> 00:25:36,091
Because we need a vocalist!

275
00:25:39,004 --> 00:25:39,993
We want to ..

276
00:25:40,973 --> 00:25:42,431
Recruiting a new singer ...!

277
00:25:42,875 --> 00:25:44,035
Then I refuse!

278
00:25:44,109 --> 00:25:47,977
we come as a group,
a collective

279
00:25:49,014 --> 00:25:50,982
Please find someone else!

280
00:25:58,123 --> 00:26:02,291
Seeing his condition,
if it continues like this,,

281
00:26:02,961 --> 00:26:04,952
I go alone!

282
00:26:05,097 --> 00:26:07,065
I think this all the time
for me to end it.

283
00:26:07,133 --> 00:26:09,159
You want to give up just
because things like this?

284
00:26:11,069 --> 00:26:12,866
What about you?

285
00:26:13,005 --> 00:26:16,198
Yesterday, I got the interview call.

286
00:26:17,109 --> 00:26:19,374
My girl ordered to leave the band.

287
00:26:19,745 --> 00:26:21,645
Seeking other employment.

288
00:26:23,315 --> 00:26:25,849
I filed an application in the company, so ...

289
00:26:26,651 --> 00:26:32,056
Fight is not a reason to do more,
but there is no reason for treason

290
00:26:32,090 --> 00:26:33,079
Losers!

291
00:26:48,073 --> 00:26:49,340
Please in enjoy!

292
00:26:54,212 --> 00:26:55,201
Om ..?

293
00:26:57,950 --> 00:27:00,009
It's not wrong?

294
00:27:01,053 --> 00:27:05,080
And he had my differences
so big?

295
00:27:06,058 --> 00:27:07,855
Regular customer!

296
00:27:09,861 --> 00:27:11,021
Well, I understand!

297
00:27:45,130 --> 00:27:46,097
As I understand it ..

298
00:27:46,932 --> 00:27:49,924
Indeed there is something wrong ..
om the noodles with the seller.

299
00:27:50,135 --> 00:27:53,969
Analisaku to the boy that he worked in warkop morning,
night in a car dealer, jd introductory weekend!

300
00:27:54,072 --> 00:27:55,935
But he says

301
00:27:56,041 --> 00:27:57,872
He always practiced
playing music in between time.

302
00:27:57,976 --> 00:28:01,070
Several years ago, Kim Su-Ro
The band auditioned group.

303
00:28:01,847 --> 00:28:02,939
He was then elected.

304
00:28:03,715 --> 00:28:06,306
but according to the info?
The band seemed now defunct.

305
00:28:26,238 --> 00:28:27,662
Wedang round!

306
00:28:42,921 --> 00:28:43,945
Du Chan!

307
00:28:49,928 --> 00:28:50,826
Singer genius!

308
00:28:50,996 --> 00:28:51,963
You want how much?

309
00:28:52,064 --> 00:28:53,031
Come to me!

310
00:28:56,001 --> 00:28:56,990
I am a driver.

311
00:28:57,669 --> 00:28:58,829
Please ask for going in between where?

312
00:29:05,077 --> 00:29:06,401
Where should aja!

313
00:29:07,379 --> 00:29:12,705
Do you follow me for it?
just for this?

314
00:29:19,024 --> 00:29:19,991
Hello Assalamualaikum.

315
00:29:20,092 --> 00:29:23,118
Du Chan!

316
00:29:33,939 --> 00:29:35,065
Please Wait!

317
00:29:37,843 --> 00:29:39,771
Last month was the first nunggak ..

318
00:29:39,945 --> 00:29:41,705
I will also surely pay.

319
00:29:42,981 --> 00:29:44,573
So the system here .....

320
00:29:46,017 --> 00:29:49,010
It is the policy,
I can not do anything about it.

321
00:29:49,054 --> 00:29:50,521
Can not do anything about it?

322
00:29:50,922 --> 00:29:51,911
You was the receptionist!

323
00:29:52,023 --> 00:29:54,856
I really do not know what to say.

324
00:29:55,026 --> 00:29:56,857
Plus it makes me crazy!

325
00:29:56,962 --> 00:29:57,986
Find other hospitals and go!

326
00:29:58,964 --> 00:30:00,898
Come on,
we also got to go!

327
00:30:02,901 --> 00:30:05,893
If the payment can be cash
debit wear it!

328
00:30:07,038 --> 00:30:09,029
I beg you a little time,
This time only!

329
00:30:09,975 --> 00:30:10,907
I beg you!

330
00:30:11,042 --> 00:30:12,066
This salary for 2 years.

331
00:30:22,087 --> 00:30:23,850
Are you ..?

332
00:30:49,014 --> 00:30:50,845
In your eyes,
we are beggars?

333
00:30:51,082 --> 00:30:53,445
Or are you done voluntarily?

334
00:30:56,054 --> 00:30:57,885
I'd hire you for 2 years

335
00:30:58,056 --> 00:31:00,624
So starting today means
2-year contract with me.

336
00:31:04,062 --> 00:31:05,893
So this is the salary for 2 years

337
00:31:06,131 --> 00:31:07,962
Also have you spend money.

338
00:31:08,099 --> 00:31:09,088
so I asked for flowers!

339
00:31:09,435 --> 00:31:10,724
I can only pay once!

340
00:31:11,102 --> 00:31:12,069
there is not another payday?

341
00:31:12,104 --> 00:31:13,962
Decision at hand.

342
00:31:14,973 --> 00:31:16,907
Why do I have to like it?

343
00:31:17,876 --> 00:31:19,002
You will make me a star singer?

344
00:31:19,945 --> 00:31:21,971
You can do it,
but not liable to the end?

345
00:31:21,980 --> 00:31:22,969
Hhmm

346
00:31:23,114 --> 00:31:24,877
Tried it once dong.

347
00:31:27,986 --> 00:31:29,044
Music Stars

348
00:31:30,121 --> 00:31:31,952
I know Kim Su-Ro

349
00:31:52,944 --> 00:31:55,913
Kim Su-Ro there!
Even the more moderate view again!

350
00:31:56,147 --> 00:31:58,911
although he also knows me.

351
00:31:59,017 --> 00:32:00,917
But current trends are not!

352
00:32:01,052 --> 00:32:03,885
Television media is not
place for a joke!

353
00:32:04,022 --> 00:32:06,081
This is no time like that,
claim was rejected!

354
00:32:06,358 --> 00:32:08,850
Leave it alone, do not need anymore!

355
00:32:09,094 --> 00:32:10,959
No need to talk a lot!

356
00:32:11,730 --> 00:32:14,398
This title, the latter does
I'll never forget.!

357
00:32:28,914 --> 00:32:29,881
I honestly do not know

358
00:32:31,049 --> 00:32:32,846
Why do we?

359
00:32:33,252 --> 00:32:35,412
I will not give up.

360
00:32:35,854 --> 00:32:37,348
to revive the era who have been missing!

361
00:32:38,924 --> 00:32:40,892
Another person who heard,
What else do this?

362
00:32:41,960 --> 00:32:44,019
What? Now go!

363
00:32:44,963 --> 00:32:46,021
But you must remember this.

364
00:32:47,032 --> 00:32:49,891
Of course this must be clearly
done voluntarily.

365
00:32:50,068 --> 00:32:51,968
The most important thing

366
00:32:52,103 --> 00:32:54,003
Most important, ok?

367
00:33:04,015 --> 00:33:05,004
Why did you come?

368
00:33:05,850 --> 00:33:08,011
If I did not come!

369
00:33:09,054 --> 00:33:10,021
I was on KTV

370
00:33:10,989 --> 00:33:12,013
In turn has several times!

371
00:33:13,024 --> 00:33:15,857
The car has a fairly
output space of 88 years.

372
00:33:16,027 --> 00:33:17,927
And now I am the dreamer,
we start from the most basic?

373
00:33:23,969 --> 00:33:24,936
I'm tired!

374
00:33:39,084 --> 00:33:40,073
He said jobs are still open,

375
00:33:41,052 --> 00:33:43,717
He wanted to make food to go!

376
00:33:46,091 --> 00:33:47,854
I need a little capital.

377
00:33:48,026 --> 00:33:49,960
So this is intentional,
Go here for a second chance!

378
00:33:50,028 --> 00:33:51,052
40 minutes late

379
00:33:51,930 --> 00:33:52,954
Do it 14 000 times

380
00:34:18,089 --> 00:34:18,987
Run!

381
00:34:23,895 --> 00:34:24,862
Run!

382
00:34:24,996 --> 00:34:25,928
Run!

383
00:34:46,084 --> 00:34:48,052
What are we?

384
00:34:48,987 --> 00:34:51,854
Could it be that the
country star?

385
00:34:54,025 --> 00:34:54,923
I

386
00:34:55,927 --> 00:34:58,020
Would be a national star.!

387
00:34:59,964 --> 00:35:00,953
I

388
00:35:05,970 --> 00:35:06,834
It is ..

389
00:35:06,871 --> 00:35:08,529
Basic dance ..

390
00:35:09,040 --> 00:35:11,838
Do this new
you could dance another!

391
00:35:12,077 --> 00:35:13,840
But do not fail

392
00:35:13,978 --> 00:35:15,104
or no
Another dance dance!

393
00:35:21,019 --> 00:35:21,917
See, right?

394
00:35:22,020 --> 00:35:23,851
I can not get basic things!

395
00:35:23,955 --> 00:35:24,853
Why?

396
00:35:24,956 --> 00:35:26,414
Because I'm not a star, so

397
00:35:26,925 --> 00:35:27,892
You should be here!

398
00:35:29,894 --> 00:35:31,953
I'm a rapper!

399
00:35:31,996 --> 00:35:33,054
I do not need to do it

400
00:35:34,099 --> 00:35:36,932
Why should I
beginian too?

401
00:35:37,035 --> 00:35:38,402
Just try nge-RAPP

402
00:35:38,837 --> 00:35:40,198
All right!

403
00:35:52,984 --> 00:35:53,973
Did he succeed?

404
00:35:54,119 --> 00:35:55,051
Give me a week

405
00:35:55,854 --> 00:35:56,878
I'll intensive train.

406
00:36:19,110 --> 00:36:20,839
I want to be a star!

407
00:36:23,014 --> 00:36:24,914
I want to!

408
00:36:25,049 --> 00:36:25,981
Do not run!

409
00:36:27,886 --> 00:36:30,081
Do not overdo it! Stop!

410
00:36:38,329 --> 00:36:40,529
Hot rice soup
heavenly fun

411
00:36:40,999 --> 00:36:43,125
The scent tickled to the bone tunnel Nose.

412
00:36:44,102 --> 00:36:46,832
People born with gourmet food, clean

413
00:36:47,038 --> 00:36:48,796
So so hungry!

414
00:37:30,982 --> 00:37:31,846
Repeat!

415
00:37:33,588 --> 00:37:34,520
Repeat!

416
00:37:37,399 --> 00:37:38,263
Repeat!

417
00:37:48,007 --> 00:37:49,127
Repeat!

418
00:38:11,856 --> 00:38:12,948
This is the final practice before meeting him!

419
00:38:14,125 --> 00:38:15,888
I have a question!

420
00:38:16,461 --> 00:38:18,019
If the last round of meetings

421
00:38:18,930 --> 00:38:19,954
selanjutya how?

422
00:38:19,998 --> 00:38:21,995
Of course the premiere.

423
00:38:22,266 --> 00:38:23,997
You have to look good.

424
00:38:24,002 --> 00:38:25,833
In order not to ruin the show.

425
00:38:25,937 --> 00:38:28,097
It's all been funded

426
00:38:28,973 --> 00:38:30,907
Do not just look at the stars in the sky

427
00:38:32,844 --> 00:38:34,004
Be one of them.

428
00:38:34,979 --> 00:38:36,937
Who is to say words like that?

429
00:38:37,015 --> 00:38:38,039
I!

430
00:39:02,641 --> 00:39:03,569
Repeat!

431
00:39:03,977 --> 00:39:06,777
Do not see the camera before changing!

432
00:39:10,908 --> 00:39:12,028
Repeat!

433
00:39:12,083 --> 00:39:13,880
I said,
Do not see the camera before changing!

434
00:39:16,888 --> 00:39:19,718
enough, enough!
Tell them to go, annoying!

435
00:39:20,524 --> 00:39:22,355
Replace 'Wonder Boys'!

436
00:39:27,031 --> 00:39:29,898
Permformnya not identical,
Drama is not the same part!

437
00:39:56,928 --> 00:39:57,917
Ask break moment!

438
00:39:58,129 --> 00:40:00,360
Take a break and come back! Thank you!

439
00:40:00,898 --> 00:40:02,092
what's wrong with you, NHE!

440
00:40:02,900 --> 00:40:04,060
Geez, he was again sick!

441
00:40:05,036 --> 00:40:07,361
Why is that?
The timing was not right.

442
00:40:08,072 --> 00:40:09,039
What?

443
00:40:09,907 --> 00:40:10,874
What are you doing?

444
00:40:11,075 --> 00:40:12,042
Want invites a fight?

445
00:40:14,045 --> 00:40:15,012
Do not fight woi ...

446
00:40:15,980 --> 00:40:16,969
Stop, do not fight anymore!

447
00:40:17,982 --> 00:40:19,074
Stop, do not fight anymore!

448
00:40:19,951 --> 00:40:20,975
Do not fight anymore!

449
00:40:21,853 --> 00:40:23,013
Do not fight anymore, that's enough!

450
00:40:23,888 --> 00:40:25,716
Okay! You feel right at pecundangi?

451
00:40:26,057 --> 00:40:26,989
You said what?

452
00:40:33,865 --> 00:40:36,959
Something that does not need to happen!

453
00:40:38,970 --> 00:40:41,029
This is the reality of 'rough star'?

454
00:40:44,976 --> 00:40:45,943
Stand up!

455
00:40:46,044 --> 00:40:47,011
Ready for directions!

456
00:40:52,116 --> 00:40:53,083
Complete!

457
00:40:55,853 --> 00:40:56,842
The plan?

458
00:40:57,889 --> 00:40:59,083
The first broadcast of me?

459
00:40:59,090 --> 00:41:00,955
He's not a group!

460
00:41:01,059 --> 00:41:03,027
We are a group!

461
00:41:03,861 --> 00:41:05,021
PD Goo what say?

462
00:41:05,096 --> 00:41:07,087
Continue like this, I will seek
way that they can gig again.

463
00:41:20,912 --> 00:41:21,879
Mother?

464
00:41:23,014 --> 00:41:24,072
Remember me?

465
00:41:25,149 --> 00:41:26,878
Ricky

466
00:41:27,118 --> 00:41:29,018
Mother, make you miss?

467
00:41:32,023 --> 00:41:32,955
What?

468
00:41:33,091 --> 00:41:34,415
Looking for my mother?

469
00:41:35,026 --> 00:41:36,891
There will be opportunities to meet

470
00:41:38,096 --> 00:41:41,961
If a star,
it will be realized.

471
00:41:42,867 --> 00:41:44,493
Is that why you do all this?

472
00:41:46,638 --> 00:41:47,730
the words can be jadiin lyrics!

473
00:41:50,041 --> 00:41:51,838
Expertise that you, not!

474
00:41:52,877 --> 00:41:54,071
Mother remember? I'm Ricky!

475
00:41:57,081 --> 00:41:59,879
Mother remember? I'm Ricky!

476
00:42:00,585 --> 00:42:01,552
Forward!

477
00:42:12,063 --> 00:42:12,995
Crazy!

478
00:42:42,059 --> 00:42:43,617
Where other squid?

479
00:42:47,932 --> 00:42:49,058
There are further 'Wonder Boys',

480
00:42:49,934 --> 00:42:51,094
There were also 'Brave Girls' and
'Wonder Boys' still in charge.!

481
00:42:51,903 --> 00:42:52,927
Please go ahead!

482
00:42:53,971 --> 00:42:56,030
This weekly winner

483
00:42:56,140 --> 00:42:58,108
'Wonder Boys'!

484
00:42:58,109 --> 00:43:01,875
Congratulations, this is our first time
Seeing a band like this ...

485
00:43:10,054 --> 00:43:11,817
PD Pob!

486
00:43:12,123 --> 00:43:13,886
Long time no see!

487
00:43:18,863 --> 00:43:19,830
Let's go,

488
00:43:20,831 --> 00:43:21,991
The problem that you say.

489
00:43:22,133 --> 00:43:23,862
If you want pemecahanya.

490
00:43:23,968 --> 00:43:25,833
For those who always annoying ..

491
00:43:25,937 --> 00:43:27,837
Can thus, great!

492
00:43:36,080 --> 00:43:37,012
Long wait?

493
00:43:48,059 --> 00:43:51,028
Well, he said the issue was not on set?

494
00:43:51,862 --> 00:43:53,022
How can it be?

495
00:43:53,097 --> 00:43:56,931
Reasons 'Star Music' to do it is because they ...

496
00:43:57,034 --> 00:43:58,058
Hello?

497
00:44:01,005 --> 00:44:02,939
Why give up in the middle of the road like this huh?

498
00:44:03,074 --> 00:44:05,099
What did he do it with me?

499
00:44:05,910 --> 00:44:07,878
It is, hello, brother?

500
00:44:08,112 --> 00:44:10,012
First she PD Goo

501
00:44:10,114 --> 00:44:12,878
Park Sang-Sik-I will confirm it!

502
00:44:12,950 --> 00:44:14,975
It ... hello?

503
00:44:17,121 --> 00:44:18,918
Why should this bother?

504
00:44:18,923 --> 00:44:22,086
The first is the management
and office rental

505
00:44:22,960 --> 00:44:24,928
I also spend all your money, right?

506
00:44:25,029 --> 00:44:28,829
Moreover, it is, we do not
After singing in the club!

507
00:44:34,972 --> 00:44:35,904
Hello, Assalamualaikum?

508
00:44:36,140 --> 00:44:37,937
Welcome him! Well?

509
00:44:38,109 --> 00:44:38,973
Yes!

510
00:44:40,077 --> 00:44:42,944
What is it? Really!

511
00:44:43,914 --> 00:44:45,882
Of course, not that!

512
00:44:47,918 --> 00:44:48,942
No way!

513
00:44:52,089 --> 00:44:52,987
Wait a minute!

514
00:45:17,148 --> 00:45:18,843
Why are we here

515
00:45:19,050 --> 00:45:20,881
And should encourage vehicle

516
00:45:21,052 --> 00:45:22,952
To save costs?

517
00:45:25,122 --> 00:45:27,056
We must show
our music to all.

518
00:45:27,892 --> 00:45:29,951
Even for these people.

519
00:45:32,796 --> 00:45:33,922
My stomach mules!

520
00:45:37,068 --> 00:45:38,831
What do you eat?

521
00:45:45,042 --> 00:45:47,101
Long time no see!

522
00:45:47,978 --> 00:45:50,071
Park Sang-Sik mengamb means
gas well, grab something to eat!

523
00:45:50,981 --> 00:45:52,846
But he did not think to stop!

524
00:45:52,950 --> 00:45:54,815
Not to mention a long way here!

525
00:45:54,952 --> 00:45:55,941
What to do in there!

526
00:45:56,887 --> 00:45:58,047
The girl next to you a dancer?

527
00:45:59,990 --> 00:46:02,049
Or the girl guides karaoke?

528
00:46:03,027 --> 00:46:04,016
Ah. not?

529
00:46:04,862 --> 00:46:08,988
This is the general manager Us.

530
00:46:09,033 --> 00:46:12,093
Of course you know, I
under his hand prior to making a living here!

531
00:46:12,403 --> 00:46:13,427
Manager?

532
00:46:14,839 --> 00:46:19,499
I'm the director here, Hong-Ji-Dong

533
00:46:19,977 --> 00:46:21,001
How do you think?

534
00:46:44,068 --> 00:46:45,899
The next event is

535
00:46:46,371 --> 00:46:48,229
5 pretty girls on stage

536
00:46:48,939 --> 00:46:51,100
See who is fastest

537
00:46:52,843 --> 00:46:54,834
As a "chill'' 'member of come-on!

538
00:46:54,979 --> 00:46:57,846
DJ mercy ..! Dong music ..

539
00:46:58,015 --> 00:47:00,848
What then of the members of the chill?

540
00:47:01,085 --> 00:47:03,883
Wow .. someone started open shirt!

541
00:47:06,891 --> 00:47:10,827
Is this going to make
chill member of passion?

542
00:47:10,928 --> 00:47:12,054
Sang-Sik, How are you?

543
00:47:12,096 --> 00:47:13,996
He said this was a public lie.!

544
00:47:14,098 --> 00:47:15,895
Terusin like this!

545
00:47:16,000 --> 00:47:17,865
Spectators will watch you, NHE!

546
00:47:17,868 --> 00:47:19,836
Continue to entertain everyone,

547
00:47:19,870 --> 00:47:20,996
Very good!

548
00:47:21,105 --> 00:47:24,040
He may have other plans?

549
00:47:24,041 --> 00:47:26,839
I want to slap a cast or a star?

550
00:47:26,944 --> 00:47:29,845
Pour water into the body, all
his body was soaking wet!

551
00:47:29,880 --> 00:47:31,973
Surprised!
I come to do something!

552
00:47:31,982 --> 00:47:33,973
No!

553
00:47:34,018 --> 00:47:35,883
It's refreshing!

554
00:47:35,886 --> 00:47:37,080
I also wet all the time!

555
00:47:37,087 --> 00:47:39,078
Call vi

556
00:47:39,123 --> 00:47:43,958
In the last 7 seconds enthusiastic jump!

557
00:47:59,143 --> 00:48:00,906
It's like ..

558
00:48:01,011 --> 00:48:02,876
My body burned.

559
00:48:05,850 --> 00:48:07,574
Maybe just my feeling.!

560
00:48:10,988 --> 00:48:11,977
I just ..

561
00:48:12,990 --> 00:48:15,959
Smell .. on fire in front,
rotate my head ...

562
00:48:18,062 --> 00:48:20,826
Try to see that happen .. ..

563
00:48:21,966 --> 00:48:23,934
.. But then ..

564
00:48:24,034 --> 00:48:25,831
Please tell kejadianya ..

565
00:48:37,948 --> 00:48:40,007
They survived this event ..

566
00:48:40,084 --> 00:48:42,882
electrical equipment causes
accident was secured.

567
00:48:43,954 --> 00:48:45,979
Too many events
in the news broadcast on TV!

568
00:48:48,025 --> 00:48:49,083
But at least

569
00:48:50,027 --> 00:48:52,286
This is your first time
appear on TV.

570
00:49:13,050 --> 00:49:14,915
Why in this place ..

571
00:49:15,019 --> 00:49:17,078
Just heard "For Elise" ..

572
00:49:17,988 --> 00:49:19,922
I prefer 'Wonder Boys' ..

573
00:49:22,893 --> 00:49:25,554
For two days we did not see it?

574
00:49:29,033 --> 00:49:31,797
Weeks after surgery, she was gone.

575
00:49:34,872 --> 00:49:37,067
So I would tell them to come here ..

576
00:49:37,875 --> 00:49:38,967
One of them.

577
00:49:46,050 --> 00:49:47,950
Let's try it!

578
00:50:11,842 --> 00:50:14,037
What's this? what is wrong?

579
00:50:14,945 --> 00:50:15,934
Sorry there is little interference.

580
00:50:15,946 --> 00:50:18,005
This hospital,
do it do not fit here.

581
00:50:18,115 --> 00:50:19,980
It seems not a good thing?

582
00:50:22,920 --> 00:50:23,887
Sorry!

583
00:50:24,121 --> 00:50:26,021
Please be patient a little!

584
00:54:30,000 --> 00:54:31,900
Left school to play?

585
00:54:32,970 --> 00:54:33,959
What are the benefits cut?

586
00:54:34,071 --> 00:54:35,995
We just isntirahat lunch.

587
00:54:38,041 --> 00:54:39,008
Very beautiful!

588
00:54:40,077 --> 00:54:41,566
Good game?

589
00:54:42,112 --> 00:54:43,979
great ..

590
00:54:50,053 --> 00:54:51,953
Kayae great kalu you shave.

591
00:54:53,056 --> 00:54:54,545
Lazy no yaa ..

592
00:54:55,993 --> 00:54:56,960
Why?

593
00:54:57,928 --> 00:55:00,689
Since this is the style of Rock.

594
00:56:04,094 --> 00:56:05,959
Please do not hit me.

595
00:56:06,930 --> 00:56:08,898
When it hit, we will not discriminate anyone.

596
00:56:15,072 --> 00:56:16,096
Father

597
00:56:16,974 --> 00:56:18,908
Reflexes slow, so it could not escape.

598
00:56:18,942 --> 00:56:20,602
But why are you dancing?

599
00:56:20,911 --> 00:56:23,846
I take it you're from Sanghai
not to crazy things like this.

600
00:56:24,948 --> 00:56:26,882
If you're still singing

601
00:56:27,050 --> 00:56:29,041
From now on you
not my child anymore.

602
00:56:42,499 --> 00:56:44,225
Why did he come to that?

603
00:56:46,937 --> 00:56:47,995
What happened?

604
00:56:48,872 --> 00:56:49,930
Can you tell me?

605
00:56:50,874 --> 00:56:51,966
Just because

606
00:56:52,976 --> 00:56:54,034
Dream

607
00:56:54,845 --> 00:56:55,869
Dreams?

608
00:56:57,914 --> 00:56:59,848
Often, the dream did not materialize.

609
00:57:10,961 --> 00:57:12,053
I just wanted to take
my own way!

610
00:57:13,897 --> 00:57:15,091
Humans, not machines

611
00:57:24,975 --> 00:57:25,942
I am a machine.

612
00:57:30,047 --> 00:57:31,844
You've never been in love right?

613
00:57:34,051 --> 00:57:38,010
When abroad, I never liked
and the like ...

614
00:57:38,922 --> 00:57:40,822
.. At least 5 people.

615
00:57:42,059 --> 00:57:43,856
so what?

616
00:57:45,128 --> 00:57:46,857
He said

617
00:57:46,997 --> 00:57:48,055
When you kiss someone

618
00:57:49,032 --> 00:57:51,899
You will hear
certain tone?

619
00:57:54,971 --> 00:57:57,838
If you continue like this,
there was no time for you to be sure.

620
00:58:01,429 --> 00:58:02,549
<font color = "red"> * Cipok * </ font>

621
00:58:03,980 --> 00:58:04,947
Find a dead huh?

622
00:58:09,853 --> 00:58:10,911
Why I do not feel it?

623
00:58:44,388 --> 00:58:47,888
Video Mr **. Children are
Spread to the virtual world **

624
00:58:48,407 --> 00:58:51,907
Akoustik their appearance **
pains in the home fans faforit **

625
01:00:44,074 --> 01:00:45,006
Persistent

626
01:00:48,912 --> 01:00:51,904
Day 31 - World War Ballad music

627
01:01:08,632 --> 01:01:11,624
Such systems can be done, so
need a singer who can dance.

628
01:01:17,541 --> 01:01:18,833
The basis of crazy people.

629
01:01:21,945 --> 01:01:23,810
Why are you so stubborn ...

630
01:02:32,115 --> 01:02:34,380
No one can talk about it.

631
01:02:35,118 --> 01:02:36,813
I miss mom.

632
01:02:38,922 --> 01:02:39,946
I want to ..

633
01:02:42,926 --> 01:02:43,950
Mom is not too ..

634
01:02:45,962 --> 01:02:47,054
Miss you ..

635
01:02:50,033 --> 01:02:51,000
Mother

636
01:03:18,094 --> 01:03:20,085
This is a meeting
after so long.

637
01:03:21,498 --> 01:03:22,556
But I think ngak running smoothly.

638
01:03:26,304 --> 01:03:28,328
Love is really confusing, yes.

639
01:03:29,939 --> 01:03:32,673
Up doing crazy things,
things like that is still quite normal.

640
01:03:35,111 --> 01:03:36,874
Sorry

641
01:03:41,084 --> 01:03:42,847
Sorry

642
01:04:04,007 --> 01:04:04,996
What are you doing?

643
01:04:07,143 --> 01:04:08,940
Another in which

644
01:04:12,882 --> 01:04:14,907
why not say that the sick children,
or go to the hospital?

645
01:04:15,985 --> 01:04:17,511
why even say anything?

646
01:04:17,954 --> 01:04:19,546
sorry for your body,

647
01:04:19,989 --> 01:04:21,047
I do not care,

648
01:04:40,043 --> 01:04:41,806
Let me see,

649
01:04:43,046 --> 01:04:44,946
how can it explode?

650
01:04:47,083 --> 01:04:48,050
hoo,

651
01:04:48,685 --> 01:04:50,710
I do not know what is allowed and
should not be put in the microwave,,

652
01:04:52,021 --> 01:04:53,921
To allow him a chance to Appear,

653
01:04:57,927 --> 01:05:02,125
At first he said he ate at the stall,

654
01:05:03,099 --> 01:05:04,999
and see the song-dance on TV

655
01:05:07,871 --> 01:05:09,031
But then

656
01:05:10,106 --> 01:05:11,869
It seems he was very interested

657
01:05:12,008 --> 01:05:13,908
Wait

658
01:05:14,844 --> 01:05:15,936
Do not move

659
01:05:16,913 --> 01:05:18,005
Your face will hurt,

660
01:05:20,950 --> 01:05:23,077
Actually, the phrase
is often said

661
01:05:24,954 --> 01:05:26,922
If you feel like falling in love
then all will happen.

662
01:05:29,859 --> 01:05:30,848
Do not move

663
01:05:35,932 --> 01:05:36,990
They doing?

664
01:05:48,912 --> 01:05:49,879
Are you busy?

665
01:05:51,848 --> 01:05:52,109
I?

666
01:06:03,092 --> 01:06:04,081
I want to ask

667
01:06:06,930 --> 01:06:08,056
You really like me?

668
01:06:09,899 --> 01:06:10,888
Yes

669
01:06:14,137 --> 01:06:18,073
But we can not find out!

670
01:06:19,909 --> 01:06:21,001
I like you

671
01:06:21,878 --> 01:06:22,936
As a fan.

672
01:06:26,049 --> 01:06:27,073
Is that

673
01:06:31,921 --> 01:06:33,980
If so we, ..

674
01:06:35,297 --> 01:06:37,117
Tu, Wa, Bang, ka ..

675
01:06:40,997 --> 01:06:41,986
Cool ..

676
01:06:42,932 --> 01:06:45,901
It is a memento of my fans

677
01:06:47,070 --> 01:06:48,094
Thank you.

678
01:06:48,972 --> 01:06:51,133
No need to thank.
Can a group photo that was enough.

679
01:06:54,010 --> 01:06:55,068
Did you know?

680
01:06:56,012 --> 01:07:03,312
You were very similar to Kim Ji-hoon

681
01:07:05,021 --> 01:07:05,988
Who?

682
01:07:52,068 --> 01:07:54,036
My vote today
again not good.

683
01:07:56,105 --> 01:07:57,094
But I'll try.

684
01:08:17,994 --> 01:08:22,690
It was chaotic, with little
gross, weird lah.

685
01:08:24,901 --> 01:08:25,868
Naon?

686
01:08:25,968 --> 01:08:28,960
But I could hear
Of the original sound.

687
01:08:31,140 --> 01:08:33,005
You can sing

688
01:08:34,010 --> 01:08:38,438
Let everyone,
your voice heard.

689
01:08:57,367 --> 01:09:00,597
Why did you turn off your HP?
and go like that?

690
01:09:11,047 --> 01:09:12,014
Why?

691
01:09:15,918 --> 01:09:17,852
Because he saw it, and very angry

692
01:09:18,054 --> 01:09:19,043
It's not relevant to you both

693
01:09:19,889 --> 01:09:22,050
I do not mempermasalhkan Kim Ji-hoon

694
01:09:27,864 --> 01:09:28,956
For me, Kim Ji-hoon who?

695
01:09:29,999 --> 01:09:30,988
What do you mean?

696
01:09:31,901 --> 01:09:33,895
He is Kim Ji-hoon Lee Yoo-Jin, right?

697
01:09:35,071 --> 01:09:36,971
I do this for as
I feel a little less economy,

698
01:09:39,142 --> 01:09:41,910
But you want to use me
to replace Kim Ji-hoon's dream?

699
01:09:41,911 --> 01:09:42,878
You're crazy,

700
01:09:43,012 --> 01:09:44,070
Yes, I could be Kim Ji-hoon,

701
01:09:44,113 --> 01:09:46,877
She can sing, dance.
I am also but since you're already set.

702
01:09:48,117 --> 01:09:49,948
Will eventually die, right?

703
01:09:53,990 --> 01:09:55,848
You want to know the truth?
new

704
01:09:55,958 --> 01:09:58,018
I just need
someone to fill his position.

705
01:09:58,060 --> 01:10:00,028
happen to you the right person,

706
01:10:00,129 --> 01:10:01,892
Satisfied?

707
01:10:02,899 --> 01:10:04,924
But you know what?

708
01:10:07,870 --> 01:10:10,498
Things that are uncomfortable ..

709
01:10:14,110 --> 01:10:15,941
Some time ago ..

710
01:10:17,914 --> 01:10:20,408
He said about Kim Ji-hoon

711
01:10:23,886 --> 01:10:24,978
It .. ..

712
01:10:26,956 --> 01:10:28,856
.. I never have.

713
01:10:39,101 --> 01:10:41,001
1 position this week is ..

714
01:10:41,037 --> 01:10:42,704
Mr. children,
congratulations ...

715
01:10:43,940 --> 01:10:47,876
For 4 weeks in a row, finally
award-winning Ballad music

716
01:10:48,077 --> 01:10:51,877
Greeting directly from Mr. Kin, and we will return
with the song 'Summer Dream', do not go anywhere.

717
01:10:51,981 --> 01:10:54,006
Good-bye to You,
Do not forget next week.

718
01:11:57,146 --> 01:11:58,943
I always can never
sing well.

719
01:11:59,982 --> 01:12:02,007
Next time will not be
waste of time, right?

720
01:12:05,855 --> 01:12:08,016
I see you've
they put a rocker.

721
01:12:08,958 --> 01:12:10,926
You're doing really well there, Goo-Joo Oh

722
01:12:11,961 --> 01:12:13,385
What would you say?

723
01:12:18,000 --> 01:12:19,934
If we work together, you will shine

724
01:12:20,069 --> 01:12:21,866
You're not going to win from me.

725
01:12:22,071 --> 01:12:23,003
Now what?

726
01:12:23,339 --> 01:12:25,365
Everything now looks fine.

727
01:12:26,042 --> 01:12:28,676
Of course, I mean the 'Wonder Boys'

728
01:12:29,078 --> 01:12:30,909
Life is hard.

729
01:12:30,980 --> 01:12:33,039
Would not you know who the best?

730
01:12:34,050 --> 01:12:38,851
Is it because of that,
This child had never suffered?

731
01:12:39,922 --> 01:12:41,782
This song is so lifeless

732
01:12:41,991 --> 01:12:43,982
I've put together a team.

733
01:12:44,093 --> 01:12:46,027
You already know
strategic vision in Rock?

734
01:12:47,063 --> 01:12:51,032
Be careful, "Mr Childen'' will
difficult to adapt.

735
01:12:52,935 --> 01:12:54,903
I give you time to think.

736
01:12:55,972 --> 01:12:58,340
Indeed, they still need to practice more.

737
01:12:59,942 --> 01:13:02,903
You have done their best to "Mr Childen '

738
01:13:03,713 --> 01:13:06,773
But do not let you
sorry in the end.

739
01:13:17,093 --> 01:13:21,729
I will not give anything to you,
although the microphone is broken.

740
01:14:15,017 --> 01:14:16,075
Yoo-Jin Lee

741
01:14:16,919 --> 01:14:18,853
Please come out for clarification,

742
01:14:19,121 --> 01:14:21,055
Yoo-Jin Lee

743
01:14:23,375 --> 01:14:24,495
my opinion,

744
01:14:27,963 --> 01:14:29,188
This garbage

745
01:14:30,200 --> 01:14:32,594
I saw you just
we use as entertainment.

746
01:14:33,135 --> 01:14:35,103
Music is not competition, but

747
01:14:36,539 --> 01:14:38,530
To cheer the sad soul.

748
01:14:39,041 --> 01:14:40,872
Video of this statement
was spread on the Internet and television.

749
01:14:40,943 --> 01:14:44,037
Authorities
was trying to prevent it.

750
01:14:44,080 --> 01:14:45,945
So that this does not continue to spread

751
01:14:46,115 --> 01:14:47,878
Responsible party television said,

752
01:14:48,017 --> 01:14:51,148
Will cut its repertoire.

753
01:14:52,021 --> 01:14:54,988
At the same time 'Mr. Children' is certainly not
will appear next few months

754
01:14:54,990 --> 01:14:57,049
Music awards
ballad was canceled.

755
01:14:57,927 --> 01:14:59,895
Lee Yoo-Jin is
companies 'Champion'

756
01:14:59,995 --> 01:15:02,754
Unofficially voiced this to the media.

757
01:15:07,069 --> 01:15:11,062
Our advertising revenue decline

758
01:15:11,941 --> 01:15:14,067
I have scolded the head section.

759
01:15:15,445 --> 01:15:18,038
The better the artist,
the greater our income.

760
01:15:20,916 --> 01:15:21,974
So, this time

761
01:15:22,852 --> 01:15:24,979
You have to cancel the operation
and the rest of this week

762
01:15:25,020 --> 01:15:26,920
Let me check the truth.

763
01:15:27,890 --> 01:15:28,914
I will solve all problems.

764
01:15:30,993 --> 01:15:32,051
Give me time

765
01:15:33,829 --> 01:15:34,853
Goo Joo-Oh

766
01:15:37,967 --> 01:15:39,025
Sorry

767
01:15:53,749 --> 01:15:55,607
Goo-Joo, could have a word?

768
01:15:55,951 --> 01:15:57,518
Everything will be fine.

769
01:16:02,858 --> 01:16:03,985
I'll try ..

770
01:16:04,059 --> 01:16:05,283
I do not do this

771
01:16:06,929 --> 01:16:07,896
Really?

772
01:16:07,997 --> 01:16:09,021
Then who?

773
01:16:10,132 --> 01:16:12,965
Explain to me.

774
01:16:12,968 --> 01:16:14,868
At that

775
01:16:17,139 --> 01:16:18,071
Just me

776
01:16:18,074 --> 01:16:20,032
Even now he says?

777
01:16:20,042 --> 01:16:22,507
This will not change anything

778
01:16:31,887 --> 01:16:32,854
Yoo-Jin Lee

779
01:16:33,889 --> 01:16:35,914
Is a member of the team
which is fine.

780
01:16:36,091 --> 01:16:38,025
Clip this controversial issue ..

781
01:16:38,961 --> 01:16:40,019
Regardless of the cause.

782
01:16:40,896 --> 01:16:42,864
Only because of juvenile delinquency.

783
01:16:42,965 --> 01:16:44,956
Affecting young people
To act ...

784
01:16:45,034 --> 01:16:46,968
Makes many people angry

785
01:16:47,903 --> 01:16:48,927
We are here for this

786
01:16:49,505 --> 01:16:51,897
On behalf of Yoo Jin Lee,
inner and outer apologize.

787
01:16:51,941 --> 01:16:52,873
Please ask any questions.

788
01:16:53,108 --> 01:16:54,075
There is the question

789
01:16:54,477 --> 01:16:56,435
Please, Lee Yoo-Jin story
do they really?

790
01:16:56,979 --> 01:16:57,946
Not

791
01:16:58,047 --> 01:17:00,838
Is it true that there will be selection
New members?

792
01:17:00,916 --> 01:17:01,974
Of course not.

793
01:17:02,051 --> 01:17:03,848
So how do members
group dealing with this?

794
01:17:04,053 --> 01:17:07,879
Jio reportedly been
involved in violence in America?

795
01:17:07,957 --> 01:17:10,248
And 2 times of persecution in this country?

796
01:17:10,859 --> 01:17:12,918
Ricky has two international criminal
citizenship, and illegal immigration?

797
01:17:13,062 --> 01:17:16,122
Hyun Yi makes boyfriend
pregnant, right?

798
01:17:16,932 --> 01:17:19,493
Now all members of the group
has changed from before.

799
01:17:19,902 --> 01:17:22,871
If by chance

800
01:17:22,972 --> 01:17:25,907
Do you have a way to
help them through it?

801
01:17:26,875 --> 01:17:28,103
The fans are very angry

802
01:17:28,911 --> 01:17:31,880
Many found the negative facts
of members of the group.

803
01:17:32,047 --> 01:17:33,912
I think Social Matters
Council has given special attention

804
01:17:34,917 --> 01:17:37,010
The soul is not entertainment
to improve life.

805
01:17:37,119 --> 01:17:38,848
Well ..

806
01:17:38,954 --> 01:17:40,012
If the reporter is saying ..

807
01:17:40,122 --> 01:17:41,054
A little too exaggerated ..

808
01:17:41,890 --> 01:17:42,914
I agree.

809
01:17:43,926 --> 01:17:45,018
What he said was true.

810
01:17:47,830 --> 01:17:50,799
So "Mr. Children" began to sing

811
01:17:51,967 --> 01:17:56,295
Because they can,
only for this reason alone.

812
01:17:56,839 --> 01:18:00,798
Singing and dancing can relieve
suffering in life.

813
01:18:01,110 --> 01:18:02,941
Realize a dream.

814
01:18:03,112 --> 01:18:05,080
Then what is the purpose of all this?

815
01:18:06,048 --> 01:18:07,845
Sing 100 thousand times

816
01:18:08,017 --> 01:18:09,882
It can not change the past.

817
01:18:10,085 --> 01:18:11,848
But at least

818
01:18:12,054 --> 01:18:16,222
They have devoted their ..
With singing and dancing.

819
01:18:16,257 --> 01:18:20,827
Gossip of his, one member
not yet recovered from a broken heart?

820
01:18:21,030 --> 01:18:22,964
Shucks, Emanya you know what?

821
01:18:25,000 --> 01:18:26,358
All my fault?

822
01:18:26,402 --> 01:18:27,969
So would you?

823
01:18:28,037 --> 01:18:28,969
Enough

824
01:18:33,042 --> 01:18:34,031
Yoo Jin

825
01:18:38,047 --> 01:18:39,947
All this is my fault.

826
01:18:41,850 --> 01:18:42,942
If for me,

827
01:18:44,019 --> 01:18:47,919
Causing chaos on the other members

828
01:18:49,855 --> 01:18:51,720
If for I
so we do not gig anymore,

829
01:18:51,892 --> 01:18:53,252
So I ...

830
01:18:55,674 --> 01:18:57,794
Resigned from the state .. "Mr Childen".

831
01:18:59,902 --> 01:19:02,029
Are there any auditions new members?

832
01:19:02,104 --> 01:19:03,969
After leaving the group,
is there any other plans, Yoo-Jin?

833
01:19:04,006 --> 01:19:04,973
He would do it right?

834
01:19:04,973 --> 01:19:06,941
Maybe he did not think
the other members?

835
01:19:08,010 --> 01:19:08,942
Yoo Jin

836
01:19:09,912 --> 01:19:10,879
Yoo Jin

837
01:19:11,046 --> 01:19:11,978
Yoo Jin

838
01:19:13,949 --> 01:19:15,075
Now she is very worried right?

839
01:19:29,131 --> 01:19:31,861
'Wonder Boys' managed to sell
more than 300 thousand pieces of tape.

840
01:19:31,967 --> 01:19:33,935
New record.

841
01:19:34,103 --> 01:19:36,094
This afternoon they had a party.

842
01:19:37,906 --> 01:19:39,032
'Wonder Boys' and ...

843
01:20:03,031 --> 01:20:03,998
What's this?

844
01:20:04,900 --> 01:20:05,889
Seafood Pasta

845
01:20:15,544 --> 01:20:16,711
Good baseball.

846
01:20:17,112 --> 01:20:18,044
Really nice.

847
01:20:26,121 --> 01:20:27,884
What is your plan then?

848
01:20:28,957 --> 01:20:33,183
All parents care about their children.

849
01:20:34,997 --> 01:20:38,431
I do not have a plan
excessive for this pub?

850
01:20:41,003 --> 01:20:43,096
Look at my face this time,
I was strangely delicious bread

851
01:20:44,907 --> 01:20:47,000
I want to make good food,
so it is always my first taste that customers are satisfied.

852
01:20:47,109 --> 01:20:49,907
Do new things well,
other things will also improve.

853
01:20:52,114 --> 01:20:53,945
I'm always smiling.

854
01:20:56,952 --> 01:20:59,819
If the kids are eating it,
happy.

855
01:20:59,922 --> 01:21:00,889
See delicious

856
01:21:01,023 --> 01:21:03,082
Parents and children smile.

857
01:21:10,966 --> 01:21:13,500
People are strange.

858
01:22:37,052 --> 01:22:38,849
Having decided to quit.

859
01:22:40,088 --> 01:22:41,851
you choose this place?

860
01:22:43,992 --> 01:22:45,016
I want to ask?

861
01:22:46,929 --> 01:22:50,992
Do you want to join
again with "Mr Childen '?

862
01:22:52,034 --> 01:22:53,058
This place ..

863
01:22:54,937 --> 01:22:55,995
Right for me ..

864
01:22:57,005 --> 01:22:58,097
Not that you have a dream?

865
01:23:00,008 --> 01:23:00,997
yes

866
01:23:01,977 --> 01:23:03,069
So what?

867
01:23:03,979 --> 01:23:05,105
Now it no longer.

868
01:23:07,983 --> 01:23:09,542
I can not ...

869
01:23:10,935 --> 01:23:13,155
.. To do it again.

870
01:23:31,073 --> 01:23:32,097
Others also have come out.

871
01:23:34,042 --> 01:23:35,805
What did I do wrong?

872
01:23:38,113 --> 01:23:40,381
I would not expect them again.

873
01:23:40,916 --> 01:23:42,816
No point in us doing it.

874
01:23:45,053 --> 01:23:46,020
Goo-Joo!

875
01:23:47,122 --> 01:23:49,022
We can no longer expect
Mr. Children.

876
01:23:51,927 --> 01:23:53,895
Why do not we form a Girl Band?

877
01:23:54,963 --> 01:23:56,897
I'll take care,
I've made light music.

878
01:24:01,103 --> 01:24:03,797
Singing makes one's heart sick,

879
01:24:05,156 --> 01:24:07,256
I'm sick of all this.

880
01:24:08,844 --> 01:24:11,409
Although left out of necessity ..

881
01:24:12,981 --> 01:24:16,040
But .. there is no reason,
to stay!

882
01:24:22,491 --> 01:24:23,958
Want a drink?

883
01:24:30,899 --> 01:24:31,866
-There I have to say.
-What would you say?

884
01:24:33,969 --> 01:24:35,893
He said before leaving!

885
01:24:36,905 --> 01:24:39,900
But the way we
go is not the same

886
01:24:39,941 --> 01:24:41,633
The aim although the same place.

887
01:24:42,944 --> 01:24:47,072
If you want to say?
Do not beat around the bush anymore, just say so!

888
01:24:47,249 --> 01:24:48,707
Huh ..
.. That I wanted to say is ...

889
01:24:52,988 --> 01:24:54,480
Make life more lightly!

890
01:24:55,924 --> 01:24:56,948
Do you want to die?

891
01:24:57,893 --> 01:24:59,986
Not dead,,!

892
01:25:01,863 --> 01:25:03,091
My intent is ..
I want to live with you.

893
01:25:37,499 --> 01:25:39,023
Listen to this, Yoo Jin

894
01:25:41,069 --> 01:25:43,037
Hope you like it ..

895
01:25:43,339 --> 01:25:46,532
I made this song,
overview of anger ..

896
01:25:47,943 --> 01:25:49,401
I understand now.

897
01:25:49,578 --> 01:25:51,172
Listen to this song.

898
01:25:53,048 --> 01:25:54,913
Will the latest singgle.

899
01:25:55,884 --> 01:25:57,044
Stay by my side.

900
01:25:58,086 --> 01:26:00,953
I also hope you will like it.

901
01:26:02,057 --> 01:26:03,888
Yoo Jin, then how your decisions?

902
01:26:05,994 --> 01:26:06,961
Yoo Jin à

903
01:26:09,064 --> 01:26:11,264
Go, go.

904
01:26:12,668 --> 01:26:14,596
He's waiting for you to come back.

905
01:26:35,023 --> 01:26:35,990
Yoo Jin back?

906
01:26:36,124 --> 01:26:38,991
What happened?

907
01:26:40,061 --> 01:26:41,050
The others in?

908
01:26:42,030 --> 01:26:45,124
They're fine, free ...

909
01:26:45,901 --> 01:26:47,835
I also do not know where to go.

910
01:26:47,936 --> 01:26:48,960
Goo Joo to the airport.

911
01:26:50,071 --> 01:26:51,003
Yo ..

912
01:26:55,043 --> 01:26:57,978
Yoo-jin ah, What is it?

913
01:26:58,046 --> 01:27:00,844
There are posts for Goo Joo Oh.

914
01:27:01,016 --> 01:27:01,983
Goo Joo?

915
01:27:03,885 --> 01:27:07,878
No. 482-21, Yan Hau Park Lane, Bell Road, Second City "Star Music"
Goo Joo oh.
"Received"

916
01:27:14,530 --> 01:27:16,028
Remove the Eike ..

917
01:27:16,031 --> 01:27:16,963
Sang Sik

918
01:27:21,937 --> 01:27:24,929
Oops ... You want to die ..?

919
01:27:25,073 --> 01:27:28,065
If you let go of my hand, I would die.

920
01:27:28,877 --> 01:27:30,037
Do Dong.

921
01:27:32,981 --> 01:27:33,948
Yun's à

922
01:27:34,950 --> 01:27:36,574
Me please help me.

923
01:27:40,889 --> 01:27:42,583
Yoo-jin Well, I'll call the others.

924
01:27:42,591 --> 01:27:43,649
You know the DC-based PD.

925
01:27:44,059 --> 01:27:46,084
The song of war,
on the night of the festival, you know?

926
01:28:15,257 --> 01:28:16,924
Are you here?

927
01:30:19,381 --> 01:30:20,348
Standards.

928
01:30:21,082 --> 01:30:24,108
Penjiwaanya less,
It makes people tired.

929
01:30:26,021 --> 01:30:27,045
Even the very standard.

930
01:30:29,311 --> 01:30:30,711
Sotoe.

931
01:30:41,036 --> 01:30:42,094
Where my motor?

932
01:30:53,081 --> 01:30:54,844
Was prepared.

933
01:31:07,128 --> 01:31:08,026
See this

934
01:31:13,574 --> 01:31:14,774
What's this?

935
01:31:15,036 --> 01:31:17,427
Do you have comments about this song
that raises the spirit?

936
01:31:17,906 --> 01:31:19,095
Which raises the spirit of the fans.

937
01:31:19,140 --> 01:31:21,908
Make me do,
I've never done.

938
01:31:22,877 --> 01:31:26,238
What are your plans for
was so successful?

939
01:31:26,848 --> 01:31:28,008
Personally I see,
you're just wasting time.

940
01:31:28,950 --> 01:31:29,917
It's rubbish

941
01:31:31,986 --> 01:31:33,817
I saw you just
we use as entertainment.

942
01:31:34,022 --> 01:31:35,080
However

943
01:31:36,057 --> 01:31:37,991
Music is not competition, but

944
01:31:38,927 --> 01:31:39,985
But to comfort the sad soul.

945
01:31:40,929 --> 01:31:41,953
It seems you're too honest.

946
01:31:43,865 --> 01:31:44,957
The next question ...

947
01:31:45,066 --> 01:31:48,934
Show, Show, Show, ..
Show ... Time à ..

948
01:31:49,938 --> 01:31:51,929
Hello all,
our 'brave girl'

949
01:31:55,977 --> 01:31:58,844
Today, we came here for
to enjoy this show.

950
01:31:58,947 --> 01:31:59,936
Today people would say the winner.

951
01:32:00,048 --> 01:32:01,106
Today we are happy,
We've tried.

952
01:32:01,883 --> 01:32:03,009
We are the 'Wonder Boys'

953
01:32:09,924 --> 01:32:10,891
Om, where they

954
01:32:12,060 --> 01:32:12,924
You are ...

955
01:32:13,862 --> 01:32:14,886
Newcomers ...?

956
01:32:14,996 --> 01:32:18,989
No, I represent 'music star'

957
01:32:19,901 --> 01:32:20,993
Yoo Jin Lee, do you hear?

958
01:32:22,103 --> 01:32:23,866
About the video ..

959
01:32:24,105 --> 01:32:25,902
That was in engineering
and the video was edited.

960
01:32:26,141 --> 01:32:27,039
So today

961
01:32:28,910 --> 01:32:30,935
I want people to see Mr. Children

962
01:32:31,045 --> 01:32:32,876
Returned to the stage

963
01:32:34,983 --> 01:32:36,917
It turned out that way ..

964
01:32:37,085 --> 01:32:38,848
So finally they are invited

965
01:32:38,920 --> 01:32:39,887
Say a few words.

966
01:32:43,024 --> 01:32:43,922
All,

967
01:32:44,058 --> 01:32:45,847
With so to come soon.

968
01:32:45,894 --> 01:32:48,955
Jio, Hyun Yi, Rickey

969
01:32:49,030 --> 01:32:49,962
Yoo Jin.

970
01:32:50,098 --> 01:32:51,995
Not have to change clothes,
here there are many.

971
01:32:52,000 --> 01:32:54,935
There are yet too late, jammed the streets again,
So do not drive.

972
01:32:55,069 --> 01:32:56,036
Take the train alone.

973
01:32:56,137 --> 01:32:57,900
Hurry, hurry.

974
01:32:58,039 --> 01:32:58,971
I beg of you.

975
01:32:59,140 --> 01:33:01,537
A good time was, this was it.

976
01:34:21,788 --> 01:34:23,813
Still yet to come?

977
01:34:31,899 --> 01:34:32,957
Now ..
The time is ...

978
01:34:33,968 --> 01:34:34,935
Almost Start.

979
01:34:35,003 --> 01:34:35,992
If they do not come within 5 minutes.

980
01:34:36,871 --> 01:34:37,929
The event will be a mess.

981
01:34:44,447 --> 01:34:45,467
Jio ..

982
01:34:45,913 --> 01:34:47,813
Just ... only 1 person only?

983
01:34:49,451 --> 01:34:50,509
Hyun Yi

984
01:34:51,953 --> 01:34:52,920
Late train.

985
01:34:53,054 --> 01:34:54,021
So have to wait.

986
01:34:56,090 --> 01:34:57,955
Rickey

987
01:36:19,574 --> 01:36:21,101
He's not going to come ..

988
01:36:22,043 --> 01:36:22,907
Yahh ..

989
01:36:24,011 --> 01:36:25,509
Emang think our fate ...

990
01:36:26,948 --> 01:36:29,040
No ... it can achieve a dream.

991
01:36:55,109 --> 01:36:56,976
Do you ..

992
01:36:57,245 --> 01:36:58,506
Who's kidding ...?

993
01:37:08,890 --> 01:37:09,822
Show them

994
01:37:10,057 --> 01:37:11,820
How about trying on the stage.

995
01:37:15,096 --> 01:37:16,859
Singing my heart.

996
01:38:03,911 --> 01:38:05,405
See the rankings while ..

997
01:38:05,713 --> 01:38:07,605
.. 'Wonder Boys' is still at the top.

998
01:38:07,982 --> 01:38:08,846
Now ..

999
01:38:08,983 --> 01:38:10,951
We call the new group ..

1000
01:38:11,118 --> 01:38:12,949
Bringing new wind ..

1001
01:38:13,120 --> 01:38:14,883
Boy band is ..

1002
01:38:15,022 --> 01:38:16,922
"Mr. Children"

1003
01:38:16,991 --> 01:38:17,923
"Summer Dream"

1004
01:38:32,139 --> 01:38:33,071
Hello all.

1005
01:38:34,942 --> 01:38:36,876
I'm Lee Yoo Jin of "Mr. Children"

1006
01:38:39,847 --> 01:38:41,109
I want to talk briefly.

1007
01:38:43,017 --> 01:38:44,985
I was not a good singer ..

1008
01:38:46,854 --> 01:38:47,980
That is why ..

1009
01:38:48,956 --> 01:38:50,614
I'm sorry.

1010
01:38:51,092 --> 01:38:51,990
Well ..

1011
01:38:54,028 --> 01:38:55,825
Now I know ..

1012
01:38:56,998 --> 01:38:58,898
When I sing ..
if I feel comfortable ..

1013
01:38:59,667 --> 01:39:02,227
Then others should be happy ..

1014
01:39:02,470 --> 01:39:04,394
That is real music ..

1015
01:39:05,873 --> 01:39:07,299
I understand all this ..

1016
01:39:08,876 --> 01:39:11,104
Of members of the "Mr. Children" others ..

1017
01:39:12,113 --> 01:39:14,843
Also one more person,
Who always support us ..

1018
01:43:41,148 --> 01:43:42,311
Video of Lee Yoo Jin

1019
01:43:42,583 --> 01:43:43,874
This is because you are doing ..

1020
01:43:43,985 --> 01:43:45,374
Could you comment on this incident ..

1021
01:43:45,987 --> 01:43:47,014
So here goes ..

1022
01:43:48,055 --> 01:43:49,079
All right.

1023
01:43:50,958 --> 01:43:53,184
I announced at the procuracy and ..

1024
01:43:56,096 --> 01:43:58,929
You do not want Lee Yoo Jin be the star?

1025
01:43:59,033 --> 01:44:01,900
Again and again I say,
My music is not like this ..

1026
01:44:02,102 --> 01:44:03,000
This

1027
01:44:04,104 --> 01:44:05,969
See how the expression of mu ..

1028
01:44:06,907 --> 01:44:08,966
What's the expression?
I want something new ..

1029
01:44:09,043 --> 01:44:10,032
Want to die?

1030
01:44:13,047 --> 01:44:14,071
Ja Jagain my suitcase ..

1031
01:44:49,083 --> 01:44:52,052
Some people do not? ...
I just want to grab a suitcase ..

1032
01:49:20,021 --> 01:49:25,721
Mr. Idol