Cinergy house 8 Lotte Entertainment
Presents
Distributed by
Cinergy house 8 Lotte Entertainment
Produced by
Daisy Entertainment
International Sales by
Showbox / Mediaplex
You say goodbye.
But your eyes seem painful...
So you wanna retire quite early.
Aren't you?
Ji-hoon.
What is this?
Do you love her?
You?
You and her?
You two will not be seen
in one place, you got it?
- Let's hear what they have to say.
- No!
It was a one-time thing.
It'll not happen again.
Ji-hoon!
Open the door!
Are you gonna let some girl
ruin your career?
I don't know.
This was my dream.
I've tried so hard for this.
But now i don't know.
Think about the other members.
And the stage.
It was all a lie.
He's not in a condition
to go on a stage.
- Give him some time and...
- And what?
You know the answer.
Just put them on stage.
Mr. Children's Showcase, 20O8
MR. IDOL
Three years later
Welcome, O Gu-ju.
You're gonna find the bag
in the lost and found.
Hello, we're Wonder Boys!
We'll hold a showcase right away
after the audition.
Of course, the audition is part of PR.
Take off the headphone.
Spit the gum.
Get out.
We're Wonder Boys!
Where's Mr. Children?
I came to see them.
Sign this.
You'll be a director
and a shareholder.
We can't sell Mr. Children.
They're out of date.
Well, i totally understand.
You've been alienated for long.
It's gonna be much easier than
Mr. Children.
Just try half as hard.
Then i'll do the rest.
You mean Mr. Children
doesn't get second chance?
After you left, l had to work
my ass o for 3 years.
It was a nightmare!
Money doesn't grow on trees.
I can't make any money
with them.
It wasn't their fault.
So they didn't pay
bust-up fees.
Send me a document
proving the breach of contract.
From now on,
I'll work with Mr. Children.
It's losing game.
You're gonna be tapped out.
- Do as i say, it's better...
- No thanks.
I'll work on my own.
Are you throwing
down the gauntlet?
You didn't know?
I've already started the game.
Are you leaving for real?
Do you have a plan?
Find the members
and set an office.
Think again.
You could lose big.
Listen!
He's not the same man
you used to know.
Alright.
See you soon.
Yeah, see you soon...
But it's better for me
to stay here.
Hey!
You never listen!
What is that?
I don't know.
What should we do?
What's the problem?
Just take it with you.
Oh, my god.
I see a disaster and illness.
You can't change your fate,
but you can change the future.
You need a strong will
and preparation, right?
What kind of preparation?
Is it okay if i give you
some advice?
Of course it is.
It's not like any other insurance.
You only need to pay...
What are you doing?
How much do we have
to pay for nursery school?
How about home schooling
her myself?
Then she would have
even less friend than now.
I'll pay the bills, later.
Debt Repayment Reminder
You think about medical bills.
A suitcase?
Don't open it.
Why not?
I have to find the owner.
Your fate changes
once you open that bag.
It is? Then l really
have to open it.
I told you not to touch it.
I didn't open it.
It opened itself.
Eun-Seo?
She's not sleeping?
Let me talk to her.
No, she's sleeping.
Hello?
Did you steal my bag?
Not me.
Someone wants to talk to you.
The king lived here, right?
- Where are you?
- I'm going up.
You have to come up some more.
More?
I think you'll be here.
Can't you see me?
No, nothing.
Put your hands up.
What the...
The bag!
Get the bag.
Me?
I can't.
Help me!
Hey, you got old.
I have two kids.
It's not surprising.
Oh, yes.
You got married again.
Yes, i did.
And they died.
Why?
Stop following me!
Where's the emergency...?
There he is.
He's fine.
I told you to be careful!
I had a bad dream.
We're here.
My friend needs money.
So i bought it at a fair price
for quick sale.
You can sleep and work in here.
You can do literally
everything in here.
You see, some years ago...
This was a room
for many champions.
Hey, i understand.
This is one lousy office.
But the rent fee is so cheap.
You don't have money, right?
I like it.
Our next guest is JEONG Im-bok,
adopted to Canada in 1986.
- Thank you for coming.
- Hello.
If you have some memory
of that time, please tell us.
I remember a lamppost
in an alley.
I was three years old.
And l was playing with a girl.
Huh?
Ms. O?
I miss the time.
If you ever feel sad...
You want me to dance?
I can't even lift a baby for long.
Hyun, clean room no. 5!
What are you doing?
you lazy ass!
I want to dance again.
Stop it!
I'm sick of you.
It's over.
Jio.
Oh, you all came!
What's this place?
Do you do boxing?
No, it's for you.
It'll be a good dancing floor.
Do we have a lead singer?
A singer who will
dump us again?
Jio, don't say...
Anyway, i'm happy to
see you guys together.
Remember HWANG?
You'll perform in his show.
Have you talked to him?
No, you make an arrangement.
President PARK.
President PARK?
Who, me?
I handed in your resignation.
Letter of Resignation
O Gu-ju and PARK Sang-sik
You little...
President PARK?
A Cottage on a Grassland
I wish my words
stay in your heart
like an old picture.
Knock it out.
I'm having a conversation here.
We're going on an audition
this Saturday.
I feel good about it.
I bought your outfits.
Look, they're expensive!
So don't expect your back pay.
- No way!
- Hey, guys.
If you do well in audition
and become a star...
I'm giving you loads of
money.
Believe me boys.
You all wear size 100.
I mean, even your sizes
prove you're a team!
- You don't feel it?
- I don't feel it.
I'm a loner.
Don't you love me?
What i can do?
We're looking for boys.
Ok, but we'll just do it.
Mimicking
Will you marry me?
Where are all the good ones?
Mr. SA has set his audition
on the same time as ours.
I will not say that i am sorry.
Next!
Are you the member?
I'm the manager.
What are you doing here?
Are you a team?
- We're the underground band.
- ''Rebel Without a Cause.''
Start.
I wish my words
sink into you
and touch your heart.
Stop!
You want stronger beat?
Faster?
Solo.
We're okay.
The sound of a warm breeze.
Comes to me and comforts me.
I feel sweet.
Happy as in a dream.
I can smile because of you.
Summer dream.
The sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
It may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
He's out of breath.
What a mantrap.
You suck.
Poor, rough and dull.
You're self-indulgent.
There's just your voice.
But i can hear it.
You can't be a star
unless you work with me.
Only me?
Isn't it a band audition?
Why do you say like that?
We need a lead singer.
We need a singer
for an idol pop group.
I won't do it.
As you can see,
we are a band.
Hope you find the right one.
I'm going to take a train
and go to the countryside.
You know, l always
wanted to be a farmer.
Band without a bassist?
Are you leaving too?
I had a job interview,
yesterday.
My girlfriend wants me
to work at some company.
Her father runs it.
Come on!!
We rebel without a cause,
not betray without a cause!
Eat when it's hot.
Excuse me.
I don't understand.
Why is hers and mine
so different in quantity?
She's a regular.
I see.
Run as fast as you can,
little boy.
If you look back now,
you will give up...
He is a freelance worker
doing several jobs.
A coffee shop part-timer,
a chauffeur and a performer.
You know, he was
a trainee in Star Music.
SA wanted to make a band
few years ago, remember?
He was kicked out
for his bad attitude.
Caramel Macchiato.
Work with me.
Here.
You're born to be a singer.
How much?
Work with me!
Hello, where should i go?
Miss...
Tunnel No.1.
Are you stalking me?
Stop following me around.
- Hello
- Eugene...
i'll pay the bills
at the end of the month.
I said i'll pay!
Alright, I'll talk to the director.
it will be better
begging for mercy.
What?
You’re telling me to beg?
I don't like it, here.
Let's go to another hospital!
We don't have
anywhere else to go.
You should pay right now,
or leave the room, got it?
Please, i beg you.
Let it go just this once.
24-months installment.
Who are you?
I don't want your charity.
Are you always like that?
You are in a 24-month
contract with me.
I will pay back for 2 years
on bank interest.
Pay in a lump sum.
- Are you a loan shark?
- Yes, from now on.
What do you want from me?
You’re gonna make me a singer?
Can you promise that?
Depends on you.
Star Music.
I'm gonna bust Mr. SA.
When the cool breeze blows,
please remember
that i was with you.
You are quite naive
than i thought.
They don't sell.
I just know it.
They're out of trend.
National television is not a joke.
It's not for some rubbish studio.
The answer is no.
Do not speak!
You wasted my time.
I don't understand.
Why do we have to leave?
You are just not
what Koreans want now.
People don't want to
listen to your song.
Anyway, you have to accept
that you resigned voluntarily.
That's the most important.
You got it?
Is he coming or not?
I can replace him.
I practiced a lot
in my karaoke.
This is not the 80s.
Boy groups should
have 4 members at least.
I quit.
It's a gift.
Good luck with your business.
I dropped by just to
have a talk with you.
Four minutes late.
4,000 jumps.
Good!
Go!
Faster!
Who are we?
A national team
for the Olympic?
I'm a national team
for Korean music!
This is the first step of dancing.
If you can do it,
you can do any movement.
You can't dance,
if you can't do it.
See? I can't do it.
Because i'm not an Idol.
But you should do it.
I'm a rapper.
Rappers don't dance.
Why do i have to do it?
- Is it hard?
- Yes.
I never give up.
I never stop.
I'm a warrior.
Nothing can stop me.
He's a lousy dancer.
You have a week to
make him dance like you.
I don't wanna be an Idol!
I want to go home!
Let me go!
Catch him!
Seaweed rice roll.
Pork sausage soup.
Roasted beef rib...
Want it so much...
Ricky is hungry.
- The waves...
- Again!
- for my dream...
for my dream...
- forever...
- Again!
Do it again.
The soft sound of the waves.
But your voice is sweeter.
Let's do the final rehearsal.
What do we do
after a final rehearsal?
Your debut.
Don't crease it unless
you wanna pay for them.
I borrowed them from
a designer boutique.
Don't look at the stars,
be one.
Who said that?
I did.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
Cut!
Let's do it again.
Don't look at the camera.
- We will stay together.
- Cut!
Don't look at the camera,
will ya?
- feel your dream...
- Cut, Cut!
I said don't look!
Take a break.
Wonder Boys, come up.
Come back to me.
Their look and song are
really different from us.
I'm ravaged.
Without you,
I'm ruined.
It's so hard to live
without you.
I am a fool
and i hate myself.
I'm ravaged.
Can we take a break?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Come on!
- I could have tripped over.
Do it properly.
What's your problem?
Hey, stop!
Let it go.
Guys, you're younger.
I can't believe my eyes.
They are real 'wild idols'.
Aren't they?
Let's go.
Pack your things.
What?
What about the show?
You're not a team.
What do you mean?
They are a team.
I won't let you debut
like this.
Mom, do you remember me?
- I'm Imbok, mom...
- Are you separated?
- You surprised me.
- Looking for your mom?
PARK said i can find mom
if i become a star.
So have you written that?
Then, make it into a rap.
You're good at it.
Mommy, remember me?
It's Imbok?
No.
Mommy, remember me?
It's Imbok.
Keep going.
Mommy, remember me?
It's Imbok.
I became a star for you.
I want to meet you.
What a moron.
One octopus is missing.
Thank you, Wonder Boys.
Brave Girls, please come up.
The winner of this week is,
Wonder Boys!
Congratulations!
Now, you can perform
at the Music Festival.
Mr. HWANG!
It's been a long time.
l was saying...
Oh, you came early.
A personal problem?
What do you mean?
Star Music is doing that
because we...
Hello?
Was it cut o, again?
Yes, i see.
So have you talked to
the producer? Hello?
You know Ms. O, right?
You can trust us!
Hello?
Don't hang up!
We have to pay for the rent.
My credit card is maxed-out.
But we can't perform
in nightclubs for money.
Hello?
Oh, Mr. HONG.
Nightclub?
Oh, they can't.
Can't do it.
Hold on, please.
Please help me.
I have to earn a crust.
I have worked so hard.
I have tried so hard.
We starved and pushed a car.
Is this what we get?
You are nothing.
Just do what you're told to.
I need a toilet...
What has he eaten?
It's been so long.
My dear friend, PARK!
I'm happy to see you.
I didn't think you'd come.
Are you a back-up dancer?
Or a back-up singer?
No, she is a producer,
O Gu-ju.
He's a friend of mine.
You remember?
A producer?
I'm a singer-songwriter,
HONG Gil-dong.
Same as the hero.
We'll dream forever.
Summer Dream.
Let's take itto the top.
Close your eyes and imagine it.
It's gonna be okay.
Hold back your tears.
Spread your wings
and fly high.
A bright future is
waiting for us.
Five women are standing here.
And the members of
Mr. Children are behind them.
The women have to
seduce their partners.
Start the music!
Feel it, guys!
You are doing great.
But this one is too old
to be children.
He hid his face with
a sunglass.
Who will be the winner?
Yes, good.
Oh, she got water bottles.
Are you gonna pour it on me?
Oh, she's poured it
on herself.
Why are you coming to me?
Alright, good.
I am all wet.
From now on,
show your best dance moves
for 10 seconds!
A CEO of Nightclub Middle-Aged.
Electrocuted.
My skin was burning...
Damn it.
Mr. Children, boy group.
I could smell
something burning.
I saw him shaking, and...
Do you have something
to say?
You look better in television.
Anyway, we made a TV debut.
Yo, baby.
Why do they play classics?
I like Wonder Boys.
Let's go to see them
when my hair grows.
We have a surgery next week.
How about i ask them
to come here?
Alright, we will.
The soft sound of the waves.
But your voice is sweeeeee......
What's the noise..
Speaker seems to be broken..
I'm sorry.
Wait a second.
The Red Cross Medical Center
The soft sound of the waves.
But your voice is sweeter.
Come closer.
We will go together.
And make a dream come true.
The sound of a warm breeze.
Comes to me and comforts me.
I feel sweet.
Happy as in a dream.
I can smile because of you.
Summer dream.
It's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
It may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
Center for the Sight and
Hearing Impaired
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Hogye Center for Teenagers
Mr. Children Concert
Public Health Center
Summer dream.
It's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
It may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Let's take it to the top.
Close your eyes and imagine it.
Spread your wings
and fly high.
It's gonna be okay.
Hold back your tears.
A bright future is
waiting for us.
Summer dream.
It's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
lt may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Summer dream.
You have to be in school.
Are you playing hooky?
It's a lunch break.
Hey, look.
It's a rainbow.
You're right.
How about shaving your face?
I can't
Why?
It's a rocker thing.
I feel anxious.
Can't find peace of mind.
I think of you
all the time.
The sound of a warm breeze.
Comes to me and comforts me.
I feel sweet.
Happy as in a dream.
- Calm down, please.
- Stay away.
Dad!
You say you're a dancer?
You can't even dodge.
You told me going to China
to be a tourist guide.
If you're gonna be singer,
I'll never see you again!
Why didn't you
give up music?
After you got kicked out
from Star Music.
- It's my dream.
- Dream?
Dreams never come true.
Are you always poker-faced?
You're a person, not a robot.
I'm a robot.
I guess you haven't
had any relationship.
I've dated 5 Michaels
when i was abroad.
- I'm offended.
- You're lying.
People say...
you hear a chime bell
when you kiss someone?
That could be
the death bell.
Are you crazy?
I can't feel anything.
I really want Mr. Children
to come to my school!
Horse Chestnut Park
The most expected
boy group of the year!
Mr. Children!
Summer Dream.
Ranked 34th this Week
Hongdae Performing Stage
Vocal Hyun
Dancer Jio
Rapper Ricky
Leader Eugene
Nominated for the winner
one month after a debut!
on August.
The winner is,
Mr. Children.
Cheers!
31st of December.
The Music festival!
lt's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
Those boys are too skinny.
Just like a skeleton.
Can't understand them.
I can't understand you.
You haven't changed.
I missed you.
Always.
I missed you, too.
Mommy.
Mommy, remember me?
It's Imbok.
I became a star for you.
I want to meet you.
Where are you? I miss you.
Come to me. I'm right here.
Don't be sorry.
I'm here, look at me.
You're my life.
I miss you. I love you.
That's it.
Is that what you call
the long-waited reunion?
I think they love
each other too much.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
What're you doing?
Where's the others?
You should've called me,
or go to a hospital.
Just sitting here
like a child!
l'm fine.
Let me see.
Didn't you know
it would explode?
No.
They are things you shouldn't
put in a microwave.
Shut up.
When l first met you,
you said you don't want to
perform or talk on TV show.
But you look happy now.
Hey, don't move.
You'll get hurt.
You feel affection towards
something you touch or see.
Don't move.
Are they a couple?
Do you have time?
Me?
Do you like me?
Yes, i do.
You shouldn't.
We can't be a couple.
I like you as a fan.
Well, in that case...
One, two, three.
Nice picture.
My niece is your huge fan.
Thank you.
No, thank you for
taking a picture with me.
Eugene, do you know?
You remind me of Ji-hoon.
I do?
Mr. Children
That's what i love to do.
You can't stop,
because i'm the truth.
I just want to dance.
I have a bad cold.
But i'll try my best.
Summer...
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Poor, rough and raw.
- What?
- But i can hear it.
I will make you a singer.
So everyone can hear it.
Where have you been?
- Get out.
- Why?
You didn't want me
to see this?
- It's none of your business.
- It is.
I think it has a lot
to do with me.
- What do you feel about him?
- What?
Am i a substitute
for KIM Ji-hoon?
So you can feel better?
- Coz i'm living out his dream?
- Shut up.
Okay, i'll be KIM Ji-hoon.
i'll sing, dance and everything.
Then kill myself like him, right?
I needed someone to replace him
and you were the right person.
Do you know
what hurts me the most?
That i was another
Ji-hoon for you.
Eugene didn't exist to you.
- The winner of this week is
- Mr. Children, Congratulations!
You won 4 weeks in a row and
earned a ticket to the Festival!
It's time to say goodbye.
Thank you for watching.
Simon SA
I am nothing
without you.
You broke my heart
but i wait for you.
I'm tired of waiting.
I'm out of my mind.
I just can't get over you.
Tell me, tell me.
Oh why
I don't want to love
anybody.
Tell me, tell me.
Oh why
Please, come back to me.
I'm ravaged.
Without you, i'm...
This part is so difficult.
There're things you can't do.
You turned a rocker to an Idol.
Well done, O Gu-ju.
What do you want?
Star Music
Artist Transfer Contract
If you play a game with me,
you will lose.
So?
They're doing great.
I mean Wonder Boys.
But they won't last long.
They are too fragile.
They don't have tenacity.
You know what i mean?
Actually, they can't sing.
I was thinking about
making a visual rock band.
Mr. Children will be perfect.
Hand them to me
when they hit the top.
Those boys were mine.
It's better for you
and the members.
Or will you run o again
after one of them dies?
You can't even keep
a microphone with care.
You hold my hand
and stayed by my side.
Now, i can feel
your heart.
Eugene!
Idol pop groups?
Trash.
They are stupid.
I think music should
feed your soul.
Eugene of Mr. Children.
His controversial remarks on Idols!
Mr. Children is temporarily banned
from TV show programs,
and it remains uncertain whether
they can be seen at the Music festival,
the biggest K-pop event.
The agency 'Champion' hasn't
made any announcement yet.
My boss blamed me for
losing ads because of this.
This video clip thing
is quite serious.
It's better for them to skip
this week's show.
I'm verifying the video.
I'll take care of it.
Give me some time.
O Gu-ju.
I am sorry...
We have to talk.
Listen.
What is it?
I didn't say that.
You didn't?
What a relief.
Then prove it.
I was just...
- I mean...
- Whatever you say...
Nothing changes.
Go home.
LEE Eugene was a singer
in underground band,
when he took this video.
Whatever the reason may be,
his thoughtless action has
disappointed many fans.
And he caused trouble
to related people.
Once again, i apologize
for his behavior.
We'll take questions.
Is it true Eugene will
drop out of the team?
It's not true.
I heard you're searching
for a new member.
Not true.
What about the
other members?
Jio was arrested for
assault in San Diego.
He was booked without
detention in Korea, twice.
Ricky is an illegal immigrant
with double nationality.
Hyun has a girlfriend
and a baby.
These things are their
private lives of the past.
People say that if the rumors
are true, they should break up.
There are so many
pop groups nowadays,
but many are unqualified.
lt's definitely a social problem.
Music industry is
not a rehab.
Excuse me but that
sounds like an offense.
You're right.
I agree with you.
So Mr. Children sang.
lt was the only thing
they could do.
They sang, dance and mend
their hearts with music.
Music was their dream.
Is that even relevant?
They can't make a
clean break with the past
But what they put in music
It was real.
Do we have to sit out the
whole play until one dies?
Bullshit!
What the fuck is this!
You blaming us for all this?
- You know nothing!
- Stop it.
Eugene.
I apologize for having
caused trouble.
This is all my fault.
If the members can't
perform because of me?
From now on,
I will drop out of Mr. Children.
You mean you'll stop
your career as a singer?
What about Mr. Children?
Tell us some more!
LEE Eugene.
Eugene!
Just a moment!
Wonder Boys records sales
hit O.3 million.
- What is this?
- Rainbow spicy noodle.
The noodles are tough.
I like it.
So what will you do?
People will recognize you.
You said i should
take over the restaurant.
Are you going to cook
with that face?
You have to feel happy
when you're cooking.
If you cook with a smile
on your face,
the dish will be delicious
and the customer smiles!
Dad, smile.
You smiled a lot
on television.
You ran away like that
and end up being here?
I'll ask one thing.
You don't want to be part of
Mr. Children anymore?
This place suits me better.
That was our dream.
It was.
Then do it.
It's not a dream, now.
And dreams never
come true.
Why are you leaving?
It's not your fault.
You grew into a habit
of flying abroad.
Gu-ju.
How about we train
another group?
A girl group, this time.
I manage and
you write songs.
I don't want anyone
to be hurt, again.
I don't have a reason to leave.
But i don't have
a reason to stay either.
Wanna drink?
-I have something
-i've got something?
You first.
We had a different life but
we understand each other.
What does that mean?
What's your point?
Well, i Want to say?
Marry me.
You wanna die?
Yes, i'm happy to die
If i can live with you.
Eugene, it's me.
Are you gonna be mad at me
for working on your song?
But you won't be able
to turn it off.
I want you to sing again.
And i want to hear you
singing this song.
You, sad Rudolf.
Hey.
Go and find her.
She's waiting for you.
I can hear you laugh
when l close my eyes.
You were always
next to me.
Eugene!
Where's Gu-ju
and the members?
They went to?
I don't know.
Gu-ju is in airport.
Hey!
Eugene!
Who are you?
- Delivery for O Gu-ju.
- For Gu-ju?
What are you doing?
Hey!
You wanna die?
- I'll fall if you let me go.
- Stop it!
Yong-su!
Please, i beg you.
Eugene, bring Gu-ju with you
to the Music festival.
The members are coming!
You got it?
What're you doin' here?
When i was hurt
and shut my heart,
you hold my hand
and stayed by my side.
I can hear you laugh
when i close my eyes.
You were always
next to me.
This song is for you.
Can you hear me?
Can you feel my heart
I will always be here
and sing this for you.
The story that never ends.
The time that passes.
A glimpse of your back.
I will sing for you.
I don't like it.
It's poor, rough and dull.
Nothing glamorous.
Gu-ju.
Where's my scooter?
Hold on tight!
Look at this.
It's hilarious.
What do you think
about Idol pop groups?
Pop group?
They are so talented.
What do you think about
copying other’s work?
I think they are trash.
Trash?
I just think it's unfair.
I think music should
feed your soul.
You're a sweet looking boy.
Thank you.
Next!
We're Chocolat!
Hello, we're Brave Girls.
Let's have fun tonight!
I love you, my fans.
We are so happy.
Thank you.
We're Wonder Boys!
Who is he?
Are you a new trot singer?
l am a CEO of
Champion Music.
I want to say
Eugene is innocent.
The video clip was proved
to be manipulated.
So from today,
you can see Mr. Children
perform on a stage.
Thank you.
Okay, that was...
unexpected.
Do you have something else
to say?
Why don't you guys
return my calls?
Jio, Hyeoni, Ricky, Eugene!
This was your dream.
It's not too late.
There's a traffic jam.
So take the subway!
Hurry up, guys!
l'm always beside you baby.
You're my shining star.
You were bad last night.
Where were you?
l said bad things
and i regret it.
I just hung up on you.
They are not here?
If they don't show up in 5 mins,
I get fired!
- Jio.
- Is it only you?
- Hyeoni.
- Had to transfer
Ricky!
Now i can tell you
how i feel.
Can you hear me?
Can you feel me?
Do you know
my heart belongs to you?
Now i know.
I miss you so much.
The boy group of the year,
Wonder Boys!
It's so hard when
you're not with me.
I can't live.
Please, let me go.
I don't know why
you're not with me.
I can't forget you.
I just can't.
I'm without you.
Will they come?
Yes, they will.
After the show.
Take it o, stupid.
Just feel the music.
That's all you have to do.
I'm ravaged.
Without you,
It's so hard to live
without you.
I am a fool.
I hate myself.
I'm ravaged.
Without you,
So much energy here.
It was Wonder Boys!
The next group is a rookie who
made so much issues this year.
- l think l know.
- They are Mr. Children.
Hello, i'm Eugene
of Mr. Children.
I had a thought
on the way here.
Actually, i'm from band.
And, pop music was
not what i wanted to do.
But then i realized that
any music is great,
if i can enjoy singing it
and also make you happy.
The members and one person
taught me this.
And i will sing for them.
The soft sound of the waves.
But your voice is sweeter.
Come closer.
We will go together.
And make a dream come true.
The sound of a warm breeze.
Comes to me and comforts me.
I feel sweet.
Happy as in a dream.
I can smile because of you.
Summer dream.
It's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
It may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Like the burning sun,
Like the shining star.
I feel sweet.
Happy as in a dream.
I can smile because of you.
Summer dream.
It's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
It may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Let's take itto the top.
Close your eyes and imagine it.
Spread your wings
and fly high.
It's gonna be okay.
Hold back your tears.
A bright future is
waiting for us.
Summer dream.
It's a sweet melody.
feel your dream.
We will stay together.
It may break your heart.
It may bring you down.
But you have me.
We'll dream forever.
Summer Dream.
Mr. Children!
Why did you fabricate the video?
How do you feel
right now?
I will tell everything
in prosecutors' office.
When are you gonna
make me a band vocal?
Depends on you.
I can't trust you.
Tell me when.
Shut up.
Watch my bag.
Hello?
Your bag just went in.
When l was hurt
and shut my heart,
you hold my hand
and stayed by my side.
I can hear you laugh
when i close my eyes.
You were always
next to me.
I wanted to run to you,
wherever it would take me.
The world around me
have changed me.
I could not tell you
the feelings deep in my heart.
I want you to feel it
with this song.
I felt lost and
my mind was uneasy.
My dream was so far away.
I could never touch it.
I could not see
the star in your eyes.
You gave me strength.
I wanted to run to you,
wherever it would take me.
The world around me
have changed me.
I could not tell you
the feelings deep in my heart.
I want you to feel it
with this song.
Do you remember
that song?
Your sweet voice
made me dream again.
This song is for you.
Can you hear me?
Can you feel my heart
I will always be here
and sing this for you.
The story that never ends.
The time that passes.
A glimpse of your back.
I will sing for you.
English Subtitles
LEE Jee-heng l KIM Jae-min
edit and re-timed by
~potatoheart