1 
00:01:33,460 --> 00:01:37,419 
2 later just wanted to sing songs 
own in KTV. Must not 

2 
00:01:39,299 --> 00:01:40,459 
Ji Won 

3 
00:01:41,301 --> 00:01:42,290 
You think about how 

4 
00:01:42,435 --> 00:01:44,300 
Do you want to continue to love each other? 

5 
00:01:44,404 --> 00:01:46,463 
You're with her. 
What was her face 

6 
00:01:46,539 --> 00:01:50,373 
following need not meet each other. Do not need it 
not need to breathe in an atmosphere with more. Listen 

7 
00:01:50,510 --> 00:01:52,273 
But sir Representatives 

8 
00:01:52,378 --> 00:01:54,369 
2 people should hear them say 
Think of them first and then go ... 

9 
00:01:54,380 --> 00:01:55,347 
No need to ache 

10 
00:01:55,348 --> 00:01:57,339 
Also new is only met a few times 

11 
00:01:58,485 --> 00:02:00,385 
After this there will be no 
Such a happening anymore 

12 
00:02:06,292 --> 00:02:10,319 
Ji Won. Kim ji won 

13 
00:02:16,503 --> 00:02:19,472 
Honestly just because to the extent of this failure sucp u? 
What else can the system still 

14 
00:02:20,440 --> 00:02:22,408 
I do not know me anymore 

15 
00:02:24,277 --> 00:02:26,404 
I think too much about 
how to become a singer 

16 
00:02:29,282 --> 00:02:31,341 
It had been everything to me 

17 
00:02:34,454 --> 00:02:35,512 
I really do not understand 

18 
00:02:36,322 --> 00:02:38,381 
The show this time not 
only concerned with his own personal 

19 
00:02:38,458 --> 00:02:40,358 
Now to concentrate certain 
stage in repertoire behold 

20 
00:02:47,400 --> 00:02:50,335 
Hyun's spirit is not good now 
do, has to adjust the time 

21 
00:02:50,403 --> 00:02:51,392 
Please give him some time 

22 
00:02:51,437 --> 00:02:53,302 
If the time for him 

23 
00:02:53,306 --> 00:02:57,367 
This is not just a story a 2nd time, 
I quickly told him to work with on stage to 

24 
00:03:01,314 --> 00:03:07,253 
The show press release 
band 'Mr Children' in 2008 

25 
00:04:56,296 --> 00:05:03,361 
The film: Mr. ldol 

26 
00:05:16,349 --> 00:05:18,408 
(3 year) 

27 
00:05:21,354 --> 00:05:27,315 
Queue, any person 
misdemeanor order to follow 

28 
00:05:27,427 --> 00:05:28,451 
Going in this direction 

29 
00:05:37,337 --> 00:05:38,463 
People followed me any order 

30 
00:05:55,488 --> 00:05:59,254 
Goo Joo Oh welcome her 

31 
00:05:59,492 --> 00:06:03,292 
Tomorrow or the day after tomorrow. Commit to 
to keeping rooms luggage lost heart 

32 
00:06:43,369 --> 00:06:44,336 
'Wonder Boys' 

33 
00:06:49,442 --> 00:06:52,411 
1 2 3 Welcome, brothers and sisters. 
We are the group 'Wonder Boys' 

34 
00:06:53,379 --> 00:06:57,281 
After the selection of this end. 
next conference is always prepared. Started to work 

35 
00:06:57,483 --> 00:07:01,317 
ù star winner in the contest 'recruiting to 
Stars' finally they also would be the only 

36 
00:07:02,255 --> 00:07:03,415 
Put the headphones to 

37 
00:07:07,293 --> 00:07:08,351 
Spit out chewing gum 

38 
00:07:10,463 --> 00:07:11,487 
Then go out to 

39 
00:07:13,266 --> 00:07:14,233 
Out 

40 
00:07:17,370 --> 00:07:20,339 
We would be the 'Wonder Boys' 

41 
00:07:27,346 --> 00:07:29,473 
'Mr. Children' 

42 
00:07:30,316 --> 00:07:32,284 
I think this conference 
related to our 

43 
00:07:33,486 --> 00:07:37,445 
Signed off. She will be the manager. 
There will also be assigned to her for the team responsible for delegation 

44 
00:07:38,291 --> 00:07:42,284 
'Mr. Children' them well, three years ago there 
able, but not now anymore 

45 
00:07:42,395 --> 00:07:48,356 
The story of Nepal u, or 
German Man both are fleeting. 

46 
00:07:48,434 --> 00:07:51,369 
No need to labor very hard 
demand at 'Mr. Children' so anymore 

47 
00:07:52,371 --> 00:07:54,430 
Trying to help them 
Only one half is then 

48 
00:07:54,507 --> 00:07:57,305 
The rest I arranged 

49 
00:07:59,512 --> 00:08:01,275 
Now that said 

50 
00:08:01,447 --> 00:08:03,415 
'Mr. Children' was dropped 
the repository, right? 

51 
00:08:03,516 --> 00:08:08,385 
Since she left, a running back and forth myself. 
amniotic confused you can restore the reputation and roots 

52 
00:08:09,455 --> 00:08:12,253 
Do you know the three years I had to 
How much misery does not bear 

53 
00:08:12,358 --> 00:08:14,292 
Not getting anywhere also 
idiots in the oil services industry 

54 
00:08:15,261 --> 00:08:17,354 
Make the effort they have any, as well 
Accretion can not it be a lack huct 

55 
00:08:17,463 --> 00:08:19,260 
Can not have more 
long-term plans are 

56 
00:08:19,365 --> 00:08:20,525 
But this is not all their fault 

57 
00:08:20,533 --> 00:08:23,400 
So I do not need money 
cancel the contract where penalty 

58 
00:08:25,271 --> 00:08:27,364 
Give evidence of 
they canceled my contract for 

59 
00:08:27,540 --> 00:08:30,373 
'Mr. Children' s later 

60 
00:08:30,376 --> 00:08:31,365 
I will by takeovers 

61 
00:08:31,477 --> 00:08:33,377 
They are clearly broken 
checking that expenditures exceeded revenues 

62 
00:08:33,412 --> 00:08:35,505 
He wanted to fill the gaps, sometimes 
will destroy herself there to 

63 
00:08:38,384 --> 00:08:40,249 
I gave her staff at this plan 

64 
00:08:41,354 --> 00:08:43,322 
Obediently follow the upcoming 
set, I go about making 

65 
00:08:43,456 --> 00:08:44,445 
Neither 

66 
00:08:45,291 --> 00:08:46,485 
I will be making plans 

67 
00:08:47,426 --> 00:08:49,223 
Did she want to now 
with me? 

68 
00:08:49,328 --> 00:08:50,420 
Detected out? 

69 
00:08:51,430 --> 00:08:53,364 
I started early and 

70 
00:08:58,371 --> 00:08:59,395 
You really want to go back 

71 
00:08:59,472 --> 00:09:01,337 
After going, then plan what 

72 
00:09:03,276 --> 00:09:06,336 
First, set them back, 
he helped me find the gym 

73 
00:09:06,445 --> 00:09:08,310 
No heat but want to go on stage 

74 
00:09:08,414 --> 00:09:10,382 
She was doing so only punish myself! 

75 
00:09:10,449 --> 00:09:12,246 
Sa boss 

76 
00:09:13,386 --> 00:09:15,513 
He was no longer the Sa Hee Moon 
whom she met before anymore 

77 
00:09:19,492 --> 00:09:21,517 
I know, I go to work 
his work go offline 

78 
00:09:22,328 --> 00:09:23,352 
I will go 

79 
00:09:23,462 --> 00:09:24,394 
But that 

80 
00:09:24,463 --> 00:09:27,296 
I still think I should 
continue to work here is pretty ... 

81 
00:09:27,500 --> 00:09:28,432 
This 

82 
00:09:29,402 --> 00:09:31,370 
This is defective in 
Her weakness there 

83 
00:09:34,340 --> 00:09:35,364 
Thanks 

84 
00:09:37,443 --> 00:09:38,432 
Good people dream happy dreams 

85 
00:09:39,512 --> 00:09:40,479 
Good people dream happy dreams 

86 
00:09:45,384 --> 00:09:46,316 
This is what it 

87 
00:09:49,255 --> 00:09:50,279 
What is a pediatric 

88 
00:09:50,523 --> 00:09:52,286 
Why the extra one so we 

89 
00:09:52,458 --> 00:09:55,256 
Lack of a new problem, many 
what should I do more than this one 

90 
00:09:55,361 --> 00:09:57,329 
Seeing then take time 

91 
00:10:22,488 --> 00:10:26,424 
Disease, we see that 
story is wrong 

92 
00:10:27,326 --> 00:10:28,486 
Although the destiny can not be changed 

93 
00:10:29,428 --> 00:10:31,419 
But the future can be changed 

94 
00:10:32,398 --> 00:10:35,299 
So, want to change the relative 
future must have the will 

95 
00:10:35,434 --> 00:10:37,299 
And fully prepared 

96 
00:10:37,403 --> 00:10:39,268 
Prepare how a 

97 
00:10:39,438 --> 00:10:42,271 
Forgive me this venture. 
Do not know ... 

98 
00:10:42,475 --> 00:10:44,500 
There should give some idea of ​​how this 

99 
00:10:44,543 --> 00:10:46,511 
So a big thanks to all teachers 

100 
00:10:47,413 --> 00:10:48,402 
So ... 

101 
00:10:50,282 --> 00:10:52,443 
Commercial Insurance 

102 
00:10:53,319 --> 00:10:57,483 
This is the type of insurance 
most basic well known 

103 
00:10:58,290 --> 00:11:00,281 
Said work time, 
no other work of that 

104 
00:11:02,495 --> 00:11:04,486 
Kindergarten Tuition is missing how much a 

105 
00:11:05,297 --> 00:11:07,288 
Or we are not sent to kindergarten 
In addition, she will raise it okay 

106 
00:11:07,400 --> 00:11:09,459 
Friends do not have to get a little, at least 
also to children in daycare instead 

107 
00:11:10,503 --> 00:11:12,368 
One day you get paid then 

108 
00:11:13,305 --> 00:11:14,397 
The other clause postponed a little pepper 

109 
00:11:15,374 --> 00:11:17,342 
Spending money just take care 
. . 
medicines for children is being 

110 
00:11:21,280 --> 00:11:22,247 
Vali drag Asia 

111 
00:11:22,381 --> 00:11:23,370 
Do not open the Nhe 

112 
00:11:23,516 --> 00:11:25,381 
Why, I have to find out 
Eh there suitcase owners 

113 
00:11:26,252 --> 00:11:27,310 
Opens then very unlucky 

114 
00:11:27,420 --> 00:11:29,251 
Will there fortunes change 

115 
00:11:29,355 --> 00:11:30,322 
Why 

116 
00:11:30,423 --> 00:11:32,414 
Then as quick to open only, 
modified little bit destiny 
. . 

117 
00:11:36,529 --> 00:11:39,293 
He was not sure 
then why not open 

118 
00:11:39,298 --> 00:11:40,424 
Alo, alo 

119 
00:11:40,533 --> 00:11:42,296 
Where she is not open 

120 
00:11:42,401 --> 00:11:43,425 
It turned out there themselves 

121 
00:11:43,536 --> 00:11:47,233 
So Eun Han, Han Eun So not 
sleeping, turn the machine for her to 

122 
00:11:50,509 --> 00:11:53,410 
It's asleep 

123 
00:12:33,319 --> 00:12:34,286 
Alo a 

124 
00:12:35,321 --> 00:12:36,481 
Her luggage, I have not stolen 

125 
00:12:37,289 --> 00:12:38,256 
Not a 

126 
00:12:38,324 --> 00:12:39,382 
I have not stolen 

127 
00:12:42,394 --> 00:12:44,294 
Told him to come to the phone the other Party 

128 
00:12:45,397 --> 00:12:47,297 
This is where King had been in 

129 
00:12:48,267 --> 00:12:50,326 
Yoo Jin, King has been here so 

130 
00:12:51,270 --> 00:12:52,328 
Where she is so 

131 
00:12:52,404 --> 00:12:53,462 
I have just arrived 

132 
00:12:54,340 --> 00:12:56,240 
We went directly 

133 
00:12:56,308 --> 00:12:57,400 
She just went to go offline 

134 
00:12:57,543 --> 00:13:01,309 
Asia is still going up? 
I saw her coming and then make that 

135 
00:13:01,313 --> 00:13:02,473 
I still do not see why 

136 
00:13:04,250 --> 00:13:05,410 
Removed 

137 
00:13:06,318 --> 00:13:07,410 
Did not find it inherently 

138 
00:13:08,354 --> 00:13:10,481 
Stands where? 
High hands up let me know 

139 
00:13:36,415 --> 00:13:37,313 
Is a suitcase 

140 
00:13:55,267 --> 00:13:56,359 
Picked to go 

141 
00:13:57,503 --> 00:13:59,334 
She told me to go back 

142 
00:14:01,407 --> 00:14:02,396 
Not 

143 
00:14:15,321 --> 00:14:16,310 
Help me 

144 
00:14:17,389 --> 00:14:18,287 
Save me 

145 
00:14:39,511 --> 00:14:41,240 
You're fast aging 

146 
00:14:41,547 --> 00:14:43,515 
I have two girl children, old age is of course 

147 
00:14:44,316 --> 00:14:45,248 
With whom are young again 

148 
00:14:45,417 --> 00:14:46,475 
As also, also married 2 times 

149 
00:14:47,286 --> 00:14:50,278 
I not only have remarried, 
My men were then squeezed dry 

150 
00:14:50,389 --> 00:14:53,256 
Why? Do not you? 
Relate to him instead 

151 
00:14:53,359 --> 00:14:54,348 
I am now very busy 

152 
00:14:54,360 --> 00:14:55,349 
Do not follow me anymore 

153 
00:14:56,428 --> 00:14:57,395 
It's frustrating 

154 
00:14:58,297 --> 00:14:59,525 
Please ask Where is the emergency room 

155 
00:15:04,270 --> 00:15:05,259 
Yoo Jin over there 

156 
00:15:06,372 --> 00:15:07,498 
He looks not for what 

157 
00:15:08,474 --> 00:15:11,500 
She spoke yesterday this is the point 
notice, make me fall into the water 

158 
00:15:21,320 --> 00:15:22,480 
Until then, this is where 

159 
00:15:50,449 --> 00:15:51,438 
I knew who he 

160 
00:15:52,484 --> 00:15:56,215 
Later marriage should need money urgently, 
ceded this room for less 

161 
00:15:56,522 --> 00:15:58,353 
Resting 

162 
00:15:59,525 --> 00:16:01,322 
Workplace 
. 

163 
00:16:01,493 --> 00:16:03,461 
Practice entertainment are 
no problem 

164 
00:16:04,463 --> 00:16:05,452 
In which the game 

165 
00:16:06,365 --> 00:16:07,332 
In the past 

166 
00:16:08,400 --> 00:16:11,301 
Having been awake output 

167 
00:16:16,275 --> 00:16:17,242 
I also know 

168 
00:16:17,343 --> 00:16:19,470 
She is also the body parts, 
do not want to like this place 

169 
00:16:20,379 --> 00:16:21,539 
But do not need to spend money 

170 
00:16:22,348 --> 00:16:23,280 
Monthly rent is also 

171 
00:16:23,449 --> 00:16:24,438 
Money managers do not need much 

172 
00:16:39,531 --> 00:16:42,398 
This time we invited him Jang 
Ricky when he was 3 years old in 1986 

173 
00:16:42,468 --> 00:16:45,437 
Have professional training in Canada 

174 
00:16:47,272 --> 00:16:47,499 
Hello 

175 
00:16:48,340 --> 00:16:53,471 
nowhere I know he was very young then, do so c 
t difficult, but if he remembered any details r 

176 
00:16:54,313 --> 00:16:56,372 
Invite all to say a 

177 
00:16:58,384 --> 00:17:02,445 
At 3 years old, went through a column 
power an alley behind 

178 
00:17:04,490 --> 00:17:06,424 
There are two children playing together 

179 
00:17:07,493 --> 00:17:09,290 
A child that I 

180 
00:17:11,296 --> 00:17:12,456 
But the child is a girl kai 

181 
00:17:18,337 --> 00:17:19,361 
Jang Ricky 

182 
00:17:21,540 --> 00:17:24,236 
Sit down 

183 
00:17:39,258 --> 00:17:41,453 
Back to the game, is P 

184 
00:17:42,261 --> 00:17:44,320 
Now holding a child also 
feel the whole body aches 

185 
00:17:45,364 --> 00:17:47,457 
Baek Kon, room number 5 about finished 

186 
00:17:48,434 --> 00:17:51,267 
This is what's wrong. 
No. 2 star room no one moved so 

187 
00:17:55,307 --> 00:17:56,501 
I want to try again 

188 
00:18:16,361 --> 00:18:17,453 
Stop it, Jang Jio 

189 
00:18:18,464 --> 00:18:20,398 
I do have enough trouble then 

190 
00:18:26,405 --> 00:18:27,463 
We stop here to 

191 
00:18:31,510 --> 00:18:33,341 
Boy, 

192 
00:18:40,352 --> 00:18:42,286 
Until then, the leaves for him to 

193 
00:18:51,296 --> 00:18:52,320 
Only thing what's the matter here 

194 
00:18:53,465 --> 00:18:54,432 
Want to exercise à 

195 
00:18:55,534 --> 00:18:57,365 
Naturally I was not then 

196 
00:18:58,270 --> 00:19:01,296 
Can exercise here recently 
What it has also been dancing 

197 
00:19:01,373 --> 00:19:03,432 
The main theater where? 
We do not have a vocalist? 

198 
00:19:05,310 --> 00:19:07,301 
Where are you okay, sooner or later 
will fail only 

199 
00:19:10,415 --> 00:19:12,280 
Failure. He really is 

200 
00:19:13,519 --> 00:19:16,511 
Left, one can once again gather 
like this, watch out not bad at all 

201 
00:19:17,523 --> 00:19:20,287 
The manager Su Yin Huang 
there before, but remember? 

202 
00:19:20,392 --> 00:19:23,384 
This modified by Huang is responsible for managing information 
t the first item will be transmitted from place to manage H 

203 
00:19:24,463 --> 00:19:26,226 
So she contacted him yet 

204 
00:19:26,398 --> 00:19:27,365 
No 

205 
00:19:27,533 --> 00:19:30,331 
Within weeks of this sort help 
I met him, representing Park 

206 
00:19:31,403 --> 00:19:32,335 
Representative Park 

207 
00:19:32,504 --> 00:19:33,436 
Who? 

208 
00:19:34,306 --> 00:19:35,273 
I u 

209 
00:19:35,474 --> 00:19:37,374 
His Title I 
will help him to recommend 

210 
00:19:39,444 --> 00:19:41,503 
Park Sang Sik you dare ... 

211 
00:19:43,382 --> 00:19:44,314 
Representative Park ... 

212 
00:19:45,317 --> 00:19:46,249 
Representatives ... 

213 
00:19:57,462 --> 00:20:00,295 
Yesterday I was no longer any other way 

214 
00:20:01,433 --> 00:20:02,491 
Thanks 

215 
00:20:04,403 --> 00:20:07,395 
So I did not come home again 

216 
00:20:08,440 --> 00:20:09,498 
Noise is dead! 

217 
00:20:11,510 --> 00:20:13,478 
Do not know why say this? 

218 
00:20:16,415 --> 00:20:18,406 
Saturday this week recruiting 

219 
00:20:19,451 --> 00:20:21,419 
This sense of where I'm not wrong! 

220 
00:20:23,355 --> 00:20:26,415 
This is the shirt I chose Parkland of performance for 
recruitment of this period, the money hard to avoid it! 

221 
00:20:27,359 --> 00:20:30,294 
Should public money this time he was little 
subtract decision mild fun! 

222 
00:20:31,430 --> 00:20:32,454 
Why is that? 

223 
00:20:33,265 --> 00:20:35,358 
Little public money is worth what? 

224 
00:20:35,500 --> 00:20:36,489 
If the period for recruiting good expression 

225 
00:20:37,302 --> 00:20:38,462 
Contract for additional money 
reward, as John Kennedy! 

226 
00:20:39,304 --> 00:20:40,396 
Why I still do not understand how you? 

227 
00:20:41,273 --> 00:20:42,365 
100 large and small clothes dong 

228 
00:20:43,275 --> 00:20:44,503 
I said back to him even 
also the same size clothes that? 

229 
00:20:47,312 --> 00:20:48,336 
I'm feeling here! 

230 
00:20:48,447 --> 00:20:50,244 
How is this possible are the contrast? 

231 
00:21:23,382 --> 00:21:24,349 
We hire only men only! 

232 
00:21:25,384 --> 00:21:26,510 
It's then please see 
us only for a moment! 

233 
00:21:44,536 --> 00:21:46,401 
Why are these people 
both have similar properties? 

234 
00:21:47,272 --> 00:21:48,330 
'Dream job' 

235 
00:21:49,441 --> 00:21:51,341 
Start with us, but at the same time! 

236 
00:22:08,327 --> 00:22:09,294 
He is the singer? 

237 
00:22:09,528 --> 00:22:11,257 
I am a broker! 

238 
00:22:31,483 --> 00:22:33,417 
Why are you here? 

239 
00:22:34,519 --> 00:22:35,508 
The group you are game? 

240 
00:22:36,421 --> 00:22:38,218 
We come from the group 'no reason' 

241 
00:22:39,291 --> 00:22:40,417 
'Why not protest' 

242 
00:22:41,426 --> 00:22:42,393 
Starting! 

243 
00:23:44,256 --> 00:23:45,280 
There are more than a little effort? 

244 
00:23:46,291 --> 00:23:47,258 
Or is it faster? 

245 
00:23:47,526 --> 00:23:49,221 
Do not play friends! 

246 
00:23:53,265 --> 00:23:54,289 
I see huge obstacles already! 

247 
00:24:59,397 --> 00:25:00,523 
His respiration stops then! 

248 
00:25:06,271 --> 00:25:07,431 
This song to get the network! 

249 
00:25:08,373 --> 00:25:09,499 
Can only say that the spend profile 

250 
00:25:10,375 --> 00:25:12,400 
That was chaotic, tasteless, 
makes people bored with 

251 
00:25:12,544 --> 00:25:15,513 
Singers only have you here 

252 
00:25:16,414 --> 00:25:18,279 
His popularity has only 

253 
00:25:20,452 --> 00:25:22,283 
But I can hear 

254 
00:25:23,288 --> 00:25:24,448 
Alone will not be forever 

255 
00:25:25,290 --> 00:25:26,450 
But with me it can succeed 

256 
00:25:29,327 --> 00:25:30,385 
Only me? 

257 
00:25:30,462 --> 00:25:32,396 
This is not a group game selection? 

258 
00:25:33,465 --> 00:25:35,262 
Further, why only me? 

259 
00:25:35,433 --> 00:25:36,491 
Because we need a vocalist! 

260 
00:25:39,404 --> 00:25:40,393 
But this 

261 
00:25:41,373 --> 00:25:42,431 
Being recruited new singer! 

262 
00:25:43,275 --> 00:25:44,435 
So I refuse! 

263 
00:25:44,509 --> 00:25:48,377 
She also shows us 
as a group, a collective 

264 
00:25:49,414 --> 00:25:51,382 
Will you find another person! 

265 
00:25:58,523 --> 00:26:00,491 
According to this last shift 

266 
00:26:03,361 --> 00:26:05,352 
I also have to go away then! 

267 
00:26:05,497 --> 00:26:07,465 
He is not also the poorest 
before I start to finish already? 

268 
00:26:08,333 --> 00:26:09,459 
Lack of bass and also 
group called stars? 

269 
00:26:11,469 --> 00:26:13,266 
How about you? 

270 
00:26:13,405 --> 00:26:15,498 
Yesterday I interviewed then! 

271 
00:26:17,509 --> 00:26:19,374 
Girlfriend told me to leave the group 

272 
00:26:20,345 --> 00:26:22,245 
Find a job normally 

273 
00:26:23,515 --> 00:26:25,449 
I told her to three companies, so ... 

274 
00:26:26,351 --> 00:26:32,256 
'Resistance is not reason' we have 
do over, but no reason betrayal 

275 
00:26:32,490 --> 00:26:33,479 
Is not worth! 

276 
00:26:48,473 --> 00:26:49,440 
Please eat at hot! 

277 
00:26:54,312 --> 00:26:55,301 
Ask? 

278 
00:26:58,350 --> 00:27:00,409 
This is not somewhat irrational? 

279 
00:27:01,453 --> 00:27:05,480 
Analysis of mine and her 
that was so big difference? 

280 
00:27:06,458 --> 00:27:08,255 
Incentives patrons! 

281 
00:27:10,261 --> 00:27:11,421 
Well, I get it! 

282 
00:27:45,530 --> 00:27:46,497 
As I understand it 

283 
00:27:47,332 --> 00:27:50,324 
General appearance like his 
Japan, the African National Special 

284 
00:27:50,535 --> 00:27:54,369 
Work in the morning coffee, evening 
make car dealers, weekends at the track! 

285 
00:27:54,472 --> 00:27:56,235 
But speak out 

286 
00:27:56,441 --> 00:27:58,272 
He was a practicing 
Birth of 'Star Music' that! 

287 
00:27:58,376 --> 00:28:01,470 
Several years ago Kim Su-Ro to 
improve the group's vision to 

288 
00:28:02,247 --> 00:28:03,339 
He then selected 

289 
00:28:04,315 --> 00:28:06,306 
Do not you remember? 
As the name may be dismissed because he talked back! 

290 
00:28:27,238 --> 00:28:28,262 
Caramel Macchiato! 

291 
00:28:43,321 --> 00:28:44,345 
Du Chan! 

292 
00:28:50,328 --> 00:28:51,226 
Singer genius! 

293 
00:28:51,396 --> 00:28:52,363 
You want how much? 

294 
00:28:52,464 --> 00:28:53,431 
Come to me! 

295 
00:28:56,401 --> 00:28:57,390 
I am a driver agent 

296 
00:28:58,269 --> 00:28:59,429 
Please ask him to go? 

297 
00:29:05,477 --> 00:29:06,501 
Go straight! 

298 
00:29:08,279 --> 00:29:09,405 
She came from a pair of hunting game? 
. 

299 
00:29:10,482 --> 00:29:12,313 
What followed me for that? 

300 
00:29:19,424 --> 00:29:20,391 
Welcome! 

301 
00:29:20,492 --> 00:29:23,518 
Du Chan! 

302 
00:29:34,339 --> 00:29:35,465 
please save it! 

303 
00:29:38,243 --> 00:29:39,471 
Before last month to be paid here! 

304 
00:29:40,345 --> 00:29:41,505 
I'm also not fail to pay 

305 
00:29:43,381 --> 00:29:44,473 
So sure abbot over here! 

306 
00:29:46,417 --> 00:29:48,510 
said lia lia said, leaving the 
I do not know what to say! 

307 
00:29:49,454 --> 00:29:50,421 
Do not know what to say? 

308 
00:29:51,322 --> 00:29:52,311 
She said that! 

309 
00:29:52,423 --> 00:29:55,256 
I really do not know what to say then! 

310 
00:29:55,426 --> 00:29:57,257 
It makes me hate that! 

311 
00:29:57,362 --> 00:29:58,386 
Switch to another hospital to go! 
. . 

312 
00:29:59,364 --> 00:30:01,298 
Come on, we also 
there is no place to go! 

313 
00:30:03,301 --> 00:30:06,293 
Today if payment is not 
procedures had to discharge only! 

314 
00:30:07,438 --> 00:30:09,429 
Maybe relaxing bit longer? 
This time only! 

315 
00:30:10,375 --> 00:30:11,307 
Please! 

316 
00:30:11,442 --> 00:30:12,466 
Of which paid up to 2 years 

317 
00:30:22,487 --> 00:30:24,250 
Please ask her? 

318 
00:30:49,414 --> 00:30:51,245 
In her eyes, we 
just begging to work? 

319 
00:30:51,482 --> 00:30:53,245 
Why did so voluntarily always you? 

320 
00:30:56,454 --> 00:30:58,285 
I've split up paying for 2 years 

321 
00:30:58,456 --> 00:31:00,424 
So starting today means 
2-year contract with me? 

322 
00:31:04,462 --> 00:31:06,293 
She split paid in 2 years 

323 
00:31:06,531 --> 00:31:08,362 
So do I also spent 

324 
00:31:08,499 --> 00:31:09,488 
The interest rate banks! 

325 
00:31:10,335 --> 00:31:11,324 
I can only pay once! 

326 
00:31:11,502 --> 00:31:12,469 
She usury game? 

327 
00:31:13,304 --> 00:31:14,362 
I think of this king 

328 
00:31:15,373 --> 00:31:17,307 
Why to me like that? 

329 
00:31:18,276 --> 00:31:19,402 
She would make me a star singer? 

330 
00:31:20,345 --> 00:31:21,471 
She can be held 
. 
not responsible to the end? 

331 
00:31:22,380 --> 00:31:23,369 
This 

332 
00:31:23,514 --> 00:31:25,277 
To see how his expression? 
. 

333 
00:31:28,386 --> 00:31:29,444 
'Star Music' 

334 
00:31:30,521 --> 00:31:32,352 
I will deal with Kim Su-Ro 

335 
00:31:53,344 --> 00:31:56,313 
Kim Su-Ro you there! 
In fact even more moderate look again! 

336 
00:31:56,547 --> 00:31:59,311 
Listen in between are known as I though! 

337 
00:31:59,417 --> 00:32:01,317 
Not with the current trend! 

338 
00:32:01,452 --> 00:32:04,285 
From left! Public television is not 
Where to place for joking! 

339 
00:32:04,422 --> 00:32:06,481 
Keep up this momentum is not fundamental pitch 
be credited, rejected claims! 

340 
00:32:07,358 --> 00:32:08,450 
Every so be it, do not need anymore! 

341 
00:32:09,494 --> 00:32:11,359 
Needless to say many words charge! 

342 
00:32:12,330 --> 00:32:14,298 
This degree, the latter not 
need to listen to me anymore! 

343 
00:32:29,314 --> 00:32:30,281 
Honestly I do not know 

344 
00:32:31,449 --> 00:32:33,246 
Why are we this? 

345 
00:32:34,252 --> 00:32:35,412 
I'm not giving up his 

346 
00:32:36,254 --> 00:32:37,448 
Which is the era he was eliminated! 

347 
00:32:39,324 --> 00:32:41,292 
Others who hear, 
What else is this way? 

348 
00:32:42,360 --> 00:32:44,419 
What? Well away! 

349 
00:32:45,363 --> 00:32:46,421 
It is important 

350 
00:32:47,432 --> 00:32:49,491 
Certainly this must be clearly 
voluntary withdrawal 

351 
00:32:50,468 --> 00:32:52,368 
The most important point 

352 
00:32:52,503 --> 00:32:54,403 
Most important, ok? 

353 
00:33:04,415 --> 00:33:05,404 
Why did you not come? 

354 
00:33:06,250 --> 00:33:08,411 
If I was not coming up! 

355 
00:33:09,454 --> 00:33:10,421 
I'm on KTV 

356 
00:33:11,389 --> 00:33:12,413 
Practiced a few times already! 

357 
00:33:13,424 --> 00:33:16,257 
The car he is not objective 
a room of 88 years 

358 
00:33:16,427 --> 00:33:18,327 
But also led the team does not know 
is now the most basic game? 

359 
00:33:24,369 --> 00:33:25,336 
I do not do anymore! 

360 
00:33:39,484 --> 00:33:40,473 
Sao said he opened? 

361 
00:33:41,452 --> 00:33:43,317 
He wished to make food to go! 

362 
00:33:46,491 --> 00:33:48,254 
I went a little capital out about 

363 
00:33:48,426 --> 00:33:50,360 
But the accidental means, 
Visit here to ask a second! 

364 
00:33:50,428 --> 00:33:51,452 
40 minutes late 

365 
00:33:52,330 --> 00:33:53,354 
Making 14,000 times 

366 
00:34:18,489 --> 00:34:19,387 
Run! 

367 
00:34:24,295 --> 00:34:25,262 
Run! 

368 
00:34:25,396 --> 00:34:26,328 
Run! 

369 
00:34:46,484 --> 00:34:48,452 
We are what? 

370 
00:34:49,387 --> 00:34:52,254 
Could it be a representative group 
star country star? 

371 
00:34:54,425 --> 00:34:55,323 
I was 

372 
00:34:56,327 --> 00:34:58,420 
Representing the country star! 

373 
00:35:00,364 --> 00:35:01,353 
I was 

374 
00:35:06,370 --> 00:35:07,234 
This is 

375 
00:35:07,371 --> 00:35:08,429 
Basic dance 

376 
00:35:09,440 --> 00:35:12,238 
Doing this may 
dance dance any other! 

377 
00:35:12,477 --> 00:35:14,240 
But do not reverse 

378 
00:35:14,378 --> 00:35:15,504 
Can not make any 
other dance dance! 

379 
00:35:21,419 --> 00:35:22,317 
See, right? 

380 
00:35:22,420 --> 00:35:24,251 
I went to the most basic 
do not! 

381 
00:35:24,355 --> 00:35:25,253 
Why? 

382 
00:35:25,356 --> 00:35:26,414 
Because I'm not a star, so 

383 
00:35:27,325 --> 00:35:28,292 
Need you guys do here! 

384 
00:35:30,294 --> 00:35:32,353 
I'm the Rapper! 

385 
00:35:32,396 --> 00:35:33,454 
No need to jump that 

386 
00:35:34,499 --> 00:35:37,332 
Why do I have to 
handstand you? 

387 
00:35:37,435 --> 00:35:38,402 
Meter A? 
. 

388 
00:35:39,237 --> 00:35:39,498 
Yes! 

389 
00:35:53,384 --> 00:35:54,373 
He ended up okay? 

390 
00:35:54,519 --> 00:35:55,451 
Give me a week's time 

391 
00:35:56,254 --> 00:35:57,278 
For qualified him as he 
. 

392 
00:36:19,510 --> 00:36:21,239 
I do not do the stars anymore! 

393 
00:36:23,414 --> 00:36:25,314 
I want to! 

394 
00:36:25,449 --> 00:36:26,381 
Do not run! 

395 
00:36:28,286 --> 00:36:30,481 
Do not over here! Catch him! 

396 
00:36:38,529 --> 00:36:40,429 
Steamed rice soup is hot 
heavenly delight 

397 
00:36:41,399 --> 00:36:42,525 
Aromatic nose tingle bone tunnel 

398 
00:36:44,502 --> 00:36:47,232 
People born with gourmet food clean 

399 
00:36:47,438 --> 00:36:48,496 
So tired so hungry! 

400 
00:37:31,382 --> 00:37:32,246 
Back! 

401 
00:37:37,388 --> 00:37:38,320 
Back! 

402 
00:37:48,499 --> 00:37:49,363 
Back! 

403 
00:38:12,256 --> 00:38:13,348 
This is the last round of meeting him! 

404 
00:38:14,525 --> 00:38:16,288 
I have a question! 

405 
00:38:17,261 --> 00:38:18,319 
If a meeting last round 

406 
00:38:19,330 --> 00:38:20,354 
What then? 

407 
00:38:20,498 --> 00:38:22,295 
Of course, meeting 
then broadcast the first! 

408 
00:38:22,466 --> 00:38:24,297 
Note that there do not scatter pants! 

409 
00:38:24,402 --> 00:38:26,233 
Not wanting to take charge used 

410 
00:38:26,337 --> 00:38:27,497 
These are all goods financed 

411 
00:38:29,373 --> 00:38:31,307 
Do not just look at the stars of heaven 

412 
00:38:33,244 --> 00:38:34,404 
Instead, become the star! 

413 
00:38:35,379 --> 00:38:36,437 
These are the words who said it? 

414 
00:38:37,415 --> 00:38:38,439 
I say! 

415 
00:39:03,341 --> 00:39:06,469 
Again! Do not look towards the lens instead! 

416 
00:39:12,483 --> 00:39:14,280 
Said lens then do not look at that! 

417 
00:39:17,288 --> 00:39:19,518 
No need to see or not? 
Tell them to go! 

418 
00:39:20,524 --> 00:39:22,355 
Change 'Wonder Boys' 

419 
00:39:27,431 --> 00:39:30,298 
The scenes are not identical, to the yard 
Dramatic indeed is not the same! 

420 
00:39:57,328 --> 00:39:58,317 
Please pause! 

421 
00:39:58,529 --> 00:40:00,360 
Rest a moment and come back! Thank you! 

422 
00:40:01,298 --> 00:40:02,492 
Get back that spirit, as well Nhe! 

423 
00:40:03,300 --> 00:40:04,460 
Medium, which almost hurt! 

424 
00:40:05,436 --> 00:40:07,461 
Why is that? 
Not before time very good? 

425 
00:40:08,472 --> 00:40:09,439 
What? 

426 
00:40:10,307 --> 00:40:11,274 
What are you doing that? 

427 
00:40:11,475 --> 00:40:12,442 
People want to provoke heated game? 

428 
00:40:14,445 --> 00:40:15,412 
Do not type anymore! 

429 
00:40:16,380 --> 00:40:17,369 
Stop, do not fight anymore! 

430 
00:40:18,382 --> 00:40:19,474 
Stopped, do not fight anymore! 

431 
00:40:20,351 --> 00:40:21,375 
Do not type anymore! 

432 
00:40:22,253 --> 00:40:23,413 
Do not fight anymore, that's enough! Hands off! 

433 
00:40:24,288 --> 00:40:25,516 
Okay! Do you then give 
bit is not fast? 

434 
00:40:26,457 --> 00:40:27,389 
You said what? 

435 
00:40:34,265 --> 00:40:37,359 
Something is really happening 
not much happened! 

436 
00:40:39,370 --> 00:40:41,429 
This is the 'star brute' real stars? 

437 
00:40:45,376 --> 00:40:46,343 
Stand up! 

438 
00:40:46,444 --> 00:40:47,411 
Ready to go! 
. 

439 
00:40:52,516 --> 00:40:53,483 
Settlement Map it! 

440 
00:40:56,253 --> 00:40:57,242 
Arrange something? 

441 
00:40:58,289 --> 00:40:59,483 
First broadcast 
of me? 

442 
00:40:59,490 --> 00:41:01,355 
The he is not a group! 

443 
00:41:01,459 --> 00:41:03,427 
We are the collective! 

444 
00:41:04,261 --> 00:41:05,421 
PD Goo she suddenly say? 

445 
00:41:05,496 --> 00:41:07,487 
Continue like this, I do not how 
What brought the people on stage are! 

446 
00:41:21,312 --> 00:41:22,279 
Mom? 

447 
00:41:23,414 --> 00:41:24,472 
Remember him? 

448 
00:41:25,549 --> 00:41:27,278 
Ricky 

449 
00:41:27,518 --> 00:41:29,418 
Mother, the whole canopy à li? 

450 
00:41:32,423 --> 00:41:33,355 
What? 

451 
00:41:33,491 --> 00:41:34,515 
Mother looking me? 

452 
00:41:35,426 --> 00:41:37,291 
There will be opportunities to meet that 

453 
00:41:38,496 --> 00:41:40,361 
If stardom 

454 
00:41:43,267 --> 00:41:44,393 
The line also because I wrote that game? 

455 
00:41:47,238 --> 00:41:48,330 
Direct use of lyrics is okay! 

456 
00:41:50,441 --> 00:41:52,238 
That's his forte, but! 

457 
00:41:53,277 --> 00:41:54,471 
Mother remember? You are Ricky! 

458 
00:41:57,481 --> 00:42:00,279 
Mother remember? You are Ricky! 

459 
00:42:01,285 --> 00:42:02,252 
Keep going! 

460 
00:42:12,463 --> 00:42:13,395 
Real disease! 
. . 

461 
00:42:42,459 --> 00:42:43,517 
Where is the other running squid? 

462 
00:42:48,332 --> 00:42:49,458 
'Wonder Boys' hard then! 

463 
00:42:50,334 --> 00:42:51,494 
Invite 'Brave Girls' and 
'Wonder Boys' on the front! 

464 
00:42:52,303 --> 00:42:53,327 
Standing in front! 

465 
00:42:54,371 --> 00:42:56,430 
This weekly class is 

466 
00:42:56,540 --> 00:42:58,508 
'Wonder Boys'! 

467 
00:42:58,509 --> 00:43:02,275 
Congratulations, this is the first time we 
I fight this music ... 

468 
00:43:10,454 --> 00:43:12,217 
PD Pob! 

469 
00:43:12,523 --> 00:43:14,286 
Long time no see! 

470 
00:43:19,263 --> 00:43:20,230 
So 

471 
00:43:21,231 --> 00:43:22,391 
This problem which says 

472 
00:43:22,533 --> 00:43:24,262 
If you want to solve 

473 
00:43:24,368 --> 00:43:26,233 
For those who always flies disrupt bu 

474 
00:43:26,337 --> 00:43:28,237 
As such there, good! 

475 
00:43:36,480 --> 00:43:37,412 
Wait now? 

476 
00:43:48,459 --> 00:43:51,428 
Well, he said the problem in the set not you? 

477 
00:43:52,262 --> 00:43:53,422 
How could you? 

478 
00:43:53,497 --> 00:43:57,331 
The reason why 'Star Music' to do so is because they ... 

479 
00:43:57,434 --> 00:43:58,458 
Hello? 

480 
00:44:01,405 --> 00:44:03,339 
Why give up halfway through you? It is 

481 
00:44:03,474 --> 00:44:05,499 
What it does with me then? 
. 

482 
00:44:06,310 --> 00:44:08,278 
It is, hello, big brother? 

483 
00:44:08,512 --> 00:44:10,412 
First she was the Goo PD 

484 
00:44:10,514 --> 00:44:13,278 
Park Sang-Sik-I will confirm that! 

485 
00:44:13,350 --> 00:44:15,375 
This ... hello? 

486 
00:44:17,521 --> 00:44:19,318 
Why bother in the middle off this? 

487 
00:44:19,323 --> 00:44:22,486 
The first kind is a waste management 
and rental office 

488 
00:44:23,360 --> 00:44:25,328 
I also spend all your cards all right! 

489 
00:44:25,429 --> 00:44:29,229 
Moreover this was, we did not 
How to sing again the club! 

490 
00:44:35,372 --> 00:44:36,304 
Hello? 

491 
00:44:36,540 --> 00:44:38,337 
Welcome him! Well? 

492 
00:44:38,509 --> 00:44:39,373 
Yes! 

493 
00:44:40,477 --> 00:44:43,344 
What that? Well yes! 

494 
00:44:44,314 --> 00:44:46,282 
Of course, not that! 

495 
00:44:48,318 --> 00:44:49,342 
No way! 

496 
00:44:52,489 --> 00:44:53,387 
Please wait while! 

497 
00:45:17,548 --> 00:45:19,243 
Because here 

498 
00:45:19,450 --> 00:45:21,281 
And push all the vehicles 

499 
00:45:21,452 --> 00:45:23,352 
Energy charge slightly more so? 

500 
00:45:25,522 --> 00:45:27,456 
The people now have been pushed 
eventually to the floor! 

501 
00:45:28,292 --> 00:45:30,351 
Tell him he was running, the 
run, told his cow, the cow! 

502 
00:45:32,296 --> 00:45:33,422 
Bang my pain! 

503 
00:45:37,468 --> 00:45:39,231 
Eat what the? 

504 
00:45:45,442 --> 00:45:47,501 
Long time no see! 

505 
00:45:48,378 --> 00:45:50,471 
Park Sang-Sik-taking means 
gas as well, but something to eat! 

506 
00:45:51,381 --> 00:45:53,246 
But he did not think to stop! 

507 
00:45:53,350 --> 00:45:55,215 
Yet again the long way here! 

508 
00:45:55,352 --> 00:45:56,341 
What to do there! 

509 
00:45:57,287 --> 00:45:58,447 
The girl next door that you dance? 

510 
00:46:00,390 --> 00:46:02,449 
Or is the girl singing along? 

511 
00:46:03,427 --> 00:46:04,416 
Where not? 

512 
00:46:05,262 --> 00:46:08,288 
This is the general manager 
Our processing 

513 
00:46:09,433 --> 00:46:12,493 
Sure she knew it then, before I 
under his hand to make a living here! 

514 
00:46:13,303 --> 00:46:14,327 
Manipulated à CEO? 

515 
00:46:15,239 --> 00:46:18,299 
I'm the director here, Hong-Ji-Dong 

516 
00:46:20,377 --> 00:46:21,401 
Is the name really! 

517 
00:46:44,468 --> 00:46:46,299 
The next item is 

518 
00:46:47,371 --> 00:46:48,429 
5 beautiful girls on stage 

519 
00:46:49,339 --> 00:46:51,500 
See who's fastest 

520 
00:46:53,243 --> 00:46:55,234 
As members 'Children' 
behind the excitement up! 

521 
00:46:55,379 --> 00:46:58,246 
Simple! Music emerged! 

522 
00:46:58,415 --> 00:47:01,248 
What then of his 'Children'? 

523 
00:47:01,485 --> 00:47:04,283 
Note that a bit lighter! 

524 
00:47:07,291 --> 00:47:11,227 
It is not know this brother 
be called 'Children' not here? 

525 
00:47:11,328 --> 00:47:12,454 
Sang-Sik, about you? 

526 
00:47:12,496 --> 00:47:14,396 
He said this was fake fool! 

527 
00:47:14,498 --> 00:47:16,295 
Keep on this mo! 

528 
00:47:16,400 --> 00:47:18,265 
The audience let you Nhe observation! 

529 
00:47:18,268 --> 00:47:20,236 
Continue back any! 

530 
00:47:20,270 --> 00:47:21,396 
Very good! 

531 
00:47:21,505 --> 00:47:24,440 
She probably does this give back? 

532 
00:47:24,441 --> 00:47:27,239 
Wanted to slap me or star casts? 

533 
00:47:27,344 --> 00:47:30,245 
Pour water over all people, all 
Then her body drenched! 

534 
00:47:30,280 --> 00:47:32,373 
Makes it startled there! 
I came to do something! 

535 
00:47:32,382 --> 00:47:34,373 
Do not! 

536 
00:47:34,418 --> 00:47:36,283 
It's refreshing! 

537 
00:47:36,286 --> 00:47:37,480 
I also wet the whole time! 

538 
00:47:37,487 --> 00:47:39,478 
Invite the vi 
. 

539 
00:47:39,523 --> 00:47:44,358 
In the last 7 seconds enthusiastically jump in! 

540 
00:47:59,543 --> 00:48:01,306 
Feels like 

541 
00:48:01,411 --> 00:48:03,276 
So my burning flesh! 

542 
00:48:06,250 --> 00:48:07,274 
Sort crazy! 

543 
00:48:11,388 --> 00:48:12,377 
I just 

544 
00:48:13,390 --> 00:48:16,359 
Smell the barbecue 
next, turning his head to see 

545 
00:48:18,462 --> 00:48:21,226 
Behind the discovery turns out to be the 

546 
00:48:22,366 --> 00:48:24,334 
But then 

547 
00:48:24,434 --> 00:48:26,231 
Please tell me a question 

548 
00:48:38,348 --> 00:48:40,407 
They have looked out from this incident 

549 
00:48:40,484 --> 00:48:43,282 
The electrical equipment in 
1 m radius around 

550 
00:48:44,354 --> 00:48:46,379 
For reality TV sex 
there is simply too much! 

551 
00:48:48,425 --> 00:48:49,483 
But at least 

552 
00:48:50,427 --> 00:48:52,486 
This is your first look up 
Our TV then! 

553 
00:49:13,450 --> 00:49:15,315 
Why in this place 

554 
00:49:15,419 --> 00:49:17,478 
The only resounded 'For Elise' 

555 
00:49:18,388 --> 00:49:20,322 
I like 'Wonder Boys' more 

556 
00:49:23,293 --> 00:49:25,454 
Over the two days before we see any? 

557 
00:49:29,433 --> 00:49:32,197 
Weeks after surgery, but we? 

558 
00:49:35,272 --> 00:49:37,467 
So I definitely told them over here? 

559 
00:49:38,275 --> 00:49:39,367 
Much he 

560 
00:49:46,450 --> 00:49:48,350 
So just take a look! 

561 
00:50:12,242 --> 00:50:14,437 
What is this? English about? 

562 
00:50:15,345 --> 00:50:16,334 
What face? 

563 
00:50:16,346 --> 00:50:18,405 
Asked a bunch of health 
not do well here? 

564 
00:50:18,515 --> 00:50:20,380 
Looks like your not a good thing? 

565 
00:50:23,320 --> 00:50:24,287 
Sorry! 

566 
00:50:24,521 --> 00:50:26,421 
Please be patient a little! 

567 
00:54:30,400 --> 00:54:32,300 
Leave school for game? 

568 
00:54:33,370 --> 00:54:34,359 
Or is that truancy? 

569 
00:54:34,471 --> 00:54:35,495 
Be a lunch break 

570 
00:54:38,441 --> 00:54:39,408 
It is wonderful 

571 
00:54:40,477 --> 00:54:41,466 
Great game? 

572 
00:54:42,512 --> 00:54:43,479 
Great 

573 
00:54:50,453 --> 00:54:52,353 
He then there is shaving away 

574 
00:54:53,456 --> 00:54:54,445 
No thank you 

575 
00:54:56,393 --> 00:54:57,360 
Why? 

576 
00:54:58,328 --> 00:55:00,489 
We can say it's the style of Rock 

577 
00:56:04,494 --> 00:56:06,359 
Please do not hit 

578 
00:56:07,330 --> 00:56:09,298 
When hit, we will not distinguish anyone 

579 
00:56:15,472 --> 00:56:16,496 
Dad 

580 
00:56:17,374 --> 00:56:19,308 
The reaction is too slow, we avoid floating 

581 
00:56:19,342 --> 00:56:20,502 
The dancing, but also what 

582 
00:56:21,311 --> 00:56:24,246 
At first there was talk of family that goes 
Shanghai travel guide out 

583 
00:56:25,348 --> 00:56:27,282 
If you still want to sing 

584 
00:56:27,450 --> 00:56:29,441 
Then from now on we will not 
This child also has another 

585 
00:56:43,299 --> 00:56:44,425 
Why does he just have to endure that? 

586 
00:56:47,337 --> 00:56:48,395 
Happened at 

587 
00:56:49,272 --> 00:56:50,330 
Can you give that 

588 
00:56:51,274 --> 00:56:52,366 
Just because 

589 
00:56:53,376 --> 00:56:54,434 
His dream 

590 
00:56:55,245 --> 00:56:56,269 
U dream? 

591 
00:56:58,314 --> 00:57:00,248 
Often, dreams will not 
true can be 

592 
00:57:11,361 --> 00:57:12,453 
This is how I show u? 

593 
00:57:14,297 --> 00:57:15,491 
Humans, not machines 

594 
00:57:25,375 --> 00:57:26,342 
I am a machine that 

595 
00:57:30,447 --> 00:57:32,244 
I've never been in love right? 

596 
00:57:34,451 --> 00:57:38,410 
When overseas, I used to love 

597 
00:57:39,322 --> 00:57:41,222 
At least 5 people 

598 
00:57:42,459 --> 00:57:44,256 
I understand, but 

599 
00:57:45,528 --> 00:57:47,257 
In summary 

600 
00:57:47,397 --> 00:57:48,455 
When you kiss someone 

601 
00:57:49,432 --> 00:57:52,299 
Are you will hear 
a certain tone? 

602 
00:57:55,371 --> 00:57:58,238 
If he continues like this, 
ensure that life will not do 

603 
00:58:04,380 --> 00:58:05,347 
Are you insane? 

604 
00:58:10,253 --> 00:58:11,311 
Why do not you feel that? 

605 
01:00:44,474 --> 01:00:45,406 
Tenacious 

606 
01:00:49,312 --> 01:00:52,304 
Day 31 - World War Ballad music 

607 
01:01:09,332 --> 01:01:12,324 
Such a system can do, so 
which also requires singing dancing 

608 
01:01:18,241 --> 01:01:19,333 
Just like these guys damaged 

609 
01:01:22,345 --> 01:01:24,210 
You see, it was announced ... 

610 
01:02:32,515 --> 01:02:34,380 
I have nothing more 

611 
01:02:35,518 --> 01:02:37,213 
I do remember my mother 

612 
01:02:39,322 --> 01:02:40,346 
Always like 

613 
01:02:43,326 --> 01:02:44,350 
Mother too 

614 
01:02:46,362 --> 01:02:47,454 
Miss you 

615 
01:02:50,433 --> 01:02:51,400 
Mother 

616 
01:03:18,494 --> 01:03:20,485 
It is a moving encounter 

617 
01:03:22,298 --> 01:03:23,356 
But such was not 

618 
01:03:28,304 --> 01:03:29,328 
If love really deep 

619 
01:03:30,339 --> 01:03:32,273 
Then a little crazy like that 
. 
This is also normal 

620 
01:03:35,511 --> 01:03:37,274 
I'm sorry 

621 
01:03:41,484 --> 01:03:43,247 
Sorry 

622 
01:04:04,407 --> 01:04:05,396 
What are you doing? 

623 
01:04:07,543 --> 01:04:09,340 
Others where 

624 
01:04:13,282 --> 01:04:15,307 
sick things, why not call 
children, or go to hospital but 

625 
01:04:16,385 --> 01:04:17,511 
Where his limbs? 

626 
01:04:18,354 --> 01:04:19,446 
Are you a child where 

627 
01:04:20,389 --> 01:04:21,447 
Never mind that 

628 
01:04:40,443 --> 01:04:42,206 
Let me see what 

629 
01:04:43,446 --> 01:04:45,346 
I do not know how to explode? 

630 
01:04:47,483 --> 01:04:48,450 
I do not 

631 
01:04:49,485 --> 01:04:51,510 
I do not know what is allowed and 
not allowed to put in the microwave à? 

632 
01:04:52,421 --> 01:04:54,321 
To let him have the opportunity to show 
. . 

633 
01:04:58,327 --> 01:05:02,525 
At first he said he fed the scene 

634 
01:05:03,499 --> 01:05:05,399 
The dance song on TV 

635 
01:05:08,271 --> 01:05:09,431 
But recently 

636 
01:05:10,506 --> 01:05:12,269 
It seems very interested 

637 
01:05:12,408 --> 01:05:14,308 
Wait 

638 
01:05:15,244 --> 01:05:16,336 
Do not move 

639 
01:05:17,313 --> 01:05:18,405 
Will make your face hurt here 

640 
01:05:21,350 --> 01:05:23,477 
Actually, like sentences 
that people often say 

641 
01:05:25,354 --> 01:05:27,322 
Once you feel like or love 
then that would be something like 

642 
01:05:30,259 --> 01:05:31,248 
Containers moving 

643 
01:05:36,332 --> 01:05:37,390 
2 people are talking to u? 

644 
01:05:49,312 --> 01:05:50,279 
Are you busy? 

645 
01:05:52,248 --> 01:05:52,509 
I asked him u? 

646 
01:06:03,492 --> 01:06:04,481 
He wanted to ask 

647 
01:06:07,330 --> 01:06:08,456 
I like you really? 
. 

648 
01:06:10,299 --> 01:06:11,288 
Yes 

649 
01:06:14,537 --> 01:06:18,473 
We can not like that 

650 
01:06:20,309 --> 01:06:21,401 
I like you 

651 
01:06:22,278 --> 01:06:23,336 
As his fans 

652 
01:06:26,449 --> 01:06:27,473 
Is that so 

653 
01:06:32,321 --> 01:06:34,380 
So we, any 

654 
01:06:41,397 --> 01:06:42,386 
Very nice 

655 
01:06:43,332 --> 01:06:46,301 
In fact, he is the grandson of my fans 

656 
01:06:47,470 --> 01:06:48,494 
I thank 

657 
01:06:49,372 --> 01:06:51,533 
Thanks for nothing instead. He is to feel 
I have thanked the new right of picture with him chucp 

658 
01:06:54,410 --> 01:06:55,468 
Did you know? 

659 
01:06:56,412 --> 01:06:58,312 
He is very similar to Kim Ji-hoon 

660 
01:07:05,421 --> 01:07:06,388 
Like u? 

661 
01:07:52,468 --> 01:07:54,436 
My voice today 
not normal 

662 
01:07:56,505 --> 01:07:57,494 
I would start 

663 
01:08:18,394 --> 01:08:22,490 
It feels chaotic, with little 
something gross, insane 

664 
01:08:25,301 --> 01:08:26,268 
What? 

665 
01:08:26,368 --> 01:08:29,360 
But I can hear 
was his real voice 

666 
01:08:31,540 --> 01:08:33,405 
You can let him sing 

667 
01:08:34,410 --> 01:08:37,538 
Let everyone hear 
was his voice 

668 
01:08:58,267 --> 01:09:00,497 
Why did you turn off your phone? 
and left like that? 

669 
01:09:11,447 --> 01:09:12,414 
Why? 

670 
01:09:16,318 --> 01:09:18,252 
Because he saw it, so angry 

671 
01:09:18,454 --> 01:09:19,443 
Irrelevant to you both 

672 
01:09:20,289 --> 01:09:22,450 
No. Kim Ji-hoon has 
little concerned him 

673 
01:09:28,264 --> 01:09:29,356 
For me, Kim Ji-hoon is what? 

674 
01:09:30,399 --> 01:09:31,388 
What do you mean? 

675 
01:09:32,301 --> 01:09:33,495 
He is Kim Ji-hoon Lee Yoo-Jin or 

676 
01:09:35,471 --> 01:09:37,371 
I do like this to help 
I feel a little less 

677 
01:09:39,542 --> 01:09:41,510 
Want to use this to replace Kim 
Ji-hoon continue the dream of u? 

678 
01:09:42,311 --> 01:09:43,278 
You're crazy 

679 
01:09:43,412 --> 01:09:44,470 
Yes, he could be Kim Ji-hoon of children 

680 
01:09:44,513 --> 01:09:47,277 
He can sing, dance. 
I can do everything arranged 

681 
01:09:48,517 --> 01:09:50,348 
Will eventually die, right? 

682 
01:09:54,390 --> 01:09:55,448 
He wanted to know the truth? 

683 
01:09:56,358 --> 01:09:57,518 
I just need someone to stand 
his position 

684 
01:09:58,460 --> 01:10:00,428 
That he is the right time 
appropriate, so I do 

685 
01:10:00,529 --> 01:10:02,292 
Enough? 

686 
01:10:03,299 --> 01:10:05,324 
But you know what? 

687 
01:10:08,270 --> 01:10:09,498 
The thing that makes me most uncomfortable 
. 

688 
01:10:14,510 --> 01:10:16,341 
It was a while ago 

689 
01:10:18,314 --> 01:10:19,508 
She said if Kim Ji-hoon 

690 
01:10:24,286 --> 01:10:25,378 
Feeling 

691 
01:10:27,356 --> 01:10:29,256 
As I do not exist 

692 
01:10:39,501 --> 01:10:41,401 
Congratulations Mr Childen 
The No. 1 position this week 

693 
01:10:41,437 --> 01:10:42,404 
Congratulations Mr Childen 

694 
01:10:44,340 --> 01:10:48,276 
For 4 consecutive weeks, finally 
win the award and Ballad music 

695 
01:10:48,477 --> 01:10:52,277 
Childen congratulate Mr Kin, and we will again 
reachable enjoy 'Summer Dream' goodbye to replace b 

696 
01:10:52,381 --> 01:10:54,406 
Goodbye to you and you, 
appointment the following week you 

697 
01:11:57,546 --> 01:11:59,343 
I always can not sing well this paragraph 

698 
01:12:00,382 --> 01:12:02,407 
One time was not then the next time 
will not be, right? 

699 
01:12:06,255 --> 01:12:08,416 
I see she has put the rocker back 
Then the English elite 

700 
01:12:09,358 --> 01:12:11,326 
She did very well there, Goo-Joo Oh 

701 
01:12:12,361 --> 01:12:13,385 
He calls what I have that? 

702 
01:12:18,400 --> 01:12:20,334 
If we continue to apply, he will shine 

703 
01:12:20,469 --> 01:12:22,266 
She will not win me where 

704 
01:12:22,471 --> 01:12:23,403 
So why? 

705 
01:12:24,239 --> 01:12:25,365 
Although everything is now convenient 

706 
01:12:26,442 --> 01:12:28,376 
Of course, I mean group 'Wonder Boys' 

707 
01:12:29,478 --> 01:12:31,309 
Long-term survival is a very difficult 

708 
01:12:31,380 --> 01:12:33,439 
Did not you know best are u? 

709 
01:12:34,450 --> 01:12:39,251 
Was it because the guy 
This boy had never suffered? 

710 
01:12:40,322 --> 01:12:41,482 
The song is pretty lifeless 

711 
01:12:42,391 --> 01:12:44,382 
I recently prepared a team 

712 
01:12:44,493 --> 01:12:46,427 
She heard the vision 
strategies in the Rock yet? 

713 
01:12:47,463 --> 01:12:50,432 
Watch out, 'Mr Childen' 
difficult to adapt well 

714 
01:12:53,335 --> 01:12:55,303 
Give her time to think that 

715 
01:12:56,372 --> 01:12:58,340 
Indeed they are due to my training that 

716 
01:13:00,342 --> 01:13:02,503 
By doing just fine for 
her and 'Mr Childen' 

717 
01:13:04,313 --> 01:13:07,373 
But do not wait until the damage die 
we then find a cure 

718 
01:13:17,493 --> 01:13:21,429 
I can not give them to a person, even 
the microphone did not appreciate the 

719 
01:14:15,417 --> 01:14:16,475 
Yoo-Jin Lee 

720 
01:14:17,319 --> 01:14:19,253 
Please let me out little 

721 
01:14:19,521 --> 01:14:21,455 
Yoo-Jin Lee 

722 
01:14:28,363 --> 01:14:30,388 
Can be said is rubbish 

723 
01:14:31,300 --> 01:14:32,494 
I saw their minds only 
used to make jewelry 

724 
01:14:33,535 --> 01:14:35,503 
Music was created to not only 

725 
01:14:37,339 --> 01:14:39,330 
Compensate for the soul 
are painful 

726 
01:14:39,441 --> 01:14:41,272 
Social networks are 
This television clip together 

727 
01:14:41,343 --> 01:14:44,437 
The authorities are 
conducted to prevent it 

728 
01:14:44,480 --> 01:14:46,345 
Do not let it continue to spread 

729 
01:14:46,515 --> 01:14:48,278 
The responsibility for said television 

730 
01:14:48,417 --> 01:14:50,248 
Will cut the'' repertoire'' Mr Childen 

731 
01:14:52,421 --> 01:14:55,288 
At the same time 'Mr Childen' will not 
participate in next month 

732 
01:14:55,390 --> 01:14:57,449 
Ballad For music awards 
was void 

733 
01:14:58,327 --> 01:15:00,295 
Lee Yoo-Jin is the 
company's 'Champion' 

734 
01:15:00,395 --> 01:15:02,454 
No official voiced these Jobs 

735 
01:15:07,469 --> 01:15:11,462 
My ad revenue has decreased 

736 
01:15:12,341 --> 01:15:13,467 
Should be scolded for a match head 

737 
01:15:16,245 --> 01:15:18,338 
The larger the incredible 
Our object then 

738 
01:15:21,316 --> 01:15:22,374 
So this time 

739 
01:15:23,252 --> 01:15:25,379 
She should cancel operation 
and rest this week 

740 
01:15:25,420 --> 01:15:27,320 
Verifying the truth of that 

741 
01:15:28,290 --> 01:15:29,314 
I will solve all stories 

742 
01:15:31,393 --> 01:15:32,451 
Give me time 

743 
01:15:34,229 --> 01:15:35,253 
Goo-Joo Oh 

744 
01:15:38,367 --> 01:15:39,425 
Sorry 

745 
01:15:54,449 --> 01:15:55,507 
Goo-Joo, a little talk with me okay? 

746 
01:15:56,351 --> 01:15:57,318 
Everything will be fine 

747 
01:16:03,258 --> 01:16:03,485 
He said try 

748 
01:16:04,459 --> 01:16:05,483 
I do not do this 

749 
01:16:07,329 --> 01:16:08,296 
Really? 
. 

750 
01:16:08,397 --> 01:16:09,421 
So what is? 

751 
01:16:10,532 --> 01:16:13,365 
Proved to me that going 

752 
01:16:13,368 --> 01:16:15,268 
At that 

753 
01:16:17,539 --> 01:16:18,471 
Just me 

754 
01:16:19,274 --> 01:16:20,332 
Even now he say? 

755 
01:16:20,442 --> 01:16:22,307 
It will not change anything 

756 
01:16:32,287 --> 01:16:33,254 
Yoo-Jin Lee 

757 
01:16:34,289 --> 01:16:36,314 
Team which is fine 
shock of the school prayer 

758 
01:16:36,491 --> 01:16:38,425 
Back clip this controversial 

759 
01:16:39,361 --> 01:16:40,419 
Whether the cause Whatever 

760 
01:16:41,296 --> 01:16:43,264 
Only due to the folly of youth 

761 
01:16:43,365 --> 01:16:45,356 
Affect the crystal 
I fan 
. 

762 
01:16:45,434 --> 01:16:47,368 
Makes people angry 

763 
01:16:48,303 --> 01:16:49,327 
For this I have been here 

764 
01:16:50,405 --> 01:16:51,497 
Yoo-Jin Lee behalf apologize 

765 
01:16:52,341 --> 01:16:53,273 
Please ask questions 
. 

766 
01:16:53,508 --> 01:16:54,475 
There are questions 

767 
01:16:55,377 --> 01:16:56,435 
Please, Lee Yoo-Jin story 
withdrawal is that true? 

768 
01:16:57,379 --> 01:16:58,346 
Not 

769 
01:16:58,447 --> 01:17:00,438 
Please, story selection 
New members are true? 

770 
01:17:01,316 --> 01:17:02,374 
Just edit the text only 

771 
01:17:02,451 --> 01:17:04,248 
So the members of the group 
How to face this? 

772 
01:17:04,453 --> 01:17:07,479 
Jio has ever heard of causing 
of violence in America? 

773 
01:17:08,357 --> 01:17:10,348 
And 2 times by 'behavior' in the country? 

774 
01:17:11,259 --> 01:17:13,318 
Ricky has two international criminal acts 
citizenship, and illegal immigration? 

775 
01:17:13,462 --> 01:17:16,522 
Hyun-Yi made girlfriend 
pregnant, right? 

776 
01:17:17,332 --> 01:17:19,493 
This is a shift from prior 
establishment of group members 

777 
01:17:20,302 --> 01:17:23,271 
If the truth 

778 
01:17:23,372 --> 01:17:26,307 
What he has ways to help 
them through this 

779 
01:17:27,275 --> 01:17:28,503 
The fans are very angry 

780 
01:17:29,311 --> 01:17:32,280 
For the multitude found in cognitive 
goods of group members 

781 
01:17:32,447 --> 01:17:34,312 
I think that Social Matters 
Assembly to pay special attention 

782 
01:17:35,317 --> 01:17:37,410 
Spirit is not entertainment 
is to improve lives 

783 
01:17:37,519 --> 01:17:39,248 
Let me make a sentence 

784 
01:17:39,354 --> 01:17:40,412 
Word of journalists said 

785 
01:17:40,522 --> 01:17:41,454 
It seems a bit too 

786 
01:17:42,290 --> 01:17:43,314 
I agree 

787 
01:17:44,326 --> 01:17:45,418 
That what he says is true 

788 
01:17:48,230 --> 01:17:51,199 
So 'Mr Childen' started singing 

789 
01:17:52,367 --> 01:17:55,495 
Because they can do, 
only for this reason alone 

790 
01:17:57,239 --> 01:18:01,198 
Singing, dancing to alleviate the 
suffering in life 

791 
01:18:01,510 --> 01:18:03,341 
Realizing the Dream 

792 
01:18:03,512 --> 01:18:05,480 
Her words fit in 
press conference today u? 

793 
01:18:06,448 --> 01:18:08,245 
Sing 100 thousand times 

794 
01:18:08,417 --> 01:18:10,282 
It can not be reversed 

795 
01:18:10,485 --> 01:18:12,248 
But at least 

796 
01:18:12,454 --> 01:18:14,422 
They have devoted their 
while singing, dancing at 

797 
01:18:15,457 --> 01:18:21,327 
Of what, things can not save 
courtship before u think of a cure? 

798 
01:18:21,430 --> 01:18:23,364 
Do you know you're saying? 

799 
01:18:25,400 --> 01:18:26,458 
All the fault of me? 

800 
01:18:27,302 --> 01:18:28,269 
The people are really 

801 
01:18:28,437 --> 01:18:29,369 
Enough 

802 
01:18:33,442 --> 01:18:34,431 
Yoo-Jin 

803 
01:18:38,447 --> 01:18:40,347 
Things like this are why I 

804 
01:18:42,250 --> 01:18:43,342 
Was my fault 

805 
01:18:44,419 --> 01:18:46,319 
Causing damage to other members 

806 
01:18:46,455 --> 01:18:48,320 
If the latter is not 
Standing on a stage 

807 
01:18:50,292 --> 01:18:51,452 
I would withdraw from the 'Mr Childen' 

808 
01:19:00,302 --> 01:19:02,429 
British official withdrawal now u? 

809 
01:19:02,504 --> 01:19:04,369 
After leaving the group, he has 
do not intend to Yoo-Jin? 

810 
01:19:04,406 --> 01:19:05,373 
He will definitely do so right? 

811 
01:19:05,373 --> 01:19:07,341 
Maybe he does not think 
the remaining members? 

812 
01:19:08,410 --> 01:19:09,342 
Yoo-Jin 

813 
01:19:10,312 --> 01:19:11,279 
Yoo-Jin 

814 
01:19:11,446 --> 01:19:12,378 
Yoo-Jin 

815 
01:19:14,349 --> 01:19:15,475 
Now he is very worried right? 

816 
01:19:29,531 --> 01:19:32,261 
'Wonder Boys' and then sell 
more than 300 thousand disk 

817 
01:19:32,367 --> 01:19:34,335 
Bring life to rock 

818 
01:19:34,503 --> 01:19:36,494 
This afternoon they held a banquet at 

819 
01:19:38,306 --> 01:19:39,432 
'Wonder Boys' and ... 

820 
01:20:03,431 --> 01:20:04,398 
What did you have here? 

821 
01:20:05,300 --> 01:20:06,289 
Seafood Pasta 

822 
01:20:16,244 --> 01:20:17,211 
I feel a little hard 

823 
01:20:17,512 --> 01:20:18,444 
That delicious 

824 
01:20:26,521 --> 01:20:28,284 
Later I to do? 

825 
01:20:29,357 --> 01:20:30,483 
Everyone knows the children and 

826 
01:20:31,493 --> 01:20:33,256 
Can do? 

827 
01:20:35,397 --> 01:20:37,331 
Did not like the plan announced 
redundant pub this? 

828 
01:20:41,403 --> 01:20:43,496 
Look at her face this time, I 
delicious bread that is strange 

829 
01:20:45,307 --> 01:20:47,400 
Want to make good food, before 
First try to keep a smile on the face scad 

830 
01:20:47,509 --> 01:20:50,307 
How new is doing well, 
other things too 

831 
01:20:52,514 --> 01:20:54,345 
But must laugh up 

832 
01:20:57,352 --> 01:21:00,219 
Children who eat it do so, 
feel happy to 

833 
01:21:00,322 --> 01:21:01,289 
See delicious 

834 
01:21:01,423 --> 01:21:03,482 
Parents and children laughed to see how 

835 
01:21:11,366 --> 01:21:13,300 
Mirror must laugh 

836 
01:22:37,452 --> 01:22:39,249 
After deciding to leave 

837 
01:22:40,488 --> 01:22:42,251 
He chose this place u? 

838 
01:22:44,392 --> 01:22:45,416 
I want to ask you a question? 

839 
01:22:47,329 --> 01:22:50,492 
Later still want to join 
'Mr Childen' again? 

840 
01:22:52,434 --> 01:22:53,458 
Place this 

841 
01:22:55,337 --> 01:22:56,395 
It fit him 

842 
01:22:57,405 --> 01:22:58,497 
He did not want to 
I dream of u? 
. 

843 
01:23:00,408 --> 01:23:01,397 
yes 

844 
01:23:02,377 --> 01:23:03,469 
He continued that 

845 
01:23:04,379 --> 01:23:05,505 
Now not anymore 

846 
01:23:08,383 --> 01:23:10,442 
Can not make anymore 

847 
01:23:31,473 --> 01:23:32,497 
Others go further that? 
. 

848 
01:23:34,442 --> 01:23:36,205 
She is not what u doing wrong? 

849 
01:23:38,513 --> 01:23:40,481 
I saw her get used to it now 

850 
01:23:41,316 --> 01:23:43,216 
Not true, is certainly 
poison, poison and then! 

851 
01:23:45,453 --> 01:23:46,420 
Goo-Joo! 

852 
01:23:47,522 --> 01:23:49,422 
None specified only 
be 'Mr. Children' at all! 

853 
01:23:52,327 --> 01:23:54,295 
Female group, why? 

854 
01:23:55,363 --> 01:23:57,297 
Let me sort, I write light music! 

855 
01:24:01,503 --> 01:24:06,497 
Singing also have to get someone hurt, I 
have hated this vicious cycle already! 

856 
01:24:09,444 --> 01:24:11,309 
Although no reason was forced to go 

857 
01:24:13,381 --> 01:24:15,440 
But there is no reason 
necessarily have to stay! 

858 
01:24:23,291 --> 01:24:24,258 
Would you drink a cup with me? 

859 
01:24:31,299 --> 01:24:32,266 
I have words to say! 
Do you want to say! 

860 
01:24:34,369 --> 01:24:35,393 
He said before going! 

861 
01:24:37,305 --> 01:24:39,500 
But our way 
I go not the same 

862 
01:24:40,341 --> 01:24:41,433 
But there seem to be the same place there 

863 
01:24:43,344 --> 01:24:46,472 
He wanted to say? 
Do not beat around the bush again, said straight away! 

864 
01:24:48,249 --> 01:24:49,307 
It is, I want to say is ... 

865 
01:24:53,388 --> 01:24:54,480 
We live them lighter! 

866 
01:24:56,324 --> 01:24:57,348 
He wants to die? 

867 
01:24:58,293 --> 01:25:00,386 
Maybe, he died for you to see! 

868 
01:25:02,263 --> 01:25:03,491 
Even told me to death. 
I also want to live with you 

869 
01:25:38,299 --> 01:25:39,323 
You're listening eh, Yoo Jin 

870 
01:25:41,469 --> 01:25:43,437 
Hopefully he is not vi 
I sing this without 

871 
01:25:44,239 --> 01:25:46,332 
Just a bit of anger 
that leaves this song 

872 
01:25:48,343 --> 01:25:49,401 
I know more now 

873 
01:25:50,278 --> 01:25:51,472 
He also began 
listen then gradually 

874 
01:25:53,448 --> 01:25:55,313 
Let's add a song to start again 

875 
01:25:56,284 --> 01:25:57,444 
Do not be regarded as being at my side 

876 
01:25:58,486 --> 01:26:01,353 
But I still hope if he 
This song is good too 

877 
01:26:02,457 --> 01:26:04,288 
Yoo Jin, you do 
This is how this 

878 
01:26:06,394 --> 01:26:07,361 
Yoo Jin à 

879 
01:26:09,464 --> 01:26:11,364 
Go away, go away quickly 

880 
01:26:13,268 --> 01:26:14,496 
She must be waiting for me back k 

881 
01:26:35,423 --> 01:26:36,390 
Yoo Jin is back 

882 
01:26:36,524 --> 01:26:39,391 
Brother, where Yoo Jin then? 

883 
01:26:40,461 --> 01:26:41,450 
Others where 

884 
01:26:42,430 --> 01:26:45,524 
Others well, are free ... 

885 
01:26:46,301 --> 01:26:48,235 
I certainly did not know where to go then 

886 
01:26:48,336 --> 01:26:49,360 
Goo Joo to the airport and 

887 
01:26:50,471 --> 01:26:51,403 
The ... 
. 

888 
01:26:55,443 --> 01:26:58,378 
Yoo-jin ah, what's wrong 

889 
01:26:58,446 --> 01:27:01,244 
This is the courier of Goo Joo Oh 

890 
01:27:01,416 --> 01:27:02,383 
Goo Joo à 

891 
01:27:04,285 --> 01:27:08,278 
No. 482-21, Yan Hau Park Lane, Bell Road, into 
Second City 'champion music' Oh Goo Joo. Received 

892 
01:27:15,330 --> 01:27:16,228 
Let me out 

893 
01:27:16,431 --> 01:27:17,363 
Sang Sik 

894 
01:27:22,337 --> 01:27:25,329 
The ... question want to die 
. . 

895 
01:27:25,473 --> 01:27:28,465 
If you leave my hand, I'm dead sure 

896 
01:27:29,277 --> 01:27:30,437 
Mau let me out 

897 
01:27:33,381 --> 01:27:34,348 
Su Yin à 

898 
01:27:35,350 --> 01:27:36,374 
Please help me one time he let go 

899 
01:27:41,289 --> 01:27:42,483 
Yoo-jin Well, I will call 
some other guy to 

900 
01:27:43,291 --> 01:27:44,349 
Should he be given 
Oh, you know PD based DC 

901 
01:27:44,459 --> 01:27:46,484 
War folk songs, sunset 
mucus night festival, you know? 

902 
01:28:16,257 --> 01:28:17,224 
You are here to do something like 

903 
01:30:20,281 --> 01:30:21,248 
Normally the 

904 
01:30:21,482 --> 01:30:24,508 
There was little disorder, there is nothing negative balance 
both, it makes people tired 

905 
01:30:26,421 --> 01:30:27,445 
Even very ordinary 

906 
01:30:41,436 --> 01:30:42,494 
Where is my motorcycle 

907 
01:30:53,481 --> 01:30:55,244 
Understand the Nhe 

908 
01:31:07,528 --> 01:31:08,426 
View this 

909 
01:31:15,436 --> 01:31:17,427 
Do you have comments about this file 
proving the spirit of the 

910 
01:31:18,306 --> 01:31:19,295 
spirit of the intelligence gathering game 

911 
01:31:19,540 --> 01:31:21,508 
Make me do the most 
I do not do the 

912 
01:31:23,277 --> 01:31:25,438 
he has an idea of ​​what works 
others were the products of 

913 
01:31:27,248 --> 01:31:28,408 
Personally I see them only 
as garbage time 

914 
01:31:29,350 --> 01:31:30,317 
Star garbage 

915 
01:31:32,386 --> 01:31:34,217 
It is even just a little so 

916 
01:31:34,422 --> 01:31:35,480 
This despicable behavior and then exposed 

917 
01:31:36,457 --> 01:31:38,391 
Making music is not of 

918 
01:31:39,327 --> 01:31:40,385 
Comforted the sorrowful soul star 

919 
01:31:41,329 --> 01:31:42,353 
It seems he is too honest 

920 
01:31:44,265 --> 01:31:45,357 
Hard for you as it is, the next question 

921 
01:31:45,466 --> 01:31:49,334 
Show Show Show Time Now 
Show time program 

922 
01:31:50,338 --> 01:31:52,329 
Hello everyone, 
we are 'brave girls' 

923 
01:31:56,377 --> 01:31:59,244 
Today, we came here for 
to enjoy the show this hectic 

924 
01:31:59,347 --> 01:32:00,336 
Today people would be told only a 

925 
01:32:00,448 --> 01:32:01,506 
Today we are happy 
I was trying to 

926 
01:32:02,283 --> 01:32:03,409 
We are 'wonder boys' 

927 
01:32:10,324 --> 01:32:11,291 
Brother, where they 

928 
01:32:12,460 --> 01:32:13,324 
He is 

929 
01:32:14,262 --> 01:32:15,286 
As a newcomer to trot back 

930 
01:32:15,396 --> 01:32:19,389 
No. I represent Park 
Sang Sik's 'champion music' 

931 
01:32:20,301 --> 01:32:21,393 
Yoo-Jin Lee clear 

932 
01:32:22,503 --> 01:32:24,266 
Assume that the video 

933 
01:32:24,505 --> 01:32:26,302 
Being out after the release has been modified 

934 
01:32:26,541 --> 01:32:27,439 
So today 

935 
01:32:29,310 --> 01:32:31,335 
I want people to see Mr Children 

936 
01:32:31,445 --> 01:32:33,276 
Will the great clarity 
return to stage 

937 
01:32:35,383 --> 01:32:37,317 
It turns out that such 

938 
01:32:37,485 --> 01:32:39,248 
So he finally invited 

939 
01:32:39,320 --> 01:32:40,287 
Say a few words 

940 
01:32:43,424 --> 01:32:44,322 
People 

941 
01:32:44,458 --> 01:32:45,447 
Why not get the phone rather 

942 
01:32:46,294 --> 01:32:48,455 
Jio, Hyun Yi, Rickey 

943 
01:32:49,430 --> 01:32:50,362 
Both Yoo Jin more 

944 
01:32:50,498 --> 01:32:52,295 
Go through this color dress 

945 
01:32:52,400 --> 01:32:55,335 
Where now is not too late, driving time 
big deal now, straining not to start the car 

946 
01:32:55,469 --> 01:32:56,436 
Take the train through here 

947 
01:32:56,537 --> 01:32:58,300 
Hurry up, hurry up there is bound to 

948 
01:32:58,439 --> 01:32:59,371 
I said then done 

949 
01:32:59,540 --> 01:33:01,337 
Very well then, it's finally time 

950 
01:34:21,288 --> 01:34:23,313 
Still have not come back 

951 
01:34:32,299 --> 01:34:33,357 
This ladder 

952 
01:34:34,368 --> 01:34:35,335 
The view goes 
. 

953 
01:34:35,403 --> 01:34:36,392 
If they do not like 5 minutes to 

954 
01:34:37,271 --> 01:34:38,329 
I would not be indicative of 
valid anymore 

955 
01:34:46,313 --> 01:34:48,213 
Only ... only 1 star only 

956 
01:34:50,251 --> 01:34:51,309 
Hyun Yi 

957 
01:34:52,353 --> 01:34:53,320 
For train travel 

958 
01:34:53,454 --> 01:34:54,421 
Parties should be delayed a ... 
. . 

959 
01:34:56,490 --> 01:34:58,355 
Rickey 

960 
01:36:20,274 --> 01:36:20,501 
He will not come back 

961 
01:36:22,443 --> 01:36:23,307 
Which would be likely to 

962 
01:36:24,411 --> 01:36:25,309 
Which would be likely to 

963 
01:36:27,348 --> 01:36:28,440 
But before coming to the end that 

964 
01:36:55,509 --> 01:36:56,476 
Representative Park 

965 
01:36:58,245 --> 01:36:58,506 
He was joking 

966 
01:37:09,290 --> 01:37:10,222 
Only ones left on their 

967 
01:37:10,457 --> 01:37:12,220 
On stage to try 

968 
01:37:15,496 --> 01:37:17,259 
Nothing other than singing the whole 

969 
01:38:04,311 --> 01:38:05,505 
Space is now raising the 

970 
01:38:06,413 --> 01:38:07,505 
'Wonder Boys' list any real damage to transmission 

971 
01:38:08,382 --> 01:38:09,246 
Here 

972 
01:38:09,383 --> 01:38:11,351 
Please invite a new group 

973 
01:38:11,518 --> 01:38:13,349 
Also the new wind 

974 
01:38:13,520 --> 01:38:15,283 
It turns out that this group 

975 
01:38:15,422 --> 01:38:17,322 
Yes, please Mr Children 

976 
01:38:17,391 --> 01:38:18,323 
Summer dream 

977 
01:38:32,539 --> 01:38:33,471 
Hello people 

978 
01:38:35,342 --> 01:38:37,276 
I'm Lee Yoo Jin group Mr Children 

979 
01:38:40,247 --> 01:38:41,509 
I think to talk to a few 

980 
01:38:43,417 --> 01:38:45,385 
I teams from the good old sing song that comes up 

981 
01:38:47,254 --> 01:38:48,380 
In addition to the music industry 

982 
01:38:49,356 --> 01:38:50,414 
Nor is this 

983 
01:38:51,492 --> 01:38:52,390 
Done 

984 
01:38:54,428 --> 01:38:56,225 
I now know 

985 
01:38:57,398 --> 01:38:59,298 
When I sing, if 
can feel good 

986 
01:39:00,267 --> 01:39:01,427 
Everyone must 
happy 

987 
01:39:03,270 --> 01:39:04,294 
That is the real music 

988 
01:39:06,273 --> 01:39:07,399 
I understand the moral of this 

989 
01:39:09,276 --> 01:39:10,504 
For the members of Mr Children 

990 
01:39:12,513 --> 01:39:15,243 
With one more person, and adds 
1 again to this place 

991 
01:43:41,548 --> 01:43:43,311 
Video of Lee Yoo Jin 

992 
01:43:43,383 --> 01:43:45,374 
It is because he do 

993 
01:43:45,485 --> 01:43:46,474 
Could you comment on this incident 

994 
01:43:47,287 --> 01:43:47,514 
Really 
. 

995 
01:43:48,455 --> 01:43:49,479 
All of the truth 

996 
01:43:51,358 --> 01:43:52,484 
I announced at the procuracy and 

997 
01:43:56,496 --> 01:43:59,329 
He did not want to say please 
Lee Yoo Jin error with stars 

998 
01:43:59,433 --> 01:44:02,300 
Repeatedly said, when she 
music for my team here 

999 
01:44:02,502 --> 01:44:03,400 
This 

1000 
01:44:04,504 --> 01:44:06,369 
See how the expression of the sentence 
. . 

1001 
01:44:07,307 --> 01:44:09,366 
What expression but, ultimately 
but when new 

1002 
01:44:09,443 --> 01:44:10,432 
Huh want to die 

1003 
01:44:13,447 --> 01:44:14,471 
To keep him docile 
in my suitcase 

1004 
01:44:49,483 --> 01:44:52,452 
Does anyone not ... I just had a 
went into this suitcase 
