BODEGA BAY INN
Hey!
How are you doing there?
- Uh, doing great! It's going to work.
- Very good, dude!
Many of those chair for, though,
wedding reception tomorrow, right?
- Are you ready?
- Yeah, I'll be ready.
- Everything OK, Danny?
- Yeah.
It's kind of just ... uh...
You know, the same with the party upstair.
It sounds like fun.
Groups of soldiers shipping out tomorrow morning.
They deserve to have some fun
the last night here.
It will sound as gone with me!
I know you do, my boy, I know!
- Not everybody's concern!
- Yeah, it's not fair!
You'll be claimed for the debt toll you didn't....
review us more than a wealth,
for a while they're not as such you're going to making.
- It's time that we say "hadn't".
- Gosh, don't mean that!
Take a look at what was the values of your mother and your brother, huh!
But now all I am is a useless cripple.
A useless forehand cripple!
Useless?
What if this kind is going to shift, Danny?
As a gift!
Watch work you can do with you hands.
Yeah, but if I really have a rifle in my hands,
- going after the Jap. for the crowd!
- I know!
Is Mr. Toulon still staying here?
He did his room upstairs.
Wonderful old man!
Ah, he was an Europe, you know.
He was fighting for Nazi.
Now, that what he said,
but sometimes I think he's prone to talk tails.
No, Uncle Len, it's true.
You know, the Nazi killed his wife,
because he did some puppet show
that was making fun of Hitler.
Mr. Toulon said the Nazi want to steal his puppets.
So now he even have
a special hiding place,
so they don't fall in the wrong hands.
Now, why would the Nazi want to kill his puppets?
Because he has a secret.
He can make them move without the strings.
- Oh, I'm sorry!
- No, uncle Len, it's true, really!  I've seen it.
You know, he said
he might even teach me how he does it.
We'll come to think of it,
maybe he has some works for you.
Well, maybe you can help him with those puppets such as repairing them, picking them up,
that source of things.
Ever thought of that?
I guess you're right.
I suppose I can ask him.
Oh, you should!
Perhaps when you're done over here,
I'm not going to have any work for you.
Not for a while, anyway!
And you know if I work for Mr. Tulong,
I can stay here longer,
- and send the money to my mom.
- I know your mother,
she'd to see you again, as she misses you.
- And so is your brother.
- Yeah, I know.
I miss them, too.
But...  But you don't want to couch up here
with your own lovely, huh?
Well, you rather be oversea fighting.
Hopefully the war will be over soon,
then we wouldn't need to fight anymore.
But I want you to get your work back, Danny.
I'll tell the cook have dinner prepared for you in the kitchen when you're done, huh!
How about a nice steak, some asparagus?
- How would that be, huh?
- Thank you, Uncle Len.
Okay!
Mr. Tulong?
Are you all right?
Oh, my God!
PUPPET MASTER
Axis of Evil
What the devil!
- Danny!
- Mom!
- Oh, oh!
- It's great to see you!
I didn't think you're be back till next week.
- Your uncle Lenny said...
- Oh, yeah! We finihsed so early.
What's all this?
Oh, just stuff that I'm working on.
- Oh, I'll take care of this one in my room.
- Oh, leave it!
Let me have a look at you.
I wear, you're getting taller.
Mom, I've already been gone for three weeks.
But for sure you lost weight.
Sit down!  Let me have some food in here off-
Ahh, let me take the stuff to my room first.
Nonsense!
Leave it!
Sit down, I'll take care of a quick one.
- Look out!
- Come on!
God!  You know I'll sneak upon you!
- Oh, how the hell are you, little brother?
- I'm good.
Did uncle Len spoiled you, got
the 20 years old Scotchie, Kid?
Ay, come on!
You know I didn't get any Scotch.
What?
Oh, that right!
You are a noble teen, man!
Ah, very funny!
- You look good!
- Yeah, I didn't think you're still be home.
Don't ship out another week.
- You know where you are going yet?
- No, not yet!
I hope it's not Japan.
It looks like the reserved already!
- And?
- So I ran on all outside, by the Splatty Isle.
Well,  our own heart, Donny, there is Chinese, not Japanese.
Oh, what's the difference?
For they've never given us a lot of trouble
in all the years we've been here.
Yeah, well, after the war, I am to make enough of money to get you out the China Town, Mom.
I'm hoping that they'll send me to Eroupe.
- Wow, good cherry!
-  Yeah, look at my hands on them.
Hurry up!
it's cold over there now, though.
It's going to free my ass off!
- Then you get to watch out the frenzy tank today,
- Oh, yeah!
I am not talking about the war.
What else should I talk about?
How about baseball, or
the nice weather we are having?
Mom, come on!
The war is what matter right now.
I just don't like to think about it.
That's all !
Little idea, if one of my boys
getting hurt over there....
I'll be OK, Mom!
God willing!
Talking now,
I would have going there with you, right?
I know, little brother.
Think about what would do to Mom.
I know the Mitchels on the street,
they got 3 boys serving.
Two in France, and one in Japan.
Yeah, Dan, have you seen Mrs Mitchel latetly?
Look like she waits 30 years.
You can't do that to Mom.
Our mom can handle it better than
Mts. Mitchell.
Yeah, look, what's your idea?
- Nothing, Mom!
- Two in the brink
- Oh, no!  No!
I don't want to be stuck here.
Uh, I love you, Mom, but...
I should be shooting a count-a-thon,
and I'll be going to serve,
because I'm not a God dammed cripple!
- Danny!
- Well, it's true.
Well, you may think your leg a curse,
but to me it's a blessing.
It keeps you home with me
and away from harm.
Now, the only reason known to talk about,
I'll till go other there and fight.
- I know I could.
- Oh, honey!
Nobody says you can't, Dan.
Just...
wait the ball bounce.
You have to do what you can,
from here in the home front.
Now like what?
Sewing furniture?
Come on, may I not stick to the axes, all right?
No, no!  Now I think you got something.
Why don't you ... uh...
build a special chair...
for Hitler?
He goes to sit down, and... whem!
Be here to right in with that!
Don!
You think he can make this thing
moving out street?
I saw it.
Must be some source of cheap magic chock-full.
I don't know.
There is nothing cheap about it.
You know, that's why he can kill himself.
'Cause he didn't like to
hand over the secret to the Nazi.
Nazi?
Come on!  You tell me...
that Nazi makes the trip all the way here...
to take some little puppet from an old man?
Half the world far even for fast eagle, buddy!
How smart!
It's not the puppet that they wanted.
It's just the secret of
whatever makes them move.
As well, I think you've been reading
too many of those faults.
Ah!
What's this?
I'll look.
Since it seems to take so long to repair.
Oh-ho!
Six arms, huh?
That's all we need to get the crown.
Hey, dare you, dirty Nazi!
I don't even need a gun to kill those bastards.
You know how great I am
in sneaking up to people?
Uh, point is you're up to remind me.
You know, I stay my short
when you get me up earlier.
Ah, to big to meet the Japan?
I need my skill,
sneak up all those Jap in the jungle.
Yeah, I bet you would.
Hey, today I do double deal downtown tonight,
you want to go?
Ahh, I don't know.
I think I might stay and look on the puppets.
Come on, forget the puppets.
They are not going anywhere.
Let's have some fun together,
I'm only here another week.
Call up that cute girl of your,
what her name?
- Beth.
- Beth, she the dame, huh!
Hey, have her bring her sister.
She gets one.
All right!
Yes?
We are looking for Rose in Vermont.
My master is dead.
It is a dramatic chapter to me.
A woman?
You stomach must be refreshing.
I will defy again, using your weapon.
Do we here a contact to Thomas,
what happened to him?
As you know, Thomas was a traitor as an American,
a fascist seems the fact,
a big columnist,
until aligns himself with the German.
Such as youself.
As well as the Japanese.
However, the treachery is sent to those
he align himself with.
When he  betrays him,
in a sense matter,
well, he met with the unfortunate end.
I have taken over his plan to strike...
to the heart of the American war efforts.
We're going through today, if you wish.
Or, you may leave, unharmed.
That's nice, because it easily takes over
the plan to you.
You mean, if you kill me and my men,
or more likely, we will kill each other,
while purpose was that ... uh...
the German and the Japanese are not friend?
Yet, we share our common enemy.
Perhaps we can work together.
Sake?
We're making the American blind bleed.
Let me ask you something.
Why is a Japanese woman and I had beautiful Japanese woman that night...
hiding in an opera house in the heart of China Town?
There are several places
for a Japanese to hide.
Americans can't tell any of us apart, anyway.
For English is very practice,
very commuting,
they have to do something with their head.
But it might work.
Yeah, it might just work.
Oh, there is a hole?
Oh! No, Beth!
You're waiting right now?
I can!
My lunch is almost still, right?
Sorry!
Offer it,
or resale something to eat?
Not really, I am sorry, Beth.
Now I just got to work on most puppet things.
and I lost such a time.
May be, you came out with something
that might remain in wood,
- like Pinokio, huh?.
- Don't be silly!
What's this?
Beth,
anybody I should be worry about?
He is just one of the guys in the florist,
thanks me for getting of our sub-sprouts.
Are you sure that all?
Do I see your nose growing like Pinokio?
Here's my man,
and you know it's Danny Coogan.
See?
All that you do is
playing around with puppets, huh?
That's your excuse, Coogan?
Hello, Mr. Gifford!
Delayed for your lunch paid,
to get playing around with puppet?
No, I didn't come on that.
I'll say this,
You learn your lesson soon enough,
if some quicker guy comes to the draw,
Delayed for your lunch paid,
to get playing around with puppet?
Yeah, I know.
She got fixed lunch hour, Danny Coogan.
I'm trying to run a plan.
I am doing something for the war.
What happens if my invoices...
don't get by the money my secretary
feels over from the starvation?
It's OK, Mr. Gifford.
Really, I don't mind.
Yeah, while I do!
I don't like you, Coogan.
Young guys like you should be out
fighting in the war,
not playing with the stupid pups.
Well, I would be fighting till I get hurt,
I want to be fighting, but I can't,
because of my legs, OK?
Stop pall it!
The First World War,
I was 15,
I lied about my age
so I shipped over to the France...
to fight for my country.
So, stop winning about your god dammed legs.
Why you-
Yeah, you're going to think twice, Coogan.
Look as you have your girl here,
to save your ass.
Huh, she's doing more
for the country than you are.
You get 10 more minutes, Beth.
You have some sake for him.
Don't mind him, Danny,
forget what he's talking about!
Yeah, he does!
What do you mean?
He is right,
I should be over there fighting.
But your legs...
I shouldn't lie, like he did.
You know, I should find some way around it intead of sitting around here...
feeling sorry for myself.
Danny, so?
Look, honey,
I'll see you later, OK!
Had jerk keep her invite about that!
No, she's not going to
wait for a guy like me.
If I were a great girl like that
I won't be with a cripple anyway.
She, as far as I bet, have some guy to plan.
Probably some guy with big muscles
and really handsome.
Some guy is going to do with some
of the plans and go over and serve.
Some guy like that even...
Look at me!
There's a war going on out there...
and I am stuck here talking about
the stupid puppets,
all because of the dammed leg.
Spirit of the 16 nights out!
Oh, my God!
You are alive!
You got to be quiet, OK?
Looking of surprise her!
Look, I'm going to be on time for lunch.
Can you beleive it?
You get to be still now, alright?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Hey, Honey!
Wow, you're right on time for lunch.
Let me call Riffley in.\\\
- Who was that guy?
- Who?
This guy, who was just in here.
Who was that?
That's Ben, I've told you before.
He's one of the guys who work in the florist.
He just needs someone to talk for sometimes.
That's all!
- Well-
- Is there anything you jealous worry about it?
For that you didn't know that his name isn't Ben.
What are you talking about?
Your friend, one of the guys who killed
Mr. Toulon at the end of a couple week ago.
Remember, I've told you about it?
Yeah, but...Ben?
His name isn't Ben.
He's a Nazi.
It sounds ridiculous!
I saw his face, Beth!
He bumped into me while
I'm going to help Mr. Toulon.
He looks a little bit different, but
that's definitely him.  I'm sure of it.
Ben, a Nazi?
you're being paranoid, Honey!
I am not being paranoid!
All of the papers are in order,
I check them myself..
Besides, he's not from Germany, silly.
He's from Burbank, for heaven sake!
- What's wrong with that?
- Nothing.
What is if it matter?
You don't believe me anyway.
Danny, don't feel like that!
Come one, just show me!
- I'll see the Nazi, and I will prove it to you.
- Danny!
Hey, Ben!
Cooken Dagen's going on the way to see you.
No, I got to go with Sank Luis.
Gosh, you got to be kidding me.
- What if Rommy goes down?
- Ahh, we'll see about that.
- Mega interested?
- Oh, lets talk tomorrow.
Yeah, yeah!
I'll see you tonight.
Hi Hitler!
I knows it,
Hitler doesn't want the messy sky.
For nearly a week,
you have been entrenched
within enemy's own backyard.
- No difficulty?
- None.
I've been innate a few friends.
All I have to do is bad mounters.
Crowd, with the boys specially used jacks
and a seat right in.
Oh, and talk about baseball,
and this is the toughest part.
Strike, run, error,....
dammed ridiculous source.
It all sounds promising.
Very promising!
So, were you able to procure the item?
I've been flirting with the
cute girl sitting in the front office.
And she percept nothing?
She's quite taken by me!
What can I say of making my good look?
You, German, are far to satisfy with yourself.
Comfort!
After charming the girl,
there is needy thing new to her office...
to that very bottom.
Good! Very good!
This up here to be the loading bay.
Let see if we get it tonight.
And this...
That is the storage room that's always locked.
No one is allowed in there.
It must be right there
keeping their secret and ingredients.
- The ingredients?
- Yeah!
Tomafi has a theory that
American are pending to use a new material.
We do not know what is is called,
but it doesn't matter.
This new material...
will increase their bomb payload tensile.
And this secret storage room...
appears to be right next to the break room.
Perfect! Perfect!
That's me!
This is a simple device...
but powerful.
Set the timer and we walk away.
Up to this thing.
In 2 days, when you go to work,
leave it in the break room,
set the timer, and exit.
The explosion will ignite the storage room,
and detonating this secret material within.
Setting of a chain reaction.
The entire facility. the workplace,
and also the new bomb designed
for the Egale in a moment...
crippling their war efforts.
I admire your plan. Lovely up!
And your Max,
on your substitute.
Puppet!
Get him!
Get pullet!
- The puppet!
- Puppet?
Your men're puppet  too, ones!
won't meet the set to the fight!
Kill themselves!
A two counts,...
while we got quite the information pool.
Lucky get you pretty good blade!
Nazi!
Danny?
- What was the noise in here?
- Oh, nothing, Mom.
I'm sorry!
I woke you.
I heard you come home this late.
Is everything OK?
Yeah, everything is fine.
- So that passed./N- It's alright.
So be sure you're home
for dinner tomorrow night.
for having a little celebration for your bother. He 's shipped out soon, you know.
Yeah, I know.
I'll be here.
- Good night!
- Night!
Ah!
you are OK, too!
So the blueprint,
the plan with out port!
Had Nazi to be able to get in the yank,
since they have the access to the plan.
They're planning on blowing it up.
I got to find the way to stop them.
I know I could count on you guys.
How can I just make
somebody else believes me?
Wait till it up?
I can't sleep.
Oh, wow!
That sandwich's so great!
You leave some to me?
- Yeah, there's plenty.
- Oh, Good!
- Hey, come on!
- Can I talk to you really quick?
You know those puppets
that I show you today, right?
Hey, little brother!
Let me... I want to get some of that.
You're robbing me?
And that I'm always spoil you, OK?
Opps, excuse me, Mame!
Nice to meet you!
- You've been drinking?
- Just a few...
We're down with the deal double bill downtown.
Can we just saw that last week.
And there we meet Ms. Magentis.
Oh, that's where I saw base girl.
Naval Gail...
and Au Martia.
Anyway, little brother!
There's gem on this girl.
I means they were up to her neck.
Hello!  Oh!  Shtt!
Don't wake Mom.
Hey!  Hey, how's your girl?
How is that going?
- I don't know.
- What? What's wrong?
Just something is not going to work out.
You know, the guys who's not in the plan,
they get their eyes on her.
Fuck!
So what?
You have got to make sure
you're the only one she's thinking about.
One of those guys goes in you way,
you just...,
- So moon bar, right?
- Yes, I guess so.
You are better than any of those guys.
Don't you forget that, OK?
Sure, Don!
Now, why don't you want
to tell me about the dolls?
The puppets.
Oh, sorry!
What about them?
Now I forget off.
I'll tell you later.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
All right!
He was right.
Even though I can't go oversea and fight,
I can still be my best, right here at home.
Then somebody gets to stop those guys
from blowing the plan, right?
You guys are with me?
Come in!
Time free!
Wow, you look great!
Well, I have a little freedom aku punya pesta nanti
- untuk prajuri spesial ku.
- Uh, thanks, Honey.
Are you okay, Danny?
- I am in the office yesterday....
- Oh, yes, look! Forget about that.
I'm sorry. I'm looking.... looking jerk!
Oh, come here, darling,
to show you something!
I just wonder if everything is
still okay as we planned.
Yeah, there will be no problem.
What do you mean, Danny?
It look like a blue print.
Uh huh, to the plant.
But, how did you get this?
From your new friend, Ben.
What?
Yeah, I follow them last night,
at Redondo Port.
and he went to the opera in China Town,
not that far from here,
where he met his partner, another Nazi.
And he laugh at-?
And three Japs, one of them was a dragon lady,
and they were all in this together, Beth.
In what together?
They're planning on blowing the plant.
They have a bomb.
- You are really serious, aren't you?
- Yes, look!
The bomb is small to put inside the one has has.
OK?  And they planted on putting it here.
In where there're fewer people.
- When?
- Two days from now.
So, I overheard everything.
Is this the treat,
you got to tell somebody.
Then, he's not going to believe me!
You know, I have a trouble getting you
to believe me, let alone anyone else!
I'm the boy who cries "Nazi."
What are you going to do?
I'm going down there,
to the Opera House.
- Danny!
- Don't worry!  I'm just going take some pictures.
I'll make somebody believe me.
- I'll be alright!  For guys's help.
- Who?
They want her if-
Oh, my God!
How are they moving?
Toulon's secret,
I found it.
Sure it!
Ease, go ahead!
I'm so sorry, Danny.
Sorry for what?
For not believing you,
you've told me all of this.
Look, I need you stay here
and help Mom with the party.
As soon as I am to take it some excuse.
I don't like you to be hurt, Danny.
On the field guys' helping me,
I'll be alright.
And don't worry!
Like I said,
I'm just going to take some pictures.
Infernal record!
Shut up, dafter!
I take it, you are upset!
Stay calm, Buta.
Our German friend has a temper.
What?
What's happening here?
Our disagreement over the difficult taste.
Nothing more, isn't that right,
my dear Klaus?
We don't have time for this nonsense!
A missing maybe in jeopardy.
Because of the boy?
He can't know anything.
He does!
He must be taken care of.
How?
They know the phones of Bodega Bay Inn.
It seems our boy was doing
furniture for them during his stay.
His address is Los Angeles,
not far from where we are.
Once again,
stay as it was.
Get the boy and his pups,
have nothing stands in our way!
- Hi Hitler!
- Fur Führer!
Perhaps we should celebrate
our upcoming victory, Ozu.
What did you have in your mind,
my dear Max?
Maybe something to unite our partnership.
Do not mistake me
at our Western hearten,
or one of your German horses,
who find your arrogant of Balcon!
Have I made my point clear,
my dear Maximilian?
I'll put plum in here, dear.
It looks great, Mrs. Coogan.
I'll put the paper.
You get that in the kitchen,
I'll handle things at here.
- You think so?
- I know so, go on.
Okay!
Oh!
Oh, mine!  What are you doing sneaking
around like that, little Donsy?
- That's what I do, Ma!
- Don!
Don, you have put you as little 6.
You ruin the surprise!
Oh! Oh, look at that!
Nice, thanks!
What stands do yo think?
What do you mean?
You know we're having a party?
Yeah, but he's wishing he could go over there,
fighting as the rest of us!
This is just a remind him
that he's not going.
- You get to get a party for him, too.
- Well, we are!
And, I get a few surprises for him.
I don't know where he got what I bought,
but, I make a beef steak with apple pie.
The pie!
Oh, really I bought it in the pios.
Honey, perfect!
Where is Danny, anyway?
He went to get somewhat skinny stuff, I think.
What's being stuffed?
You know, whatever he returned from.
Oh, yeah!  Hammer and nails,
all that technical though.
Go on, Don!  Let us have things finished here.
We'll call you when it's ready.
Alright, alright!
I see what's going on here.
You guys are shipping me out
before I got shipped out.
Oh!
Must be the mailman with
package of the main things.
Yes, can I help you?
These pictures, please splash it, please.
You got it down there!
Mom?!
Oh, God!
I just want to be with you!
Come on, Don!
Come on, hang on!
I think I can help, come on!
Go! Go ahead...
Oh, God, Beth!
He took Beth.
I know that.
Something I can't ... OK?
Just go get them!
Look, go get them!
Don!
No!
I'm going to get those bastard, Don.
You get to help me.
As far as you can keep on living, OK?
As long as we don't the inside Jap.!
Just please work!
Come on!
How do you feel?
I know it's really good with you filled in.
Wow!
Stop!
But, she again, will be the last thing,
do you remember?
I apology for the tied down.
You know better than they are.
To you perhaps it may seem that way,
but again, I apology.
I don't care about your apology.
Right now I should let you know
my name is not Ben.
You are Nazi, just play the others set.
A soldier who following order.
- For Hitler.
- The leader of the new world.
Not of our voice has anything to say about it.
What's going on here?
Your men are savaged!
They are men,
with the needs and desires of men.
I see!
To my desire, the men should be denied.
If it's the desire of your men, your animals,
must be granted, is that it?
Don't be jealous,
that's not be fitted a little.
The task is still here,
in the center of the stage.
So that no one can attemp to free her without a fee.
I understand,
but does that mean she must be toyed with?
Why do you care?
She's nothing but this.
Does that  a guest worm in a hook still attract the fish?
She is not a worm.
It seems you have developed feeling
for a fellow child.
Do not let this... cloud your judges.
I help you done expect me to thank you.
No, I don't expect you to understand either.
What don't I understand?
You can never understand the cause
which I am fighting for.
Slottering of innocent people by a mad dictator?
It's not a cause,
it's an evil.
You'll never to hit freedom nor democracy.
Such a strong domine!
Perhaps in a different time and a different life,
we could mean something to each other.
I'm better to be dead!
You may trust what you wish!
Take the bomb.
Can you hear me?
Can you?
Excellent!
Yes.
It is going well here, Commander.
Shall we think for the arrival of the boy?
Yes.  He will be killed,
as well the two German.
And we will take the point, secret.
The one the German are so eager take control.
Yes, it will belong to Japan,
to the Emperor.
Hello!  Hello?
Commander?
You'll never win the war.
You might kill me and Danny,
even if you blow the plan,
you still won't win.
Did your mother know
what you do for a living?
Heaven will see if  this a shame to your own.
Hey, care acquired!
You got another disappointment through
your own life, haven't you?
Aren't you a little German boy
flowing the wing of a German fly?
She brought everything the best
she could, didn't she? Did you hold one?
The boy is here.
Until I thought...
my withdraw wasn't sound very good.
Would you call it "strategus"?
I call pride.
You, Nazi, always study for
a good stepping parade, aren't you?
Lets go!
It seems the men of Coogan will be quite threaten.
to beat two examples of Japan finest,
to cut to a no hope for winning this war.
They were killed by magic.
There is no defense against sorcery.
They were killed by a boy and his puppets.
- And Don...
- I know, I know.
Come on!
It's OK.
Don is still here, his spirit.
And he won honest pride right now.
We both cry about that later, OK?
Right now I'm going to get you out of here.
- OK!
- That's why I come. Come on!
Klaus?
Your man proved to be
no more efficient than my own.
It appears only you and I remained.
I'll find them before they escape.
You'll take the rear,
and I'll get the front, for the envelope.
- Kill them surely I.
- We shall see!
They had to go somewhere.
You have performed acmatic
but now it's over for you.
What's in the bag?
Drop it forward!
- Danny
- We'll be okay!
Amount control endless, now I got.
Ninja!
I mean you're cut from the stained draw, Ninja!
- Gosh!
- Ouch!
No!
You're out with me statically.
Looking for something?
Where's the bomb?
There is no way without it to blow the plan.
Where is it?!
The timer is cutting down.
Yeah, and the focus switch
is turning off for the timer now, too.
A much, maybe you want to be blowing up.
And now if you come a Kamikaze pilot too,
deplore himself such a course.
The Kamikaze is a special kind of destruction,
better fight within, dedicated, and brave.
Okay!
There are more!
I guess it does take some spy to know die your airplane in the belly of a battleship, but...
brave, I don't know about that!
Just think about it!
Here is the one holding the bomb.
Order it to move away from the bomb!
No, he is not a puppy.
He isn't rolled over and play patch.
Besides, I don't think he likes you very much.
And I know he doesn't like the German,
after all, the German killed his master,
Mr. Toulon.
The forgery is truly powerful.
And that why you never get your hand on him.
As it still comes.
You don't blow us in this point, boy!
Much better than I ever to be
expected from a cripple.
The victory is far from a ship!
You still never get the secret.
Once again, you speak before victory is in hand.
Danny, you got the puppets.
I know our alliance will improve
for the prosperous  like Eroupe.
Step away, dear!
Lay down your sword!
I should have known that
Nazi can not be trusted.
You have no codes of honor.
Do I have the puppet and the gun,
so stay back!
The serum in this puppet
only lasts a limited time.
- Where the rest of it?
- Hidden!
Then you will take me to it!
- Like hell!
- Over it, you will!
Third, I'll do things to a girl that you have...
never even dreamed of doing.
Then I'll hurt her,
badly, all while you watch.
And if that is not giving out,
and I'll begin torturing you.
And if anyone know torture as we, Nazi,
adopter and devise of
funny manageable techniques,
you've seen in death camps
of Auschwitz and Dachau.
- You have tortured innocent civilians. - Oh, we've tortured the soldier, too!
In our prisoners of war camps, we've tortured
many of Allied soldiers, many!
We serve the country more nobly than you.
Men of true value and integrity,
strong sentiment!
Now, while the cripple lies down.
She's gone!
She takes the puppet with her.
She took the Ninja, Blade, and Pin Head.
This war the Jap won.
I give it to her.
New Year 2012.