what's a hanger Beltran well Jay Tommy
get this he'll kill worse addy Niner you
can search me hello Mac Mac this is
kelly come in I want to talk to you I
come on hey Mac beautiful sure
Buckingham Palace you know this place
used to be a refueling station during
World War two I'll bet there hasn't been
anybody here since I can't imagine why
Dutch six square miles of lush tropical
garden spot Hey look what I expect we're
only 200 miles off the coast of Africa
right all right let's now get you some
help
Veronica Lake what not what man who this
is Veronica Lake didn't you ever hear a
Veronica Lake huh I want to tase him
this chick was cool before they invented
the word come on let's get out of here
kill he's gonna be on our tails were
supposed to be fixing up you know what
I'll bet your small life magazines
around here all right fellas what's the
story hey coach comas Ava Dutch used to
be an old Explorer Scout II can't seem
to break the habit yeah will you fellows
are being paid to hack out a base camp
for Warburton's drilling crews not
rummaging around you see if you can find
the saddle of that benign ok ok don't
get uptight hire the best look at your
job done on schedule only got five days
left ah good point out go rev up my big
yellow baby you do that come on Dutch
let's go Veronica Lake careful I'll suit
hey Dutch
I want you to get Beltran a hand on the
access road
okay sweetheart destroy
you
what's the matter won't come out funny
looking rock here yeah it's metallic
there's much geological formation maybe
we've uncovered Captain Kidd's treasure
well whatever it is it's gonna have to
come out you sound like the dentist show
you how it's done kid
germek
hey what's the matter boy hey Matt what
happened Mack how could it happen I
don't get it what was Kelly doing anyway
famous always pushing if we're driving
the d9 is max job not Kelly's mica the
guy's gonna die did you want Mac to hear
you well somebody's got to do something
well Kelly's on the radio call it who
look the supply ship is four days out
and besides too slow I'll listen to the
guy Mack needs a doctor in a hospital or
maybe the company can arrange for a
mercy flight land where will you shut up
we can rough on a strip as quick as they
can fly here we'll catch a patch me
through to a doctor I don't care ghana
liberry anywhere as long as he speaks
English
but any ships in the area will call me
back when you do know what as well be on
the moon any chance of a plane I still
can't figure what happened there power
why
how's it going Tiger what are you doing
about getting back to a hospital tell
gotta talk sure plenty of time later man
no no I'll old come on what do you have
to say to this joker if it wasn't for
him come on he's my buddy you hang in
there here I'm sticking with you all the
way we all are I know what you lookin at
me you heard the man
did you see it see what I don't know
exactly when you hit the rock blue
whatever was you musta seen it I didn't
say anything but it was their wedding
killed me Kelly oh come on I'm telling
you I saw it was a thing oh man it was a
weird unreal I never seen anything like
it you're sure it's ok not lie back and
forget about it I saw it jump when the
blade hit the rock I'm I'm trying to
warn you kelly blue light Mike it's
there the blade
I ever tell you I introduced him to his
girl at a Halloween party back in the
States oh yeah yeah but I call her up
ahead of time see and I said honey put
on to mass so when Matt took off the
first mask he saw the second he would I
said to Mac I said well man what did I
tell you not much one looks but terrific
personality so what do you think so he
says that's would you like to play dunk
the apples I said certainly he said with
your head I said no way
don't go in there Dutch yeah I want to
be with my friend what Kelly said
division I don't care what Kelly said
and what was so important nothing
better get a tarp
gonna have to bury him for the time
being
is that all you gotta say
what's the good Dutch he's bleeding in
his own way
like an IceCube
you
we should have had a priest for Mac
they'll send him back so he spoken to a
proper sir his Dennis come to grace us
with his presence Kelly's bringing in
the Niner so we can work on her tonight
I haven't seen Dennis Dennis doesn't put
himself out even for Dennis why should
he care about Mac hey man Diane makes
everybody care maybe a fella could care
less if he knew how somebody died don't
read something that isn't there dead it
doesn't help anyone least of all Mac I
liked him chub I miss people I like
can we say goodbye now
sorry
you only get one shot of that Mackey
what do you say his trip was short too
short rest in peace man
we'd better go and turn him now
be working later getting a head start on
tomorrow
there's only one way to say goodbye to
an Irishman right yeah Mac he'd like
that here you you knew invest did I ever
man that was the most crazy beautiful
kid he and I worked together on his
first job you know chub I sorta showed
him the ropes only did he learn quick
listen let me tell you behind that young
face he was about as green as your
average fire truck I remember this time
we're working down in San zabar you know
and it's hot man is it hot so we get
done him to go at the local saloon we're
gonna relax a little bit have a little
coconut juice so we're sitting there in
through the door walk through the local
talent well they give us the eye I look
at Matt Mac look at that bang the kids
gone like a shot I turn around hey hey
what do you think you're doing well
somebody's gotta do it not a mark on her
rough on you since when would you care
sorry mostly science fiction yeah he ate
it up no sweat
it's got me really stronger where'd that
come from for having one for Mac then
returning in no problem you better make
it fast because nobody's sleeping leave
tomorrow I was slugged no one special
occasion nobody's gonna report you to
the company for one little shot the bars
closed what you mean reporting to the
company he's a dried-out drunk making
good with his jobs his last chance with
a company oh you're real sweetheart
dinners what's wrong Kelly you always
used to know when to bear down and one
to you that look I'm human well then
remember we are too yeah you're right
how did you get that would be minor I
want you to check her out in the morning
and I mean good why what's wrong you
find out and then you tell me hey let me
do that give me some clue I don't like
to waste you
I'm telling you was a fluke accident
money there was no negligence now listen
you tell Warburton nobody's letting him
down it's got my personal guarantee that
this job is coming in right on the money
romani one more thing you notified
McCarthy's mother yeah well I want
somebody to go over there personally I
don't want to get into some lousy
telegram right okay yeah same time
tomorrow hi Callie Callie
what'd you find nothing you sure well I
found the compression lever wired down
the drain cocks open the air intake
blocked and the main fuel line cut yeah
I'll come cuz I didn't want her going
anywhere you sure made sure will you saw
this remember that 99 m greater we had
nobody could handle yep think we got
another it's a possibility still if you
say she's okay well there there was one
thing come here right here listen you
hear that I couldn't locate whatever is
causing it probably not important belton
came by asking for up at the morrow pit
well he's just gonna have to make do
with the d4 I don't want anybody taking
this machine out until I give the green
light okay you holding back on me yeah I
guess I am for right now well when the
time comes
maybe I'll better move your cut into the
atd so we can get some work done around
here no worry I'll get my job then get
at it now i'm getting tired of your
attitude and I'm tired of being kept in
the dark what's this with its funny blue
light I know piece of candy your ass our
ball yeah I'm the best shovel operator
you'll ever have now back to the blue
light I'm listening
you breathe one word he didn't take back
seriously he was out of his head no
make sense
still last night I wondered I could've
sworn a d9 blade moved was took my foot
off you better be more careful
you
makes you wonder okay how did it happen
don't give us none of that about the d9
or going haywire we want to know I don't
know why you were there you saw it maybe
you were seeing pink elephants to Kelly
Mack and Al are dead get off his back I
saw Belton lose control and go plowing
into that radio before the thing ran
away with it you must have bailed out
you saw by the tracks how he got it what
more do you need a logical explanation
yeah he's got to come up with one sooner
or later it's gonna have to be later
because it's an IR daylight left and
there's work to be done so let's get at
it huh
do you believe that guy
gee Dennis it's real tough you know I
mean beltran and his wife just started
to plan a family
hey you know what I'd like to do I'd
like to go swim it me and Mac used to go
swim we go swimming all the time mostly
at night splashed around like a couple
of Jaybirds people used to think we were
crazy we're crazy you have to be crazy
to be in this business right live hard
laughs hard cuz hey Dennis come on go
swim yeah come on right now we can go
John while we're at it let's send out
for some pizza
jellied thought beltran what exactly did
you see thanked 0 apple's strength huh
the D Niner was operating by itself when
it ran him down throttling pivoting
floating the blade ha I don't know how
some malfunction in the controls you
seen rogue machine may operate before
look I heard McCarthy tomb I'm trying to
warn you it a blue light my god it was
there in the blade you don't believe
that the question is to you know touch
shut that noise off and get some sleep
when in doubt floss around why don't you
start hella you can't play ostrich that
d 9 is harmless now it's out of fuel are
racked up out there somewhere so we
leave it be and let the company
engineers come in and find the bugs in
it later and if you're wrong tomorrow's
gonna be another tough day you'd better
get some sleep
where've you been I don't believe Mac
was delirious I saw the D Niner
operating all by itself you're paid to
work you saw two did you when it got
Belgian forget it you know I suppose
it's possible for two guys to have the
same hallucination but for two guys as
different as you and me he never listen
Buster I got a completion date now I
haven't got time on my bed we're up
against something we can't fight until
we can figure it out I picked up a piece
of that rocket you hit what about it you
know geology better than me look close
and tell me if you ever saw anything
like it meteorite maybe oh the love of
God man will you face it two of us are
dead what'll it take to make a believer
out of you another one all right Sahra
ball what do you think I should we gotta
level with the other guys assuming there
is something inside that dozer we find
it and destroy it oh we got plenty of
dynamite are you crazy that D Niner cost
okay come on you see Dennis bail out of
bed this morning knob so so he and your
friend Kelly are up to something I mean
for them not us I think the pressures
got to both of them we're looking out
for number one and two I think this Mac
thing bought you a bad dream what bad
dream there are two graves down there on
the beach and there's lots of room for
two more listen Dutch for once and for
all you know there's not a more
experienced construction boss in the
business so let's clam up this dumb dog
you get this thing back on a job sure
he's most experienced Boston a business
survival of management that's what they
call it guys like us we're expendable
you better take that paper bag off your
head and open up those trusting eyes you
and me chub we're gonna be on the beach
pretty soon stretched out chub for
little bodies all in a row
hey Dutch chupke marijuana talk to you
Oh first check it out and gas them all
up will you
there's food canned stuff to jerrys of
water that oughta hold us til the supply
boat day after tomorrow hey Dutch will
you shut that thing off he's coming off
his spool
remote control that's got to be it huh
that thing is running by remote control
listen listen you guys we gotta do
something I mean something's wrong Mitch
machines just don't run by themselves
that means there's somebody else on this
island you know foreign spies or
something how about a mad scientist no
listen Dennis come on I'm serious we're
wasting my time there's got to be a
logical explanation
got him gassed up yep I'd sure like to
know what that d nighters running on yes
so would I are we gonna get out of here
where to that high ground oh we're not
going after the Dean I well not until we
figure out how that dynamite didn't faze
it I still say it's remote control we
can move faster we'll hide and run gain
time until that ship shows up you're
calling the shots Dutch you better ride
with me
hey Dennis did I ever tell you our plate
in the Cotton Bowl and 64 I caught two
touchdowns
you
she won't make it any further up this
grade
well I think we'd better take a look
around up there first we don't want to
get ourselves trapped hey guys you want
to laugh where do you hear the
cockamamie story Oh Denny's been handed
me best we can do best man it's terrific
well the truth is we don't know anything
for a fact except that bulldozer kills
that's good enough for me you stay here
with Dutch sharp let's take a look
there's some logical explanation
hey Dennis
listen want some music that thing can't
hear look maybe this isn't such a good
idea you know maybe would be smart to
split up Kelly and chub you and me like
teams and we stand a better chance what
do you say why not every man for himself
you serious we stick together
what about this slope you think the D
Niner can get up given time it can make
a road any word wants to go well then
we'd better fight back what do you think
about building a signal fire maybe a
airplane or a fishing boat might
we're chubbs got an idea we ambush that
dozer run his truck into it and Kapow
fire won't stop steal it'll take out the
electrical systems in the rubber hey
that's beautiful hi I got a feeling
we're going about this wrong there's a
good spot down the road about a half a
mile let's get down there and set it up
you
I'm beginning to get this you know sort
of like being on patrol in Vietnam yeah
I'll sure
chop-chop
Tow Mater wife Marjorie two boys in
college and a few good friends yeah for
what that was worth I'll finish
do you believe that thing
what's it waiting for what's a Terry
it knew that ambush it knew what we were
gonna do and it did it first at least
you got our Dutch I'm no coward Kelly I
don't want to die but that's not being a
coward of course it isn't
what if it comes they call for artillery
support we got speed we run and keep
running until help gets here my tummy
for days we gotta fight gonna find some
way to total that thing you can't kill a
machine maybe we should appeal to its
sense of decency and fair play you stink
all right come on want to be a knife at
all come on Dutch listen ah fucking
she's right on the edge sorry pain makes
me slide will you take your shirt off
I'll see what I can do don't mind I can
make it it's tougher loon
let's get out of here
hey you hear that hear what the surf oh
man oh man what I wouldn't give for a
moonlight swim you know hey Dennis I
ever tell you about the time in Kuwait
me and Mac we were
what's it doing out there
doing a war dance maybe it won't attack
at night like John Wayne's Indians
you're crazy coach he's crazy he's gonna
get us killed that thing's trying to
murder us hey easy take it easy Dutch
tell you what how about uh for medicinal
purposes only huh hey right why don't
you um stretch out and relax for a
little while we'll keep an eye on things
a private stock
might as well
Dutch put this back with you
you know you're finished with Warburton
even if we do get out of this thing
there's gonna be investigations asking
for things we don't have like a logical
explanation so we tell him the truth
like you did after that Andy's power
plant fiasco I told him the truth femto
and they crucified you for it what did
it cost you your job your reputation
you want a piece of advice never have
anything you care about losing travel
light and travel alone that's the way
you play it and nobody lasered love on
me long as you're happy
good i'm goin swimmin
the show
now you got it work
why
you
this coming fast
Wow
let's get out of here
thought she was right you can't kill a
machine but Cho a machine hey wait a
minute of course you can't kill a
machine don't you see our mistake the
thing whatever that's what has to be
stopped but how I don't know but doesn't
we there's gotta be a way think man how
do you go about killing on a killer it's
too heavy to hang it's too big to put in
the gas chamber wait a minute
electricity brilliant I'm serious
electrocution we shoot juice into that
big dosa we got that generator looks
damaged maybe maybe not we need a
conductor some guy spinning your wheels
can do or not it'll work and that's
what's gonna make it work come on sarbo
give me a hand
you got it straight I'm gonna make that
dozer to charge the greater when he gets
both treads on that grid Wham we prize
like bacon assuming it'll come from that
direction I'll jockey the greater and
assuming it's dumb enough to be suckered
you're gonna be at that generator ready
to throw the switch right it doesn't
work it has to it's under warranty you
know you may make it yet sorry ball
get down it's coming
come on dozer
come on come on and get me
come on over here
listen nothing the homes gone the things
dead yeah but we're not exactly home
free no I guess not all we got is our
word that the thing existed you know we
could fake things tell the authorities
the guys got caught in a landslide no
tell the truth no matter what no matter
what you known about a hundred years I
might get to like you and blow your
whole philosophy all i know is i'm sure
glad to be alive so my sarma
so am i
you