(calm music)
♫ Ain't I fair ain't I kind
♫ And I'm paid to feel fine
♫ But I haven't spent a dime
♫ Since I met you
♫ Your breasts are like two wrists
♫ That I've handcuffed to my dick
♫ In a subculture of love and refraction
♫ But I die every morning again
♫ Me at my worst is fun for them
♫ And I die with the feeding tube
♫ While you try to fix my blues
♫ Your city is so unclean
♫ In a Washington machine
♫ And your face is like
a cage and two of them
♫ And your sentiment is gone
♫ And you're now enslaved by gods
♫ While I strum my
broken legs like a banjo
♫ But I die every morning again
♫ Me at my worst is fun for them
♫ And I die with the feeding tube
♫ While you try to fix my blues ♫
- "Phoning in the Blues,"
Zintendo Records, take 15.
Rolling.
♫ I'm phoning in the blues
♫ Cuz my life ain't stalling
♫ The phone just rang
♫ To say the blues ain't calling
♫ I thought that I'd always
called it like I saw it
♫ I've got the blues and I
know just how to call 'em
♫ Baby that's how they call the blues
♫ I'm phoning in the blues ♫
Wait cut, cut.
Aladdin, are you okay?
- I honestly feel that
I'm deaf to my own soul.
- You remind me of somebody
who's about to get fired.
- I'm just trying to pinpoint the moment
that I lost my mojo.
- That's when you started getting drunk?
- I get drunk so that I
can continue my research.
- You told me that you spent
30,000 spacebux on cocaine.
- I only take cocaine to go to Brooklyn,
besides it helps me phone in the blues.
- Zintendo has been a
company since medieval times,
always on the forefront of innovation.
We invented flesh cubes, flesh digits,
faggot rock, houseface.
In your case, we are
not going to continually
press the same button
expecting a different result.
- Okay, Ms. President, so will I be judged
and discarded at the
hands of a corporation?
- Have a seat.
I passed a diner on my
way into Regular Town
that serves shit sandwiches,
so I got you one.
I hope you enjoy it.
- You're delivering me a shit sandwich
and you hope that I enjoy it?
- [Both] Uh-huh.
- But Farmer Dave, you made
me change my name to Aladdin
for my ninth album.
- C'mon, let's try
another take of the song.
♫ People say I'm the nature of the clown
♫ They say can't hold anything down
♫ If it's true will you
help me cheat on you
♫ What I know on your secrecy depends
♫ Treating every girl as my girlfriend
♫ When I do is it healthy being through
♫ If we do will you help me cheat on you
♫ Because my hope Is a vision unruly
♫ And people say I'm the
nature of the clown but
♫ I'm not gonna kiss you
I'm not gonna kiss you
♫ Unless you want me to
♫ So you want me to woo hoo ♫
- [Princess Barbara] No, I'm not!
- You will get married to a Prince!
- Stop trying to bully me
when you have no idea what's in my heart!
- Even if it is just symbolic,
it must happen.
- Great Sultan, with all due respect,
perhaps we just need to
get her the right drugs,
Your Majesty.
We are developing things all the time.
This is one of the protesters we arrested,
he's from a rebel group
called Magical America.
- What is he charged with?
- We have Internet evidence
that he pursued being gay and failed.
- I wish that I was bisexual.
- There is a prison
inside all of us, yeah.
- Hey Dad, do you think
that I'm a criminal too?
- Princess Barbara!
It is the law that if you
are not married in a month,
I have to execute you.
- So that we can film the second season
of your 'Virtual Reality Show?'
Love is not a savage form
of publicity, besides,
I like to fuck average people.
- We are fighting the war on privacy,
the Virtual Reality Show
is the next frontier.
- Normally I advocate Internet removal
for this type of thing.
However in this special case...
- What is so special about this case?
- Well, Your Majesty,
he didn't have to act
like he had a big dick.
- Thou shalt not advertise falsely.
- I didn't have to act
like I had a big dick.
- Goodbye, Mister.
(screaming)
- It just bores me to chairs.
- I like everything,
some things I like a lot,
and other things I just like.
- King of kings, in
accordance with your wishes,
all exposed people will now be developed!
- So long, guys.
- [Emily] Hey, Laddy, hey!
Long story short, your father's dead,
and I told you so.
They emailed me from Africa.
- To announce the death of the monster
who forgot about us?
- He/She didn't forget about us,
they sent a check every week
since the two of you were born,
though I guess now that's going to stop.
Could you hold my cigarette for me?
- Hey, how was your film class?
- Hmm, it was awesome!
I'm gonna make a movie about our family.
- Is that what you think
is cool now, Emily?
Making movies?
- If you play my mom
real good in the movie,
I'll let you be my mom in real life.
(laughs)
Why are you smiling?
You're still ugly.
- Hey, Laddy, check out this camera I got!
- Is your goal to wear me
out and make me sentimental?
- I want to make a profound documentary.
The entire working world
is either on probation or unemployed,
so there's never been a
better time to make artwork!
I want this movie to be a cry for peace.
- This is a mining town.
These mountains are filled
with baseball diamonds.
Your father, before he was a woman,
was a miner just like
everybody else in Regular Town.
Well then, that Sultan
came in from Hollywood.
Who put him in charge?
Yeah, I heard his father was a stunt-kid.
- The Sultan is God's grandson,
he is, according to e-history,
the grandson of a god.
- C'mon, Laddy, let's go for a walk
and check out the protests.
- No!
- C'mon!
(calm guitar music)
- The protestors have been camping
outside the Sultan's castle for weeks,
they call themselves
the Magical Americans.
They're an actual rebel
army that does crazy stuff
that's gonna change the world.
Hey!
- Hey!
- Wouldn't it be amazing
if we joined them?
- I only want to be bad
enough to get spanked.
- Can I knick a fag mate, a ciggie?
- You know, we're not walking
down the street for you.
- Where am I supposed to buy cigarettes
on an 8-Bit pixilated street, yeah?
Hey, not that it matters,
but I used to be a big fan.
You still making music?
- Oh god!
- Let's go!
- Testing!
- [Crowd] Testing!
- Cheers, One, Two!
- [Crowd] Cheers, One, Two!
- Who out there is perverted by nerves?
- [Crowd] Who out there
is perverted by nerves!
- Don't believe the hype that you're dead.
No gods allowed!
- [Crowd] No gods allowed!
- Maybe I'm a robot because
I definitely feel dead.
- I think he's amazing.
It's better than being
a sitting duck at home.
- But you are not dead yet,
you gray, huddled masses,
stuck in this bureaucratic
hell of secret government
and bad money,
all while your shadow
is trying to eat you.
But if you aren't gray
enough, or eaten enough,
or in debt enough, then
he's gonna lock you up
for a few years in the Labyrinth of Lies.
We're all his pets!
- [Crowd] No Gods Allowed!
- No Gods Allowed!
- Shit, CIA!
- You're all under arrest!
(ominous music)
- Oh fuck!
- Follow me, quick!
- Okay!
- We have to correct the world's posture.
The world was meant to be beautiful!
- I've just arrived from Africa,
and I'm glad I found you when I did.
I'm your Uncle Gary!
- Uncle Gary?
Mom never told us we had an uncle.
- I've always wondered if
Dad even knew I existed.
- Oh, he was very impressed by you...
no example.
Anyway, we spent years together
on the coffee house
scene being entertainers.
- What happened, you guys
just never hit it big?
- Oh, to me, pleasure's always been
the finest form of entertainment.
I convinced him to leave
all the mining and seek fun.
- So at what point did Dad
decide to become a lady?
- It was at the end of me,
and the beginning of us.
- Huh?
- Let's go find your mother.
- Hi Mom, this is Uncle Gary from Africa.
He's here because Dad sent him.
- Well, Gary, thanks for coming by,
but it's a little much because
I barely knew their father,
although he gave me twins
and a few hangovers.
- Ah, but you would like
some golden spacebux though.
Hmm?
As I said before, I'm just here to help,
and you'll find that
I always keep my word.
- How did you know I collected gold?
- Gary, you are terrific
because I was just saying
it's time for us to meet a rich person!
- That ought to cover your
rent for a little while,
and look, my instinct is to protect you.
I am the protector of women from men.
And now, I'd like to
prepare you a frittata.
- A frittata!
- We're fools, I'm from a family of fools.
- See, guys, all that nothingness
we've been doing is
finally having some effect.
- Y'know, Aladdin,
- your father wanted me to
impart some wisdom upon you,
just general life lessons, you know.
Tomorrow morning, I wanna take you
on a hike in the
mountains, what do ya say?
- Hey, Laddy, I don't trust Uncle Gary.
Hang out with me tomorrow, will ya?
- Well, I see you're
used to having your life
run by some little chick.
- No, I wear the pants,
but they're her pants.
(calm music)
- Your father was never late,
but he did also not
believe in being early.
Being early for something is
an aggressive act in itself.
- I deny the date entirely.
What's the difference,
I'm an upper middle class pauper
about to get dropped
from Zintendo Records,
I don't even subscribe to romance
outside the family tradition.
- Oh, wouldn't it be great
if we had an emotional
stuntman for our hearts?
- What's up here, the Ten Commandments?
- Right now, we're in
the high part of hell,
up there is the lowest part of heaven.
There's a mine up here
your father used to work in
I'd like to show you.
- Ciao.
- Uncle Gary, what's that?
Are we not supposed to be here?
- Yeah, this place is also
a graveyard for aliens,
the Lumambrians.
- [Aladdin] The Lumambrians.
Are aliens natural?
- Sure, all technology is natural.
Look...
God equals Humans
divided by Nature plus Aliens.
♫ And then they make you smoke a bowl
♫ I've been switching cages
and I need your ego glue
♫ We're in a world that runs on words
♫ And I'm some cannibal for you
♫ I don't believe that
you broke everything
♫ I just believe each man is a lost king
♫ And I'm feeling sorry
for someone else's plan ♫
- Hey, look, it's the old mineshaft
Do you have the key?
- It'll be dark soon.
Gather some wood, I'll build a fire.
As I said, this is a very special place.
Miners discovered things
here, magical things.
Underneath this ground
is the stuff that makes up everything,
you know, the real star stuff!
Something I learned back in the days
when I was talking real fast in Cairo.
We start by globing the circle,
then cubing the globe,
and finally triangulating the cubic globe.
My, my! Ramaho! Niya! Niya!
- What's it for?
- It's the cave computer,
it's a sacred intelligence
that begins and does not begin
with everlasting and
never-lasting colored cords.
In the left corner, that's you.
That's me.
And at the bottom,
that's what's down there.
- I've never seen anything like it,
how are you supposed to hold it?
- You've got to go down there and get it!
Go to the entrance of
the mineshaft and say,
My, my! Ramaho! Niya! Niya!
- My, my! Ramaho! Niya! Niya!
- Each man is a lost king.
Inside this cave is a treasure
that will make us richer
than a fugger, it's true!
Through that entrance
is the wreckage of an alien spacecraft.
Down the stairs, there are three rooms.
Walk straight through them
and you will come to a garden
with beautiful trees and many treasures.
Cross the garden path
and walk up many steps
to where a lamp is displayed
on a fiery pedestal.
This is not an ordinary lamp.
Take the lamp and bring it to me.
- Why don't you do it?
- No, I can't.
This is your door.
Believe me when I say this
door was made only for you.
(calm music)
- Aah!
♫ A nose cannot smell an
eyeball but eyes can feel a nose
♫ Mystics say the Bible is
God wearing paper clothes
♫ Don't you want to sit in a high chair
♫ Climb up the gravity stairs
♫ Don't you want to sit
in a high high chair
♫ Where time cannot interfere
♫ Jesus was a baby Adam had sex with Eve
♫ When you make a baby
you spray your geometry
♫ When you have a baby
you're giving birth to me
♫ Arms are too short the legs are too wide
♫ And time is just a fantasy ♫
- I'm the guardian of the lamp.
- It looks like a gourd.
- If you wish to possess this lamp,
you must first answer
this riddle correctly.
What is the most beautiful
language in this world?
- The most beautiful
language in this world
is sign language.
- The lamp is yours.
- The CIA!
Aladdin!
Aladdin, quick throw up the lamp!
- Uncle Gary, give me
your hand and help me up.
- [Uncle Gary] I will, of course.
Just throw up the lamp first
so it doesn't get in your way.
I'm afraid we're out of time.
- [Aladdin] What the hell! Come back!
(grunting)
Lord, please forgive my transgressions.
(enchanting music)
What?
- You have a lot of nerve
to drive me out of the lamp.
- It's true, I have a lot of gumption.
- What are you?
- I'm Mustafa, the interface of the lamp.
I'm the future as the present.
- Mustafa, can you save me?
- I can save you from your corporate fate
if we work together.
- I don't want to get involved
in any monkey business.
- The lamp is a printer,
I can print you anything
that you wish for,
but understand, unlike a gift,
a wish has more in common with a hole.
- I couldn't seem to imagine the depths
at which I wouldn't want a wish.
- Just let go of what you don't have.
- That's personal.
- Just let go of it.
- Okay, yeah.
Print me out a ladder
and a key to that door.
(scratching sound)
- I've heard that you reject every prince,
no matter what, but I was curious
if your confidence masked
a greater insecurity.
- No, I'm about as arrogant as I look.
- You look as if you are
going to hate growing old.
- You waste of flesh, go home,
you can't win me
because you are not worth
being made a fool over.
It's as simple as that.
Delete your face.
- Time is running out, Princess,
and you know what you haven't done.
- Mom, I'm not sure if Uncle
Gary's really our uncle,
and also on that walk we
took, he tried to kill me!
- Oh Aladdin, don't be so hard on him.
Uncle Gary is a complicated man,
but he's been very generous with us.
- But he was still trying to sacrifice me
on top of a mountain for a god.
- But he made me a great frittata.
- Look, check this out!
- Who's that?
- I'm the guy who knows what time it is.
- Mustafa, print us a luxury living room.
- Okee-dokee.
(scratching noise)
(squeals)
- Print us 10 million spacebux!
Wow, this is a lot, maybe too much stuff.
You know, some people
like to go on the road,
but I'm the progenitor of
the "Stay at Home" movement.
- Aladdin, you really are
the world's greatest son.
Mwah!
- Everything's a number these days.
(calm music)
- Well, the bad news is that
Magical America is bankrupt,
we are completely broke.
- Give us some good news, Ralph.
- Well, 15-Year-Old, the good news is that
ultimately we're all
working for the Internet.
Preventing the Sultan and the CIA
from seizing control of e-history
is one way to subvert the doom spiral,
yet we have no resources.
- I'll do whatever I need
to do to aid in that.
Hi, I'm Emily, I'm a fan.
- Hi, I'm 15-Year-Old.
- So, what does your graffiti stand for?
- Oh, it's Graffiti Stands For.
- I'd like to make a Fahrenheit
9/11-style documentary
about all the shit that's
going down in Regular Town.
- We believe 9/11 was an accident.
- In general, our stance
on creative endeavors
is that everyone's amazing,
so we have a strict no-masterpiece policy.
- Huh.
I can deal with that.
So, what's your stance on monogamy?
- Great Sultan, we prepared
the technology report.
- Terrific!
First question, can you fuck it?
- We discovered a particle
that responds to prayer.
- Why are people always
trying to fix something
when there's nothing wrong?
Yes, yes, pray to Grandpa God.
- Also down at the lab,
we've invented a robot.
It's a walking briefcase.
We call it the Storage Eunuch.
Your daughter seems to
be quite fond of it.
- Bravo, bravo Gennaro Russo!
The promised age of leisure has arrived.
These robots, they will
do all the work for us.
You know, I think I might still be it
from my last game of tag.
(phone ringing)
- [Aladdin] Hi, this is
Aladdin, I'm not here right now.
Please don't leave a message, send a text.
(long beep tone)
(phone ringing)
- Aladdin, you decadent
fool, pick up the phone.
(calm music)
- Ah, Princess Barbara, may
I speak with you a moment,
do you have a meeting with the drama club?
- I'm going to the Chinese Dance.
- Oh no, it's just, do you know who I am?
- You're the head of the CIA.
- I'm far more than just an enabler
of your father's technophilia.
After a few drinks, I assure you
my face can become quite average.
- Gennaro Russo, what did I
tell you about being cool?
- What I'm trying to say is
there may be an opposite
world where pain is good.
- I left my keys in the Storage Eunuch,
and I'm off.
- Please allow me to
accompany you, Barbara.
(funky music)
- Hey!
- Aye!
- You partying tonight?
- Aww, yeah, mate, what
are we getting into?
- I was thinking about
giving myself a little taste.
- Sure, mate, I've always
justified it in the past meself.
I got some clean needles in me roadcase,
or maybe a bindle of beak perhaps.
- Gimme a bindle of beak,
you know, I'm going to the Chinese Dance.
- Nice one.
(engine revving)
- Whoa!
- Ciao, Paesanos.
- Princess Barbara, mate,
she's a well fit bird.
♫ Feel my love
♫ Coming from the heavens above ♫
- Fuck me, guy.
♫ When my eyes meet your eyes
(calm music)
♫ Baby come dance with me
- Try and drink this!
♫ I'm TV at the TV station
♫ Baby come dance with me
- Will you go on a date with me?
Yes, maybe, of course?
Of course.
A fountain pen is a serious aphrodisiac.
- I also have a headphone splitter.
- Your shirt looks like it has a big cock.
- Well, I'm hiding a genie in there,
so when's our date?
- Honestly, it's not going to happen,
my father will only let me
go on a date with a prince.
- Great Sultan, there's
a woman here to see you.
- A woman, I'm jealous
of every woman I see.
Does she have poise?
- Is having poise the girl
equivalent of being cool?
If so, she does not.
- Very well, let her in.
- Your Majesty, I'm a messenger
from a wealthy prince from a far away land
who wishes to ask your daughter on a date.
Additionally he has all the
cool things that assholes own,
I beg you please do not
delay his dream fulfillment.
Oh, also he asked me to deliver a note
to the Princess Barbara.
- Oh father,
maybe I would like to go
on a date with this prince.
I've been thinking about it
and I may have been leading
an inappropriate life.
- You tell your prince
he can have his date as
soon as he brings 36 slaves,
handsome, well built,
and 36 laptop computers made of gold.
Golden computers...
- Your majesty, I think
perhaps this suitor...
- What's the prince's name?
- He goes by Prince Average Cabbage.
♫ And I say uno dos
♫ Uno dos tres
- Cheers.
(relaxing music)
♫ Bingo birthday bimbo bambo
♫ This is Aladdin's birthday mambo
♫ Jingo Django light the candles
♫ Aladdin's birthday mambo ♫
This hotel room comes with a
complimentary Swedish roommate.
Will my butler please give
her a bump of Pinocchio?
- Yeah, that's the good stuff, mate.
- We're going on a drunken spree!
I feel as dumb as a cool guy.
Let me just print out a condom.
Keep playing!
- Hey Aladdin, so what
were you saying before
about vaginal theory?
- Ah, vaginal theory, here goes.
A pussy is a vagina that
comes pre-moistened,
and as it dries out,
turns into a vagina again.
- I'm watching that
pussy turn into a vagina
right before my very eyes, mate.
- A twat is something a 3-year-old has,
- and a cunt is a man's mouth
where a vagina should be.
- You stupid cunts, cunts all of ya',
ha-ha, right, mate?
- Well, technically,
that's just your perception
of the pieces.
(moaning)
(victory music)
- It's hard to keep me hungry.
Hey, let's drink another song
and listen to another beer.
Hey, fellas, can I make a request?
Do you guys know how to
play "Interested in Music?"
- We play an excellent 11-minute version.
Two three four.
(calm music)
♫ Are you interested in music
♫ You like to walk in town ♫
- Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you
a royal prince, Average Cabbage!
(cheering)
- It's the next contestant on the Sultan's
virtual reality show!
Everything we used to call
porn is now our culture.
- The Princess is a connoisseur of trash!
- I'm just a cool cat in a small town.
Ms. President?
- You look really stupid up there.
- I'm not stupid, I'm just inconclusive.
- Farmer Dave.
- Call me.
- Welcome to Primavera Palace.
(groaning)
- He spends his whole life
sitting on that dildo.
- You remind me of somebody pretty.
- I'm clever to feel
and expensive to love.
You remind me of somebody nice.
- Come with me on a flying rug ride!
(calm music)
- I like it up here away
from all those cameras.
- Too many gods always blocking our view.
- Ciao, birds.
- Level after level of
heaven after heaven,
I'm your Pegasus, dollface.
- I dare you to respect
me more than I do you.
- Hmm, sexuality is imbalance,
perhaps it's nice to live in a world
dominated by gravity.
You see that traffic light?
I'm gonna get that for you.
And that bike, and that pickaxe,
I'm gonna get that for you too!
Mustafa, print us out a shit sandwich.
(scratching noise)
- Ha-ha!
- What is this, a shit sandwich?
Who gave this to us?
- Hey man, we don't
want your shit sandwich!
(laughing)
Let's print out some ecstasy.
(scratching noise)
- I wonder what
self-realization would mean
for a guy like me.
- It would probably be pretty ironic.
What does ironic mean anymore?
- Ironic is what comes after modern.
Everything after modern is ironic,
including all of e-history.
- If we had sex, would that be ironic?
(moaning)
- I think you're a big deal, Barbara,
I love you.
- You don't love me, it's
just the ecstasy talking.
- No, no, not true, dollface.
If you keep on peeling off the layers,
you'll just discover a guy
who wants to be with you.
I have an idea.
Mustafa, print us out a baby.
(scratching noise)
(baby coos)
- Cute, what shall we name him?
- Let's call him Gizmo.
Hi, Gizmo.
- How many of these Aladdin passports
are we gonna make?
- Seven billion.
- Maybe his next album could come
with a free pack of cigarettes.
- Maybe his next album could
be a pack of cigarettes.
He's just turned so massively nihilistic.
First with all the cocaine,
and what's he even celebrating?
Well, I guess an artist
is a captain at sea
just keeping a ledger.
- Artists are people who
are constantly in search
of the reason why people like them.
Only in his own world
can he feel handsome.
(funky music)
♫Do some blow with me do some blow with me
♫'Cause I could never withstand the light
♫ I'm back in Disneyland
I'm back in Disneyland
♫ 'Cause I could never withstand the light
♫Of the day doing it all
♫I'm having a ball
♫I'm doing it all tonight
♫Do some blow with me do some blow with me
♫Well I'm looking for a
friend who put a hole in me
♫And all we're saying is
the lights are down low
♫And all we're saying
is it's everybody's blow
♫Come do some blow with
me do some blow with me
♫'Cause I could never
withstand the light ♫
- I've been looking for Aladdin everywhere
he's not picking up his phone.
I can see you've been
appreciating the Midas touch.
- Aladdin's at the Ferrari store.
No, no, no, actually,
he's at the Chinese Dance.
Y'know, Gary, I can't help,
but think about that night
so many years ago with your brother.
Sometimes...
Sometimes I wish that he'd
just aimed for the toilet,
then I could have really
done something with my life.
(funky music)
♫ You've been praying for me every day
♫ But there's no such
place as away you're afraid
♫ That I'm going to have a few
♫ If I do you should help me cheat on you
♫ Because my hope is a vision unruly
♫ And people say I'm
the nature of the clown
♫ But I'm not gonna kiss you ♫
- You're doing amazing work, Emily.
We are what's missing from this world.
- I hope those files we
posted about the CIA's
surveillance efforts
does something to subvert
their control over e-history.
- We need transparency from
the government on down.
This entire system was built
with 18th century technology in mind.
We could create a digital liquid democracy
and live in an experimental
prototype community.
We could recreate what money is
and develop a money that
rots like vegetables.
But we just don't have any resources.
- My brother has something
that I think could help us.
I'm gonna go find him.
(calm music)
- Your Excellency, these
are gifts from your suitor.
- I told you I was
gonna get those for you.
- How did you have the time
to print those without me noticing?
Oh well, I guess I had
time to fuck Mustafa
while you were in the shower.
- What?
- I said I fucked Mustafa.
He's very fun to fuck.
I won't be made a fool of.
- My disappointment is like
a third party between us.
Where's Gizmo?
Gizmo!
- It was your job to feed him, not mine.
He's now dead like our
love was an aborted wish.
- You have a despicable soul.
Your personality is like a mind trick.
- The worst part is that
I probably do love you.
- Why don't you go fuck a genie instead?
- Doesn't this prove that
you don't love me forever?
- Just because I'm sensitive
doesn't mean I'm nice.
My goal was always to change
you and then discard you.
- Listen up here, Prince Average Cabbage.
You've been up for five days straight,
go home and sleep.
- Can you please squeeze me?
I just want your little ass to hold me,
and I need more and more.
- Delete your face!
(calm music)
♫ Things are not so horrible
♫ Now you're not my Oracle
♫ Something died for all time
♫ When I saw you conspiring
♫ To never lift a finger ♫
- Print out a magic lamp.
(scratching noise)
♫ Once you were my manager
♫ Then you were my passenger
♫ Different highs different lies
♫ 'Til no soul would reshape you again
♫ But your hold came in at a loss
♫ And the ecstacy has worn off
♫ Something died for all time
♫ When I saw you conspiring
(phone ringing)
- Ms. President?
- What are you doing?
- I'm looking in the mirror at garbage.
- Nonsense, you're blessed
with an extremely pure soul, Aladdin.
- I'm surrounded by sentimental fools
and psychic vampires.
- Well, where do people go
when there's no such place as away?
- I'm glad you asked that question.
In the future, bad people
will have to be encouraged
to kill themselves.
- Reasons should be abundant,
maybe it's time for a
visitation of judgment.
- Will you go get vodka
and caviar with me?
- Definitely.
- Chinese Dance.
- Hey mister, read all about it,
"Average Savage."
Barbara and her new boyfriend
got into some kind of
digital printing accident last night.
- Let me see that.
Aladdin!
Franchastic!
The lamp.
It's the ultimate outsider's curse!
Come with me, boy.
(sucking sound)
- That was the best
blowjob I've ever heard.
- Now you can't say anything
about me doing drugs.
- I never would, Barbara.
(zips)
I never would.
Great Sultan, with all due respect.
We like everybody in some kind of debt.
That way we get the most
amount of work out of them,
and they are too emotionally distracted
to rise up against us.
- I'm so hungry and fat.
- An emotional tax will be necessary
as well as an economic one.
Firstly we can extract
psychic debt using Wi-Fi.
Now Wi-Fi is basically a video game
that simulates drowning.
Timing is everything, time versus choice,
and it's because choices take time
that we can really drown them in Wi-Fi.
For example, a mandatory app we developed
called 'Thankster.'
People have to thank
everybody for thanking them.
It's an endless thank loop.
They'll never have time
to leave the house again.
People break dozens of laws each day.
The only thing that stops everybody
from being in jail for life
is our inaccuracy in detecting
all the little laws they broke
and then prosecuting them for it.
These tiny drones, the size of a housefly,
hover over their heads,
monitoring everything that they do.
We're gonna need millions of them,
and they're expensive.
For everyone's debt,
we demand that they shower us with tech.
We're gonna need money to buy drones
to make debt to get tech!
- I'm the luckiest god in the whole world.
In the whole world!
Ohh!
- Awesome!
- Let's get together 300
of the best people we know
and start a community
based on our own integrity,
and the gift of the lamp that
Emily has bestowed upon us.
Mustafa, print a stack
of guns for our militia.
- (15-year-old) Nice.
- The love generation
was a failed experiment,
until it worked!
- Being a revolutionary
has always been attractive to a young man.
- What ever happened to
correcting the world's posture?
- I dunno, maybe it could be solved
by the simple writing of a check.
- I completed an algorithm
for the new digital-spacebux currency.
- Good job, 15-Year-Old.
Are you guys okay with
this being all digital?
- It doesn't even matter.
This lamp is making
money with its copyright.
- Do your dreams pay
attention to copyright?
- If life is a dream, then
it certainly is a long one.
- For our main meeting hall,
we'll need you to print
out a geodesic dome.
(scratching noise)
- What about the rest of the planet?
- How manageable is my
neighbor's delusion?
I think we'll just have
to speak for ourselves.
- Prints are like martinis.
Printing one thing is
fine, two is too many,
and three is not enough!
- Life is a gift.
After that, we just
live the life we print.
- I've created a printing cult!
(sighs)
(calm music)
- So it didn't work out
with your girlfriend?
- Her heart was a butcher shop.
- Don't you mean the kind of shop
where they massage the
money out of your pants?
(calm music)
- She's always holding herself
hostage with her drugs.
She must be miserable without me.
- Can someone like that love
you without killing you?
- Her love is a guilty pleasure of mine.
I have the choice between
broken hearted or delusional.
- Well, I guess some things
don't have to be settled.
- I see no cooperation in the night sky.
The planet to me is just a stone tumor.
- Yes, we are bacteria and fungus,
but that's the least
important thing about us.
- It's encouraging that we're
getting someplace together.
- Now, we must make the world remember
where it left the lamp.
One cup of ground up computers,
one bucket of rainwater.
- What's it to ya if
it's rainwater or not?
- Memories just a bucket of rain.
This will help the world unforget.
Now, My My Ramaho Niya Niya!
- That bubble's made out of stone, Mister.
- It's the Cave Computer,
it's leading us to the lamp!
- This world runs on worlds.
It's a cannibal universe.
- Everybody always feeding
off of everybody's privacy.
Mustafa, print us some caviar and toast.
- We all fight for privacy
and we all lose the fight.
The 'Virtual Reality Show,'
it's pornography of the soul,
but then again, just a few days ago,
you were famous and broke.
- They were gonna throw
me in debtor's prison.
- Human life on earth is purgatory,
so don't be surprised when
purgatory doesn't stop.
- So we think that pornography
is an aspect of purgatory.
- And so is technology.
One day we will all be naked
again through technology.
- Sometimes it makes me wish there was a
technology-limiting-machine.
- Until we are naked and alien,
it's a purgatory.
We gotta be quiet, my
roommates are sleeping.
I wanna try try using the lamp sometime.
- You'd love it.
It's like mainlining your dreams.
I wanna use your body in a different way
than I'm accustomed to.
- Question: Do you feel like
you are being pulled inside the lamp?
- Yeah, every time I feel closer to you,
I feel like I'm being pulled
inside the lamp a little bit.
- I'm thinking it might be
fun to go inside the lamp.
- Just because it's inside
doesn't mean it's good.
I only get with lunatics and
hot idiots, Ms. President.
I am that awful man.
- Aren't you content
just to be a naughty boy?
- Sometimes I'd just like to have sex
and feel like it's vaguely fair.
- I'll be sleazy just to contradict you.
- But this shit sandwich
keeps flying towards my face.
I don't know how to avoid it.
- Aladdin,
I don't mind splitting a
shit sandwich with you.
- It is one of the most important things
in the universe that we make love.
- [Ms. President] Don't
look back, Aladdin.
(moaning)
- I was jerking off the other day,
and Mustafa came out of my dick.
- Well, isn't that the saddest
sexual fantasy of all time?
- No, I think it happened.
Lemme put this mask on.
- I'm not into it.
C'mon, don't you want to
be sexually - creative?
- You, Ralph Caulfield and Emily Green
are being charged
with possession and
distribution of marijuana,
pirating music and films.
Jaywalking, littering,
public intoxication,
failing to declare income,
larceny at a salad bar,
public exposure, cohabitation,
sodomy, and printing guns.
You're both monsters,
and I am sending you
straight to bureaucratic hell
in the Labyrinth of Lies.
- The law is a tax, and paying your taxes
is like having a subscription to jail.
- You're the devil!
- No, I'm the Devil's clone!
- No! (gasps)
- Let this be a wake-up alarm to you.
- I didn't realize that
my body parts were alarms.
- And I'll be confiscating this!
- Hey, what's the big idea?
Give that back, Mister!
(calm piano music)
- That was the strongest orgasm
I've ever had in my life.
- Ms. President,
I always thought you were a company girl.
- And that's a bad thing,
because I have a job?
Besides, the company
I'm working for is you.
- You're working for me?
- I have a bad-boy part of my personality
which I need for my
partner to express for me.
We are now insiders of each other.
You have a bottomless need
for every woman in the world
to love you, as every
woman in the world knows.
Yet it's you who now seek averages,
in moderation and balance.
- My biggest fear is
to be poorly suspended
on a tightrope between birth and death.
- Well, of course, you're
going to be insecure
if you're not tucked in correctly.
- I never thought that
I could trust myself
with someone else's heart,
maybe I had to be a
prince to become a genie.
Mustafa, you live here!
- I'm the big fat bear
hiding behind a tiny little tree.
- C'mon! C'mon! C'mon!
- Aww, geewhiz!
- So this is what mainlining
your dreams looks like.
- In here, we all look like
what's right next to us.
- The lamp connects to
a frequency of Wi-Fi
that mushrooms tap into,
fungus is a space-age material.
- So the lamp is basically a mushroom.
- Even Jesus was a
little bit of a mushroom.
And at Zintendo, we've been
developing digital mushrooms
for quite some time.
Within a hundred years,
assuming we live in an average universe,
humans will be contacted by aliens
and during that time, we'll
have evolved ourselves
into a techno-fungal insect species.
- If they are going to
start reinventing humans,
they should really start at
the back and the spine area.
- Human beings are basically insects
wrapped in pigskin.
- So our culture is more
of a yeast after all.
- Technology is ushering
in a neoclassical age.
These columns of data,
tablets, icons, and graffiti
are a continuation of the Roman arts,
reappropriated ideals that form the basis
for a monolithic social sculpture
that is greater than the pyramids,
the Parthenon, the Coliseum, Disney World,
all manmade wonders combined.
Have you ever even wondered
why Mario is Italian?
- Here's something.
Why are we symmetrical vertically,
but not horizontally?
- We actually don't look anything
like what we think we do.
The lamp is five-dimensional.
In the five-dimensional view of things,
we are all one person,
one great person with invisible string
connecting all of our hands.
All our hands are actually the same hand.
- Winged-sandals!
What a relief.
Mustafa, how does it feel
to have a bird's eye view
of time and space?
- I'm dying to die,
but there is no death inside of me.
- They didn't even hide it,
they just left it on the bed,
now where is Aladdin?
- Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uncle Gary? Oh no!
(groaning)
(evil laughter)
- Aladdin!
Oh there you are, franchastic!
- Well, Uncle Gary,
I'm really glad that it happened this way
because at least from inside there,
you can't hurt us.
- Hurt you?
Aladdin, I'm here to save you.
I'm not your uncle.
I'm your dad.
- King of kings, it's time
again for the Technology report.
- I'm kinda busy right now;
I have to thank all my friends
for thanking my photos on Thankster.
What are you wearing on your head?
- It's a hat, it records
everything I am thinking,
it tastes like bananas,
and it's crushable.
- Psychic soft electronics, incredible!
How did you design such a thing?
- I printed it,
with this lamp that I confiscated
from Magical America.
Watch.
Mustafa, print out a million drones
and a million drone printing machines
to print out a hundred million more.
- Genarro Russo,
we can finally have anything that we want!
- Aaah!
Oh Aladdin, I don't know what to do!
Emily and her friends
are in jail for life!
They delivered me her arm this morning.
- My poor daughter!
Aladdin, you must go save her!
- Who's that inside the lamp?
That doesn't sound like Mustafa.
- Mom, Uncle Gary is
stuck inside the lamp,
and now he says that he's actually Dad.
- Gary?
- First off, Dad,
why did you abandon me in the mineshaft?
If I hadn't rubbed the
lamp, I would have died!
- The CIA was coming,
and I didn't want to risk
them getting the lamp.
I came back the next day
but you weren't there,
and I couldn't find you anywhere,
I've been looking for you for over a week!
- Due to the constant
irritation of Magical America,
would you consider
hosting a mass-beheading
later this afternoon?
- Oh, I think if we
chopped off their heads,
they would love it.
- Also, it has come to
my attention from the CIA
that our Prince Average
Cabbage is not a prince at all
but a recording artist
for Zintendo Records.
- Send the drones after him at once!
- I was a wanted man!
You see, after I left to
become an entertainer,
I ended up hanging out in Hollywood.
The Sultan was hanging out too,
but he wasn't a Sultan yet,
you see, he was the ne'er-do-well son
of a former stunt kid who
had started his own religion.
Me and the Sultan opened up
a children's massage parlor
for rich and famous children.
But kids started to go
missing and I came to realize
that the sultan was comparing
the size of his penis
with all the boys who came in,
and every time there was a
boy who had a bigger one,
he'd kill them.
Now the Sultan was so well
connected in Hollywood
that the cops wouldn't
do anything about it
no matter how much I begged.
They even told him I was
trying to turn him in.
The last thing he ever said
to me was to leave town
and if he ever saw me again,
he'd kill me and my boy.
- Well, then, your cover is blown,
there's drones all over this house.
The CIA will know everything.
- You all have a disease
and the only thing that will
cure it is sucking my dick!
Just kidding.
You actually signed a contract
allowing the Sultan to
kill and enslave you,
perhaps you should read the fine print
on your cell phone bills.
- We already knew the
Sultan was a murderer.
The Sultan is not a murderer, he's a king!
In a couple of hours, you
will be smited by headsmen.
Thanks for playing the video game.
- Fucking CIA pig.
- Why do we assume pigs
are bourgeois policemen?
- Only last week, we
were trying to shed light
on dark, inhumane, secret government shit.
What happened?
- I'm in desperate need
of salad and religion.
- Considering the state of the planet,
maybe people who think
of themselves as average
are enlightened.
- Now to reprogram this
Flesh-knob of disappointment.
Mustafa, print me a 40-inch cock.
- Look at him treating the
lamp like it's his mistress.
Despicable!
- It fits right over the old one.
Wow!
(evil laughter)
Forty inches soft, I
didn't even think of that.
Fair enough, Mustafa.
♫ Bigger than yours bigger than yours
♫ I like mine when it's bigger than yours
♫ Bigger than yours
♫ Bigger ♫
(funky music)
- Get your canned lamps here,
canned lamps, free magical
3-D printing lamps in a can.
Hello Sir, what will you print?
- Thanks, I'm gonna print
a jungle of pornography.
- Hello, ma'am, what will you print?
- I'm printing a living
bird inside my brain.
- Print me a digital pickaxe
to mine digital spacebux.
- Print me a contact lens
that teaches my eyes to
think like an insect.
- That's cool!
- Print me a robot that
thanks all my friends
for thanking my photos on 'Thankster'.
- I like everything.
Some things I like a lot,
but other things I just like.
- Print me an asparagus chair!
Wow!
By the way, who are you?
- I'm the Princess.
- What?
- I mean, I'm not the Princess,
I'm just a prince named "S."
- Oh, okay.
- That checks out, yeah, yeah.
(calm music)
- The surveillance drones
can't fly this high.
- We'll get you out of
the lamp soon enough, Dad.
- I don't even want to
get out of the lamp!
Let me explain.
All my life I've felt that
I was somehow degenerate,
and after some time of
practicing Dark White magic,
I came to believe that the planet
was mirroring my degenerate ways.
That night in the mines, I cast a spell
trying to summon Father Earth,
I thought I could give
the planet a sex change.
I cut open my own penis
and turned it inside out
as part of the ritual,
trying to unleash the information
necessary to create Lover Earth,
the beautiful hermaphrodite.
I thought I could turn the planet
from degenerate to regenerate this way
and I mistakenly thought that my cock
was the Tree of Life.
- Wow, yeah, the planet
probably does need a sex change.
- Well, it turns out, Aladdin,
that you're gonna have a son,
and your lamp and all that it creates
is basically just my grandson's cock.
So now I've crawled
into my grandson's cock,
you need to cut it open,
turn it inside out,
give birth to your father.
- So the lamp is like a
womb inside of a dick?
- Yeah, and after you open it,
the planet will become Lover Earth,
a planet where gender is no longer binary,
nor is technology.
- Print me vampires in submarines.
- Print me Pandora's Box bombs!
- Print me pointy boots, see,
I like to look down and see pointy boots.
- That's the most epic,
brilliant, ace thing on the planet!
You're a total legend mate.
Print me the biggest bindle of beak.
- Print me the immortal
jellyfish regeneration algorithm.
- Print me my baseball
uniform that I love.
- Print me the hair from
last year's haircut.
- Print me everything I've ever lost.
- Out of the way!
Out of the way!
Stay back!
- [Crowd] Free Ralph! Free Ralph!
- Let him speak!
- Yeah, why doesn't everybody pipe down
and let him say somethin'.
- This place is starting
to look like Hollywood.
You're just going to print
out an analogue version
of the Internet, and
there's no room for it!
And since we are bound to this planet,
industry and production can't mirror
the infinite expansion of the universe,
though we fantasize about
filling the stars to their brim.
We must change the nature
of what we wish for.
- You know, Ms. President,
I don't remember Regular
Town being this big,
what's going on over there?
- That's 982,000th Street
and 14,512th Avenue,
the town has been expanding
as the world keeps printing.
Holy shit, those are
anti-fungal chemtrails!
- I can't see anything!
Aah, aah, aah!
(calm music)
(all gasp)
- Oh my God!
(machinery noise)
- Farmer Dave!
- Hey, Aladdin, you little pervert!
(music intensifies)
Open Sesame.
- [Sultan] Ouch, my cock!
- Gimme my arm back, motherfucker!
- Welcome back to the
two-armed girls club!
- Yeah.
- Phew.
- I missed you.
(cheering)
(calm music)
- (giggles) Hi!
- Hey!
All right, Dad,
are you ready for
irreversible planetary status?
- C'mon, man, what have
I been talking about!
(calm music)
♫ I leave love behind her
♫ I was scared to know her
♫ Now the high is over
♫ Because I need a shoulder
♫ Love is on its way
♫ Sometimes you're me from far away
♫ Just waiting to get blown hard ♫
- Someone quick, help!
(life support beeping)
- We plugged in his brain
and it's downloading onto the mainframe
to the Undernet,
which is the Internet
that dead people use.
The other end of the universe
doesn't seem very far away from here.
There's pieces of it all around us
but our brains can't organize
the materials properly.
- Us fifth-dimensional guys
can build a computer out
of a chair, no problem.
- Well, it's time to return
to the fifth dimension.
- What is dying like?
- At first, death emerges from within
like a blackened burning insect
springing out of your bones,
filling up your body
with the brightest fluorescent colors,
till your body is filled to the brim
and language loses all meaning.
Your mind is so fried from
contemplating googolplex
that it gives way to fractals
and complex abstractions.
Then the fluorescents
start to spin like a wheel
and that wheel carries
you off towards oblivion.
- The deathbed is a horrible hang.
- Aladdin, you're a pretty cool guy
considering you came out of my dick.
(life support flat lines)
I'm on the computer now.
- I love you, Dad.
- That's nice.
- You are the keepers
together of a sacred flame.
- I feel like we're inside a fiery cocoon.
Where you are vulnerable,
I will build walls and
fortresses around those areas.
- I will always be the
closest person to you,
anything else requires an intervention.
- Your feelings are always right.
- I will persevere until
we agree on everything,
even in a heated argument.
There's no bluffing in our relationship.
- You are the hero of my heart.
You are my heart hero.
- You are my black magician.
- I will be the Hashem to your Moses.
- I will be the Guadalupe
to your Juan Diego.
- Home is wherever the two of us are.
- I will share my intellectual
property with you.
- I will love you unconditionally,
challenge you intellectually,
and sexualize you forever.
- I will give you the best
deal of any married man.
- I will be eternally
devoted to our family.
- I will never question having
faith in doing life together.
- You're under arrest,
because you're the best.
- You're under arrest
(applause)
(calm music)
- As a regenerate who has the world,
I must say it's nice to have a wish
that I can make come true all the time.
- I take care of the boy,
and the man takes care of me.
The prince was the genie,
and the genie was the prince.
- I gave birth to my father.
- Nice one, mate!
Let's go, mate.
- Let's go back to Hollywood
and try to salvage what's
left of pornography.
- Like preserve and archive it all
on a giant hard drive in a giant building?
Great Sultan, you're too much.
- You think I'm too much,
but I'm not even enough.
- Now that's the good stuff, mate.
Yeah.
♫ I'm phonin' in the blues
'cause my life ain't stallin'
♫ The phone just rang
♫ To say the blues Ain't calling
♫ I thought that I'd always
called it like I saw it
♫ I've got the blues and I
know just how to call 'em
♫ Baby that's how they call the blues
♫ I'm phoning in the blues
like a phony version of the
♫ Blues that they thought that they had
♫ It was a phoney baloney
version of the blues
♫ It was the version that
I thought my baby had had
♫ I try to retract him
♫ My baby never had
'em till we called them
♫ On the telephone but they didn't listen
♫ Baby that's how they call the blues
♫ I'm phoning in the blues
♫ Cuz my life ain't stalling
♫ The phone just rang
♫ To say the blues ain't calling
♫ I thought that I'd always
Called it like I saw it
♫ I've got the blues and I
know just how to call 'em
♫ Baby that's how they call the blues
(calm music)
♫ The words I needed to soothe me
♫ Turned gray from being defenseless
♫ But I had another plan too
♫ Believe it if you're tell me too
♫ Sharing my home
♫ And everywhere we go is home too
♫ We're trading our graves
♫ Now you'll never have to see me afraid
♫ Unless we are a liar
♫ The call I needed came early
♫ And tried of using my patience
♫ The words I wanted came through me
♫ And out of confrontation
♫ I asked you what to do with my fists
♫ If she could ever see me like this
♫ Sharing my home
♫ And everywhere we go is home too
♫ We're trading our graves
♫ Now you'll never have to see me afraid
♫ Unless we are a liar
(calm music)
♫ Sharing my home
♫ And everywhere we go is home too
♫ We're trading our graves
♫ Now you'll never have to see me afraid
♫ Unless we are a liar ♫