On the Centenary of Russian Cinema
With the support of the
Russian Ministry of Culture
Channel One
Film Direction
I checked in the studio photo records.
It's definitely her.
Dago Film Productions
Present
The wife of an enemy of the revolution.
Konstantin Khabensky
Where am I going to find a face like that?
Elizabeta Boyarskaya
Sergei Bezrukov
In a film by
Andrei Kravchuk
ADMIRAL
Baltic Sea, Pillau Region.
German Waters. 1916
Look sharp. Mines at least
seven meters from the surface!
82 feet under the keel.
85 feet under the keel.
- Officers on deck.
- At ease!
- Well?
- It's foggy.
No signals from the "Sentry"
or the "Hunter" for a while.
Try signaling them again.
I'll be with the division Commander.
Everything's calm,
Alexander Vasilievich.
- Would you like some tea?
- Thank you.
That's the Kazan Mother of God,
if I'm not mistaken?
Sofia Fyodorovna gave it to me,
before our marriage.
Anna Vasilievna gave me this.
As a memento. Look..
Beautiful.
Yes?
May I come in?
Gentlemen. Please, proceed to the bridge immediately.
The Germans, gentlemen.
The Germans..
Their 210mm cannons
against our 45s.
- That is "Friedrich Karl".
- So much for your "Sentry"..
Thank God they're quiet.
They've missed us.
All hands to battle stations!
All to fighting stations!
Battle stations! Attention!
- Full speed ahead!
Helmsman, full speed ahead.
Bear for action! Cut the ropes!
Hold her steady!
- Why have we slowed down?
- Engine room! Why have we slowed down?
What's happening?
A shell got the pipes
in the engine room!
- How long to fix it?
- Half an hour.
You have 15 minutes.
In 15 minutes they'll
turn us into a sieve.
Yes, we're a sitting duck!
Why have you stopped firing?
Midshipman!
Are you alive?
Alexander Vasilievich!
Should we get the orderlies?
Go to the deck-cabin.
Gurov, you alive?
Man the guns!
To arms!
To arms, I said...
Lads!
Fire!
- Yes!
- We got them on the main bridge!
They're off us now.
The German's bridge is damaged!
Relieve the gunners!
Third gunners to the main guns
Good thing we dropped the mines...
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Good that we dropped the mines,
if not...
Your Excellency, we've
repaired the pipes.
- The bridge can't be fixed quickly.
- They will the reserve one.
Let's get out of here,
while we still have time.
Mines, mines.
Full speed ahead!
- Head for Pillau!
- But that's our minefield!
Assemble the officers
on the starboard deck.
At attention!
Gentlemen!
There's a German squadron behind us.
The "Friedrich Karl" is in front.
The way back to base in shut.
So I see no way out except
to lure the Germans onto our mines.
We head for Pillau.
Onto our minefield. Questions?
I have a question.
One meter from the mines!
We won't make it.
Our own mines. We're
digging our own graves.
Calm down, midshipman.
We're going onto the minefield.
God help us!
Let us pray.
Remove your headwear.
All powerful God...
Lord our Saviour...
Pardon Your faithful servants
hear and protect us...
- Mine at port side!
- Stop engines.
Ready to reverse.
Mine at port side!
Calm down, gentlemen.
God have mercy...
The Germans are opening sights.
Right, now they're all together.
Reverse.
We've missed the mine.
- That's the end..
- Goodbye, my friends.
They're going to finish off.
What a shame, gentlemen...
Give the order for battle.
Stop! As you were.
Slow ahead!
Previous course.
We're past the minefield.
Head for home, gentlemen.
Champagne for the captain.
Podgorsky, come back to us.
- You've already completed your dare.
- No!
I promised to stand until
the end of the game.
Russian naval base.
Helsingfors, Finland.
What is the dare for this one?
A new uniform!
Down a glass of cognac
for our victory.
That'll be a pleasure for him.
We need something more challenging!
Make him kiss someone.
The first person to come
through this door.
Yes! PassionateIy.
And with feeIing.
That's your dare,
Alexander Vasilievich.
- Quite a situation...
- Gentlemen, this is not funny.
The first through the door will be
the sailor I sent for champagne.
- Have you no conscience?
- That's how it is in war time:
Rear Admiral Kolchak
kissing a common sailor.
Until he comes in,
I suggest we continue.
What should this dare be?
- Vladimir, we're waiting.
- Attention!
And here's the sailor.
I was just Iooking for you.
I've been called to headquarters.
Afraid I won't be back.
Will you see my wife home?
As a friend. If I don't have time.
This is Anna Vasilievevna.
My wife.
I ask you...
What's going on here,
gentlemen?
Alexander Vasilievich just
took on a dare.
To kiss the first person
to come through the door.
That is, your wife.
So off you go to your watch.
Alexander Vasilievich.
We implore you...
You ought to honour it!
Rules of the game -
Like service regulations!
Come on Annushka, it's just a dare!
You really should obey!
Dares are more serious
than card debts.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Your attention please!
- Slavushka, run off and play.
- All right, papa.
Volodya, see what a
ship I have!
I'm starting to believe in fate,
Anna Vasilievna.
Today, when I came to
Helsingfors,
for some reason
I was sure
that I would meet you.
Really?
Yes, indeed.
Sonechka, do you remember
when we Ieft Moscow so suddenly?
Your father had the bad luck
to fall in love.
Why are you telling me this?
Your neighbour - she is just
too beautiful.
Sasha is prone to infatuation.
But it never lasts long.
Yes, and I wanted to ask,
There'll be a ball at the
Podgorsky tomorrow. Are you coming?
Kirill Fyodorovich,
come over here!
Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
Why on earth do you have
to entangle all these balls of yarn?
How did the Tsars
choose their brides?
The brides would untangle a yarn.
The Tsar watched through the keyhole.
If a girl fidgeted, or lost her temper,
that was it.
Out you go, lazybones!
That's because Tsar's wife
must have angel patience,
and self-restraint.
That's how my grandmother
prepared me to be a bride.
Interesting.
And why did your grandmother
call you a Shelkova village cossack?
Because I am a Shelkova woman.
Our Cossacks married Turkish women.
I have Turkish blood too.
So, let's drink to the Turks!
With pleasure.
- Mama, is father an Admiral?
- A rear-Admiral.
Better if he'd stayed a captain.
I Iike him as a captain better.
Rear-Admiral is hard to say.
Better if you got some sleep.
Go to sleep, my dear.
You won't go swimming
again with father.
So what did you find out?
It turns out, these
Turkish ladies from the harems,
would not give anyone anything!
A traveler comes along,
and asks for a glass of water.
What does the lady of the house reply?
"When Ivan comes, he will
give it to you, traveler".
Slander! Slander and calumny!
I for one would never
turn you down.
I fear, Anna Vasilievna, you
would have your hands full.
I'm very partial to drinking.
I understand you perfectly.
Generally speaking, it seems to me that
water and war are the only
loves in your life.
It seems to me you know
perfectly well -
that's not how it is.
Well.
It's getting late.
We had a nice walk,
and now it's time to go.
Who knows, Anna Vasilievna -
whether we'll ever have such a
good time as we did today?
Thank you... dear
Alexander Vasilievich.
Go now, go.
This is the light signal of
a sinking ship, Anna Vasilievna.
Good night.
I was thinking that something had happened:
Sasha...
Is everything all right between us?
Not exactIy.
Tell me if this is - but...
Are you sure this is serious?
I don't know...
I have no intention of getting in your way,
Slavushka, Mother and
I will leave. To St. - Petersburg.
Sonya, I...
You don't need to go anywhere.
Everything will be all right. I promise.
You are my wife and I am your husband.
That's how it will always be.
How is Slavushka?
His temperature is nearly normal.
Shall I wait for you at lunch?
No, I'll be dining at the Assembly.
Alexander Vasilievich, congratulations
on your new assignment!
What a brilliant career!
No, I understand well that you can't force
someone to love or hate
against his or her will.
- But we took vows before God.
- So what?
You swore before God,
to love me and remain faithful.
You understand perfectly well that...
Remain faithful - what do you mean?
Not go to bed with someone else?
If that's what you mean, I haven't
been unfaithful to you.
God, you're still such a child...
I don't understand.
What on earth are you doing here?
Nikolai, tell headquarters
that the mining operation is
complete and there are no losses.
We're heading back to base.
Thank you for your service, gentlemen.
Alexander Vasilievich, please submit
my report to the Naval Command.
- What is this report?
- I request a transfer to another ship.
Have we let you down somehow,
Sergei Nikolaevich?
Rear-Admiral, Sir,
a radio message from the coast.
From prince Melikov. To all at sea.
Ragotsem Cape, Gulf of Riga, 1916
- A communications buoy ahead.
- Stop the engines.
- Engines stopped.
- Drop anchor!
Your Excellency.
We received a radiogram.
- "I arrived with the "Glory". Kolchak".
- Go.
The cable is connected.
The communication is established.
Alexander Vasilievich, we're
connected with the coast.
Man the starboard battle stations.
Man the battle stations.
Hurry!
This is the commander of cruiser the "Glory",
Rear-Admiral Kolchak.
The situation is critical. The Germans
are pressing us on the right flank.
I will coordinate your
firing operation myself.
Grid thirty. Coordinates.
Three thousand five hundred.
Two thousand two hundred.
Battle stations! Man the guns!
Sight eighteen.
Deflection forty three.
Fire!
Twenty more to the left. Three higher..
The Germans are turning their guns!
Hallo! Hallo!
Hallo!? I can't hear you.
Man the guns! In pIace!
The Germans have opened fire on us.
- So?
- We're a sitting duck now.
- We need to head out the sea.
- Then how do I adjust the fire?!
We're staying in place.
Check the communication!
Are you wounded?
Let me help... This is not the time
or place, Sergei Nikolaevich.
But as a military officer you surprised
me with your report.
To leave your comrades with whom
you have served so long.
Given the personal situation that has
arisen between the two of us.
What situation?
The onIy situation now is war -
fighting the enemy and doing
your duty to the homeland. Yes!
Rear-Admiral Kolchak. What are
your new firing coordinates?
Ten to the Ieft and five higher!
Open fire!
Mates! Attack! Hurray!
Stop! Stop!
Here is a letter in Morse code.
I did my best with a textbook at home.
Thank you. But today is the
last time we shall see each other.
We can't meet again.
What happened?
Did we do something wrong?
Anna Vasilievna...
We didn't even dance.
Why AIexander Vasilievich?
Because I Iove you.
Farewell!
Alexander Vasilievich.
Give me the letter.
My darling Annushka! You're all drenched.
Be careful or you'll fall ill.
I'm very tired.
Sure Annushka, I...
Mogilev, the Emperor's
General Headquarters
The Emperor will see you here in the park.
- I wish you health, Your Majesty.
- Greetings.
I have been told of your bravery.
Of the courage you showed
on the Baltic Sea.
I acted according to the call
of duty, Your Majesty.
I invited you here to inform
you of our decision.
You have been assigned
the rank of Vice-Admiral,
and become the Commander-in-Chief
of the Black Sea fleet.
Thank you for your trust,
Your Majesty.
Take this, and may the icon
of the long-suffering Job
give you strength.
Thank you.
I wish you luck!
Allow me to take my leave,
Your Majesty.
Godspeed, admiral.
"I must know that you're alive ".
Cabman!
To the train station!
Faster, please...
Gentlemen...
to buy Alexander Vasilievich
protection - from the sun!
- It's like a resort area there.
- Sevastopol is not Baltics.
When are you going there,
Sophia Fyodorovna?
Tea, gentlemen.
This is your fleet!
Yesterday I was walking by Mikhailovsky
castle when I heard children arguing:
"Mine, give it me", "No"...
Then all of a sudden it
became crystal clear to me.
"Everything will come in due time.
It already has come".
There is no more mine or yours.
Every morning I open my eyes
and smile... I'm alive...
I am waiting... This is a reward,
not a punishment.
Because against all the laws
of physics you give,
the more you give
the more you receive.
Just imagine,
I can feel in my hands
a big and unbelievabIy
shiny ball.
This is Grace.
A gift...
Happiness... That's the
way it is.
Don't laugh. I know.
I stand on the edge
of a vast unseen world.
And although we see the future
unclearly, as the Apostle said:
"Through a glass darkly...
And now abideth faith,
hope and love.
But the greatest of these is love".
Alexander Vasilievich,
I heard that you
will be in Petrograd...
How soon? March, April?
For some reason it seems
to me that it won't be long.
May I come in? Your Excellency,
a wireless message just came in.
On March 2nd the Emperor Nicholas
the Second abdicated the throne.
Power is with
the Provisional Government...
The monarchy has fallen.
A Provisional Government...
What does that mean?
I don't think it bodes
at all well for Russia.
I think you're right.
Anna Vasilievna, unfortunately...
Kronstadt, 1917
The revolution has eclipsed our future.
The darkness is approaching.
- Where are you taking us?
- Wherever...
Gentlemen, are we just
a herd of animals?
- We should do something!
- Hands off, sailor!
Please, obey.
It's a treason.
- Listen to my command.
- My God!
We're at war. Come to your senses!
What are you doing?
- Sort out the Admiral.
- Fear the Lord.
Gentlemen! Save yourselves,
that's an order!
- Run!
- Shoot them...
Kolya!
May God be with you!
Sevastopol
Annushka, good you're
home. Pack your bags.
- What happened, Serezha?
- Admiral Nepenin has been killed!
- How did he die?
- I said he was killed!
He was clubbed with rifle butts
and stabbed with bayonets. Brutes!
Serezha, I can't understand
what's happening.
God! What on earth
is happening?
Serezhenka, calm down, explain.
Podgorsky has also been killed.
He died in my arms.
Out of the way!
- What's the matter?
- The first order...
...of the Petrograd Soviet
is for all officers
to hand over weapons.
To prevent a counter-revolutionary
conspiracy.
Turn in your weapon, Admiral.
- We're leaving for Petrograd...
- Why are we leaving?
- I was able to take some leave...
- Wait a minute!
What are you waiting for?
Pack your bags...
Admiral, follow
this order immediately.
- Get out of here!
- Listen here, Admiral..
Get out!
All right men,
we'll figure this out on deck.
Officer of the watch, tell everyone
to line up on deck.
Wait, Serezha, how can I...
how can I go...
All letters come to this address.
I'm waiting...
At least close your suitcase?
Anya. Anya,
Anechka, please my dear. I'm begging you.
The boat leaves in half an hour.
We're finished
if we don't make it on time.
Arms!
As you were!
Attention! Align up the crew!
- Fall in!
- Who are you obeying?
- You afraid, lads!
- Fall in!
Quick.
Officers, gentlemen.
- Weapons up.
- I'm sorry!
At ease.
To avoid bloodshed,
I order the officers
to turn in their weapons.
Admiral, sir, your weapon...
Sir...
Petrograd
Come with us, lady... Let's go!
You weren't home today.
I got the mail and there is a
letter for you.
From Sevastopol.
It's strange that mail
still arrives.
I'm feeling tired today.
In three days I'll be in Petrograd.
Seeing you is all I'm dreaming of.
Sevastopol
Hearing your voice.
- Kerensky has summoned me.
- It's dangerous in Petrograd...
the sailors and workers
have rebelled.
Admiral Nepenin was stabbed
to death with a bayonet.
- Can I see you to the station?
- Sonya, I...
Rostislav is waiting for you.
Go to him.
- Will you come back?
- Of course.
What silly thoughts.
PETROGRAD
Kerensky wants to offer you
the post of war minister...
We'll see. I wish he wouId
see me on time.
But he is coming late.
Today...
at the Mikhailovsky Castle...
I can see we have a different
view of the war...
By condoning anarchy
you have broken up the army...
- ... and destroyed the Russian navy.
- Don't you forget yourseIf?...
Unless I have authority
to impose strict order
your proposals
are unacceptable to me.
Former procedures in the army
are not acceptable to us.
I was the first to swear allegiance
and I'll be the first
to leave the Navy.
In this way,
I will make a public statement
that the current state of affairs
is ruinous for Russia.
I accept your resignation.
I am honoured.
You should be arrested for your
counter-revolutionary leanings.
But given your merits,
I offer you to go to America.
I'm giving you the chance to
continue the war against Germany.
Are you exiling me from Russia?
The Americans need an expert who can
conduct a landing
and seize Constantinople.
My family is still in Sevastopol.
I'll take care of them.
I'll ask the allies to have
them brought to you overseas.
Thank you.
Dear...
My darling, Anna Vasilievna.
You are my happiness.
How will I live without you...
What?
Their times are over!
- I'm leaving Russia.
- Why?
How tired you look...
I love you.
And I always will.
Forgive me.
Farewell,
Alexander Vasilievich.
I know that you are alive.
Sevastopol
Is it ready?
At least let us pray.
Pray if you want to.
Listen, bring the rope.
Let's go while he draws the
sailors away!
Stop!
Quick, Iet's go...
we can't wait for him here
Stop!
Mrs. Kolchak! Open the
door, Mrs. Kolchak!
Document check!
Break it down!
Break the windows!
It's time, the British ship
sets sail in an hour.
A YEAR LATER. AUTUMN 1918.
TRANS-SIBERIA RAILWAY
I think I'm doing it better.
Take your place.
What a good shot!
Let's drink to our wishes.
Even the ones that don't come true?
Does that make them
any less wishes.
- Excuse me, Madam.
- Yes, of course.
- Mikhail Ivanovich.
- Anna Vasilievna!
- My God!
- What a surprise!
I haven't seen you for a year...
What brings you here?
Sergei Nikolaevich has been
sent to the Far East.
He's on a mission to
disarm the Pacific fleet.
Sergei Nikolaevich?
...So he's in power now?
- A red commissar.
- I have no right to judge him.
At a time like this.
It's the same time for everyone.
- Where are you going?
- To Omsk.
But the Soviets are in
power there too?
No. Kolchak is there.
But I thought Alexander
Vasilievich was abroad?
Kerensky did send him abroad.
But after the Bolshevik coup
he returned to Russia
to fight the Bolsheviks.
I'm sorry, Anna Vasilievna,
I must go.
Goodbye.
Serezha...
Aha... yes... yes, Anya!
What is it?
Kolchak is in Omsk
gathering an army.
Anya, if this is a rebuke,
you know I agreed to collaborate
with the authorities because
they allowed us
to go far away from
this fratricidal madness...
To Japan, China...
It's all for your sake, Anechka.
I don't blame you for anything.
But I love Alexander
Vasilievich, Serezha.
and now I need to be with him...
I realize that these are harsh words,
but I have never
stopped loving him.
I see!... Stop, stop...
Let me help.
So there it is. A time of wars
and revolutions.
Anything goes.
The time has nothing
to do with it.
When I fell asleep I
was your husband.
I woke up and I am
no longer your husband.
I know it's hard for you
but you've got to be strong.
You'll forget me before long.
Let me be the one
to decide that.
Siberia, Eastern Front.
November 1918
I pledge and swear
before Almighty God,
His Holy Gospel
and the Life-Giving Cross:
to be faithful and ever true
to the Russian state
as my Homeland.
I pledge and swear
to serve it as the Supreme Ruler of Russia,
without regard for my life,
family ties or friendship,
enmity, or gain,
and mindful only of the revival
and success of the Russian state.
Hereby I make the sign
of the cross,
and kiss the words and
Cross of my Saviour.
Amen.
Omsk
Hello, my lady!
Who are you looking for?
You, I think.
How can I help you?
I'm the one who would
like to help you.
My dear,
sweet...
Alexander Vasilievich,
I have realized that I simply
can no longer wait!
Do you remember how I dreamed
to be on the deck of your ship?
Just to see you.
You would not even notice me,
I would not disturb you;
all I need is to stand nearby.
And now it seems that I will
experience this happiness.
Take joy in your victories.
Our troops are already
moving towards the Volga.
And God willing,
we will all see Moscow soon.
And I will know that
I have played a small part
in all of this.
I congratulate you, General,
on a successful operation.
Thank you...
Not only my achievement,
but the entire army...
Nothing can lift spirits
of the soldiers as an attack.
I heard from the Allies that
they're about to recognize your government
as the only legitimate one in Russia...
Whatever laws we pass we'll still be shot,
if we lose this war.
My heart swells with pride for you
and all who are fighting beside you
for the revival of Russia...
We need to build on our success
and continue the offensive in all directions.
Your goal is to reach Ufa.
Good luck, general. Godspeed!
More than a year has gone by
since the last time we met.
Your Excellency.
General Janin from
the Allies has arrived.
After all the changes we've been through
I was wondering how you would...
I... I'm afraid even
to think about this.
Most of all I'm afraid to place
you in an awkward situation
because of my unexpected arrival.
General Janin, our allies France and Britain
Have given you the rank
of Head Commander.
And you are the Supreme Commander of Russia.
Put it over here, bring the hot water!
A foreigner cannot command
the Russian army.
Do you invite me to command
the Czech prisoners of war
who guard the railway?
It is a strategic object.
From now, you are commander
of the allied Czech forces.
- I thank you, Admiral.
- I thank you, General Janin.
All I need to know is that you
are in the world.
That nothing bad has
happened to you.
To see you sometimes,
even from afar.
If only you knew how
I am tempted to come
and see you so we could talk.
My love for you is
even greater than before.
I've been writing this letter
to you for so many days
and I still cannot bring
myself to send it.
Your Excellency!
I welcome you to our city!
Accept this bread and salt
as our hospitality.
The geese saved Rome and you
have saved our city.
Here you are, your Excellency...
It's a good thing it's
not a cow, gentlemen!
Write it down as a gift.
Officers and soldiers of the Russian army!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Perm, Ekaterinburg and Elabuga
have been taken.
General Kappel recently took Ufa
in battle.
We're only about 100
versts away
from Denikin's armies.
The Reds have broken the front in three places.
The First and the Second armies have been defeated.
Together with them we shall
move on Moscow!
Go.
As the Apostle Paul said:
"For now we see
through a glass darkly...
And now abideth faith,
hope and love... "
May God help us!
You are starting to recover.
God is merciful.
There are rumours that
there will be evacuation.
Where are we going to load the wounded?
Anna Vasilievna,
you should speak with him:
well, about the rail wagons.
- Are the Reds so close?
- Haven't you heard the cannons?
There are not enough cars
for the wounded.
Kolchak can't think about them.
You should have reminded him.
Vera, it's impossible.
Besides, we were not that close.
Who will listen to me?
But you are a lady.
They will listen to you
and kiss your hand.
I don't know
how to act as a petitioner.
Come on, my dear,
it would be easy for you.
Ladies,
they brought some
wounded officers. By revolted soldiers.
Let's go.
There are pockets of resistance
even in the far rear.
It's worse at the front,
not to mention the constant lack
of ammunition and provisions.
The Reds have crossed the Tobol River.
Omsk can never surrender.
Losing Omsk means
losing the army.
We can't risk the army.
Gentlemen! There can only be one decision.
To fight with our last force
to save Omsk.
Yes. Of course.
I swear before God! I am with you!
Kappel's army is still trying
to keep back the Bolsheviks,
Giving up Omsk -
That would be the disaster!
Excuse me, gentlemen.
I'm from the front, so no time
to make myself more presentable.
- May I report?
- Yes.
Bad news, gentlemen. Treason.
The second Ukrainian regiment has
defected
and abandoned the central front.
The Reds are moving towards Omsk.
They will be here in another week or two.
That's how it is, gentlemen.
It's your decision,
Sir Supreme Ruler.
I declare Irkutsk to be
the seat of power.
I order the evacuation
from Omsk to begin.
We will make this sacrifice
to save the army. To carry on...
Omsk, november 1919
...our struggle against the Bolsheviks.
I'm not letting you through!
Move aside!
The Prime Minister's office
will be in carriage B.
Viktor Nikolaevich, how is loading
transportation of the wounded proceeding..
This is where the Executive Office
will be located.
And the last compartment
will be used for telegraph calls.
Alexander Vasilievich.
Could you come here
for a minute?
What?
I think I just saw Anna Vasilievna here.
Alexander Vasilievich,
the medical cars are completely full.
No room even for minor injuries.
- Open the carriage.
- I can't.
- Make room in the second car.
- The merchants boarded are in there.
- They paid.
- Did you hear my order?
- It's up to you...
- Carry the wounded.
Would you like them to lie
in the snow?!
- Do as you... They're frozen.
- Carriage full.
Dear Anna Vasilievna.
Once I made an unforgivable
mistake in parting from you.
I never want to make
the same mistake again.
I... Will you come along with me?
In the same carriage.
I'm not sure if you'll agree
to remain always by my side
from now on. Morning and evening.
Otherwise I...
I can't go on without you...
My sweet dearest Anna Vasilievna!
No room! Where are you going?!
Paris, France, 1919
"How Iong will the Supreme Ruler
of Russia continue to retreat?"
"The Ruler of Russia abandoned Omsk.
Has Kolchak lost the war to the Bolsheviks?"
Trans-Siberian railroad.
470 km to Irkutsk
Merry Christmas.
Where is your ring, Anna Vasilievna?
I haven't worn it for a while -
and you didn't notice.
Anna Vasilievna, there is something
I need to tell you.
Today I wrote a letter to Sophia Federovna.
I asked her for a divorce.
I don't know how much time
the Lord has left me,
but I want to be honest
with her until the end.
Tell me... will you be my wife?
Alexander Vasilievich...
We're together at last.
Isn't that enough?
Anna Vasilievna, I asked you
a very clear question.
Why do you remain silent?
We haven't even said our Chirstmas toast.
What happened?
Nizhneudinsk station.
450 km to Irkutsk
- Mama, Iook it's the Czechs!
- Step back!
It's the Allies!..
Merry Christmas.
Greetings, Anna Vasilievna
- Why have we stopped again?
- The Czechs have delayed us.
The bastards are moving
their 20,000 cars
stuffed full of junk
and then perhaps it will be our turn.
They are completely brazen!
Convoy - to the arms!
Stand aside!
Major! Stopping the Ruler's
train is an act of treason...
The Admiral told the
convoy to take up arms.
It's an order from
General Janin...
General Janin obey
the orders of Admiral Kolchak.
Who is the Supreme Ruler of Russia.
Mr. Prime Minister.
There is an uprising in Irkutsk.
You have nowhere to go.
Please let me pass.
Kappel's army is moving
after us
and we are prepared to
quell any resistance.
- May I come in?
- Certainly.
There is a telegram from Kappel...
from Kulomzino.
Bypassed Kulomzino. Heading straight.
Quick! Put me through
to General Kappel!
Your army must reach
Irkutsk at all costs!
The city is rebelling.
I am heading there now.
Discharge your duty honorabIy!
Thank you!
My horse!
Why have they stopped firing?
We're out of ammunition!
Your Excellency,
we're out of ammunition.
- Run to Lozhkin and get some!
- None there either!
Lieutenant-General Voytsekhovsky
with an advance detachment...
We're being pressed on the left flank.
And we are out of ammunition.
You may go.
- What about communications?
- We can't... Line's cut.
Keep trying!
- Answer, headquarters...
- Headquarters here.
Vladimir, how did you get here?
Everything is under fire. Why have
you ceased the offensive?
What offensive? We haven't
got a single bullet left.
I received Kolchak's telephonogram.
There's a rebellion in Irkutsk.
We must free the city.
We'll get through to the Admiral.
Only we can save the city.
We need to attack.
- Is the main army on the way?
-We'll be dead when they arrive.
Prepare for battle. We have
no other option. Time is running out.
Sergei Nikolaevich, tell
the men to line up.
Officers and soldiers!
Lads... We have nowhere to get
ammunition. To hell with it!
God is with us!
And with God and prayer
we have always defeated the
enemy and we will go on doing so!
All is in God's hands.
If we are destined to die
we will go down with honour!
We will go down with honour!
It's do or die now!
To faith, to the Homeland,
Bayonets ahead - forward march!
Attach bayonets!
Vladimir Oskarovich, you can't.
You're leading the army.
Where are the musicians?!
Army Music! QuickIy!
Music, I said!
Musicians - forward, march!
CIose formation!
Into fire!
Lads - advance!
Music! Faster! Forward!
Hooray!
- Eh, you got shot a woman...
- Bastards!
Get back!
Forgive us Lord out of your great mercy,
we pray to you, hear our prayers.
Are we going to lay the Reds
by the Whites?
Together.
We are all Gods people.
God didn't paint them
in different colours.
Irkutsk. General Janin's
control headquarters
Greetings!
I understand...
that you cannot suppress
the riot in Irkutsk.
General Janin!
The situation is difficult.
You must ensure
that my convoy reaches Irkutsk.
The Czechs reject
all their obligations as Allies.
They have declared neutrality
and are evacuating.
They are tired and angry.
Admiral, the railway
has already been
taken by partisans.
My garrison is blockaded there,
I have to go!
The Reds won't touch you,
if you go to Irkutsk
with the Czechs.
The outcome of the war depends on
how soon I will be in Irkutsk.
You must believe me.
I give you the word of an officer.
I guarantee your safety.
Only the convoy officers
will accompany me to Irkutsk.
All other ranks will remain with
their convoy in Nizhneudinsk.
Nizhneudinsk train station.
450 km to Irkutsk
Mr. Udintsov, it's time to go.
Yes, officers, please enter the carriage.
Admiral, I would ask you
not to leave the car at stations
and not to stand by the windows.
Tell nobody about your whereabouts.
- This is like being under arrest.
- No, sir Admiral.
The workers are rebelling.
They demand to hand you over.
Trans-Siberian railroad.
400 km to Irkutsk
I wish we could just move on and on...
You know, Anna Vasilievna,
I never like traveling by train.
There really are Reds at the stations.
It's like sailing through a minefield.
Like when you were off the coast of Pillau?
Sergei Nikolaevich told me all about it.
I just wish we could meet
with Kappel now.
The Czechs have disarmed
our garrison in Irkutsk.
Kappel has 2,000 kilometers behind him.
In minus 40 weather. You know,
he is a man of light.
I will definitely introduce
you to him in Irkutsk.
I would be glad to meet him,
Alexander Vasilievich
Taiga, bank of the Kan.
375 km to Irkutsk
Your Excellency, we've veered
20 kilometers off course.
Cut across the river.
Time's up! Move on...
Don't spread out!
Pick up the pace.
- Vladimir Oskarovich!
- Get back! It's an ice-hole here.
Help the commander, quick!
Check the ice further up stream!
Get back!
We have to cross it anyway.
Dry boots here!
- Hurry!
- Discharge, lieutenant..!
All we need now is for
you to get sick...
I'll go on foot to stay warm. Hurry.
- What?
- Put your boots on. That's an order.
Trans-Siberian railroad.
320 km to Irkutsk
I've just received a message...
Our garrison in Irkutsk has fallen.
Kappel is moving towards the city
and I have to meet him there.
- And you, Anna Vasilievna...
- I will be with you
wherever you are.
- And don't argue with me.
- My dear Anna,
what a dreadful story you
got mixed up in.
I have been here with you
and these were the best days
of my life. I have only one regret...
What is that?
We never had the chance to dance.
I promise you that
at the first ball...
we will dance till we drop.
May I come in?
- Greetings.
The officers
have arrived as you ordered.
I haven't danced for so Iong.
I won't be Iong.
Zima station.
230 km to Irkutsk
Wait... where are you going? Wait!
Where are you going gentlemen?
What is wrong with you?
Are you scared?
Why are you abandoning him?
Don't you realize that
this is treason?
The Admiral himseIf
dissolved the convoy.
If you want, I will stay.
No. I don't want you to.
So what are your orders?
Live, Misha, live -
always the best thing.
Now go. Go.
Find Sonya, Rostislav. Hug them.
Tell...
tell them something.
Farewell!
Irkutsk. General Janin's
control headquarters
It seems your situation could
not be worse, Mr. Janin.
The railroaders are in revolt,
decided to rip up the tracks.
I barely managed to talk
them out of it.
The workers' committee decided
to blow up the Baikal tunnel.
- Monsieur...
- Comrade.
Comrade...
I am grateful to you
for your kindness.
Where will you go, Mr. Janin
without a railroad?
With your Czechs?
I understand you.
What do you want?
We demand that Kolchak be
turned over to the Political Center.
But I am supposed to
be protecting him...
All right, since you are obliged,
then go ahead and protect him.
But what should I tell the workers
who demand that
Kolchak be turned in?
That could lead to Lynch law..
Then I cannot guarantee
your personal safety.
Maybe we don't have to, doctor?
There's no way around it...
Frostbite on your lower limbs.
Gangrene has set in -
there's no other choice, I'm afraid.
Go ahead, gentlemen...
Your Excellency, leave us.
Lord,
help your son to endure
these dreadful sufferings.
Shut the door.
And may God be with you.
Irkutsk
Two of you come with me.
The rest of you wait.
Here? May I come in.
- Mr. Kolchak.
- What is it?
- Gather your belongings.
- Greetings.
We are turning you over
to the local authorities.
- Which authorities?
- The Irkutsk Political Center.
I see...
Mr. Kolchak, gather your belongings.
Mrs. Timireva?
- Excuse me.
- It's all right.
Mr. Admiral.
- What?
- One minute, please.
I beg your pardon...
Do you have a weapon?
Yes.
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
What's going on?..
Get your hands off me.
- Mr. Pepelyaev, court decides.
- But Janin promised...
Mr. Kolchak, one minute.
Wait here.
- I demand...
- What is it?
- Anna, why are you here?
- Arrest me!
- Out of the way!
- Mrs. Timireva!
No order for your arrest.
On what grounds?
On the grounds that
I am the admiral's wife.
I implore you, don't do this!
Let me disobey you just this once,
Alexander Vasilievich.
It's your right.
Your Excellency...
Vladimir Oskarovich,
I insist again...
- ... that you...
- I repeat...
...that I will not abandon the army.
God is merciful.
Mr. Admiral, enter the cell.
Mr. Prime Minister, go ahead.
- How is it there?
- Bad.
Voytsekhovsky...
We'll take Irkutsk,
expel the Reds,
and free the Admiral.
Take charge of the command.
And tell the troops...
that I remained faithful to them...
and proved this by dying
among them...
- Do it... my friend...
- Yes, Sir!
How could I get trapped...
Irkutsk ahead.
Put on the pace.
You heard, they're saying
Kappel is nearby.
Look, Admiral.
He has gone grey-haired...
Stop, Iady. You're not to
be with him any longer.
Okay, but only for a minute.
Anna Vasilievna. Don't let me down.
Hello, Anna!
Kappel's troops are just outside Irkutsk.
They'll set us free.
My love, my darling,
we will get out of here.
- They have issued an ultimatum.
- How do you know?
I overheard from the next cell...
- What are they demanding?
- That you be set free!
Now they will act quickly.
No! No.
Kappel will make it.
Can't be any other way.
Anna Vasilievna!
- It's time.
- Go. Go.
No I can't permit you,
I've allowed you...
Irkutsk.
To the arms!
Mr. Kolchak,
on behalf of the Irkutsk
Revolutionary Committee,
we have come to announce
a resolution about you...
I understand.
There is no
need for you to continue.
Would you like to make
any requests or statements?
Let me say goodbye to my wife,
Anna Vasilievna Timireva.
This is not possibIe.
Anything else?
- Here?
- Yes, here.
Would you like to be blindfolded?
No.
- And you?
- No, thank you, there is no need.
Lord God, forgive me my sins, wilful
and unwilful, I appeal to your mercy.
Is there something you
would like to say?
Please tell my wife in Paris
that I bless my son.
How many wives do you have?
All right, I will relay the message.
- Farewell, Admiral.
- Farewell.
Aim.
Fire!
Hey, you three. Put their
things on the cart.
Three of you.
Drag out the next one...
What an odd hole in the ice?..
It's baptism thing for
a church celebration.
MOSFILM fiIm studio, 1964
Leave these ones,
and those we don't need...
I just checked the records.
It's her for sure.
30 years in exiles! Wife
of the enemy of the revolution...
In our patriotic movie...
- Hello.
- It isn't her.
No, big dark fans.
Do you need this?
Excuse me, Anna Vasilievna.
I need faces. Where am I going
to find one like that?
Where?
Ready for the rehearsal!
Take your places!
Break's over... all those involved
in the shoot, on set.
They've brought the carriages.
Can you take a look?
- Yes.
- Okay. And what?
- Don't use her even in the crowd scene.
- All right...
The rehearsal is starting!
Comrades, quickly, go to the set.
- All take position.
- Quiet, everyone.
Everyone else off the set!
Sound track!
Waltz! Waiter, roll it!
Come on comrades,
put some life into it!
Step aside, you're in the way.
You won't be in the shoot today.
You're free to go.
What a ball!
ANNA TIMIREVA. AFTER
ADMIRAL KOLCHAK WAS EXECUTED -
SHE SPENT 37 YEARS IN PRISONS
AND IN EXILE. REHABILITATED IN MARCH 1960.
DIED IN MOSCOW
ON THE 1st OF JANUARY 1975.
SERGEI TIMIREV. AFTER ANNA
LEFT HIM HE HEADED
THE WHITE GUARD'S NAVAL FORCES
IN THE FAR EAST. EMIGRATED.
SERVED AS CAPITAIN OF A SHIP.
DIED IN SHANGHAI IN 1932.
SOPHIA KOLCHAK. AFTER FLEEING
FROM SEVASTOPOL SHE LIVED IN PARIS.
SHE DEVOTED HER LIFE TO RAISING HER SON.
DIED IN LONGJUMEAU HOSPITAL IN 1956.
ROSTISLAV KOLCHAK. SOLDIER.
HE FOUGHT IN FRENCH DIVISIONS
AGAINST THE GERMANS DURING WORLD
WAR ll. DIED IN PARIS IN 1965.
ADMIRAL
KoIchak - Konstantin KHABENSKY
Anna - EIizabeta BOYARSKAYA
GeneraI KappeI - Sergei BEZRUKOV
Sergei Timirev - VIadisIav VETROV
Sophia - Anna KOVALCHUK
MikhaiI Smirnov - Yegor BEROEV
NikoIai Podgursky - OIeg FOMIN
RostisIav Ognivtsev - AnatoIy PASHININ
VIadimir RybaItovsky - Dmitry SHERBINA
Kerensky - Victor VERZHBITSKY
PepeIyaev - AIexander KLYUKVIN
FiIm director Sergei Fyodorovich -
Fyodor BONDARCHUK
NikoIai BURLYAEV as the Emperor
Script - VIadimir VALUTSKY,
with Zoia KUDRI
Directed by Andrei KRAVCHUK
Music by RusIan MURATOV,
GIeb MATVEICHUK
Editor - Tom ROLF
Producers - Dmitry YURKOV,
NikoIai POPOV
Producers - AnatoIy MAXIMOV,
Dzhanik FAISIEV
With participation of the
STRANA FiIm group company