what the hell do you think you're doing
dragging your butt through the day
selling body and soul to a bunch of plan
normals actin stupid so they'll think
you're one of them but I'm getting all
of the guilt but none of the sex there
is a simple answer dear friend a glowing
beacon of slack amidst the turmoil and
darkness it's junior dogs the living
slack master in his church of the sub
jeans Bob brings a new destiny for the
abnormal what Baba comes to justify our
sins to unmask the conspiracy and to get
us back the slack they stole away it's
us versus them are you gonna try and
hell on earth alongside the pink boys or
will you pull the wool over your own
eyes and accept Bob into your mind
repent what's your job and please Church
of the 17 is eternal salvation of triple
your money back praise Bob the fates
have brought you into possession of a
sub genius instructional video barrage
tape prepare yourself you are about to
be remade into a new being through
forbidden knowledge previously kept
secret for centuries by the jealous
priest words of many religions caution
improper viewing techniques may lead in
summers to dependency seizures cranial
fits priapic condition
tuitions to hire glandular locations and
in some territories legal arrest however
if the viewer follows instructions and
trusts completely involve this tape can
produce an unsurpassable beatific
experience that can last for hours these
weeks possibly even say
this videotape there's a Penta Dobbs
drom PowerShell time code which may
cause some home video text to react
unpredictably although only a small
percentage of playback systems or their
owners have suffered permanent damage
from the signal the subgenius foundation
incorporated is not responsible for
injuries or damages inflicted by
paranormal events during a play mode the
tape also contains a subliminal hypno
Helio tricks trance inducement tone
operating beyond the range of human
perception however pets in the viewing
may exhibit unusual behaviors may small
children and certain less evolved adults
if such behavior anomalies last more
than two days after viewing consult a
physician however this brainwave in
folding signal is generally harmless and
would actually enhance your learning
abilities during the program special
interactive Jolla sonic stereo effects
produced on the automate cerebral sync
loc interocitor are designed to trigger
stem cleavage or brain division between
the forebrain and hindbrain using newly
discovered break thinking principles the
viewers brainwaves are locked into
synchronization with the tapes
underlying suggestions by means of
neuroelectric Ethel's plant growth gas
mileage of nearby automobiles may be
affected for the unworthy this tape may
be a one-way ticket down a bottomless
mental pic from which there can be no
escape
in unreceptive viewers there is a danger
of synaptic backfire in the brainpan
caused by overheating of the attention
gland this bent specking of brain cells
without proper organic coolants such as
fraud has been blamed for three recent
cases of spontaneous human combustion do
not over medicate high dosages have so
sensitized the third nostril receptors
of some viewers that they were unable to
stop seeing the tape even after it had
been turned off this tape is to be used
only by the person to whom it is
prescribed do not operate a motor
vehicle following if you do not operate
heavy farm machinery at speeds over 70
miles an hour there are demons and macey
during the initial hallucination
sequence are not real if you do not
panic this phase will end after a few
minutes always resurface from the
hypnosis slowly coming out of the tape
has been likened to a total rebirth
process if managed successfully if you
have trouble reentering the earth plane
focus on a bottle and chant his name
until you remember your own experience
of Justin we're having operating
difficulties which has necessitated a
beret
do not attempt to flip the tape when you
reach the end of side one no matter what
you are told by later instructions on
the tape there is no side too however if
you do discover one don't look at it if
you follow these instructions you will
experience a profound cathartic reaction
to the flow of archetypal images and
racial memories you may find yourself
laughing and crying can possible and
even cast rly pretenders these reactions
are normal enjoy them Bob that's your
key phrase it will trigger the entire
message without logging all your pad
battery baba wawa father falls down
alarm Santa Fe parents met again with
elementary school officials last night
to discuss the growing presence of Bob
in the schools Bob the deity of the
dallas-based Church of the subgenius is
a comic book character who communicates
with aliens and worships money parents
and teachers complain that the Bob
stickers and pamphlets which have turned
up in school laboratories with
increasing frequency encourage
troublemakers and weird behavior it's
not healthy for the children I'm
convinced of this there has been a
pamphlet going around a Bob pamphlet
that I have looked at and it's the least
well-adjusted
he'll be coming
if they are uncomfortable with their
classmates it is because they are better
than their classmates you imagine this
better not smarter mind you but better
wise up they're out to get you by a
global conspiracy weird men arrive find
out who they are and how to smash them
you probably already knew that the US
government is a sham something propped
up there for you to blame but did you
know that the real powers that be are
not even people that they are actually
shambling unbelieving unmentionable
unthinkable fazed yes Jehovah drills and
Balian and still divided the sinister
star horses which mock us all evil
demons have kept the truth from humanity
for thousands of years God has been
misquoted all this time his actual words
may disturb you but Bob Dobbs is a
bulwark against the unbearable fear and
anxiety tormenting mankind with it
cultural chops walk earth it gives to
all draw
or a six million years cycle in 1998 dad
sees the world entering a new a yard
wait in a few years will bring more
wondrous and miraculous change and
carnage and sanity and destruction than
all of mankind's history and prehistory
before it all brings a new destiny for
America a type of cataclysmic economic
table of untold riches and power those
in the know while billions of deserving
conspiracy oops fry in hell uncontrolled
bleeding controlled by barb will usher
in the spiritual rebirth for the task
pane of a spell that mystery
supernatural riches and a restoration of
lost psychic ability for the lives of
those who dare to sing them hand painful
that's right you're lucky to live in the
time here's my last fi that processes
reveal this is it the only thing that
promises action thrilled success in sex
and business mom is a way of life to
millions even nope is the one true
living slack master with the spirit will
know how to help you fast through the
locked door way to financial heaven he
is the one real shortcut to slack
now we'll see another dimension on your
teenage yes fear the scalp vista removal
no longer become physically attractive
overnight attain status luck prosperity
by blowing them
Bob's promises to widen the scope and
nature of abnormal behavior to explore
new ways of going over the edge and
coming right back baboons treatment on
your own can help you create the highest
possible earnings from the
psychodynamics of abnormalities the vs
bears implanted personality disorders
around and gentlemen into an illusion of
creativity better feeling normals and
get you six
Oh
and remain with
30 minutes welcome to Babylon children
it's great to be here in the belly of
the beast tonight before we get started
with our second lav bottle we could all
please bow our heads and have a moment
of sacred traditional nod little
realized even by leaving scientists
there are really two races actually two
distinct species of so-called human
beings if you gaze upon any given Street
normally you might never suspect that
only some of these people are true
humans outside appearances offer no clue
that among this ordinary-looking crowd
on an ordinary day a certain number of
these people are actually sub geniuses
we would have to creep inside their
heads to know whether this person or
that carries the rare subgenius gene but
once inside those hits we would discover
a vast new universe a new dimension
coexisting not always at harmony
alongside the mundane workaday world of
the common human another world that
until now has been forced into hiding
now at this very moment the veils of
secrecy can be torn aside we the
persecuted may now dare to raise our
heads high and declare behold us for we
are the sub geniuses
but what is a sub genius how can they we
differ so much from the humans whose
nonsensical laws and customs we have
been forced to obey why have so many of
us been kept in ignorance of our true
heritage a heritage that dates back
farther than man is thought to have
existed for in the days of Atlantis we
helped to design the humans certainly in
retrospect this now seems to have been
our greatest mistake so what is the
difference examine this seemingly docile
crowd and know that in some few
simmering beneath a placid service there
broiled a veritable cauldron of
repressed subgenius awareness ready at
any moment to explode outward often with
catastrophic results
stickers and graffiti were showing up in
really strange places like inside pencil
sharpeners and so on and in some classes
we don't even know who the SubGenius is
what is all this I hear about this you
called this church of the SubGenius sure
yeah I don't know how about you saw huh
what what about you it's it's about Bob
yawns it's Bob that's it that is great
but just who is this man Bob some call
him the slack master the high e pop the
saint of sales others call him liar pimp
whoremonger a sleazy con man hoisting
his dangerous scam off on gullible
suckers well hahaha dear friend JR Bob
Dobbs isn't some outmoded overused da
from ancient fairy tales but a living
bleeding deity for today the divinely
appointed messenger of slack the mystic
super salesman upon whose wheeling and
dealing skills the fate of the universe
you just you can sell you anything and I
bought it and I tell you what that
flower by that man
shit from bob dobbs wonderful Bobby is
still in the blank Bobby is still in
play the Baltic that kind of been
described as out the true boss
Oh
he's a trickster obviously look at his
face and you could just see you know
what what's behind that smile you know
what's what's in the pipe that he's
smoking and what is what is this game
that is that Bob Dobbs represents JR Bob
das random
walk with the gods he wore a silly grin
and smoke resume it by default on his
jersey every day of his life
with his mother mobile everybody or two
humble parents somewhere in the Midwest
the child Bob experienced a traumatic
close encounter with a UFO at the age of
three soon thereafter he began to
exhibit strange powers of persuasion by
age six he had made his first million
almost by accident in college he met and
married his first and still his primary
wife Connie who is now revered by female
sub genie ii as the Blessed anti virgin
with Connie's encouragement the young
dobbs became a salesman of legendary
almost frightening abilities known to
his peers as the man who could sell
anything he worked his way up to the
very top of the conspiracy ladder and
might have stayed there but late one
night in 1953 while working on an
amateur television of his own design an
event occurred which was to become a
milestone on man's mind path to slack he
was suddenly seized up in the spirit by
the hand of Jehovah one itself the
cosmic puppeteer of the Old Testament
the wrathful alien space God from some
corporate sin galaxy in this timeless
moment which we call the divine
immaculee shin of the bob dobbs received
the first of countless brain curdling
pronouncements which form the sacred
pre-scripted of
he was shown a vision a world where all
humanity was equally wealthy rich beyond
imagining but without working this
experience combined with his UFO given
sales magic led him inevitably into the
religion field he quickly discovered the
golden rule embodied in his classic
saying they'll pay snow what they really
think the truth of genius can learn to
think for himself but only bahama can
show and so Bob Dobbs founded his church
on a sandy beach of common sense sense
of humor and dollars and cents a likely
story you say but it's simple really bob
is lucky not smart in fact by the
perverted conspiracy standards of
intelligence he is gifted with
incredible stupidity he lives in a
perpetual state of contracted
consciousness this enables him to act
without thinking to surf effortlessly on
the lock playing to float down the
fabled path of least resistance in fact
to make a million dollars every time he
screws up thus it is not his wisdom but
his divine Follies his holy blunders
which we emulate the miracle is not in
what Bob does to you but in what he
allows you to do to yourself he brings
the student to the realization that
everything you know is true under the
conspiracy you're being ripped off every
day but you can learn to enjoy it
he called his seminars instant
instructions for those who follow no
master he journeyed to tae Baek and
under ancient holy man he perfected the
arts of Glen's gaping and a competing he
also began modeling for hundreds of
magazine heads leaving early clothes of
his presence these old ads are the only
known photos of Dobbs or he otherwise
remains elusive shunning both the
spotlight and the authorities in 1979 he
recruited to randomly selected nobody's
Dr Philo Drummond and Ivan Stang to
begin a public outreach arm and begin
spreading his seed word of slack Wesley
the church is so Ally pervasive and so
full that we could not possibly get into
the dogma in anymore any lesson three or
four hours this will outline everything
clear and concise detail easy to read
keep it near you and we promised that
any answers that you need will be found
in this little heavy little pamphlet
right here one dollar for salvation one
dollar let's look at the word subgenius
it does not simply mean just below a
genius subji intelligence level can
range far far below genius the next
challenge tell what you doing what he
inventing a one good joke for the
thousand cited by a bomb or nevah but
the subgenius does not pretend to super
knowledge but to sub knowledge knowledge
of the under things the Hollow Earth
from whose darkness issue the Nazi hell
creatures and other demons of the abyss
it is in contemplation of the under
things the underwear lurking just below
the closing of existence that the sub
Genie display what genius they have the
study of this substratum the foundation
garment underlying reality is the
SubGenius of strength for it is from
this source that he or she taps the
infinite resources of a force that is
completely incomprehensible to humans
the force of slacking fierce he wants to
take away from it black and was a
conspiracy wants to deprive us of slack
is our way of grabbing life by the
lapels and it's created a slack what is
it well if you have to ask you will
never know you were born with original
spec an infinite supply of but the
conspiracy has most of it no they don't
even know what it is but that hasn't
stopped them from stealing it away how
do you think you ended up a slave to
their so-called word you know how your
brain stem goes down into your spine
here and how the conspiracy puts using
piano wire ropes and things and pulls it
real time to you can't think and you
stay ran all the time point of the
church is to unknot those not get the
piano wire from around your neck the
make life wonderful the conspiracy is a
patchwork of different things similar
nations summer products summer hypnotic
television shows summer bad pills now
there's a distinction there's good pills
and there's bad pills or so there's a
good Bob and there's a bad Bob right
okay and the conspiracy is the bad Bob
the bad pills the bad TV shows anything
that you know is is keeping you from
realizing you got to get right with Bob
it's the human condition
it's things falling apart as fat ladies
in double net jumpsuits beating their
kids and krogers strange idea of just
left side is I think you could buy it
actually slack for a three-fourths of
the world is a good dear but here are we
playing yeah I 3,000 kids started a new
mexico city every day dude true slack is
by definition indefinable it is a kind
of direct perception unfettered common
sense it is not mere laziness it is
rather a kind of active sloth slack in
its pure form makes happiness seem like
hanging by comparison next to slack the
Nirvana known do mystics and saints is
like endless torment slack is different
one might call it something for nothing
but the normals the mediocrity knows the
somnambula X and pseudo subs lands have
tried to make it something which we have
been led to believe we must work to buy
it is this yearning for slack that
separates us from the normals the human
may live out his entire life in a
grinding cycle of slackness his hours
consumed by meaningless toil
interspersed with meaning
yet he never feels cheated he thinks it
is natural perhaps we should pity them
but face it most people are mingled
jerks half-witted cattle racing each
other to be first to the slaughterhouse
and stampeding you along with them to
the anti Bob and pink creatures who
would defame our temple yeah I was kind
of depressed and I went over to my
friend Rick man's house and I was I was
kind of doing
and I just went in there he just he
showed me he had run out have a nice day
in the skulls of normals that he had
decapitated and I just said
across the cosmos when I drop my drawers
even mother nature follows within every
person there's some good and there's
some bad and it's a choice you choose
whether you want to love or hate that
person and for myself I just choose to
hate them little shit they'll laugh at
people its 20th century traditions it's
the old tradition of all the things that
got us where we are now it's Christ
without a penis he's part of the
conspiracy it's presidents that don't
look like they're capable of getting
erections anymore that's the conspiracy
conspiracy in a real living breathing
I want oh my gosh the bad worst crime
that ever was is the easiest to commit
the word prime is serving the conspiracy
what good do you actually do you
actually I don't think about this you
confronted with can you stand the
conspiracy crime you down with something
about that pressure to live today
wouldn't you like revenge on these
mediocrities these pink boys these boxed
willing Barbies and Ken's these normals
who have made normality the norm Pink's
are but living stereotypes insensate
meat puppets and food tools who let and
fear the spark of originality that
ignites every subgenius soul but the
long senseless march into slack lessness
may soon come to an end oh it won't
happen without a bitter struggle but at
least there is hope for in this the 20th
century we have seen the coming of a
savior a beacon of slack a banner behind
which we may all unite it is the coming
of JR Bob Dobbs and his mighty Church of
the subgenius boys and girls are gonna
shut off the house
the world moms getting down with you
here tonight bob is getting down to help
your type bob is coming here that is
your strife karma sucks let Bob into
your life Wow geekly i'm a master rap
time like a motherfucker let's go to
class y'all since Mao said oh woe is me
well I'm here to tell you and it would
be x is here to make a paid for the
bottoms of the past whoever's gonna have
to go through a rebirth and that means
paying the spaceship earth this is will
come from planet to remove from us the
paintballs heads in the meantime we will
have my say yes I and fornicating every
day not the conspiracy on his ass make
your life a fucking gas take your trophy
through the hips make the normal suck us
back take the time to break their minds
time to blow it out there be high all
them
well I'm Reverend clean the bass another
block 5dr read anymore I wanna sneak
dolomite Anthony as I know what's what
babe I've achievements aiza khan told
you but to come on over here and give up
the gap Wilson still owe me bitch Oh
give me all your cash return you wanted
to worry about your soul is where the
eggs is comes you're at on my palm to
docs on Malaysia we will go home now I'm
on me lying there with an ice pack on my
nuts or maybe I'll Jacen Solo five bucks
better this you are the will machine to
leave and to be people the fuck
conspiracy
wait you have to face and while you're
wishing upon a star probably lose me is
up until the Church of the SubGenius is
probably the single most important
organization our function is to save the
world at the end of the world that you
Bob
the people really need to be able to
understand things very quickly and the
Church of the subgenius I think confuses
him confusing isn't it is there a
typical SubGenius of course the very
thought is an Alaska money the only
thing that most some geniuses have in
common is that they're all different and
they have nothing in common with the
conspiracy of normal by definition the
Church of the subgenius can't really
exist because it's an organization for
people who are not joiners excite ryx
unpredictable true visionaries let us
observe a few examples using the hidden
camera first time it was in the first 30
issues of 90 inch worm comics and I
think in 14 issues of four and a half
inch worm comics this man so g.711
colleagues those are the Kamikaze limits
the adventures of a 7-eleven okay they
have the person that works a sibling and
just writes down everything that happens
in the whole comic is shaped like a big
seven minutes three-dimensional and
they've got the idea from the flying
saucer that was shaped like simulator
that with men flew over one night it was
a UFO bleep a sub genius obviously the
speech patterns are unmistakable and
here is another one for you and here is
another one and here is another one but
what of this management all very
different yet all sub breezes they share
only the quest course / and the love of
their beloved spiritual teacher the
living avatar of slack JR
God
oh oh ba-bop ba-bop ba-bop
ba-ba-ba-ba-ba you cannot is my jam
vodka get our awesome guy because he's
bigger you bigger dogs many fearing the
hosiery somebody she got no I was
getting these messages in the back of my
brain as long ago is about 12 or 13
months I kept comparing the word Bob Bob
Bob obvious everywhere bob is bursting
out all over the place just look through
any phone book in any city you get the
same thing Bob's construction can be
Bob's martinizing Bob's floral Bob's
auto parts pubs automotive service Bob's
Burgers Bob's Rena jalopy and then down
here we've got bobs used furniture store
I mean he's like everybody's dad should
be mom is about as American as you can
get
besides his only exaggerated human
nature at the powers granted him right
over one bob also benefits from being
the chosen broker on earth for superior
beings from the farthest reaches of
known space the so-called men from
Planet X or exsists for they are nothing
like men bob has a covered entities
angelic beings a cosmic contract a deal
on July fifth 1998 at 7am the exes shall
make a mass landing on this planet the
children of Bob shall be rewarded at
this porthole rupture this day of
judgement when all those who paid their
church to be lifted up in power and
glory to gain new homes and bodies
aboard the pleasure saucers of the sex
goddesses all the while watching the
hapless pigs twitch and bleed and wail
in the death throes of their world and
we faithful shall be transfigured new
enlightened beings superior mutants
called over man and bear women who will
start a new Jerusalem in the promised
land of Dimension X oz guard the zone of
eternal slack and cytoplasmic Superboy
Shawcross
two of the army service that is forms
that we can't do much about those evil
gods from the other side of the cosmos
who fly through the air and through the
nebulous darkness of space space my
friends the infinite inky clouds of
nebulae they fly on their membranous
leathery wings holding in there coiling
tentacles shiny steel cylinders each one
containing what was once a human soul
what was once a member of the Church of
the SubGenius but enough of this you
don't want to hear about this rightmost
and you like a doll or I'll tell your be
wishing it was that kind of anger at
least would you be worshipped it to me
can we have them on your side I just at
least them at least there's two arms of
your lame-o virtually it could be worse
it could be much worse
the exit
I've landed earth under their control
dogs vision
spies proven those cities
radioactive hole
we don't
what their game
but their name is unpronounceable
we don't love
what they came for
but what they came for
ism possible
past the door which she didn't one and
my sciences were terrified and inaudible
damage stewardess lot of stress
to have landed
they're machines
follow in our track
absolution
span is proven
a world
without slag but what is the commodity
with which Bob will bargain Earth's fate
some claim it is the souls of his
followers the true SubGenius does not
question Bob's wisdom in such matters we
have only our simple faith that heaven
will be ours if we only believe
ironically his mission will not be to
sell earth but to prevent earth being
sold and transformed into a kind of
studies in space don't forget that Bob
is he has come to as promised at the end
of the world July fifth 1998 okay when
most Americans will have hangover but
it's not just for the Americas is for
everyone in the world Yeah right that is
that is why ya start smoking start
drinking and live it up start
fornicating less if your very life
depended on it but this plan will
succeed only if conditions are just
right at the appointed time otherwise
dark forces of antiquity will be
awakened from their slumber of eons and
rise again from Atlantis to rule our
world in their size lyst grip these
primordial elementals the Elder Gods
have countless demonic and
interplanetary minions carrying out
lieske they even control Bob's own evil
twin brother dick God the unclean with
all his powers could Bob really be
defeated by these beings ah but you must
not underestimate the conspiracy its
weapons are so insidious even the human
conspiracy leaders are unaware of them
the fact that the conspiracy itself is
ignorant that it is a conspiracy gives
it such control over our minds that the
very thought becomes on the
you cannot think about your own minds as
part of the problem again thing about
your mind you cannot wash so we got see
your own run from your legs get hot fire
shooting yo you got a guy who's very
good he not really
the bull vanity and temerity of the
human mind itself does all work the evil
ones may just lean back and watch the
little humans March gladly even proudly
to their doom but we too must be
vigilant for thanks to the false slack
bombarding us daily it is terrifyingly
easy for even a sub genius to slip back
into normality we live in a dangerous
world the powers of pinkness are always
fighting the powers of slack yes Turner
they're locked in a death struggle
sometimes
we can't give you all the answers but we
can help you flesh out your fantasy that
there are some at our labs we use only
the finest homemade ingredients love
children God and the purest blend of
money your needs can buy grown right
here by our special process a process in
use since our first mom-and-pop
operation who are we we're the normal
people the most normal people in the
world
but not quite as normal as you turn look
around you testified what they've done
to the thing that you love they took
elvis presley neck turning pink they
made him into a monster we won't worry
that the church of the SubGenius is an
anti-american children we are the first
real America we know what America is
before they took it away from us and try
to sell it back to us for a prompt as
long as you can't buy slack the
conspiracy cannot win
Oh
bah bah bah person basically two
factions out there right now is us and
them and unfortunately them is much much
greater than us the fortunate thing
about is that we know that then are
actually working for us but then doesn't
know that they're working for us we
stand at a crossroads the tenuous slack
that a sub genius may occasionally enjoy
could be rent to shreds at any moment
for the human puppets of the Elder Gods
continue their senseless plunge into
madness and anti slack dragging us and
our whole beloved planet ever closer to
the brink of destruction be it by the
nuclear kiss of Jehovah one ecological
disaster or invasion by hostile aliens
which will it be destruction of planet
earth or eternal slack under the
benevolent rule of ba or are the tunes
you say it can't be true Jesus began to
give to them the signs I was coming in
the end of the age of one of the signs
he referred to was the abomination of
desolation that was spoken of by Daniel
the prophet exactly as the door getting
in the dark triggered that there you
should destroy the earth in his day and
that it's very highly possible that run
when this all takes place that a great
cataclysmic judgment will do that very
thing God will destroy the country City
Miniver cities in this nation mineral
instantly destroy
gee I can't wait till that Bob time
train comes around the bend oh look out
son here it comes now it's frightening
isn't it it's unbelievably lincolnshire
his health at Renteria language than to
receive these were but flesh and
understand not the way your for the ones
you said Jesus had a bad hold his hand a
word up hey are we o friends all there
no no no they'll make a nail yourself up
and you'll be Clark news buddy Christmas
Oh
somebody get your water
blow your fingers going off your hair
blowing off your head and win looking
for flashlights batteries will you be
saying to us probably a friend that poop
in the surf genius a little closer I do
what to do and on that day my friend
your soul will be laid bare to the eye
of the great start fiscal removal that
hurdle of you all the time will you be
naked neck into Wotan and it will know
then whether you really believed in Bob
Dobbs or not because your belief or your
life will be all you have left oh hey
lake somewhere down below marklin hell
is life here on earth without that land
ba and when the demons old when the
demons tried to tell you that you think
you're hearing us a time oh one day
you'll find yourself up to your neck in
false drugs false sex false jobs both
money and you'll say but where's Bob
words Bob you mean you mean there really
is a conspiracy you mean there really
was a bob you mean you mean I could have
had slack and I what it's going to be up
to you it's going to be up to you what
are you going to let happen to this
planet what are you going to do about it
Bob's going to let you decide what to do
is that what you're gonna are you just
going to sit there they won't even have
to do it babo need them to see that the
end of oil happens properly it'll happen
by accident and there are a lot of
well-meaning people that are involved in
this thing but it is satanic now let me
tell you we talk about Christianity and
Satan is very bridget at maneuvering the
church into a position that is opposed
to God the feminist dupes of the
conspiracy charge that not enough
members are women Bob would agree to
that indeed he would say there will
never be enough women but at least the
ones we have are all woman and Bob Bob
is all man the James bonds and masters
the most dashing religious leader of his
time you need to say the fathers
actually had one of those horrible
diseases but it's a true doctor is that
true bomb just a minute Sally one
scandal at a time yes Bob jobs is a sex
rather than for villains he offers
something far more powerful an excuse a
divine all-inclusive excuse which allows
the bearer to free himself from the grip
of temptation by overindulging until it
releases him the true seeker must give
himself up to temptation or he will
never conquer the sad weekly self-denial
preached by the New Age movement is pure
conspiracy Pamela the true son or
daughter of Bob knows that our universe
is no laid back home chanting cosmos but
an active tumultuous squirting universe
bent on rampant reproduction and easy
grins the false cults may try to teach
personal transformation psychic
developed human potential but Bob goes
straight for the glands and seeks to
amplify the self to blow the abnormality
potential of his pupils only through
excess can one contact from lower self
where the real decisions are made don't
just eat a hamburger eat the hell
the advanced initiate once freed from
conspiracy programming as well as the
worldly goods that enslaved him makes
his pilgrimage to dobbs down the
churches fabulous walled encampment deep
in the jungles of Malaysia there the
initiated nostril is surgically opened
by psychic surgeon allowing him or her
to with freed the psychic stench of
those around him he masters the sciences
of schizophrenia trics and memory
editing creating a clean slate on which
Bob may write the art of extra
meditation distort whereby the mind is
voided upon the great throne of relief
you don't use your mind to think about
your religion what is it that truly sets
Bob apart from other would-be only men
and self-appointed gurus everything for
bob has always existed there have always
been Bob's every epoch of man's history
has had its Bob most were what we would
call good bombs others well we needn't
dwell on that the Traveling Salesman
jokes of Mythology our Facebook his
early expert
so many ask is Bob God the slack master
himself vehemently deny that he is the
Messiah his mission is merely to show us
how to live with our sins and who better
Bob admits he is a sinner he practically
embodies all the failings of mortal men
he has the power to fail second right
inferior invitation churches might need
an infallible but here we've got a plan
to succeed is a very special time
religious leader bob is a short duration
personal saying yes children Bob words
here take him into your heart and in
your mind follow us to take him in any
shape folk but after you tell you many
other sacred places follow us you can
think about him consider me the end cast
him out
your own Oh short-duration personal
Savior or shorter / save it is foolish
and cowardly to cling to anyone personal
Savior the hectic pace of modern life
demands disposable saviors specific ones
suited to the moment at hand a sort of
while you wait Do It Yourself religion
now you're shorter for Sam to be
anything from a book you're reading to a
smudge on the corner of a page of that
book to a TV star you're currently
enamored of to a break that just misses
crushing your skull and involves from
the cornice of a rotting building to the
coagulated dripping next up of the
decapitated World Cup golfer hey can
last anywhere for the nano second your
entire I thought care of millions of
shorter person concurrently
consecutively and simultaneous skeptical
reporters were surprised when scientists
from the MIT artificial intelligence
laboratory corroborated the story short
duration personal saviors it solves a
key problem that kept cropping up in
earlier fast turns out it only takes
five or six generations before the
memory of a great spiritual leader like
Muhammad urges Nazareth is totally
corrupted by the people who are we
telling the story all of them have their
own motives five or six generations
that's only a hundred years and up till
now that's been the maximum useful life
of a religion after that a sexual
paranoid like Paul or megalomaniac like
the Pope King James sort of the
Ayatollah take control and that point
the religion is virtually used up the
mass repression completely outweighs the
church's other virtues like a joke
that's been told too often can only be
used for punishment but with the short
duration personal Savior blind faith and
an exalted person or object doesn't have
to last even one generation it doesn't
even have to
are exactly subgenius church can't be
corrupted because it couldn't be more
proud which makes the crucial difference
in long-term performance and maintenance
form your own local denomination or
clinch go forth into the world spreading
the seed word even humans can be tricked
into thinking they are some geniuses as
Bob once said to l ron hubbard they may
be think but their money is green but
there is a danger here a grave danger in
sharing Bob's wisdom with the unworthy
for prophecy tell them that the greatest
threat slack will come from inside the
church from those we sneeringly call the
bobbies they wouldn't know true slack if
we crawl on their hands in the form of
an evil snake not this open-face the
woman Beatles Fame throwing up grandpa
when you help the shepherd you help the
flock friends are going to try to sell
you bob dobbs on a silver platter a
clean up Bob offensive Bob a new fangled
Bob not quite as spooky and abnormal as
he once was my friend you best fear the
day when junior Bob dog becomes as
wholesome as he looks because on that
day my friend you paychecks shall
crumble your free room condos shall fall
to the ground you'll be turn your face
in agony trying to fight Bob Bob come
back to it they must be taught that Bob
is not the answer and neither is
anything else
the next row the Church of the subgenius
is if you can't tell shit from tuna fish
don't order seafood in a French
restaurant dobbs doesn't want followers
only their money and so we must purge
our ranks of the under the program our
own zombies the methods he advocates are
drastic for he hath commanded you shall
do as I say and think for yourself or
kill me Peru for dealing with the pink
members of the society the conspiracy
that wants to crush you and turn you
into a mindless do the or kill me rule
elevates every every instance of contact
every interface as we say here on the
coast with the conspiracy into the
all-time encounter let's say you go into
the bar and you are raised you say there
is one counter now you might ask what
about the Liberals
friends we hate them even more than that
conspiracy because at least the
conspiracy has the guts to try to kill
us but we really hate her wits who don't
try to completely and utterly destroy us
bob is a conspiracy dude wrong floor
they probably ought to be off and he
supports the conspiracy and eat the most
class division but other than that you
know he's pretty nice guy for personal
Savior but nothing would have guessed
how literally the words or QB were to be
taken until that fateful night of
january twenty seconds 1984 and write
that will live in infamy
for it was in this San Francisco theater
that if we are to believe the
photographic evidence Bob Dobbs was
slain by a crazed assassin's bullet
steel yourself for the footage you are
about to see is not for the faint
hearted and you'll be ready for 444
ba-ba-ba-ba-bom
Oh
Bob spiders broken could it be that the
reign of Bob on earth is ended could it
be that Bob first lived in vain good at
me but the blood on this pipe spin has
been shed for nothing was the greatest
salesman the world had ever seen he can
sell the margin after he ate all the B's
he could sell a pile of shit you're
coming all of us he would never die
ah da da
he was a real man and brain
bah bah bah
the killer he was none other than D
Woodman at well better known as puzzling
evidence a man Bob had regarded as one
of his most trusted disciples when you
see what you see the show we're puzzling
evidence shot Bob Dobbs stage and it in
a big grin a lazy to have a rare 40 oz
both the pipe and it was shooting Bob
dogs on her ovary and what kind of
liquor when drinking I'm uh Sammy show
and yeah that's good again to use
crystals I'm the only guy who your
energy this is the motions the beginning
at the end no I killed follow dominated
to do a little sterno on a drag behind
the boat but so many questions remain
unanswered some investigators insist
that puzzling evidence was but a Duke
apexi a fall guy for a concealed cadre
of trained gunmen clumsy attempts at a
cover-up have only served doing plainly
they grow enough now even given the
finding of the Twinkie commissioned the
haiti commission that are a bunch of
frauds those fools jackanapes of apes
you know senator at him cool i yes as a
matter of fact he's a personal friend of
mine night and as you wife Ellen of
water skiing with his beautiful wife
Debbie yes Helen caught on that black
day the church was left reeling in shock
from this blow without the guidance of
Bob the church is an empty
chapter Bob strangely is sickeningly
similar to early Christianity uh nobody
rises up from population close as a
beacon for the mutant at all and then
suddenly killed by one of his own
followers and then oh the herd instinct
takes over but many wonder is Bob really
dead can he died was the whole murder an
elaborate ruse staged by Dobbs himself
in which an unwitting decoy look-alike
was sacrificed so that Bob could
continue waging the good fight in
secrecy Jonah the end result is JR Bob
not entirely unlike Paul McCartney is a
lot
if your bod is there tryna go as a
psycho's got a llegar
Oh God
my friends the conspiracy is like this
big machine this that's rolling towards
the edge of a cliff and so far Bob Dobbs
has been the little monkey wrench that
was slowing it down well ever since that
alleged assassination that monkey wrench
may not be in that big machine anymore
you know what that means that means you
have to pick up where Bob Dobbs left up
will you be the last Bob or will you
surrender to hopelessness remember this
might just be his way of testing you
actually these choices were already made
for you at the beginning of time so do
it join the church and gaze upon your
own naked destiny standing proud before
Bob
I have sworn upon the altar of God
eternal hostility to every form of
tyranny over the mind of man that is why
the clergy opposed me that's not all
that is on the Jefferson Jefferson
Monument in Washington except the last
sentence they left that out in the
interest of brevity so let us March
onward harvesting the souls of the
infidels heedless of blood spilled or
money's spent for in this nameless
mission our destinies are written is my
most religions are really all about
which is the only ones who won clouded
man yesterday the Church of the
SubGenius was only a few brave fools
tugging at the shoelaces of the Colossus
today it has already become the Zorro of
world religions scratching a bloody be
on the bloated box of the conspiracy
this whole thing's all Sofia's church is
just so crazy that it just might work
the conspiracy has 50,000 nuclear
weapons and the Church of the subgenius
we've only got three but yet we dare
defy them anyway and that's the miracle
of it you can see it's always been the
crazy people the crazy huh who weren't
dumb enough to stand up against the
Colossus in a sense Bob Dobbs can never
die he represents more than just a man
with a pipe and a know-it-all dream he
represents the quest of all mutants for
freedom in talking to most sub geniuses
today
you'll find an unshakable faith that
they're high he popped will rise again
but this time he will come not as gentle
teacher and salesman but as an avenging
angel meeting out the wrath of G over 1
upon the guilty and the innocent alike
cleansing the earth with the divine
radioactive all scouring or purifying an
isolation of his boundless a friends
some people like to call this church of
the subgenius a joke a joke oh it might
be a joke it just might be the greatest
joke ever told ya huh can make it to the
punch line with unquestioning faith in
Bob's word the end of the world can
easily become your personal stepping
stone to prosperity and a new beginning
for us all when you become some D's you
realize that everybody else is wrong and
you're right
sign up miss your soul to the church for
safekeeping until it is needed in the
great bargaining session on Judgment
but what can you do bob is the gun and
you are the bullet the showdown is fast
approaching the church is still unknown
but it infectious doctrines spread
across continents church headquarters
the first mega this temple Lodge is
housed in this Dallas skyscraper from
which dhabi secret men dates are issued
to his agents in the dreaded brotherhood
of volume but this mighty edifice
represents but the tip of a wandering
realized the word hymns and sound
effects of Dobbs are disseminated on a
weekly basis to thousands of him out
radio listeners in most major cities
even as far away as China and darkest
Africa this show is so popular in order
on a heads up we're studying it from all
angles and you can even watch this show
on channel acts every how plays the
microphone it flies backwards around the
other side of the planet the SubGenius
is in china have to listen on shortwave
radios very hard you'll notice so we've
switched a huge music for the background
for this segment of the show as the
psychic surgery of Oklahoma coal mr.
sweaty brow it's white and by a small
nuclear explosion oh all better now
Christians are tuning in for a nice play
all of us come yeah did you ever stop to
think that this show just maybe a little
panel shell or inside a larger show
rammed inside of somehow is we inside
the reason why regeneration spectacular
lucrative spiritual subgenius leave
idols move from town to town like
floating crap games always a few steps
ahead of the police here slack fired
preachers and renters performed head
launchings Phil dispensations and both
healings and sickening zuv audience
members depending on their knees
dozens of church musical combos called
duck tour bands after the original
doctors for Bob of Arkansas deprogram
entire paying audiences even while
rejecting health movement notions of
rhythm vanilla tea and until the
authorities catch on even common normal
and purchase the word of Bob itself
condensed for the legendary book of the
subgenius available in bookstores
everywhere but the only certain way to
receive the dogs teachings in uncut form
is to tithe directly to the church for a
suggested love offering of only twenty
dollars sent to p.o box 140 306 dallas
texas you will be ordained as a
card-carrying minister and receive the
huge official magazine churchly news and
doctrine the stark fist of removal I
just like to say a few words about the
start fist of removal this is a official
newsletter of the church and it's got
all kinds of great stuff in it it's got
the proof of Bob it's got a picture of
Bob with Ronald Reagan in there it's got
all import instructions to the subgenius
illiterates can purchase their choice of
dozens of inspirational cassette tape
and there's even a line of casual
SubGenius where to fit every size or
budget
your salvation some purchase thousands
of Bob's handy pamphlets with which to
recruit the worthy panda 2 / flex the
normals to fill their minds with
questions questions that only Bob can
answer through his chosen apostles his
fishers of Wallace and what is money
merely another tool of the conspiracy
except when it gains power by passing
from your pocket to Bob Bob with your
castle it's because your cash is not
flowing towards Bob this is the first
industrial church we're not a tax
write-off scam where we are an
incorporated profit-making foundation if
there is such a thing we were prophets
and we want profits
I don't care who you are where you come
from if you haven't sent you twenty
dollars into Bob you gonna burn mother
Teresa I don't care how many people
she's helped she had his in her twenty
dollars into jo Bob Dobbs is gonna burn
in hell and Bob offers a guarantee that
can't be beaten eternal salvation or
triple your mind as Bob will protect you
bob is protecting the genetic future
letting let him into your life let Bob
protect you he wants to protect you he
must protect you he has to protect you
Jehovah one says Bob will protect you
breathe if you send a dollar to post
office box 140 306 dallas texas 752 141
dollar for salvation one dollar now that
you've seen what you've seen will you be
with us in the saucers on x day or
instead will you be left crawling
through the glowing rubble a doubter to
the end in the sweet name of Bob you
must be saved even if it kills you
well it was a man world's greatest a
hill
why the gas
and it's coming up
a shot from is my desire
nigga
Oh
with the head
new suspicious
he goes
with us
the
Oh
if all the
that is my
Oh
you will emerge from transom bottone
remembering everything except your
instructions for the Omega contingency
plan we realize that if Jim Jones could
talk 900 people into killing themselves
we could talk 900 people into sending us
a dollar he makes the money I spent
you
praise God this is it your last big
chance to win that your soul next day is
coming kiss all your calendars goodbye
and prepare yourself to the Metroplex in
power and glory and the coolest
campground in the united states with
sideshow marvels the spontaneous doctor
band combustion train prairie squid drop
in hanson of workshops at you've eating
psychic surgery human flights live
freaks of nature and acid casualties
face fucking fat sperm ended up putting
cook-offs privately dope sex hurt
seminars self-mutilating creatures and
oddly normal-seeming people sex
goddesses Elder Gods
Nexus X day is coming park you ready for
the finals which will it be spaz out the
holiday forever or the last roundup can
you handle Judgment Day will you brush
with no for Center shirt and run run to
buy JR Bob dog to the church of the
subjects see em ewww SMG has got come
for more information experience the
diksha slea waited moment the
nail-biting suspense of July fifth 7am
only thirty dollars none my stocks and
none may escape what's the game close
Oh
you