sir can you please tell me where I can
find all incorporated 350 to push door
on your left thank you
these are the brownies from the valley
high school the girls are here to visit
the factory mr. Frane yes mr. friend
he'll be with you in a moment I'm sure
the girls would like to see the doll
display while they're waiting thank you
don't let mr. Franz catch you he's very
particular about these dolls nobody's
allowed detachment come on let's look at
the other dog
your lady do you like my dolls oh I
think they're lovely do you really you
must meet some of them
I dogs are fashioned from all walks of
life now he has a bride she lovely hmm
and over here now let me see hmm in the
housewife going shopping and here oh my
she's very important this is my nurse
she helps to keep my little people well
wouldn't do for anything to happen to
them what it nurse you treat them like
real people but of course they're my
friends my name is fats what's yours my
dear Sally Reynolds who came about my
head as a bone yes but I don't think I'm
the girl for the job oh wait please let
me be the judgment how much experience
have you had very little I I worked a
year in a college bookstore that's all
married no maybe your family I haven't
any family I'm on my own I'm sure
there's somebody else is better
qualified you're exactly the one I won't
miss Reynolds I'd like you to start
right away I don't know what I'm
supposed to do but just answer the
telephone and take care of my accounts
and my correspondence as you can see I
no good at paperwork i'm sorry mr.
friend i couldn't i have no one to help
me with my daughter I work alone I need
someone in the office whatever you do
your work will be satisfactory my dear
and I I pay the usual wages but if that
isn't enough I could manage a little
more won't you please try it just for a
day or two dolls incorporated one moment
please I mr. grant for you I'll take it
in the back room
yes mr. Gregg yes miss Hall you was to
wait for me there well she left last
week you were going to take a better
position with passe might try to reach
her there I'd be glad to mr. grant I'll
make a note of it right away goodbye
was it mr. Franz have found your work
for you I'll need the cash ledger can
you tell me where it is oh I'm afraid I
don't know what true Janet took such
good care of things I know I'll be right
out and help you look
hello who are you my name is Sally I
work for mr. friends Oh since when six
weeks ago do you have business with mr.
friends I sure do I'm Bob Wesley the
best salesman in st. Louis well he can't
be disturbed right now you may wait a
Pratt's come back later at least you can
do is tell him I'm here but I'm sorry he
just can't be disturbed not the factory
are you gonna tell me where he is please
don't get me into trouble mr. Franz is
in the back room and when he's in that
room he never wants to be disturbed all
right all right don't get excited can't
you send up some smoke signals or
something crying on the phone you'd be
furious mr. Franz furious they don't
come any my other than him say are you
afraid of him please I've got work to do
and if you'll excuse me I'll be able to
talk look let's start all over again I
apologize I don't want to get you into
any trouble and I want to be friends ok
ok all right now that we're friends tell
me the truth are you afraid of your boss
no I'm not afraid of him well maybe just
a little he does get a little peculiar a
time what times when he talks to them
he's so serious Collins if he expected
him to talk back boo why the dolls of
course
good morning Sally then dreaming up
anything new lots of block dolls
incorporated floor second floor well I
can take the letter I work there are you
miss Hall I know well it's registered
someone will have to sign for it maybe
you better see mr. friends about it very
small you another new man since we just
got one lately I'm special delivery
fourth one who ever happen that friendly
fellow brought the mirror on it for so
long you mean old Ernie the funny thing
two days before he was to retire and get
a pension he disappeared yes sir started
out one morning with his Mail Sack and
never came back yes miss Reynolds I'll
be right out and sign for it
mama good morning I'm sorry I don't know
miss hall's new address but I expect her
to stop by in a day or two I'll see she
gets this thank you come on inbound
sorry for justice
I'll be right where you are oh how
beautiful yeah very nice mm-hmm rice
doesn't seem too out of line I'll take
four gross of that what do you like my
dear oh this one here white organdy with
blue ribbons ah it's a pity you can't
muddle it for us though I can see it
would be better becoming on you yes well
to growth of the strapless organdy and
two of the negligee how about large way
to go with it Vince you can put that
into when can you deliver them ten days
that all right yes will that be all mr.
France you mind if I keep this strapless
organdy you can charge it to my order I
think that'll be all right Thank You mr.
Franz thank you Miss yeah let me get rid
of some of this stuff for you miss
Reynolds I don't know what I'd ever do
without you
yes miss Reynolds who no by all means
tell him I'll be right there an old
friend out of the past is here to see me
shall we call it a day I I'd have to
stop soon anyway to mix more plastic so
he won't forgive me won't you certainly
sir hey how are you hey meal what a
surprise I didn't even know you were in
this part of the world I arrived
yesterday with your puppet why of course
of my puppets open their show next
Monday and listen friend I should like
you very much to come to theatre and
meet them of course I should be happy to
do it how did you ever find him well I
thought I did the services of a
marionette maker well I was here so I
open the directory and there was your
name the longtime friend pain no more
show business no no I gave that up I
just have dolls now many many does so
you can see long as you enjoy it tell me
haha sure dear Emma Emma Emma and what
the girl with a beautiful golden hairs
your wife I have tried so long to forget
that name I sometimes almost succeed she
left me when did this happen my
marionettes were playing in Luxembourg
and she ran away with someone she liked
better I could that tech oh that must
have hurt how that must have heard from
what I'm happy now at any rate and
that's what counts no Amy let me take
you to dinner why not were here we'd
have time to stop at the theater a visit
your Mary on there that's an excellent
idea French so let us know and wait to
get my
little puppets
brah excellent rats x you know I don't
tell you performance like that in it
ages well this is like the good old days
again our brunch I or once the best in
our profession and you still could be if
you wanted to well you see things have
been getting too much for me lately and
I've been thinking of a partner what
about joining it it doesn't interest me
Bernhard because my marionettes are
getting old and irritation oh I don't
mind repairing them it isn't that what
is it then I am content in my doll
factory in the time we ate do you know
what's wrong with you my friend hmm why
must someone who's content with things
the way they are always had something
wrong with intent that is unnatural hmm
Emma's leaving you must have done a
great deal of harm aboard you think so
you run away from life you've surrounded
yourself with all shapes of the what
their traces their their legs their arms
even little mannequin is open but not
their spirit you're afraid of that then
I found peace anyhow not last I have no
fear it won't I love my dolls and i'm
quite sure they'll never leave me let's
forget about the past any event have a
good time living in the present is the
only important thing and then after
dinner we'll go back to my shop huh
excellent how about that
happy did you pick the show Freddie
particular reason I get tired of the
same things all the time don't you yes I
do such as what dolls why don't you ask
me what it feels like to be a freak
please alright this is how it feels to
be so big you can speak fs2 a second
pump by a cloud mr. friends that you're
going back to st. Louis tomorrow maybe
if adjustable I can go to be a hundred
feet tall and I don't need a change of
wardrobe I'd you like to come with what
would I do in st. Louis living a pretty
little house become mrs. Bob Wesley man
lives through plutonium blast have a
great joke in the third what do you
think I've been hanging around all these
weeks what do you say I I don't know
what to say don't say anything
you want to go back to your waters will
tell you friends about the monster about
the circus freak that's right sergeant
matthis circus freak have at hand will
travel why don't you make me up a sign
saying see the amazing colossal man see
I got a terrific idea what do you say we
fly to Las Vegas tomorrow and get
married I couldn't leave without telling
mr. friends I'm going and let me tell
him I'll see him first thing in the
morning you get pack and be ready enough
to get ten o'clock how's that wonderful
I am not growing you are shrinking
you
hello read on is anything the matter
when you didn't come to the office this
morning I began to worry well hasn't mr.
Wesley been deceived yes he was here
earlier everybody's left where did he go
back the st. Louis I believe Miss
Reynolds are you all right yes and I
expect you at the office this morning
yes up I'll be there
ah there you are now things are as they
should be by the way I left the bill for
those st. Louis shipments on your desk
I'll see you them right away friends
just bought go by air no by train I
believe he had his ticket already it was
very sudden well he'd been neglecting
his business lately it probably caught
up with him didn't he tell you anything
about me yes of course he did he told me
that he does to the Miriam and that you
had consented when's it to be he didn't
I mean we haven't set the date Bob gave
me to understand that she wouldn't have
work for me after you were married I
begged him not to take you away I told
him how sad it is when people go oh my
dear I didn't mean to make you unhappy
is it because he didn't come and say
goodbye well that wasn't very thoughtful
of him we didn't listen to an old friend
perhaps it would be better if you tried
to forget him I don't know what to think
that's not true up I dunno Bob wouldn't
treat me this way if he could help it
nothing to happen to him
when did you make this mr. friends while
bob was here it could be him almost well
thank you for the compliment you know
the aim of every composer is to hit the
world within the limits of his symphony
a writer wants to put all of life
between the covers of his book well if I
can make my dolls and the image of those
I know and love are you satisfied no
it's a small talent I know but I have to
make the most of it it's the only one I
have I'll be out of the office for an
hour or so
will you lock up my dear I have my own
key
pardon me can you tell me where sergeant
Patterson is Thank You sergeant
Patterson yes I'm Sally Reynolds the man
at the desk sent me to see you oh yes so
now Miss Reynolds oh here it is you say
in this report you may downstair that
your fiancé disappeared mysteriously
just what does that mean something mr.
friends did to her such as mr. Franz did
something to it well you said that well
I I don't know how else to put it did he
hit him did he shoot him did he strangle
him know he you won't believe me well
that's my business now tell me just what
did he do he made Bob into a doll you
made your fiance into a doll I see well
we'll let you know if we learn anything
miss Reynolds I knew you wouldn't
believe me look suppose there are some
other people that disappear the same way
would you do something Ben well that all
depends who were they Janet Hall anyone
else a male man named Ernie
our nevarsin go on well isn't that
enough yes it is okay let's go and see
this mr. France bobtown you must have
him inside is the man yeah young lady
says you've been making people disappear
mysteriously turning them into dolls I'd
miss Wren us what made you say such a
thing it's perfectly ridiculous is that
Wesley how come it looks just like her
boyfriend I model all my dolls after
people I know and like people I like to
have near me nothing wrong with that is
done I safe please say to me
it's life like all right well I should
hope so but I assure you it's only a
doll watch
what did you expect my dear they're only
made of plastic see here's a whole case
full of them well looks like your
boyfriend kind of took a powder doesn't
it okay I'll put through a tracer on him
anyway be seeing you please feel free to
drop in anytime Sarge thank you
oh you weren't thinking of going to were
you dear of course please don't it would
make me so terribly unhappy do you
really expect me to work for you after
all this I think of your pretty eyes and
your lovely boys and the beautiful
flowers on your desk and I ask myself
how could I ever bear to let you go but
it's impossible now why do you say that
19 because I can't stand being in this
place another minute
you
be careful my dear well surely you
aren't afraid of me are you why I'm your
friend oh you mustn't feel bad miss
Reynolds thank you to put on your new
clothes don't want to meet your fiancé
dressed in nothing but a napkin do you
hear they are first your toilet articles
and your stockings and the dress oh it's
very pretty isn't it remember you
selected this yourself now you want to
make yourself look nice i'm sure you're
going to meet Bob so I help you
only asleep miss Reynolds but you might
call a state of suspended animation Oh
be patient you'll be with you in a
minute this pressure will revive him in
no time
ah you don't know how much I enjoy these
little reunions you funny little people
I wonder why it is you always hate me so
at first I haven't really harmed you get
the best of care I never let you get too
warm to cold too hungry or too tired you
should be grateful sink no daily grind
no budget problems no taxes or debts of
family to support I see to everything
and it's never dull you sweep away the
long boring hours and your jars and when
I take you out to wake you it's it's
only to have fun to enjoy some new treat
I thought up for you don't you see how
fortunate you are you have nothing to do
all the rest of your little lives that
be happy that's what you think change
back away we were I like you better the
way you are are you going to keep this
time always would you really like to
know it's my secret but I don't think
you'll give me away it's a very simple
principle really
notice how this slide projector throws a
visual image I can make it any size i
choose i push it closer to the wall the
picture becomes smaller being of an
inquiring mind i asked myself one day if
I couldn't do the same with living
things I reasoned that if I could pass
them through a device similar in
principle to this slide projector that I
would be able to project these living
things to any size that I wouldn't
choose this is the answer I found
Oh
yeah Tommy Tommy Tommy Tommy you project
a complex molecular structure such as a
man or say a cat it's only necessary to
change him into energy first much as the
light in that slide projector I soon
found out that the most practical way of
causing this chain was to break down
molecular structure by means of
high-frequency vibration now with this
tuning fork I will set up a sonic
vibration just as the glass
disintegrated to the resonant frequency
sent out by this tuning fork so with a
living thing disintegrate to its
resonant frequency of course it's a much
higher frequency oh there you are tummy
oh now watch this make you take
something for you
once again
you remember Tommy miss Reynolds he
always liked you take him being so small
he may feel strange at first met him I
must go and get some of the other little
people who live with me I want them to
meet you
hello big boy who's your friend miss
Reynolds may I introduce miss lane call
me Georgia they all do Gretchen each
Sally welcome to the toy department I
kid this is Laurie she's a swell kid
sorry me Bob and sad how are you hello
gosh I'm awfully sleepy hungered he put
me away this time well for a couple of
months anyhow oh say you missed a lot of
fun we had a picnic at a flower box to
dances and a moonlight swimming party
and the same on all because I wouldn't
sink for hi Laurie long time no see hi
everybody hi Stan say hello to Bob and
Sally and if it is a mad pride of the
Marine Corps that's me Father and Sally
well welcome stranger hey the old fanta
learning how to pick them better all the
time anyway we're gonna get this party
rolling yeah let's go what are we
waiting for big boy we got a new arrival
here to celebrate
I have some refreshments for our little
party aperitif for knife to cut it with
tiny little cups and saucers and a
miniature bottle of champagne please
help yourselves I'm afraid I'm a little
too clumsy to serve my guests when
they're as small as you my toast to the
new members of the family Ellie and Bob
are you two engaged hey when's the
wedding going to be you better ask him
poor Bob and Sally there's no one your
size who can marry you I have to see
what I can do about it sometime stop all
you stop having to be so calm God for
help run do something anything but then
he looked not over there anyway hi got
used to the sides about 10 minutes and
believe me brother I kind of like it I
never had it so easy in my life look at
it this way Sally we're in a jam and it
has nothing to do would make the best of
it for the time being anyway I know how
she feels i took a pretty hard true but
we sometimes have to do things we don't
want you just to have some freedom like
this listen he drops a capsule in your
charge put you to sleep don't breathe
any idea everybody's coming back
rocket
now Lori you must sing for us no I want
to say but you will my dear or back in
the bottle you go
er a dolly you're a dolly you're so cute
and lovely there's little dog
say you want me to be near
to be yours forever my love
you're so precious you're so darling you
are but I could want the Living God
never leave me don't deceive me stay
with me forever more my living nah never
leave me don't deceive me stay with me
forever more my name
yes I was passing by and saw the light
in your window I thought you might be
low some sort of divine that was kind of
you a meal tell me how did your opening
night go France won wonderful come and
sit down I'll tell you all about let me
put things away I'm how but it'll only
take one minute you must hear what
happened last night come sit on you
first of all everybody was there but
what everybody outside the police does
anyone know the number i should be never
i call it just yesterday
late department police department we're
at don't incorporated this place to
urban anybody on this line oh we can't
hear me it's the music stopped at
Francis sure to come back Telstra's Bell
dings incorporate anybody on this line
you nobody can hear little people like
us awful when you think there are people
all around us we can't even get through
to them then right after the first act
orders of old as I am you life simply
have to go now add a minute France wait
you're an old team backstage to
congratulate please just a minute I have
to take care of the record player there
you see the record produce karin-sama
come on come on let's finish it front
listen I tell you it was like that good
ol days in Brussels now we're do just
the name of the partner came backstage
come on try try I can't guess you tell
me the machine I was wondering if we
couldn't go through it the other way
come out our right sides again you said
it works like a projectory how bet I can
figure out the controls it may not be a
good idea fool you might get you I don't
care i'm willing to risk it i am too who
wouldn't be Oh once enough it only takes
one of us to go for help shall we try it
yeah not uphold it you who live in dolls
but I was one of his first puppet so I
deserve the right to be the guinea baby
okay all right Mac if that's the way you
want but you know what can happen if I
make a mistake but let's go on well have
a dove work you're going to need some
flow now I'm pretty sure he keeps their
older than that cloth that's right I saw
him egg mine up over there
come on let's go three girls better stay
up here I'll work to control stand you
go to the door keep an eye out for front
just been
let's go
No
you
hmm
how splendid boy so so I said to myself
I said at last I'm being appreciated Oh
hartford a WEP for happen in front and i
am happy for you may I go now oh well I
shouldn't detain you like this should i
do you want to see i have to be alone in
this kind of work I'm doing you you
understand Oh
why don't you want and do what you have
to do it and i'll talk to earn your work
no no i'd rather give you my undivided
attention old friend so tell me what's
happened here
ok
we may get back
but what about the nightcap with me oh I
only wish I cool oh let's de Marlin not
certainly if I call for you about new
exit well I suppose there's not any more
for us to say but good night huh let's
be bold and get it over with good night
come on Stan
we had enough fun for the night come to
bed quickly now it's time
come in Oh sergeant how are you finest
brands don't mind to find the one with
my work do you I'm short-handed did I
pull in way that I I notice you're
advertising for another secretary yes
it's quite a problem keeping help these
days how'd you happen to lose Sally
Reynolds she went to st. Louis I believe
her fiance lives there you know oh I
could have saved us a trip why have you
news of him well he didn't show up at
home and we've been asked to do some
more checking on him here how strange
what do you suppose could have become
Adina that's what I came to ask you can
you fix my dowry will you excuse me go
ahead take care of your customer I'll
just look around well let's see what we
can do for you tell me what's your doll
is named Susie she got run over oh dear
dear dear how did that happen she ran
out in the street while I wasn't lucky
that wasn't nice of I was it she's a bad
dog you know you ought the spanker when
she disobeys I do it doesn't sound to do
any good i yeard I like that they do get
rather headstrong sometimes mr. France
what's in here Oh what just to work
groom Oh Marcia please oh nothing there
that would interest you sergeant I go
there whenever I'm lonely I would like
to see it I have a key please
thank you you had so many darling hey
let's give you a lot of trouble yes but
then I I never get lonely and that makes
up for it thank you no dear no no please
why not well everybody going to know
where you got it you know grown-ups ask
so many awkward questions are you better
give it to me I'll take it away from now
on what do you call this thing in here
you can play with it till I get back oh
that well what's it look like to you cut
me you know what a photographic and
larger is don't you well this works just
the opposite i use it to make models of
people wouldn't you like to see how it
works or some other time i've got to be
running along well what you got there
little girl let's see
got a tape recording inside you like it
haha no but you can come and play with
it anytime you like yeah yes that too Oh
about those missing people I'll be
checking with you later I do hope you
find them soon such either bye honey now
to fix your daddy's this is one of the
best puppets you ever had a meal for the
best Jaclyn has ever was it was made by
Schwartz back in the good old days in
Prague but not funny thing every time DQ
comes for kjetil to change him to hide
hey nothing happens did you bring me
back here at this late hour because your
star puppet was a little temperamental
please France please understand my
predicament there only three people in
the whole world I could trust to cure
him well mariani was in Milan oh yeah
well he's in Paris and you you know
perfectly well I never could resist
flattery how much time can I have to
work on him well you see we have a
matinee tomorrow to have you tragic to
return all that money for the tickets
can you have him ready that's soon I'll
try it even if it takes me all night and
one more thing yeah how much it is gonna
cost oh nothing that's the least I can
do for an old fan that idea that you may
a dear old friend ask you something of a
personal nature they're too late now
what are you up to debride the police
over to ask me all sorts of questions
when was this this afternoon free
sergeant named the Patterson he comes to
my hotel room and it sounds fantastic
you asked me what whether you were in
the habit of making people disappear I
suppose you told him I do it all the
time ah but seriously it's bad business
to help police prime to your affairs a
meal I'm
series if I thought I were being watched
i would find life intolerable now be a
good fellow will you until the night
doorman to let me in the theater later
i'll have to give mr. Hyde to try out
when he finished I'll run along now I'll
do it on my way home I don't suppose I
have to tell you how grateful and you
follow nonsense goodnight a meal and
goodbye
sorry you're awake miss Reynolds makes
everything much more difficult what are
you going to do the police have been
asking my friend a meal questions
they're getting uncomfortably close that
means me only one course you're free is
for chip make it the right size again be
deprived of your company oh no I
couldn't let that happen can't you see
it it's better that we all bow out
together oh please don't be frightened
can't you see it's much better that we
all meet death together than for any one
of us to be left alone there's nothing
worse than loneliness
wait wait I have a splendid idea yes yes
we'll have a going away party for all of
us a celebration my friend Amy allows me
to fix his puppet and leave it at the
theater we'll have our party there a
theater party now let's all get ready
hey what's not it with being a bottle
baby look at the service we get oh the
old boy is really letting go he's been
giving us parties like they were going
out of style and tonight the theater
party no less you better enjoy it
Georgia as may be our last what are you
talking about Sally tell her he said it
tonight he said tonight he was going to
kill us all himself to you better hurry
up and dress he'll tell the boys did he
go you yeah I know we heard yourself
Georgia oh if I was just my own size 45
minute hey let's try the telephone again
there's no music now maybe don't hear it
yeah sure so it's France is just outside
the door hey the window slightly open we
can signal this away sure we can we're
only five stories up you're so fake if
somebody gets out of your writing glory
keep an eye out for friends
there's no paper that's all right up hey
here's a pencil hey that's great bring
it on yeah man let's see them all right
that help simple now shall we take a
taxi to the theater I think that would
be a nice treat of course you will be
able to see out the window but I don't
think your mind that little
inconvenience at least you'll be able to
hear what the city sounds like at night
because this time I shan't put you to
sleep you've been very good this is your
reward
Oh
you all right mr. prime yes yes I are
lonesome the theater was nobody wrong
not to me i have my puppets to keep me
company but you've been at it all night
I thought maybe I could get you some
more coffee no no more coffee I still
have plenty don't come on the stage all
right all right no more coffee
I know what those capsules used to put
us to sleep slip it in his coffee may
not put him to sleep it probably slowing
down some which did it the last time you
put us away now then I think our puppet
friend dr. Jekyll is ready for a trial
good evening ladies and gentlemen I am
dr. Jekyll I have discovered a strange
drug it is able to free my evil nature
from what is good in me then I become
the sinister monster mr. Hyde with the
assistance of a few members of our
audience I should like to put on one of
the scenes from our little plane which
one of you who will volunteer come now
we must keep dr. Jekyll waiting miss
Reynolds you will play the good doctors
fiance Georgia you will be his victim
and now let me see for dr. Jekyll's best
friend yes Bob you should be very good
in the part the rest of you just sit
back and enjoy yourselves all right
you're on now Miss Reynolds I'll prompt
you on what to do go ahead darling keep
his eyes off the coffee shop
tell him he's been strange lately and
ask him what's the matter change lately
tell me what's the matter nothing my
dear nothing at all it's only your
imagination must play up to a Miss
Reynolds remember you love him say so
Jeremy can trust you you know I love you
why can't you be kind to me more
convincing dear try it again no I love
you why can't you be kind to me that's
it my dear that's it things are
different now they can never be changed
back again perhaps it would be best if
we stopped seeing one another there is
danger here for you and I wouldn't want
anything to happen to you ask him to
confide in you why why won't you tell me
what's wrong I have traveled the road of
no return there is no going back only
death can free me from the chris i have
put upon myself or you're more of a beam
and i thought you're gonna kill us get
over cut out this cat mouse key Bob
don't ruin our last act look at this
puppet down here friends look at it
closely it's a monster all right but not
half the monster you
oh stop it Bob the puppet you're
destroying the puppets
stop it i can you stop it
who's there me again don't come on the
stage I thought I told you I don't want
to be disturbed I heard you something I
thought not what maybe you want some
more coffee oh no your cough is fine and
I still have plenty
Bob miss Reynolds where do you run to
where are you hiding where are you don't
run away from me
comics time for us to go who you talking
to annoy haven't you ever heard of them
to the quiz practice throwing his voice
oh I've heard but enough there must be
somebody nearby it's five thirty in the
morning most people are in bed now
what's hopeless let's try to get back to
France place in the machine we make it
we go back for the others it's this way
second and man do we have to go to
seventh and health how far is but am I
like thing where were our size that is
the equivalent of six miles fucking we
have a megaphone we're not gonna make it
standing here come on boy look at all
did you see the lead very oh never mind
are you sure it's this way far back is
all we're sure that it
it's detector oh c'mon litter no wait
you have to go with the floor the
elevator operator won't be on for at
least an hour we can't operate it
ourselves hey what about free what do
you mean well that must be a freight
elevator around back when did they make
deliveries I don't know shit but soon as
they come in before I get to work
hey it's all right it's back for another
load the mess
a public awaits
yeah happy
you
hey we're luck you left the doors
what's the matter honey is it mr.
Franzen to meet you well it looks like
we both missed him Justin you like him
don't you as he makes dolly and evil Joe
people may not keep up he makes little
people does he owe out of big ones with
the machine really little people people
that all and talk and everything how do
you know mr. fat showed me he said
sometimes when I'm glad I could fly with
him OC isn't here to let you play with
him and that's why you're unhappy he
said I subside with his kitty a little
tiny city it's just an keeps it in a
matchbox machine see is that time you
were going to school well come on I'm
going to take you better little people
cat in a matchbox am come on
get away from that door come on Sally
will call the police don't see me please
don't leave me don't leave me I'll be
alone