[Music]
well looks like we finally took the
little boys in blue
I don't like that governor calling out
the cover different of private war at
this privilege
all i know is i'm glad to be out of
Johnson County it's now I got to those
folks in like it very much
where did actually mean to me keep it
get out of here
yes that's why we split the blankets
Johnny and fail the building
sure you don't wanna come along no I
think our slope long up in the riots
River Country what's up there
shoot I'd like trouble well that's a way
to make 1101 know and the seat love
index now what about that job and going
and didn't say thank you what's been
happening with hey well that's good else
works you've got a big travel adventure
also everything seven down one place and
yeah i did so by on what's perhaps if we
got to like to sell one man
no I'm serious you better stop thinking
about that ranch kid you never make it
why not we've been hiring out that done
you wrong
I can forget all that well maybe you can
which is a lot of people attend but i'll
be seeing the red line going
[Music]
lose your harsh now got a little tie and
let him race go back later and carry men
same thing happened to me last week
it'll stretch a gumbo mother my team
played out on me
you may not believe it but i have to
push them for horses inside and pull the
stage myself i believe it you're one of
the few people have met again it's a
troubling yeah and that's exactly where
I'm going and getting back
I'm overdue not all right if I hope
you're not hurt you get off my lab i'll
let you know i got like I just didn't
get your knife didn't give a team and a
little trouble this morning but haven't
seen you someplace before then a lot of
place I don't give me time I remember I
never forget a face
ran into a little trouble this morning I
know you're no that's not it around a
little
and a little trouble this morning and
doing my horse back at the trail
I close my eyes and take a deep breath i
pleased to have him with this
what's the matter what you like or don't
like I've got it
your red Kittredge i remember now I saw
your picture in which i am paper when
you hired out to the ranches in the
Johnson County War you know I knew a man
once you've got himself into a lot of
trouble because you remember thanks to
this guy I'm sorry stranger I didn't
mean any offense you're not on second
thought I must have been thinking about
somebody else
I look I thought your next like
something first Carolyn you didn't have
a television jolly know probably are
driving that spook him
let's kill anybody told me down that
luggage thanks mrs. what do you want
done with these bags instructions i'll
be glad to have with him you don't learn
very fast do you just like your name is
Santa don't we can sure that girl you
don't seem to like you very much
it's not me baby girl turned you think
we can deliver those cattle Kelly two
weeks the bunch of another week to make
the drive when did you not to tell if it
comes to today's edition of time for
blood
go ahead and said providing i live that
long with children
yeah I know I'm it was me at a forum in
a dark alley some night I don't operate
that way Kelly anything should happen to
me though
come in voluntarily different
I didn't expect you guys do tomorrow i
want my job back and saying sheridan
bank won't make a longer I didn't think
they would
there's a close game and get anyone sit
in 20-something i miss Jenny mosquitoes
but i'll tell you about it later
you beat to death we go on out to the
ranch tonight dad seems to me you've
done not traveling for one day kind of
special reason point what is it red
kitchen is in town i wrote in on stage
with I see you have to look like a
showdown does that's what you've got to
stay away from there that's the reason
we have to meet and getting a little too
all the third run but you gotta listen
to me daddy the gunman you know he was
probably too can you please that don't
do it from icing and just one thing on
earth I wouldn't do for you give me this
is it does at that ranch with my own two
hands
you were born there your mother guy did
I fought Indians and snowstorms and dry
years and floods to make it what it is
i'm not gonna give it up just because
some two-bit gunslinger happens to come
to tell kelly stopping there are going
not your fight
that's what i was talking about that's
red cabbage something i could do vary
every loading ammunition fluid depends
on the caliber I got a few moles Buffalo
gun don't see many of these around
anymore here one-month supply matter of
fact there's only one man around here
Jones when it did I know what is he
really made their Foreman four games
section would not have a daughter with
really hook know he ain't even married
i'm talking about facts
Oh jewelry he's got a daughter read it
Mary jury interesting and you and jury
already get together seems you got
somethin in common
yeah looking forward to meet ye you
don't want me to read only one candidate
yet now i'm just looking for information
pops wear what you want to know already
found out
i'm dan section the manual abroad Eric
you know might as well be here enough
your food
I got no fight with you least not yet
there's a stage leaving town are so
beyond it
I just got here you heard what I said we
don't like a gunman on the Sun be on
that stage and I'm not and make your
play now you listen
[Music]
try again
I'm convinced I'm alright you're real
brave left
[Music]
like to kill you
yeah I'm still trying to figure out why
he didn't get a little spooky your
friends two men try to lift my scouts
today already
you might be this earth that's out of my
life what you want tell percent want to
see you
you'll see me right now when I don't
find your biggest my commanding bed down
for the night like a miscarriage and the
wheel nice hotel just down the street
probably like a better one when we both
we've got mice i won't bother them
yes room 20 hit a room 16 upstairs i can
just see it now
blood all over my nice clean flowers
how's this feel pretty good now let that
be a lesson to you you're getting too
old to go up against the killer ain't no
killer duck would be as we've been
taking money under false pretenses all
the way from Texas to the Canadian line
there why didn't he kill possession
maybe he can't shoot straight and still
doing a ride to the bridge with sounds
over license i know somebody without the
shoot me I think I could work up a
reasonable this light for I just doing a
job you can't hate a man for that under
the circumstances I could try real hard
you got something on your mind and what
is used to run with the Wild Bunch down
25 years ago I just like kitchen someone
hasn't given me a hand up by driving in
Boot Hill no rush shot but it's not bad
just doesn't know where he's going
so you're gonna show could be used to
add a fund and instead of a daughter I'm
not complaining
I'll catch up for the build-out double
another you've been doing that for ten
years I've never collected a dime yet
oh you don't think I choose to your duck
let's just say I never quite yet
shovel
haha
[Music]
ok
well you're in the wrong room arch you
can put the gun away
I'm not dangerous it could be the right
equipment boy how about the gun
oh I started feeling dressed without it
so I look undressed even with it and
expected company and you're going to
have to be y que no I could get out of
telling me in time no hurry
how'd you ever get me something that
isn't being a hired gun
well they're already got a talent for
man must have a good reason for hiring
out to murder murder anybody yet that's
what it finally comes down it doesn't
look you're trying to reform the u18
time
what did the man like you want out of
life anyway
oh I spread of my own someday and
doesn't anybody else working boy only
way I know how
that's my dad wanted to only he got it
the hard way
now you're helping tell them take it
away from chance you gotta take what
maybe somebody else you could kill him
while ago I didn't you get nothing SE
and why did you take this job i'm taking
it yet i thought what television saying
self-esteem to take a lot of things for
good and you're going to turn it down
No
probably made you a better off what jobs
on the ranch for two months and found 14
hours a day in the saddle chuckwagon
grand old blankets
whoo that's part of it but the rest
seems to me you're in a position to ask
whatever you want i might be that kinda
try to see to it that your work will be
very pleased you really meant that it
could be we make some kind of video way
it is so I think no matter what happens
i'll come out on the losing end of the
deal i know well she and what love is
action in my way I much
that's more than I can say about you now
get the drake sunday i hope to see you
when you can't use that right arm of
yours mr. Kittredge
the floor then the back room will have
to tell them i'm having the same go see
what the floor then the back room will
have and give them my pardon by name and
when I die I don't spend my money allows
our picture in a play your part in the
back room and now they're my and how
they Michael I can tell them my guide of
the claim for a good-looking wanna drink
her throat somebody I really wanted so I
like to count to five
we have that chance
what the hell are eventually backbone
have and tell them I depends how that
micro doubt that my daughter Sarah
cinematic children third book
Roddenberry will switch you want to
switch but you're traveling under new
name these days after speaking to your
old friends in this business you know
your friends at Monday the next maybe
better change this give it some thought
I a drink or about you safe so your
homestead misplaces your time clue i'm
still working out say when one of your
fingers get away last time I saw you was
down a difference
why did you leave right at you to read
your ad twelve reasons each one of them
had a gun in his hands
I'm just trying to get one out of 12
yeah you've got a pretty good record
Texas Arizona New Mexico Colorado now me
I'm young yet you're running out of
state to understand his last room left
in Canada like something i can always
use
guarantee Johnny lake and such a couple
days ago for his mentality you won't
have not been reaching to general
delivery in big sandy still nobody could
he always wife second chance with me but
I did not do up here to talk about going
I have a proposition for you real i
would like the only thing stopping us
hey guys
he also owns all arranged the basic
expect one and see how you get in on
that
well I get night i tried to hide what
happens then I don't you figure that out
for you
I thought I just bury you and the back
I told you I don't want any way I can
get where i would kill Matt have you met
red Kittredge is mad cows haven't had
the pleasure a little whiskey corner
I'm not a patient man mr. Kittredge I
somewhere that I wanted to see you
several hours ago I don't like to be
kept waiting and make this eve i don't
like to take orders I witnessed your
little altercation this afternoon what
everyone else seemed as the only one in
town it doesn't know what's gonna happen
when I went to a great deal of trouble
to publicize your coming
you see I anticipated mr. sections
reaction too bad you passed up the
opportunity to kill him legitimately he
drew first and you should let me know
what was going on
you got my letter didn't tell bit much
there are some things mr. Goodrich
little better set and RIT it's quite a
symptomatic mr. Sachs norms ranch I
wanted I don't you back that that's a
good question you want sell but he hope
to gain by killing I haven't all the
northern mr. Saxon stable and 30 days
now it's impossible to get his cattle to
an eastern market at that time and what
are you worried that unfortunately he
obtained a contract to supply beef to a
railroad construction crew i want to
make sure that beef is not delivered you
have the shooting to do that
of course not i just started my tumblr
final i disappoint
it's all right mr. Finch I'm sure you'll
find some other way of stopping degree
how I leave the details up to you you
are highly recommended me the specialist
in your life
so who recommended me another friend of
yours required to frame thanks for
thinking that's all right
always glad to do a favor for an old
friend and that's the worst e500 now
1500 more when the job is done is that
why consider it extremely generous
however i listen to a counteroffer
I do all that work you wind up with the
ranch maybe we ought to be partners on
the deal what's your idea of a
partnership settle for third
uh-huh i don't know i think it okay
your friend is a difficult man to deal
with
I told you we come hi little higher than
I figured why don't you paint loss to
the bed is nothing you don't understand
like images if I allowed my very
dangerous now later he wanted all of
what you do now while I didn't think
about it overnight need to make them a
better office storage
[Music]
looking for trouble is it's the only
true intent so I'm safe here
don't want anything to happen to me and
someplace where you met this is my place
of business
I like to run the daughter mr. regional
center use your jumping at shadows de mi
nobody drinks too sure if you kill him
out of my Foreman that file it say the
name was currently in massive that's not
just a little proposition for you are
already made me up and I'd say she's got
more to offer than us down curly and
I've got my daughter's visiting maybe
you think my offer was a little bit and
then you have a man lose any money list
reader says you're interested in owning
a ranch my dimension I was the square so
what I'm get it sounds good do a lot of
people come again cut the cards with I
card you win the square feet with
mortgage that's the one part of the glad
to get rid of sound like much of a
bargain me what's wrong with them all
you have to do is deliver your cattle
but if I lose then you go to work for me
for a month and found a house as long as
I think I need to submit mr. Kitteridge
was my understanding that you're working
for me it's my understanding you want to
my class yet you're a full Sun he has
more cutting 20 years gotta be just
about do you got the map just keep
everything honest I think he's on not
honest but awkward
you first like the kids on the white
construction
looks like you're in the ranching
business strikeout of the market a few
days and I'd be awfully mad at anybody
trying to stop next time you tried to
bushwhack somebody pick up the empty and
another than media arts outside form you
only want i came in later this standard
to me like somebody just outrageous I
underestimated mr. Kittredge to do
anything about the man to accept defeat
because I definitely don't you
sections one thing which is another
senior has a well-established reputation
for violence
you aren't elefante
I know someone who isn't rated what a
wide range of acquaintances you have
probably stayed patient as right people
how long would it take you to a friend
to get here
16 Centrella alright
only this time don't try to buy a cheap
[Music]
not a bad-looking hard to add their
daily throughout and I'm not working for
you not working for me get off my land
you're pretty tough with that gun
strapped around your waist wonder how
stuck you'd be without
we never gonna find out what I never
going to take it out
[Music]
Oh son so that just get rid of a little
bit would you know sometimes I think
it's a mistake to learn to read and
write you wouldn't have to go through
all of it
here's the deed to the ranch you can
ever recorded next time to get to town
and here's a copy of kelvins modest well
I guess that takes care of all the
paperwork
anything else you want to know yeah
where's the beat back in the hill
did you have a spring around it after
the winter way that we didn't need one
countries are currently wolf boy when it
killed the cab crop and most of the
beach there's two that's how telford
composition most of these wrenches it
wasn't for that railroad contract you
have this one to westock you got left
could be scattered mierda can't do if
its notes due in four weeks
it's no news to me just interrupt
country take that long around a month
that's your problem son
like I came out on the short end of the
deal actual anytime you start liking the
other side of the bed let me know i'll
take the land bag thanks I think I've
where this way one time around you ever
doing here and chill before you make a
hand no time rounding spread like this
you don't need to configure I could do
it alone
sorry your crew I keep him mom I know
this country about just about barely
handle men and he knows kettle said I
didn't think that you two friends that
we can't shoot in Bethany canna don't
mind having fun enemy now that's one
thing i want to get straight so I didn't
know it was going to try and drag out
you had something he thought up on his
own
you've got a real lively imagination but
look at it from his ankle he figured
he'd on the rain sunday you got to marry
read it and I giving some trouble there
to be any plans when you leave here when
you get to be my age you don't make
plans anymore you just playing the way
the Delta had been the gate maybe we can
make a deal
listen
I need all the help I can get stands to
reason you know more about the spread
and anyone else you offered me a job
why not you offered me one I'll think
about take your time and then start
working with my man join me around the
place their pleasure some might be the
last chance I have to see what's this
about your cook profession and take your
word for it
those are your hand at social sanction
told you to set up and then Your Honor
names kitchen
yeah we know what you may want to know
where you're saying well and the run
this place like mr. stack and their
money on jobs here for you if you want
to stay
none of us staying we just want to
collect wages we got coming
alright let him off
seems to me that your responsibility you
on the ranch
John broke didn't tell me you could meet
pelo you never asked
yeah like I'm learning more about the
ranching business every day while you're
learning what about our money do i have
two things going
actress I don't get down right now you
can stick around take a chance on get we
don't work on your butt looks like job
on college spreads got left gotta get
that beef much you meant help me not pay
you double what you got temple
what guarantee if we got two will get it
my words letting enough
what's wrong with his words I'm taking
it you mean you're going to work for him
well we gotta eat do with I'd rather go
hungry
I tried that too i would document
playing this straight down there's just
trying to copy your bet it straight on
this through the graph for 25 years I
lost it on the square there's anything I
wouldn't do outside of motor to keep
talking some gayness he said boys
I reckon if it's good enough for you
damaged good enough for me
yeah alright with me
thanks Boyce we gotta round up tomorrow
really go along with you then you want
to see the ranch
hi this is two minutes
document if you don't want to have a
long way in conversation because I'm
that contact
hey melt bring the pot of coffee and
swimming
I'm not glad to see anybody at this time
in the morning make yourself comfortable
I'll call my hair of rice the grind away
you been up and down hills
[Music]
can show you some of that coffee i'm
getting
I get along the Kittridge I can take him
or leave him alone
given a choice i leave him alone you can
have to work for him you know why I did
hiking game still like to hear it once
was
alright manager run out of work it's
probably a few cows still back up in the
hills and you better start looking for
I'll see you later
someday he's going to take you apart
Carly yes Carly and I hope I'm there to
see it
[Music]
I don't look too bad considering the
weather they put in doesn't belong to
fatten up and get good grass with almost
breaks to the north tomorrow you should
be able to start to drive today after
which way do we go
there's only one way to go straight down
the valley and around the mountain
you need to be sure to cut across the
mass and the shorter alright nobody ever
tried it I know of
leastways they never came out the other
side take your word for it you know this
country better knighted you make up your
own you cutting it close for time as it
is and help me try to stop you
I don't think he will be underestimated
he gets this Rancher control of the
whole basis Rangers getting skiers you
won't quit without trust
[Music]
they a pretty sight I've seen since I
held for 7 against in a cycle
get up by get up feat of brains up
luckily it was just looking at mystery
to take it easy now let's was looking at
how wait a minute here girlie you want
to look at it hard to go home where she
belongs
for these days you're going to start
your plane i'm going to give you a
chance to change your mind and I get why
I brought to the heart
I don't get you grunts
what do we got the point
same thing as yesterday beams and
horsemeat I don't mind eating parts
except i figure the professor on
harnessing before he could she
haha i bought something on your mind
attention mr. Saxon tells me you're
going to start to drive tomorrow right
after I expect month
what do you figure on eaten while you're
making it matter we should grab our
winch art we just run out that's all
what do you need well let me see we need
potatoes flour salt cornmeal hard fan
eglinton it the wagon going in town I
grew up today like help me as you're
driving get your breakfast and a cup of
tea
[Music]
well they are boys
alright much done
[Music]
like
yeah try to come
[Music]
I gotta turn and stop sticks scattered
from here who's hurt as us and then they
won't be changed on council of peppered
by denominator anyone he'd get my vote
then taken back to the ranch in dr.
latkin I'm daylights not getting that
heard back again I don't you give up
it'll take a week to get a bunch again I
want a bunch and ready to move by the
extra mile with you tell me about
worried and came looking for me
where's the breast there is any help in
shadowy credit after shave get that rig
turn around me
get rich is coming up mr. Kent rich this
is an unexpected pleasure is it didn't
you think i can look at me i'm sorry i
haven't the faintest idea what you're
talking about
you know what I'm talking about keep
your hands off my ranch I've never had
it to drive
I don't like threats mr. difference not
threatening trying to save your life
oh the peace-loving type Johnny iro
that's your head and she had memorized
are more girls treat their dogs but only
treat the Moon Side that I couldn't
stand the snow i see you again on the
know each other we gotta sort of a
shooting acquaintance understand you're
in the ranching business
yeah but yeah thnkx over already got one
I'm glad you dropped in Kitteridge i'm
prepared to make you an offer for the
squares that will enable you to shoulder
potential profit
it's not for state you're making a
mistake and made them before it might
interest you to know that legally
speaking you don't on the ranch
what are you talk well there's a
territorial statute that void ownership
of any land one of the game of chance
your life
read it for yourself and tell me this
before I didn't know it
mr. Bratton just discovered this action
looks like you're up against a core
group that certain belong to me why do
you want it back
let's just say i'm offering your bonus
to let the tattoo revert to its original
on take the money Roman make it easy and
brothers and I want to go gunning for
him and virtualization what about
buy a drink
why not
indistinct situation any help that our
friend the years that might help
that's looking boy that's what i like
about this job company you keep
so now trouble do a report by my food by
my true
all other keep on way
and always wear
[Applause]
gotta hold on box almost to drink and
silvertone stuck his by was getting good
for nothing but cleaning noobs defending
the job done
3500 is gonna only offered meters out
you gonna take into consideration that
kind of talent happy things and cash 25
on a bonus from the Jonathan me when you
shoot me I'll give me that mentions in
place
Alice started let my pride and passion
for one month
[Music]
it's like old times through this
together
we now demanding real nice
how do you like the ranking alright
[Music]
see you around jack it seems likely
do you think you'll have to kill don't
know and the ground black crochet
meeting okay why don't you take a look
how I like it here
maybe you didn't hear me let's take a
walk you're both in case you you
wouldn't dare should be in here because
I'm black and just keeps
[Music]
kittredge just walked out with O'Shea
and Johnny up to you one last enough I
gotta find some write down what I take
you'll get your money
can I do anything
yeah having carrots grow about
this is robbery not a robbery don't have
a charge account
[Music]
anymore now let's all get this rig out
that account wait for me
I was here generation did you get your
money and you'll get it
gun
[Music]
Stone telling you I don't want to get
mixed up in any killing
he broke into your story of me because
should I nobody's gonna kill him
minor he's a friend of mine that's over
to the hotel but what they didn't want
that delivers well I like to see cars
run
what did tonight what you gonna do with
him let's wrap up a little slow down for
this and I still don't want any party
and get out
the second self advocate would have
saved us both just
[Music]
I don't do it
first dozen
that's what I'm not gonna forget who
didn't you ever learn to do this and all
your life in the ranch and a lot of both
are thank you for getting me out of it
that's why don't you do it
wondered what it'd be like the gotta
ride are
educated and jobs without to be grateful
for that you might have something to do
with me you needed help needed help
before nobody ever David
in love with Kelly marry someone
no I didn't cookie I don't want to stake
my claim on range has already taken
because
[Music]
looking to date a bunch of that we've
got it on the other night they hit the
trail before sunup this morning
everybody to 10 miles of the valley you
figure I can get him over to the
yellowstone in a week
it's gotten pretty fine but he's pushing
them I think they will
yes we're going to be writing
[Music]
[Applause]
that you turned out to be the biggest
beef BBQ ever seen in Montana territory
don't over much of the fact that you
helped cook it like I want to get Hans
water but I guess it's already think we
found today I'm gonna get about 15 miles
good but they got a few more with you
got a couple hours of daylight left
we've been on the road full dark this
morning the cruise gotta sleep sometime
why don't we get down here you can sleep
when we get the yellow get a movie one
thing you've got to learn to impress a
man just so far is still got an arm in a
sling
let me worry about that I just thought
I'd mention all right on ahead and pick
out a plot for camp
[Music]
that's why that whole valley anybody
like a runaway train i was wondering on
helpful would take up a lot of things
[Music]
not walking down around
thanks
can you do that for himself
I thought they could spot let them do it
then and you trying to tell me what to
do I don't watching you too
I don't like what I see maybe you better
stop looking
are you following the Kittridge I'm not
falling for anybody and that goes for
you too
looks to me like you'd unlock your girl
I don't know about the rest of you but
personally I'm pulling out in the
morning looks for a while we might get
up a now we don't stand a Chinaman's
chance of it you'll get your money curly
just get those cows moving at sunrise in
the morning
where are we going to move them to the
Yellowstone you can't drive cattle over
that burn ground
don't suffocate inside a miles I don't
tend to try and take them over those
mouth
I've heard that country it can't be done
have you ever tried know and you've got
a new experience community not to me
and get out of camp
I'll leave when I'm ready to leave right
now and recognize a choice on making
myself only course you've got it how
you'll go to the riding on a horse a
feet-first have been twirling a pretty
big little better since you came here
maybe it's time somebody took the slack
out of your rope
anytime you're ready
wouldn't want a man with a bad huh
the time stopping
the rest of you think you can make it
all that moment believe mouth speaking
for myself I was to get high altitude
was health given that
[Music]
that's the best you can do you think
clearly didn't call your bluff
I never worried about terms what are you
practicing for hotel for died kill him
if he made any more trouble fun that
will get your ranch back your apartment
and get any pleasure out of it
you're not the first man has lost
anything to add lots of branched you in
the turn of a card that he didn't yell
and he said his luck advantage
yeah he was playing with the joker in
the deck
I don't know what you need you figure
didn't get the land back after i get to
save your life but maybe you better go
ask dad never welshed on the back his
life he once told me he never left
[Music]
get that wagon out there i right
get that product
what do you want me to don't take it
hard to carry about 55 feet ready to get
a rope on it I stick my
[Music]
sometimes I can't figure out why did you
quit this job is already stopped because
you like for to protect gal is working
photo we are going to finish you might
be it keeps talking as well- was
supposed to can't win property image am
reading it dirty so he could capture and
instead all away David i buy the drinks
next time a week tops
get ready to roll
[Music]
we don't have that arranged by tonight
why don't black on the other side reckon
it can't be any worse
we've already crossed him dressed like a
big on sheep's sick of stomachs
come on keep it rolling
[Music]
looks like it's gonna make it on time
doesn't always thought maybe he would
what happens to us I don't you fret
little everything's gonna work out fine
but why are you telling all this to me
it is my impression that you're working
for Kittredge i was working for until
two days ago I presumed you had a good
reason for it was good enough to stalk
me uh huh you know that country
currently what are his chances of taking
her through the hill the rest traveling
but should be done but it can be done
they will do it then I suggest you take
some steps to prevent it was afraid you
were gonna say something like that you
mind if i write out with you
yeah I mind if I like people shooting
from the front you'll need a guideline
you're doing a higher and let me just
tell me what I think
[Music]
the basis
yeah i'm gonna be an echeck getting
that's wagon down that Professor the man
tried one
ya well what what happened to him
nobody knows he's been heard from since
now I don't
better
get on the road you mean you really
expect me to drive this down that you
don't have anything with it
I look boss I don't mind going without
sleep and I don't put up with a wild
animals and rattlesnakes when it comes
to suicide
that's what I quit
[Music]
what do you think you're doing you can
try this out with a baton or break your
neck
my name is getting old Frank
[Music]
never let me do that again
I thought you quit but you might be
needing me what are you talking about
how I I thought curly and a tank Alfred
meant coming to the Gulf a couple of
fashion and I didn't waste any time
changing third it can't all those cattle
in here if they try to run them as a
black canyon up ahead little weight when
I'm in there got an idea
come on
[Music]
got your back pocket rocket get a fire
going to play a lot of fire for that
time he was done
alright make a moment yeah i remember
don't know jack about
[Music]
[Applause]
the last time boss rights movement on
the back
maybe I forgot invented like 30 minutes
much for coming about 40 miles out of
Alex and for surprised they get you you
can get those rocks
[Music]
fishing apparel it's too bad he was a
good friend of yours
come on let's get gone
[Music]
about a year don't worry about me just
get your baby to the railhead i'll be
there
here comes your way
you got a doctor in camp we've got a man
it's called in a doctor I decided drag
thanks i get to death they can get all
be back to move
[Music]
sorry August coverage
I think you'll find our county of
reasons yours take your word for that
counts out of the art dr. pulling a
pleasure room if you alright different
days that sounds like all your trouble
girl could be the beginning you wanted
to running and in turn you own something
you've got trouble as part of
responsibility i'm not too sure I'll
anything still got time to get the
buildings to tell your notice that what
I mean Devon its character that you can
win property in a gammon I've heard of
it but he under back mat Lord first take
drunken fool i'm going to want that
answer your question part of it
everything all right find our tank
what's the other foot you could have had
carded me that night we cut for the
right maybe why did that's not hard to
explain once i figured i had nothing to
lose everything again never talked much
to fear that there was nobody around
giving competition might pick me up I
didn't do the figures i just sort of for
the merchandising the window with people
you've got a good tool and now son and a
good girl
are you going to do a thing that got up
and go to work hello somebody for this
as one that you don't have to face maybe
not the way you figured but you got a
price on my head
the year to become one hand he's after
but what would you do
taking new religion only I still think
you're a hot-headed young it is thanks
that's it at your deeds second-guess
what happened but I just back in the
right light now reader
I'll be back
we've got to get out of town Johnny you
know come looking for you
you want to see me run yeah that's sort
of a change and trouble is room enough
to running he's looking for me I want to
go to bed every night thinking this
might be the one when you finally
what do you want to see that would be a
lot of things you can leave the money
with me i'll give it them want to pay
this in person maybe you forget i'm
still working with toughest you don't
want to see you buddy real please don't
drive kit one-handed
it's still worth 2500 bucks to me out
before you hit the foot of the stairs
that case I'll make it easy
[Music]
I mean like that trying to cheat me out
of my bonus some people you just can't
trust i buy drinks
boys and gentlemen we have got it will
make it i guess it's where's Jenny I'm
glad they're at red I never did like to
shoot my friends
I think somebody's looking for
[Music]
and
come on get out take you long to get is
it because I'm you can have a need
recording will be busy
looks like things turned out just the
way you figure i'm satisfied
that's our country freak don't bother
I'll pie because
[Music]