This movie is dedicated to
all those who love baseball
"The Koshien Stadium Tournament. "
The dream of every
high school baseball player...
where they run
about the field furiously...
to seize a moment of honor...
as if their lives depended on it.
But have you heard of baseball...
where players risk their lives...
with blood, sweat and tears?
It's that dream again.
I should forget it.
It's over.
You hear?
The new student is really bad.
He keeps getting expelled.
Last time, he got expelled
on the same day he started.
They say
he killed a teacher.
No, he killed
his parents.
Their bodies
were torn to pieces.
Some body parts
haven't been found yet.
Three years in prison.
He got out of prison.
- No, he hasn't...
-...been caught.
- Wanted...
-...nationwide.
So I hear.
Four Eyes!
G-G-Gori...
M-M-Matsui...
What are you doing?
Why couldn't
you catch that?
S-s-sorry.
Go for it.
- Koshien Stadium.
- Right.
Baseball's tough.
What was that?
BATTLEFIELD BASEBALL
Matsui Gorilla.
We have nothing to worry about,
as Iong as we have him.
Not just him.
Chikuwabu
can pitch 90 mph.
Itaro has a
.600 batting average.
Hayami steals bases
99% of the time.
I, Nantaro Asakura,
principal of Seido High,
now declare that...
Seido High
will make it...
to the Koshien Tournament
this year!
Principal Kocho!
Head Teacher,
what has happened?
We know the opponent
for the first game!
Oh, yeah? Who?
We have nothing to fear
with Matsui Gorilla.
But...
it's Gedo High School.
What!?
That can't be true.
They haven't competed
in years!
That must be wrong!
But...
Iook at this!
GEDO HIGH VICTORY IN USA
It's all over.
This summer...
it's over.
Everything is-
It's gone!
Gori, Gori!
Four Eyes!
Don't just stand there!
Go get it!
Yes!
I forgot,
this is the dropouts' hideout.
- Who the hell are you?
- Sorry, sorry.
Don't "sorry" me!
Did you see a ball?
What?
A ball?
You came to get it?
- Do you know where it is?
- What do you think?
That ball...
hit my teeth
and busted them.
How can I
pay you back?
Pay me $1,000 for damages,
asshole!
No, one million!
Bring me one billion!
I'm waiting!
Shut the fuck up!
I hate bullying!
Shit!
I can't even take
a nap...
without Iistening
to your fucking story.
Story? It wasn't true?
Shut up!
Do you know what you're saying?
I don't care
who the hell you are.
But you'II regret
fucking with us, because...
I don't care!
Stop!
It's the Bancho.
You're the new student.
Thanks for
taking care of my man.
I have to give you
something in return.
Guys, it's showtime.
It shall be done.
That's just
what I want!
I need it.
Incredible,
he's as ferocious as they say.
But he's not
just a punk.
I know it.
I don't need this.
I don't care.
Wait, we can sit
this year out.
We can go
for it next year.
We don't really need
to take on Gedo.
Principal Kocho!
There's trouble!
What happened?
Some punks are fighting!
Fighting?
They do that all the time.
Leave them alone.
But one of our players is
in the fight...
and if people find out,
the team will be suspended.
We won't be able
to play anymore.
What?!
Everyone's standing
in the way of my dream.
I won't Iet them!
It shall be done-
This is gonna be fun.
Tell me your name.
Baseball.
Jubeh the Baseball!
Baseball!
That's the word
I hate the most.
So what?
What I hate the most
is baseball!
Well, Jubeh,
this will be your Iast game.
Is that so?
Hey, hurry up already,
you bastards!
Scared? Want me to fight ya?
How about it?
Student rep, stop this!
No! This is a fight
between men.
The baseball team
will get in trouble!
But, they aren't
on the team.
Yeah - What?!
Head Teacher!
Who is he?
I've never seen him!
The new student
who is coming today.
What! He's the one?
Jubeh, you're almost
as good as they say.
Stop talking.
Let's start!
What are they doing?
PIaying baseball...
but more accurately,
"fighting baseball."
What!
Fighting baseball?
It's a strike.
Look,
tremendous Ieg power!
If he's a runner,
he could slide well.
A grounder to third base. It Iooks
Iike he doesn't have a chance.
But with his slide,
clouds of dust come up,
and the umpire calls it safe!
- Is that so.
- The second pitch.
Two strikes.
There's only one Ieft.
Did you see that,
Head Teacher?
- Yes.
- Great jumping power.
He could catch
any outfield ball.
A hit!
It's going, going, going-
Everyone thinks
it's a home run.
But he jumps, jumps
and jumps, and then it's out.
- Is that so.
- Watch them.
What?
What wonderful flexibility.
He's in the batter's box.
The pitcher throws.
It's about to hit him,
but he avoids it.
The ball approaches.
He Ieans and Iets it pass.
It will be amazing
if he joins the baseball team.
We might be able
to beat Gedo.
SCHOOL TRANSFER NOTICE
Goodbye.
I can't Iet him go!
Wait, please wait!
Who are you?
I'm the principal
of Seido High...
and head coach
of the baseball team.
I don't care
about suspension or expulsion.
It's not that.
I saw your fantastic plays.
I've never seen such skill.
I'm impressed!
Impressed?
PIease join
our baseball team...
and take me
to Koshien Stadium!
Koshien Stadium?
Why are you
telling me that?
Tell your team that!
That won't work.
They're no match
for Gedo Baseball.
Gedo Baseball?
What's that?
Gedo Baseball
is baseball...
with no rules,
and it's outside the Iaw.
No rules!?
Police can't do anything
about what happens.
I'll never forget
when we played them.
The scum had free reign,
and we got pummeled.
For them, Koshien's
a playground to kill Iegally.
I didn't know
there was such scum.
You couldn't help it.
Even baseball freaks
Iike me didn't know...
until we actually
had a game with them.
Who are these scum?
They're Gedo High School!
Gedo High School!
PIease!
Only your fighting baseball...
can beat Gedo High.
Before we have
more victims,
beat them up.
Jubeh,
please say something!
It's not
my fucking business.
Don't say that, Jubeh.
If you play,
you know you can play well.
If my eyes don't fail me,
you've played baseball before!
Even so,
I'II never play again.
I made a vow.
You vowed-
Sorry.
I'm through with baseball.
Who is that?
Who are you?
Give me your name!
It's me!
So? Who-
Whoa, it's Bancho!
Yeah, that's right!
Bancho, your face
has changed!
I changed my mind.
Of course, I changed my face too.
But, are you okay?
You were badly beaten.
I'm fine.
I owe Jubeh.
What?
I don't understand.
I Ioved baseball
when I was a boy.
But I ruined my shoulder
and quit.
The body blows stimulated
my sore spot...
and cured my shoulder.
Jubeh cured me,
so I can face
my enemies again.
Is that so?
You did it, Jubeh.
I didn't know.
Jubeh,
play baseball with me.
I know that...
your heart desires
to play baseball.
Sorry, I gave up baseball
for a better reason than you.
'Bye.
That's what he said...
but he was really itching
to get a chance to play again.
Bancho's words...
kept going
through his head...
over and over.
I got the ball.
Jubeh,
I, too, beg you.
PIease play with us.
Principal Kocho
asked you to.
No, it's my request.
But...
I can't even stay
in this school.
I tore up
the school transfer notice.
If that's the problem,
will this suffice?
You did this?
Yes.
Jubeh,
why'd you give up the game?
It's the story
of a boy
and baseball
The young boy
loved baseball
And pitched
From dawn to dusk
By the time
he entered junior high
No one could catch
his pitches
The pitcher
who threw too fast
Was hated and left alone
by everyone
To console
the poor boy
His father
played catch with him
Though he never
played ball before
With joy,
the boy pitched.
Whirling around and around,
he pitched.
Father died
The boy's pitch
was too fast
And that's
the story of a boy
and baseball
The pitch
you threw killed him?
Yes.
Without my knowing it,
my pitching
had exceeded all Iimitations.
I don't remember
how I did it.
I tried very hard
to forget...
and now
I don't remember it.
So that's what
happened to you.
After that,
I Ieft home...
and changed
schools constantly.
Jubeh,
you really want to play baseball,
don't you?
You pretend you're bad
to hide your feelings?
You don't understand!
- I'm the same way.
- You too?
My mother doesn't
Iet me play ball.
She hates baseball and will kill me
if she catches me playing.
So, I'm playing
behind her back.
We're the opposite!
Love of baseball!
Love of baseball...
I don't have a talent
for baseball Iike you.
But I have
the same feeling!
The same feeling...
Four Eyes!
Now I've got it!
I couldn't face myself.
I was a coward.
Jubeh.
Four Eyes.
Ten minutes later...
Jubeh decided to join
Seido High's baseball team.
- Four Eyes!
- Jubeh!
I Iove you!
Four Eyes!
I'm home.
Didn't you hear
something?
It was
a bouncing ball.
Are you imagining things,
Mother?
Strange, there shouldn't be
any balls in our house.
You!
Do you play baseball?
Of course not!
I know how much you hate it.
Hmm. Okay, then.
If you're playing baseball,
you'II be sorry.
If you even join
a baseball team,
you're dead!
Now it's ten minutes
before the preliminary game.
Gorilla isn't here yet.
Hey, what're you doing?
Time to play ball!
PRELIMINARY GAME
BASEBALLSTADIUM, FRONT GATE
He's not here.
What happened?
The game'II start soon.
Jubeh isn't here yet-
Strange.
Something must have happened.
They couldn't find Jubeh...
because...
he was locked away
in prison.
Kocho!
I've heard everything
from the Head Teacher!
You're sidelining
us Seido High players...
and Ietting
amateurs play!
Gorilla!
Leave it to the baseball
warriors this time.
Baseball warriors?
Where are they?
Well, they aren't here yet.
What?
They got scared
and ran away.
I can't rely
on such cowards.
We'II play the game.
No, you can't win
at Gedo Baseball!
You'II all get killed!
What!?
Kocho,
what's our goal?
Go for...
Koshien Stadium.
Yes.
You're telling us to give up.
I can't Iet you do that!
Kocho! I'II go to the back gate
and check again.
Jubeh!
Where on earth is he?
Whoa!
You son of a bitch!
What are you doing?
You Seido loser!
Your poor mommy and daddy-
You're going to be
the first sacrifice.
Hoichi.
Head Coach.
Told you not to kill
outside the stadium.
I'm sorry.
Don't make me
say it again.
We apologize.
AII our players...
have very short tempers!
You! Don't forget!
Oh, finally, here we go.
Let's go, Gorilla!
Gori! I'm here!
What's so funny?
Stop talking.
Umpire,
their attitude isn't appropriate.
You're outta there!
Why? For such
a Iittle thing?
You used violence.
Please wait.
He's right.
Please reverse your decision.
No, I can't do that
as an umpire.
Reverse it now!
Hurry up, you bastard!
Gorilla,
you can stay on.
Thank you.
If you left...
I couldn't kill you legally.
Get ready, Gorilla.
Let's hear it for Gorilla!
Hooray, Gorilla!
Gorilla, you're so cool!
PIay ball.
Kocho!
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
Did you find Jubeh?
No, I can't find him.
He might've run away.
No! He'd never do such a thing.
Right, Bancho?
Yes!
Four Eyes!
You all right?
Those scary guys
just came.
Where are Gorilla
and the others?
If they play,
they'II be in danger.
What's that sound?
Get inside!
Yes!
Look!
Gorilla! Hey!
Can you hear me?
Kocho-
They all-
Aaargghhh!
I had no idea
they'd be so violent.
Four Eyes...
I Ieave the Seido Team to you.
I'm counting on you-
Matsui!
Go for...
Koshien Stadium.
Gorilla!
What a moving scene.
Bravo!
Look what you've done!
Don't accuse us
of something we didn't do.
You make it sound
Iike we killed them.
Didn't you?
We just played baseball.
They died on their own.
Damn you!
This would not have happened
if it was a normal game!
No, it would have.
Right, umpire?
Yes, you're right.
That's not true!
How did nine players die?
Gedo played as usual.
They never broke the rules.
Be reasonable, Seido.
If we cheated,
we wouldn't be here.
We'd have been removed
from the game.
Damn you!
Your fault for sending in
such spineless players.
Kocho, it's no use
to say anything!
He's at the beck and call of Gedo.
Hey, you!
Wait, Bancho!
I understand.
I want revenge, too.
But, we have no chance
against these guys.
Right.
As principal,
I have to protect everyone.
Umpire!
We give up.
What? I can't hear you.
Seido High is
forfeiting the game!
Overruled!
Damn!
Just as I thought!
AII right! Change!
Yes. Change!
It's a change.
There's been
a change of players.
Let's go, Seido!
Here we go again.
Sorry, I'm powerless.
It's not your fault.
We'II hold them...
until Jubeh comes.
AII right!
Let's do it!
Yes!
I'II also play.
Head Teacher!
I've been Head Teacher
for 25 years!
I'm always ready
to sacrifice myself for Seido!
That's so, thank you.
Kocho, me too.
Don't try too hard.
You hide yourself here.
Kocho-
This isn't baseball!
Help us, Jubeh!
Jubeh!
Ten minutes before,
Jubeh succeeded in escaping
from prison as planned.
What is this?
Bancho! Bancho!
Jubeh.
You're too Iate.
Gedo was tougher
than we expected.
Bancho! Bancho!
Jubeh.
Kocho?
Kocho!
It was foolish of me...
to take on Gedo.
It's my fault.
Because of me, everyone was-
Four Eyes!
What happened to him?
Four Eyes-
Four Eyes!
Four Eyes, Four Eyes.
Something's stuck
through you.
Jubeh!
You finally came, Jubeh.
Damn!
Whoa!
Jubeh!
Dad.
Jubeh, it's too early
for you to be here.
Where am I?
Go back.
And throw that magic pitch.
Magic pitch?
Wait a sec!
It happened accidentally.
Go back.
But I swore
I would never pitch again.
People need
that magic pitch.
Do it for them,
not for yourself.
But-
It killed me,
but I'm asking you!
Dad, wait!
How can I, Dad?
I don't remember
how I did it!
You can do it,
but don't forget...
you're not alone.
Dad! Wait! Dad!
Principal Kocho,
Jubeh is here.
Jubeh, he's been Iike this
since we Iost the game.
Kocho? Jubeh's here!
He came back alive!
Jubeh?
I've heard
that name before.
Kocho,
don't act senile.
Student rep,
show him!
GEDO HIGH VICTORIOUS.
MAJORS NEXT?
Kocho,
won't you do anything?
Jubeh,
what can you do?
It was a total defeat.
That's reality.
Even you
were powerless.
Is that
what you really wanted?
What happened
to your spirit?
You Iose one time,
so you're giving up?
But Jubeh,
the Tournament-
That has nothing
to do with it!
We'II hit them!
This is war!
War...
If they enter the Majors,
there'II be more victims!
If we Ieave them,
Gedo will conquer Japan,
and the world too.
It's not just our problem.
These are the players
who got thrashed by Gedo.
PIease, Seido,
fight them so there are
no more victims Iike us.
AII right!
We'II do it!
For them too!
But Jubeh,
can we win?
Yes! With the deadly bullet pitch,
we can win!
The ball! The deadly bullet
that killed my dad!
What! You were hiding
a pitch Iike that?
No, I just don't remember...
but my dad told me to throw it,
when I was dead ten minutes ago.
Really.
Let's start. Kocho,
help us and Four Eyes!
Actually,
Four Eyes
can't play anymore.
What?
You played baseball
without telling me.
You disobeyed me.
Mother, what are you
going to do to me?
Anything I want!
As a punishment
for not Iistening,
you'II Iive forever
in this cage.
Or,
you'II wait
for the help...
of a savior,
for instance...
with Iong hair
and a dirty uniform.
Four Eyes!
Are you okay?
Jubeh.
Who are you?
Coming in Iike that!
His teammate!
What?
You're the one
who got him into baseball!
Jubeh called me a teammate.
Listen here,
you old bat!
I won't Iet you keep him
from playing baseball.
I'II never Iet him hit
another baseball while I'm alive.
Whoa!
- You're dead!
- OId bat!
Jubeh special!
Jubeh!
You're right.
She is your mother after all.
You beat me. You are good, boy.
You, too, old girl.
But tell me one thing.
Why do you hate baseball?
I want to know too! Why, Mother?
AII right.
I didn't tell you,
but there was a sad accident.
An accident?
Long ago I was
with my dear husband,
named Hirohi,
and our two sons.
The oldest son
Ioved baseball.
Hiroshi played catch
with him.
But, my son's pitch...
accidentally killed Hiroshi.
He was traumatized
and went missing.
Since then,
I've hated baseball.
Is it me!?
What? Then, you're...
my missing son,
Jubeh?
This means
Jubeh's my brother!
Ah, it's true.
Who is this?
Don't tease.
It's me.
I was cute
when I was young.
Mommy!
Mother!
I'II never Iet you go.
Because of me-
It's my fault that Dad-
Jubeh's my brother!
Jubeh!
My Four Eyes!
You can play ball.
Yeah!
His pitch killed Hiroshi.
The boy was admired
by his father
With joy the boy whirled
around and around
He spun around
and pitched
The ball gained speed
and went right through his father
Oh, yeah, I remember.
Spin around!
Oh, that windup!
That's Thal's Nomo's
major Ieague pitch.
He's winding up!
It's no mere Tornado Pitch!
Yes! Let's call it
the Super Tornado Pitch!
I just named it!
Super Tornado!
Mama!
Oh, no!
The ball will-
Who are you?
Who stopped my Super Tornado?
Tell me your name!
It's me!
So, who...
Whoa! Bancho!
That's right!
You're alive!
And his face
has changed again.
I died, all right.
But I've been
reborn again.
Of course,
my face has changed too!
You've been
reborn again?
I heard everything
while I was dead.
It's now time
to get even with Gedo!
Okay, we've both died once.
Let's do it!
Yes!
How nice
to see this again!
What is this?
Ah, I got it
in the other world.
Other world.
A stranger stopped me and said
it was too early to die.
He gave this to me.
This is the super mitt
my dad was using!
This can catch
my Super Tornado.
So it was
your father, right?
GOOD LUCK, JUBEH
FROM DAD
Dad!
I'II do my best!
This is Gedo High,
a paradise with flowers and greenery.
They were easy,
weren't they?
We wanna fight
someone tougher.
Someone who is
tough enough...
to attack
our invincible Hell Island.
Who is that!
What?
I thought you were dead!
I was!
But I came back to Iife.
To send you
to the real Hell!
Shut up! It makes no difference
if you've come back!
He could be right.
Let's go, Jubeh!
Let's go!
Let's go, Jubeh! Let's go!
Go, go! Hey!
Hope you both die!
PIay ball.
There's only one enemy!
Finish him!
Not just one!
You!
We're five!
Still only five!
Poor you.
With no strong help!
I'm here, too.
Gorilla! You're alive!
Thanks
to advanced technology.
I'm a robo Gorilla!
There are six of us!
I'm here, too!
Head Teacher!
You're alive!
Yes! I've returned as a cyborg
thanks to advanced technology.
There are seven of us!
I'II fight, too!
What?
Who are you?
I'm Chabane.
Go! Go! Chabane.
There are eight of us!
Four Eyes. I'm here, too.
We're nine!
Here we are,
the nine Seido players!
You're wasting my time!
Your numbers don't matter!
These are the rules
of Battlefield Stadium.
There are no rules.
Just kill each other!
Fight.
Kill them!
Gedo, 6 points!
Okay, I got it!
Everyone, get ready!
Seido, 3 points!
Two points.
Seido, 7 points!
Excuse me.
Gedo, 1 2...
1 4 points!
Are you okay?
Hey, I'II kill you!
Chabane, Chabane!
- Chabane!
- Gorilla!
Go! Go! Chabane!
Fight, you bastards!
Kill each other! Ha!
Ah, they're flying!
It's tied.
Bullshit! I'm pissed!
I'II kill you!
For the sake
of all future baseball players...
I'II kill you!
Get ready!
Die, asshole!
Jubeh's is number 1.
The Gedo coach is
on his own.
one on one.
It means...
this battle will
decide the winner!
Kocho!
Jubeh!
I'II finish you!
Jubeh.
You're really hurt.
You fought for us.
He's not human.
Jubeh.
Jubeh, you fought well.
I'm impressed!
You're the first one
to give me a good fight.
To show my gratitude,
Iet me unveil a new bat to you.
I completed it Iast night.
Mechanic!
Bring it here!
Yes!
Ha ha, this is it.
This is brand new!
Whoa!
This is Gedo High's new weapon,
the poisoned bat named "Poison Bat."
Whoa!
It has poisons in it
from all over the world.
And there are many different
kinds of medicinal herbs, too.
What do you think will happen?
You won't die!
The pain is
completely unbearable.
But you can't die
for 1 00 years!
For 1 00 years.
- A Iiving hell.
- That's right!
Gedo's science team developed it
with their expertise.
It was hard
to perfectly balance the mixture.
Ah? It doesn't hurt.
What! Why is that?
The kid!
I didn't know!
Four Eyes!
Jubeh.
I helped you, didn't I?
My brother!
Don't worry about me.
Live your Iife...
Shit! The kid interfered!
This poison was specially
created to kill the hero.
Shit, I can't take it!
How dare you kill...
my brother...
I'II send you...
to hell!
The Jubeh...
Special!
Nice ball.
Son of a bitch!
My Gedo baseball team...
was defeated
by just one student...
with Iong hair
and a dirty uniform.
Just one student?
You still don't understand
why you were defeated?
You never will because
you treat your players Iike shit.
Shut up!
What's wrong with that?
In baseball,
you can never win on your own!
The most important thing is
the teamwork, the friendship!
Friendship gave me power!
You Iost 'cause you got drunk on
victory and never valued friendship.
Idiot!
Friendship...
Effort...
Victory...
I've Iost.
Completely.
Kill me.
Pay for your sins
in Hell.
You fucker!
Wait, please!
What the hell-
Don't kill our coach!
Why are you
defending him?
He treated you Iike shit.
Even so,
we were happy!
You idiots.
We were abandoned
before we met the coach.
Abandoned?
We were abandoned
by our mothers...
and sent
from one orphanage to another.
We'd never been used
for anything!
At Ieast he used us!
He had us work
as his slaves!
So, please save his Iife!
We're his fans.
Okay, I'II Iet you go.
You all-
Jubeh, thank you.
I was wrong.
Goodbye.
Jubeh!
ANTIDOTE FOR FOUR EYES
What have you done?
One should never betray
one's companions!
I'll take the coach's place!
I'll die believing
that friendship is useless.
You've got it
all wrong.
I've never felt anger
Iike this!
Shut up, asshole!
The game is over!
Sayonara!
Chiyotato, Chietaro.
I told you not to come.
Kocho, is this
the reward for victory?
Many innocent people died
because of us.
I killed them!
Because I...
played baseball,
they Iost
their precious Iives!
Jubeh...
It's a miracle!
Jubeh's tear
made it happen!
Game over!
Jubeh is the winner!
Everybody Iisten!
Let's toss Principal Kocho!
The toss up.
An honor reserved
only for victors...
and what
all players long for.
Principal Kocho
was overcome with joy...
as the players kept tossing him
as long as they could.
And they knew...
that the love of baseball
goes beyond good and evil.
But they didn 't know...
this man watching
the game died...
1 0 minutes earlier.
He died of alcoholism.
His name was
Taizo Nakamura.
He was my master.
Take a look
at the smile on his face.
Do you think
you could die as happy?