hey over there Sam they're going yet
taco
entire Kiwanis Club is dead
hey no right he's kickin ass can't hold
it against such a talented fighter
especially since you have the hot form
you doing Hey look over there there's
your rival fucking not even a thief
instead of class he's also one is
clogged jealous he's cooking all the
time top of that he's charming and she's
got a positive attitude on the other
hand look at you that's this rate she's
going to beat you up is that what you
want when I see Ricky face-to-face never
know what to say well all I can do is
walking from the distance Justin Baba if
you please sure but it's still not too
late to change your mind think about it
what will you do instead of aiming for
the number one ranking in karate I want
to be the best fighter in the entire
world oh my how glorious cocky aren't we
you never know until you try captain
you're fast yodel hey you dodged my
chicken Sookie punch I've never seen
that move before you're a skillful fire
captain I see you're keeping your
distance to conserve strength and figure
out my weak points but it's of no use I
won't let anyone stand in my way after I
finished with you my study of
conventional techniques will continue
yeah
captain what ah
oh hey Rio what's up look who's talking
whatever you eat huh oh you mean about
before I had to prove to myself that I
was really good enough to move on don't
ever tell me anything like that why so
sudden I like I don't know why exactly i
just felt like fighting a thought what's
not supposed to mean maybe do you know
what you're doing Oh buzz off no I won't
father said he's gonna resign because
you beat him now what will happen to our
club then I don't care are you talking
about it's all your fault baba said that
I had to knock out the entire Club in
order to quit so that's exactly what I
did besides I had to quit this club in
order to compete with guides from the
other Club get it hey Giri you're only
thinking about yourself and what about
the need next month just about you we're
screwed I haven't been doing karate all
of this time just for the good of the
damn Club and I wasn't competing for the
good of a school either that's right
away from me I'm talking to you a second
a 30 see you later bye
[Music]
Lord Bureau the dimensional gate has
been opened and the legend foretells
when the gate is open the method headed
warrior will appear and face a being of
the dark world at that time the
legendary warrior shall be born ip ever
made i have felt my house rating and i
believe to be apart with probably I
perhaps it is being transmuted into the
power of fate the power that will
produce the legendary warrior or perhaps
is already taking some form in another
dimension if not perhaps your majesty
perhaps it is the work of the sudden a
flocculent of your Majesty's power but
why would anyone wish such a thing
[Music]
I care not that I let you make a little
bit higher
nice to fight haha okay glad so again
those homework pages for tomorrow we're
79 80 for huh what's wrong yo Ricky
you're trolling the time to fight has
come dreaming blah dan yo I'm not
through with you yet bow thank you
everyone that is all goodbye I'm going
to go buy some device what do you think
hey could give them my usual you guys
mr. Giotto there's a faculty meeting
this afternoon to discuss the mess you
caused yesterday and now you fall asleep
in my class in even mumble and drool did
you know the karate club captain vava is
now residing and the trouble Beiser is
not very happy either it possible this
could get you held back
Ricky thinks about nothing but couldn't
supplements spotlight you be the entire
karate club yes signor you are that
strong talking about guys you mean you
don't know nope the only big the entire
karate club beat them all just so he
could quit wanted you to wear a leopard
man to get attention besides I found it
in my house and thought of cruel so this
on I'll be the number one fighter on
earth captain baba please reconsider for
the sake of the club thanks but I won't
change my mind I just handed in my
resignation you see I wasn't strong
enough then he was all Ricky fault no it
was all mine Oh captain Baba sorry if I
sound a little selfish here you go they
didn't have meat pies today so i brought
cutlets and egg sandwiches instead
thanks dude and so i'll wear my mask
like a gorilla soldier and keep the hell
out of the other school and then the
media picks up on the story and I'll be
in the newspapers and TV and everything
I'll get on the nerves of those Pro
fighters with big egos they challenge me
I kick their butts one by one well quite
celebrity for more class that's awesome
man hey if you'd like you can have this
huh you sure I mean it's a future
celebrity has my lunch now when you
become a real celebrity I can brag about
it in the neighborhood oh yeah thanks
man here
oh thank you everybody thought oh my huh
Rio you to you gotta learn more me oh
you are my autograph well what are you
so happy about baba resigned from the
club you know
[Applause]
[Music]
Master violo underestimate them
they are nothing a pitiful fool what 23
I Oh why'd you do that hey die oh I hit
my head too hard or the heck cool he huh
huh huh a classroom it happen to the
hallway I did hit my head hard
weird I didn't know he had a classroom
like this yes when's Bea you dear
another my room many veterans one hotel
detail that when a gauge of light is
open a leopard headed warrior will
appear there in the other world of his
battle will be fought but before the
vigor can cover the two world he becomes
a level-headed warrior who might not
face the time that has been with home
haha fuck that yeah I'll kick your ass
come out and fight dark realm you too
many of them huh I do not sure of the
dark well you're the King I saw in my
dream I thought it was only a matter of
defeating you but there is one thing I
must confirm
not anything else you want to show me
Justin I'm home yet withal a diabolical
trap Rahman we might come on who cannot
hollering my relentless increase in
power whatever you say fruitcake stop
mumbling and get on with it what's next
gentlemen raise your left oh and then
what ah shit you think you're funny you
asshole no you paralyzed me now and what
a legend today huh don't you realize
that you are another part of me a part
30 pitch in this world you are my
counterpart oh shit this guy's a total
nutcase hey that's all very interesting
but it doesn't have anything to do with
me so um maybe we could continue this
chat a bit later
you think imma nothing you want to run
away what a pitiful fool you are so you
can read my mind too hey come back here
where I can see you returns where the
law what do you think you're doing
something you made me hit my head I was
dreaming after all you've got a long way
to go the whole way hmm what's wrong
it's Baba it is Captain bhava here I've
got apologize about the network we were
getting better don't you see it's all
your fault we didn't hear me captain
baja x0 2010 fo 4513 subject has changed
position by point Delta have you
completed calculating the total energy
level it's being redone since the
previously computed value was in
finished my guess is that a space-time
continuum distortion has adversely
affected our system calibration wouldn't
that be why we're getting an incident
reading in infinite energy reading and
an antimatter note this is definitely a
major temporal violation
there's been a while since we've dealt
with a major case ah dad can there's a
body of energy quickly approaching point
x0 it's a beard out of nowhere and it's
unlike the one we detected earlier it's
a hyper psychokinetic way what's the
location you're a bikini that's
dangerous I'd better go check it out
which one can tell matt or not please be
careful yeah well I'll be damned it
doesn't look like an antimatter beam the
other one the psychokinetic wave
activity is amazing and you really can't
judge a book by it's cover ah no I
couldn't have not from that far away not
with the jammer activated have they
started from now on the gangs in this
territory will answer to me sailu what
does the fucking joke don't make us
laugh fighting him would be sport 815 so
what are you gonna do about it huh come
on you little punk yeah dead man at all
I thought you wanted a bike not show me
your toy
yeah this is it how do you like my toy
now asshole it's a toy I can't finish me
toys ladies who the fuck are you one who
by exterminating creatures like you
tries to perfect his skills that is who
I am exterminate me what are you a demon
master a demon master do they even exist
you don't know I see are you going to
hurt me with that little stick you are
all mine to the power there is nowhere
to run
Oh
[Music]
would play w Stephen the old age
what's the matter hahaha italy the girl
may die but i have known i never dreamed
creatures existed that could transform
humans like this
so you're still alive
hold it
[Music]
it's no use you can't run away from me
there you are a fairy so the man and the
cat were controlled by you that school
has to be now this is getting
interesting
that must be him either he's very
inexperienced for his power is so great
he's barely able to contain it hmm he
come feeling lucky are you that even
after of this world wanna try me one
we'll meet again
the budget will move to good reference
203 one and two talk about a small hill
clear kilometers to the gaana keep him
under surveillance and I'll switch over
to our secondary subject the crowd was
clearly following the primary subject
this is no trivial matter I'll keep tabs
on them you analyzed the data for me he
must be in there so you've got monster
there's no escape this time
[Music]
reveal yourself hold it all at all
though I was only trying to kick a
pebble but then I met them I take the
car instead liya possible can you read
my mind take me yourself enough of your
game scholars are nothing like those of
the first creature
your attempt at intimidation are almost
entertaining well I'm certainly glad
that someone out there enjoys them who
can't be happening popping out of the
wounds now that's impressive a most
unique maneuver on your part your powers
are nothing like those of the first now
wait a minute listen I have nothing to
say to you monster listen to me before
you attack no it's impossible we can
still fight after I'm done talking to
you I am through dark realm I arrived on
this world in hopes of making a roughly
come through however I fell into a trap
laid by one of my power is that
justification for projecting innocent
people transforming them into monsters
wait this body is that a wiki Jojo my
counterpart in this world into all my
powers are contained because of the
track we have merged into one body but
my own really being a brat by your
counterpart exactly you see the monsters
who encounter today were the very master
and her minion and permeated I am here
to destroy every
yeah they are using that left alone take
a look at it they have characteristics
similar result of what vertically invade
others living organism been hot for new
brain brain disease feel awkward they
read my coaches you see 11 love Meryl he
know it time it took me to vanquish 130
more have appeared there'll be no
intuitive that certain they are the
fruit nettles who preyed on people's
weaknesses gruesome maggot their master
wants my father or whatever revolt
against me this world teams with praise
and become Hooper ferried if we don't
remember them now the calling thread is
will overcome their and you won't enjoy
indeed that is why I'll Michael Cole
argue until thumb with her head are we
agreed fine I'll do some people told
until the ferry cabal been destroyed I'm
kosher meat so Yuki people call me a
Demon Slayer
you
mega Lord from another universe and
demonic offense there's going to be a
challenge what's up girl calm person
above all kannada bottoms are coated
moving the bottle of those 13 kilometers
current position
leaky my Ricky shooting star star light
star bright first star I see tonight you
know right which is really did come true
this would be easy and the cocky minami
wasn't around oh this isn't easy is it
button I will always love Ricky Kyoto
Wow
and
Oh Harry I can make your wishes come
true let me
[Music]
someone's following me come behind
behind the trees they won't give it some
kind of pervert well hey show yourself
what a teddy bear this is unbearably
weird Oh scare me like that case first
your leopard now you're a bear it is you
isn't it
ladies have to be careful with walking
alone not bad breath shut down
yeah the bear is only a virtual agent
breathing realizes little duster alcohol
3y it's country is derived Rochelle
sorry I'm sorry i frightened you like
that are you okay I see ya glad allow me
thank you very much I mean Oh forgive me
my name is Zeng Ken I'm a space-time
continuum and for sir since yesterday
afternoon we've been monitoring a rash
of spatial distortions near your school
the stuffed bear we just saw may be a
side effect of those very distortions
there are a few questions I'd like to
ask you regarding that if I may huh
please allow me to escort you home that
way I can ask you the questions while we
walk okay sure buttons where did you go
hey butters I can't tell us if shit or
something you failed what's how about
i'm going to bed sweet dreams my darling
Ricky a six-foot-tall teddy bear and an
outer space detective that space
detective person inspector of so-and-so
add some things about you I've been
doing something to make them investigate
you do you have a fever or something or
maybe you just had a nightmare last
night you ready for the memory of last
night thank you saying something wow
that girl is fierce it's only third
period and she got it already Megumi you
don't look so good I'm all right oh hey
Joe knows someone from another school is
here to challenge you mmm I would wager
that the state detective in time to
investigate so where is he he's already
in the karate dojo waiting for you
gotcha I'll be right there yeah
freaky you must be Yoda and you are I'm
Zheng Ken as a person and as a warrior
will you accept a challenge you're here
is a person and a warrior a interesting
fine I'll accept anybody's challenge any
time hey Shoto what's up with you this
is a karate dojo take your shoes off
whoops almost forgot that knees on to I
know you forgot your leopard mask too I
don't need it huh you're not going to
use it yep how come quiet man just shop
and watch sorry to keep you waiting just
what brings you here I'm here to see
whether or not we can have a little
discussion
[Music]
my arms and legs need look as if he was
merely joshing was right body got real
pressure point what seems to be the
problem what are you doing now next
you'll probably didn't walk don't tell
me like it happening to someone else if
I can't move you're going to be feeling
the pain too if you fail to judge my
yeah looks like a draw yeah something
like that if there's something you
wanted to discuss talk to the man
himself I hope that they're still the
chance for a peaceful resolution want to
go up to the roof or someplace yeah I'd
like that if you don't mind
[Music]
I knew you'd come
I've been waiting for you confessing my
uncertainty the way it has paid off you
are surely a demon thats each other why
are you so uncertain you're the mighty
destroyer of being with me him and faro
hurricane you've made your move it is
usually only one remain but they're so
afraid of my powers that you must shower
within your barriers we share a common
vision feelings on silent I'm not so
naive at the fall for your petty tricks
reveal yourself Harry master whatever
you do you can't break these barriers my
name is kind demon master of the fairies
the demon master of the pherion I am
here in this world to assassinate to be
odo the whole distance Lord be odo not
satisfied with ruin the dark realm have
come to this world intending to ruin it
there's nobody on this planet strong
enough to interfere with whatever it is
that you are really capable of doing but
if you intend to include yourself in
this planet history then I am officially
obligated to do something about that I
shall become ruler of his world you my
colors we at any time you led me to
believe our duel would be delayed to a
later time as soon as you defeat this
fairy master whatever it is go back if
you don't return in peace you'll return
in pieces Jake Warner I suggest you
learn how
what is it you want to say if the elders
should become of this world then all
living souls will be forced to follow
his orders upon pain of death that is
undesirable well I propose we join
forces if we do then this world in the
dark realm will once again be at peace I
refuse if you cannot defeat me how can
you possibly the be spiritual how did
you break the barriers may where you get
from the very beginning even in a
consciousness he could be on the you may
need to see people otherwise betray me
thank you
why are you doing I'll let us merge and
are found in Cebu humor they gone no
there will be a school meeting during
the third and fourth period all
first-year and second-year students must
report to the gym all student council
members from each flat and class
officers are report to the council room
important are you doing right oh do you
think maybe you should skip the meeting
hey Ricky haha been actin weird it all
lately yep you're a complete pervert not
what I meant it's just that I don't know
if they're nothing kind of forgetful
these past couple of days hmm three
o'clock Hong Kong senator what is it a
good record wrong psychokinetic wave
activity the location was asking 0 5 on
5 0 3 124 just to intervenor from your
current location must be him
psychokinetic wave activity is very
unstable
I'd better go check it out then we're
going to Baylor up my second of Hyodo do
me a favor and take over for me and I
feel my my pops memories the more real
now o taki and Adi if your dough playing
hooky again if he doesn't go to that
meeting he is in big trouble shakti
Nagila do me a favor look for him I'll
go talk to the committee in the meantime
what's the rush where you going I see
that your psychokinetic wave activity is
unstable is there an emergency you have
to take care of law schools in session
I'd be very interested in knowing would
you mind telling me hold it right there
I have to verify something right now so
you're the one who's been following me
these last few days sorry but I must be
going you leave me no choice but to use
force
you intend to stop me I see that your
business must be very important in which
cases even language cannot let you go
even if it means a duel to the death in
a fact because it is you who will die is
about that now they're going at it
my my what a sight your folks are going
to cry when they see you what what you
thought being human and we can advise
you to stop being a lot
[Music]
for you you can't break those long
haven't you had enough the facts
obviously been possessed by the very
clever you can
just what I wanted to hear
[Music]
without solid evidence I cannot simply
destroy a suffering but thanks to your
confession i can fight you without
nervous very and sedation in that case
without mercy will destroy you you're
the one who will die I don't know what
your motives are about your powers like
this world stability as the space-time
continuum and father I cannot allow you
to proceed behold my true power each
other you're awake it's all right now
nothing to worry about okay thank you
thank you thank you I said it's okay I
always does thats also don't worry i
love you mean I've always been liking
you
[Music]
yo help me Wow cool it was he wouldn't
know hit this might be the mother of the
one who doesn't droid is the third scary
so with that acted lasted a little
longer bummer I'm killing you you can't
control me yo mr. narrator her
consciousness cotton to devour yet I
think it she loved me and rape you not
you the ones who loved his mane and I
can't fight anymore yeah I'll kill
[Music]
period and right cool alien stuff even
though you're just lumps of meat I'm not
finished with you
[Music]
what asking services of no use against
come on come and get me I'll tear you
apart this guy won't even obey the water
perfect what's the matter was that it
was that all your true power fine time
to get
[Music]
now the real work begins
for yes why bother Wyatt
[Music]
you've got some interesting move don't
worry she wouldn't welcome this and your
interests thanks for your consideration
[Music]
sorry
hm
[Music]
fall for the same trick again
nice fit it's obvious that you are
exhausted even in my dark realm the
reconstruction of life takes more energy
than anything else those guys must be
finished
[Applause]
who you have no one to blame but your
head I've taken too long here we were
just about to come looking for you Yuki
are true to draw that isn't like you at
all you look exhausted even so shall we
pick up out you where we left off
anytime you're ready foul
ah
[Music]
don't have the vault attack directly or
no Florida I'd appreciate it if you'd
tell me these things in advance what
with everything I did earlier on pooped
and please you make it sound like he's
already won you never told me it would
you like this the mold and the dog realm
fleeing I'm not from
[Music]
in coming to this world you've acquired
all manner of human weaknesses question
he's one of them
you should be ashamed of yourself I
both pumps in the lab were almost enough
to destroy you so much for the lord of
the dark realm if we get hit again we're
dead meat now what do we do
the hasley wounded I
he's coming for me
[Music]
only a matter of time
yoki you asshole fuck you yeah how could
you let the ferry master take you over
you got your soul as you repeated
yourself you wanna master now look at
porn will continue for slowly into you
until you die Oh paper the pain a
subject of the dark realm we had to
endure your torment and now is the build
oh lord of the dark realm the time of
our sweet vengeance is at hand
Oh
[Music]
you love your mind I only my bag the
paint from the court had rendered my
counterpart unconscious and now i am
control now as we use my powers in any
way i just start
[Music]
hmm
oh shit oh oh oh oh oh song you crawl
around any what was I supposed to be
doing down here vemia brah brah
[Music]
close it why do you want let
you know
Oh
you
[Music]