yeah
the smartest dumb band in the land
the Beastie Boys mix heavy blues smart
samples and the lowest common
denominator gut punches this new york
trail consists of Adam Horovitz or King
ad-rock as he is otherwise known adam
yauch AKA NCAA and Michael diamont
affectionately known as mike d the band
story started a long time ago way back
in the late nineteen seventies America
at the time was facing start of the home
and Reagan era as a new breed of
disillusion who was beginning to come of
age
this is the never told before story of
The Beastie Boys musical evolution
you
oh right sure what had you do what I do
bestie boys actually started life as two
separate bands that would eventually
evolve into one like DS band was a
full-piece group called the young
Aborigines who are young Aboriginal they
were Mike and John mean mainly the first
started out just as my concern
your theory is a full member of the
beastie boys from the original lineup
I played the time germany played bass
I played his drums after a while I got
the notion to introduce my two best
friends Mike and John and masterminded a
an introduction by buying ticket for Joe
Jackson and as soon as the first band
kicked into the in John start howling
like the main
I acted wildly jumping around and don't
forget it i just in his chair he didn't
stand up just bouncing down after their
set ended
John's bathroom and my company just
discussing let's discuss crazy don't you
get that
Jeremy told me that Mike but that I was
added my
and was wondering if there's anything
really seriously mentally wrong with me
I was like no no no he's cool he's cool
don't worry
good good guy and I've never been to a
concert before and so I'm act like that
before but obviously you know something
about the music and spent setting
something often and so after that though
might wind up and we sort of discovered
that we had the same interests and
both love the clash I came up with the
suggestion i said hey we want you guys
play together you know
and it was just a terrible terrible
combination is none of us knew how to
play but I mean we have a lot of
enthusiasm
let's say we were for lack of a better
word a jam band
it's terrible term but it's just been
whacking off basically
yeah
here we got a picture of the young
Aborigines and this is the only full
frame print I've got and got John Mike
and me at johns house you can see the
beer bottles lined up on the way
all there
some you know hubcap and in the back
here you can actually see a little bit
of Kate's kit kit kit was made up of
John's of a mikes old kit and this big
conga drum that John's father had and a
bunch of the missing Mike's kid is
pretty snazzy
I had some bootleg base and i think john
at gibson SG you can see there's like
the way of concealing food is just the
details it's all right there
yeah
and
the young in the useless were a hardcore
punk band they were a little bit younger
than pc boys you know
read more of its own guitar Arthur
africano and base David silken lead
singer and I was a drummer
The Young and the useless was Adam
Horovitz his band
Adam Tracy was the youngest of the group
can I met then I was still 12
and
type guess we probably rehearsed for a
month or something before we started
playing out and I may have turned 13 at
the time I don't have any new anybody
else to play the drums
maybe it's time we didn't rehearse a
whole lot anyway and i think my dad
bought me a drum set so that helped him
the enemies list played with us several
times i believe at this great club
called a 7 a-7 was another haven for
those hardcore kids most of us he should
have been probably in bed
snuck out of their houses because it was
a school night and it was is a great
place to play
yeah we put our first gig here and I was
so nervous are our sons were extremely
fast to begin with but i was so nervous
that I was playing like three times as
fast as everybody else
my sticks kept find out of my fit in
adelaide river Adam looking back at me
like i was adamant mine
he was like playing in your living with
a lot of drunk and scary children and
the young useless managed to blow
everyone away
I was actually in rehearsal studio with
my other band what band is going to
college and next door was young in the
useless and I mean we're getting a quick
look at them and then it seemed like
next thing I knew John Berry was out and
Adam horrible to me and i'm asking like
why and I just mostly have to do with
the John showing up late you know not
being on time for things i was a bad bad
boy and turning too much alcohol is in
rural experimenting leave the jack
kids out there stay away from the booze
bad stuff for you
terrible
yeah
the hardcore punk scene centered around
a small record shop in New York's east
village called rat cage records
well I'm number first time in that case
records in about nineteen eighty-one and
they were it was a little teen store
that was underground black aids was a
record store and then done
ninth street between second and third
avenues ill just about across the street
from the selca diner
the team just kind of a focus . a place
we could go to get the new records
you've got to sure to get badges you
know Dave Parsons was the owner
I mean Dave shops stay open till four in
the morning at least we just hang out
there and II just hang out i mean it was
sort of like a base camp
Dave Parsons came up to us and said a
this recorder record which we were
course completely
excited about he was really a big
believe in the music and he actually
started the recording people and started
his little rock a record label
we went to studio and
recorded BP
pollywog still the name they gave EP I
can't remember that there was some
reference some inside joke between the
four of them that led to that title
it was a great experience
a lot about actually trying to play the
recording a lot different than playing
for an audience and it turned out great
you know is it was a secret because it
was a great thing
all the songs on we're about stuff that
really happen most of this like a great
on mojo
I mean that was a real incident there
was a sign a mojo
he was a bouncer at the club and we
hated him because he would never let us
into the damn Club so we decided that
there was gonna be a great on mojo that
we looking at
literally you know the old halloween
trick and take a dozen eggs and throw
the matter
and now if this ever actually happened I
don't know I was not their provision
actual egg throwing it may have happened
but nonetheless these frustrations
turning to the song a great on mojo and
you know
next thing you know he was probably
bounced people out of the show that they
were playing people want to adam yauch
into the folds while at the same time
changing the name to the beastie boys
the Beasties were now an established
part of the New York hardcore scene even
managing to get gigs at the legendary
home of punk rock CBGB's
yeah
you know what is CBGB's everybody wants
to know everybody knows I don't have to
tell anybody with CBGB's doing
place where I think you know really
started
what they call punk rock to me hardcore
was like it came out of the punk rock
thing you know the Sex Pistols Ramones
and
it was faster than then punk rock it was
a lot of slam dancing it was very angry
we were sort of the younger brothers and
sisters of the pump
yeah
two guitars bass & Drums play really
fast
vocals are shouted you know it's a sore
back to 76 pump and the answer something
about hardcore at the time to clean 1982
in downtown New York was how immediate
and accessible it was you could sort of
go to CBGB's on a day of the Saturday
matinees on saturday and sunday would
have a matinee and that was the scene
pretty much everybody there was the
scene and you can talk to anybody and
they would never record out that was
locally distributed and and that was it
it was very immediate they would they
would like write a song recorded and and
make a record
hardcore well I call hardcore punk is
the the punk rock
yeah
the second time they recorded without me
this time and with adwords louis vuitton
they decided to record this thing called
cookie voice and Adam what's basically
crying called carvel ice cream
they have a cake called the cookie plus
it's an ice cream cake for birthdays and
the crank called the
store probably made someone's life
miserable and they put it all on tape
and it was bringing hilarious
no it's terrible to keep this is
terrible they can't play they had
absolutely no ability of sounding just
like the work hard core record in the
world
Chuck Klosterman was interviewed the
Beastie Boys on many occasions and they
remained in cookie puss and that became
like a white rat man you know they'll be
working in record stories and Danny
there's no way to defend successful is
table for the first rookie boost that's
the pack 3 is a hip-hop legend that has
known the Beastie Boys for many years I
was like this kind of weird record it's
out of more hip-hop that it did
alternative but they were always did
like i'll turn the band thing but it's
cool because i think it's cool red
respectively because people have you
know that they can see that the career
arc of this band and you know anytime
something become super popular become
disinterested like its board also
there's only so much underground secure
alternative man you never knew
that on acid one day cookie puts brought
him to the attention of another unlikely
rap fan a long head student at New York
University
they weren't really serious about music
and clearly they weren't serious because
when someone said days in your app and
they're like okay let's do that
suddenly they got asked to to play
places and play cookie puts well to do
that you really need the DJ rick rubin
was working on
this dorm room and nyu Adam took me over
there and
I met everything
I thought this is a guy who's
very serious about taking these guys
further and I remember when they came to
rick and ask him
will you will you DJ caise Rick had the
gear you gotta remember Rick had the two
turntables a mixer and the big sur 1
vega so he actually could DJ so suddenly
it was like they turn to direct and Rick
Rubin became DJ job loss is a double
lock and even had interest in becoming a
producer and you know and obviously like
he ended up becoming yeah
arguably like the most important
producer of the eighties but at the time
he was just this guy just I think that
the beastie boys are really but i did
not pee
man am I thought allowance they've
finally like they've got someone here
who really cares about them and once you
are you bring them to form
he was a very ambitious guy we all know
you would
he was making replicas dorm at NYU right
I mean that's the legends anyway
he was very into rap and hip-hop and I
mean when he heard them or saw them
something else is just click on that one
doesn't do this is it friend and former
roommates quick reading it was really
about the energy it was what it was what
Rick Rubin saw initially that there
really wasn't this wide gulf between
what punk was doing in its essence and
what rap was doing in its early essence
it was still it
the energy was still there and the and
the ability to just do something like
like this role and and angry
rap music was new it was underground
it was in the clubs and when you played
a rap record in a club or a party
he built the grandest emotional
everybody I remember the rules tell me
it's like yeah i got these parties to DJ
with with the Beastie Boys and was
quickly put the cookie puss with way
more successful than anything the
beastie boys or young useless or
whatever other bands they were had ever
done
so it's like you know it doesn't take
too much of a genius to figure well
that's that's a good road so they kept
going down that road and then Rick
Rubin's ideas kicked in
the one thing about rap music
you have to sing you can wrap to wrap
you can get a rhythm and you have the
right beat you can win
now you can talk to the beastie boys
they will tell you that like they always
grew up you know he you know intertwined
with african-american culture and it's
just part of you know their life
oh that's interesting because they all
went to like kind of really exclusive
expensive private schools like sometimes
wonder how many black kids that they
really knew growing up
sure with some but he'll York City rats
did give the beastie boys to consider
lot of credibility because I think a lot
of me in the black community
it felt like okay the beastie boys are
popular but there probably is popular
because white people already invited why
people like him
where you want to be wrapped around the
first time it was like black people
saying black people like you know these
guys
your life is white and they seem like
you know do whatever but they're
actually this is actually kind of music
you like
- so when they first walked on the stage
about rode your bike racks on the rack
on stage a white guy
how to earn his stripes and no one had
done that yet it's like if you want to
the Apollo and you were a comedian
the audience in the wrap and wrap at
that time we just like the audience
the black hole into the Apollo which a
wider audience sits there and goes ok
entertain me a black audience goes
what you got what you got sucker
basically because they want to be and
the page and you can put the fantasy
smudges for me is to you
and I think it probably seen maybe I
mean I yeah
white guys when I got out I always
wondered maybe in the black community if
the Beastie Boys almost seemed like a
novel
it was sort of like isn't it kind of
charming that these guys you know what
want to make the kind of music that we
invented
we walked over to me is I know your
backbone awful that is because the white
boys are there would be to it and I was
like wow that's just really presumptuous
of yourself and all those really
and when the Beasties first came on they
were not greeted with with widespread
upon approval but usually by the end of
their of their set
they would have won the Audience over
and they did that pretty quickly we did
a show in through Virginia and you had
five thousand little black girls
screaming howling try to make it 2-1
have a good time and and loving the guys
just generally because of they would be
real with what they were trying to say
they weren't trying to be last
we're trying to be the Beast keyboard
and it worked and translate the music
translated not the color
the reason why I Beastie Boys on it no
biggie they just make good records
DJ rather than is recognized and
respected worldwide as one of the
founding fathers of hip hop and now
playing in 86 it was a club called union
square and it was predominately black
and at that time there was to record
that was so popular one who's now hit it
and for we've it and to us it sounded
good we don't care what national I
wasn't just any good
we like what steps but it caught our
attention
sounding phone I'm just stuff that
sounds fucking like the beach with very
aggressive
so in hip-hop we always about the
aggressive means as far as stuff like
from Aerosmith stuff like from queen
stuff
billy squier ACDC so those kind of beats
what kind of similar to what they will
do with the alternative meet with the
big drums of the big powerful back has
introduced back and all that crazy
that's what we did just scratches so you
heard that it gives you good with that
think about that so we always use the
stick out like similar beat so it's kind
of like right there on the same thing
but I i was the commentary delivered
water sometimes being a black member of
a white group had its drawbacks
the time we want to perform over my
family apart and bought it was myself
and gonna be sitting inside you guys go
around the back because you know we
don't have black people
club right are you kidding
and they still have said you know they
can't come to we're not going to do
and of course such a big works is just
going to go ahead go ahead go ahead and
I heard them say I can you come back i
really need a lover
I was like you've got to be kidding me
this is my mom and this is 1986-87 crazy
and being with that come from
yeah
the beastie boys were slated to open for
Run DMC on the raising hell tour
the tour was special because it was the
first time rap music would be given such
global exposure
Rick without being a DJ and only the
label called def jam time very small
label how to group all hold on it for
real
this was long before LOL cool day before
to be people just have really started
out
he just got off the road with them with
Madonna things that you know I can do
this in turn illegal you should always
give me time to stop for a while she
said you wanted you and putting up the
creek
oh my god so buy them over to the
doorman I came over to hang out all
night long had a good time to each other
different from time to time whatever
so we did a couple of get down in the
village no you're great you know it's
doing its cool
and that's our relationship further from
the norms kept doing shows
don't do dream became the Beastie Boys
DJ but life on tool wasn't always great
we're just going to show out no
happening in the stadium but it was like
the hardest hottest day of the year
I wanted to do you can fry an egg on the
concrete without trying it was that
frickin hot in this room right now that
means all sweating my balls off of there
right now
yeah Drake was definitely an
uncomfortable situation I would say that
for sure
DJ hurricane started office part of Run
DMC's entourage in the mid-1980s
being on that shuttle bus with those
wild dude and his hat recognition our
bus broke down so we had to go back to a
hotel
taking a shower and going on yeah I
remember that because they had a
bullshit bus
it was like well in a handicap band
songs because the bus at all
I went back and begin with these are you
always the last guy I don't leave any
better things like I went back to crowd
out the room I couldn't get in
I don't think I shall i get to the next
stop
I think I told Sean I don't want to
sleep here on this couch me know when
you're ready to go I'll be here
you got left I remember that he was
pissed when I woke up there was nobody
he'll probably left right left me there
and luckily who gave me the bus was
there and I don't want to do is bust and
I was pissed off as I got company guys
left world could use can't leave in the
middle of nowhere
crazy don't think we can find you to
find you a little lobby on our couch
sleeping I'm sleeping over a hundred
degrees on Miami with no AC find my hat
off
are you crazy you know no I don't look
at that I gotta take a break down and
admit this beginning to piss me off but
midway through the raisin hell tour
dr. dre party with the beastie boys so
then they came in action
hope you DJ for us and I was still like
really hesitant because back then you
know I was so cool
I thought I was just so cool you don't
say and growing up with Hollis Queens be
on monday and see you know me
and you know they wanted to DJ for some
i doing that was very unheard of back
then you know white guys rapping and it
was wild and just throwing stuff all
over the place
i said i doing I never thought that I
would just keep doing it
I thought it was gonna be a temporary
thing about the body with the right
label on it he made of raising hell tour
was the craziest story I've been on in
my life and that tore open the doors for
hip-hop complete that broke the barriers
down that talk that so much publicity
and showed out so many concerts for the
first time here probably that everybody
was like wow dad to a really open doors
because it
wow you got to see with a little bit of
both worlds be trained in PCT and you're
seeing nothing but a whole set of people
that was so I know they say it all
barriers
it was just wild scene
girls screaming this a giant Budweiser
can stage four square root beers and
people you know and it
it was funny and I just thought man
that's you know basically what we're
doing is from grandkids
yes it was there was all the grocery of
sex drugs rock and roll going on all the
time
the beastie boys found out grabbing
antics were about to make the notorious
I remember just coming in our dressing
rules like the worst thing you can do
you know if you're coming to address
when he might get hit in the head with a
can of beer side by my squirt some
whipped cream and your face
anything can happen to you if you came
inside restaurant anything
the other problem was and this was a
major problem was they didn't realize
none of us realized there that half
their fans were 11 your own and 12 year
old kids 14 year old kids and at that
time 14 year old kids were not as
sophisticated as they are now they would
they had on a gigantic inflatable penis
on their tour they had the beer show
where they poured beer or ready
they did all kinds of great and this is
just a stripper occasion this is just
you know onstage
you can't you may God here at least had
much more to do with sort of like
obscenity they toured america with
Madonna
they were like the opening act for
Madonna so all of a sudden all these 12
and 13 year old girls were kind of being
exposed to do you know this band who was
out you know very sexual and had lots of
phallic imagery on stage and
I will seem to be in presenting
themselves as like potential molesters
oh my gosh on stage you're doing all
this crazy stuff they're cursing there
they're pouring beer there were girls
are dropping their tops and you've got
11 year old kids in the audience with
their fit with their family with their
moms and dads who brought them to the
show
that's where the real trouble started
today is a beastie boys an American band
calling itself the nastiest group in the
world arrived in London
they've flown in from Europe where
apparently they dogged the walls of
their hotel with human excrement wrecked
one bar hand in another ended up
throwing beer at other customers
I remember first going overseas and
people know who I was really kind of
brought me out first time I went over
there to get off the plane and seeing
people run up to you say yo what's up
the jerrycan yo what's up man we love
you able to kind of release that make
you say dad man this stuff is really big
now
the controversy really kicked in when
the Beasties towards Europe the British
Armed papers that they have made up a
live said that the beastie boys laughing
that purple kids
and when we got to Europe everybody was
like protesting us like really crazy
like I think one to kill us
maybe it's a shame that you have to
write articles make up lies to sell you
the papers really stupid
the Beastie Boys abandoned you were
dismissed them
I'm printable I remember given to
liverpool on the concert soon as I got
the turntables start scratching people
start doing big cans at me time I
fully-loaded big hands and I'm like a
duck in like someone will come and
towards my patient up and I was like you
know you're going to stop going to stop
right
something like let me have to bring the
guys are here and maybe they'll calm
down
demanding soon as they came out it got
worse
it was like ok corral I was running from
bullets and like going all kinds of
stuff and then i remember it was NCAA
picked up something and throw it back in
the crowd here and it hit somebody in
the next thing you know the police at
the whole turn
looking for a restaurant by dr. in 1986
the Beastie Boys released their debut LP
licensed to ill
the album was interpreted as a mindless
obnoxious party records when life is
built a map that was amazing
all about this Mike because it went to
number one
it was the fastest selling strange new
record in Colombia history the biggest
single is fight for your right to party
which is the song it like the Beastie
Boys now all hey and will basically
hardly hardly even get them talk about
it
average it it's certainly the closest
like hybrid between like the kind of
punk rock they were making clothes and
then the kind of like a suburban white
hip-hop and fight for your right to
party wasn't a hip-hop record but it was
they were hip hop group so by making
that wreckage and have a hip hop's and
made them get rock fans more rock fans
to listen to hip-hop
also it's a really straight jean that's
really flats on in there against me up
when I seen flat I mean it's just sort
of like certainly innovative it is
basically like the kind of sign you
would write if you were an 8th grader
the world was introduced to the boys
with their top 10 single and video
you gotta fight for your right to policy
you could put black and white leader on
that song is shown at MTV and it would
have been a hit
in fact maybe we should have put black
and white leader on it and show on mtv
because it might have been it anyway
virtually any video for that song
would've been big what would have been
it would have been as big as this know
because this video also put the Beasties
on mtv bragging about how great they
were
it was designed to be played on MTV it
wasn't even at the time wasn't going to
play form of it wasn't gonna play the
new style but they knew this song you
could do a great
braat braat song like you said and
visually would work and it will get them
wanting to be and get them set up and
that's what did for that all the people
that you see in that video are friends
of there
I mean there's the guys from Murphy's
Law and I are there is an answer stop
can we just stop all I mean everything
there's all these people are just
friends could have started DJ right know
every trick room and showed up I mean
everybody was just friends
the video includes a lot of people
getting hit in the face with lies and
what kind of important about that is a
sense that even you know even to a
thirteen-year-old kid in 95 that sort of
stupid that's sort of like kind of like
comedic value from the fifties or
whatever but that's kind of what they
were
it was like conscious stupidity my
mother and father played the parents in
the video and actually Taylor pretty
funny that I don't know what was great
was that at the very end of the last
visual joke is that the mother comes
home sees the destruction wrought by the
beastie boys in the
apartment and is like looking around
bewildered and then she then gets a PI
interface
no nobody at the heart to like throw the
PI interface because everyone even
though she was like it's fine just do it
she was dying I think I'm gonna shoot
that she was just nobody really at the
heart so finally what we have to do is
nobody could really throw it so they
framed up a very tight shot of her face
had turned tricks hand and he just has
the pines and just slowly like ice
crushes the blind race for me was
perfect because she had glasses we have
which meant it wouldn't get a ride which
is great but the glasses got all caught
by the pie
I got a lawyer yeah and i remember on
mtv they said that one of the guys who
directed this through the pine his
mother's face at the end
nice going kid right well that's
controversial american band The Beastie
Boys is being blamed for curious crime
currently sweeping the sound these last
month's sales of VW emblems rocketed by
a hundred and thirty percent 6500 these
were sold mostly young people who want
to stick around then next we started not
going to say that we stole me but that
was that was his thing I mean you know
when your daughter they started wearing
that we like about the ripping off of
the yeah that's right far
I mean when we heard about we heard
about that kind of stuff and not
specifically that it was it was better
all the rage when you knew where they
were getting this stuff and they weren't
paying for it legally or anything I mean
you knew all that was close kind of the
between thing about it was that they
were you know anybody was wearing an
emblem from a card you know they stole
it for a car and and that was kind of
the thing about it so my team really i
think started to be w thing on yourself
and you're not even up you know when we
might be a pain for now I'm eating a lot
of us what we put out that we're def
enjoying ourselves having a good time
hopefully not harming anybody else a
number of things happen because of that
video
apparently some kid had a fight for your
right to party party in somewhere in the
United States and almost burned down his
house
600 and I felt a mixture of sadness and
and pride the boyfriends name is the
members in the community came from but
they were making it very clear that like
you know it's not that we just seemed um
it's like we want to be as dumb as
possible which I think really relates to
people that age you are looking to be
absurd for no reason all the time
everybody wanted us to perform that song
on their TV show in their cities at the
birthday parties without really trying
it kind of became this very like and I
can seem excited and anthem for their
mindset at the time
wherever they can get us to go and do
that song
they got us to go do it that song was
was huge
that song was the one I would say so
long those records for license they're
the kind of people buy that record could
relate to it I guess because they wanted
to have parties you know it was amazing
it was it was a huge selling record i'm
feeling very proud
I always tell the story about my mother
because she likes to say when might use
to come over here to my house
he wouldn't he wouldn't talk to her you
would make eye contact he just mumbled
something and walk on down to my room
and she always had the same thought this
kid is not gonna amount to anything
she always say that and then fight for
your right to comes out and she's
dancing to it at an after ski bar you
know that the ski slope during 1988
they became involved in a bitter lawsuit
with def jam and rick rubin who claimed
that he was responsible for the group's
success
the group finally managed to break away
and relocated to California and all of a
sudden it gets the point in 1987 where
wait a minute there's a lot of money at
stake and they're like hey we want to be
a part of that they didn't say we want
it all but they were like where you know
suddenly you look at your contract and
you realize hey wait a minute i'm only
getting like this piece and you know
record companies getting this piece and
the record companies Rick Rubin Russell
Simmons and a big lawsuit followed in
basically Rick and they split and i
think that's that's part of the the
problems that they see that is before
they became in control of their own
destiny though they had a lot to do with
the videos
the breakup of of the Beastie Boys and
regrouping came about
basically because they learn the harsh
lesson that many forms learned which
which when you get successful you are
all of a sudden you you want to have
let's say you realize how little of
yourself and your own success
you're entitled to
yeah
in nineteen eighty knowing the Beastie
Boys released
Paul's Boutique the musical style was
entirely different
- licensed to ill many observers didn't
know what to make of it
Paul PT came out they looked it went to
Los Angeles and they were smoking a lot
of pod and being in like that was sort
of the aesthetic of that record we
started the slate bags donor and hip-hop
this with all like and probably involves
more samples than any major records ever
released in a sense that like you could
not afford to make Paul's Boutique now
with copyright laws on the your daily
not anymore really cracking down on the
use of samples and the use of material
I mean there are I there are hundreds
and hundreds of you know they'll be just
like you know snippet of a Bowie song
that just be you know and like all these
things they could never
you can never make that record now look
that's the end of like widespread sample
people didn't really catch on to people
was expected license to ill so they
didn't really respect Paul's team
they make this record and almost no one
pays attention to it because it's not is
superficially funny or as sort of
aggressively obnoxious all the things
that sort of made them famous initially
which really were kind of baggage of
license Dale that's all guys
I remember i'm up when Paul's Boutique
first came out and we start doing shows
and this breakfast cells didn't jump off
the way they're supposed to
everybody is looking kind of down about
it's like you know this is it's over
well I know adam said that like he
thought it was gonna be you like they
were they were working under the premise
that like okay this relapse records
still 12 million and this record is so
much better and so much more serious
you know it's going to be like Fleetwood
Mac's rumors is going to just be passive
and I did I don't know really how it
affected them because i think that you
know I success happening so quickly and
change their life so dramatically that I
don't know if they were really prepared
to make a successful record every two or
three years i think that they were
probably very close to end and
we went from visiting big arenas two
smaller ones
so it was definitely a gut check I think
you know either you down or you ain't
down you're going to jump off the ship
now you're not
I just get the impression that that as
personalities their life that all
changed and no one with dating on the
sky was inaccurate we're doing all these
other things you know and i think in a
sense maybe that that when politics
didn't do as well commercially they were
afraid of like well okay I with me know
we we still made all this money off our
first record we got all these cool
original and this record we like but
this is well you know we'll see what
happens
maybe this is the left record roll over
man
now respectively kind of the
conventional thing to say is that the
best Beastie Boys records policy but
almost no one body and it was completely
an extension of this idea that a lot of
people didn't take them seriously
license to kill
and then it was later that people shared
kind of rediscovering but there's
actually a lot of people say that but
also keeping it came on her life but now
people know Paul's Boutique you felt the
same people applied in like it back then
when i go back to listen to it now
yeah
check your head
the album they released in 1992 was the
first record since the hardcore days
where the Beasties play their own
instruments the Opie re-established the
Beastie Boys as a musical force in the
alternative scene and I think he just
decided to start playing again
so we kind of picked up the instruments
we kind of did it again
like came back in a different style when
we pick them up trying something else
out
check your head when i was at college at
the time it seemed like a big record
there now I I can't you know I'm sure
went platinum and their video like a the
video for what you want isn't even quite
a bit to get ahead you've done pretty
well but it was super popular among like
serious music fans at the time I can
check your head was I think that was a
really good genes out because it went
from just making all hip-hop album to
make him a whole complete album of hip
hop in little rock a little punks and
slow instrumental
they were one of the first kind of
outfits where it seemed like they were
like very consciously and very clearly a
merging hard rock and hip-hop and that
while they were together they still had
sort of the autonomous identities and I
crossing that record became a big deal
because it was sort of this kind of
social and universal discovery that all
actually the Beastie Boys there was just
funny band they're actually like this
brilliant man
like they have to get there there's a
lot of musicianship here and a real
understanding it's like politics
business out by the time they may take
your head
the musical climate completed in the
sense that and all this like there was
this new interest in alternative music
as the main string the response to check
your head was incredible
people loved it people love to see
instruments like when you came to the
show will check your head
I mean it was never done before now
you're not days you see people like a
let the skin and other rock bands trying
to do what we did back then which was
pick up instruments scratching with the
instruments rapping with instruments and
putting it all together and one type of
on one plate
I mean people were advising and they're
taking the beach boys but they were
revising in a way that was more accurate
that these weren't just personalities
these were actually like a very sort of
talented and sophisticated band
I mean that's the biggest thing check
your head did it kind of made people
come to the conclusion that the beastie
boys were musically sophisticated which
had not been the case in the past
in 1994 ill communication was released
its style was quite similar to check
your head but this time it was more
hip-hop focused like sabotage to me is
is a very clear example of like how the
beastie boys have been always able to
stay just slightly ahead of like the
cultural curve in a sense that when that
came out 1984
the one thing that seems really
interested them a lot and was a great
interest to this huge mass of of
listener who had I guess enabled
experiences was this sudden interest in
the nineteen seventies and seventies
culture
so when they made the sabotage video
which was really like sort of a mock
send-up of like American cop show from
the seventies like Starsky and Hutch
beretta and stuff like that was the
first time people heard that song and
solid images they like because MTV
basically broke that song and people
really liked the video and they like it
was directed by Spike Jones and was
really funny and it was really cool and
basically then position now the Beastie
Boys is like where they had been
previously like a college rock band
now they were like at home like a major
alternative rock band and sort of really
like one of the first rap rock bands
to me that was like my favorite little
communication because the tours that we
did a little communication the way we
used to rock the crowd when we did
sabotage and on shore shot
no songs like that I mean the crowds
used to go so crazy from the shows we
used to do i mean i wish i had some of
them on video
it was just phenomenal that was a hot
year at the beach boys have suddenly
decided that they're now like sort of
like statesman and kind of like is a
diplomatic element to them
you know you're in there from New York
so like this record is like a tribute to
New York in the five boroughs of New
York and but a mean they have a song
called like to the five boroughs or no
no no an open letter to NYC
it was time for the open letter to NYC
and they basically just named places
like the lame certain locations in
certain subway lines and stuff and it's
more like you know like reading the
Zagat's guide is like a tutorial to like
hearing more things in New York are but
still even now two to play you know they
haven't had a record out in six years
they just had a record out the number
one record and if you ask anybody in
will the beastie boys have a number one
record what is it's a 6 15 years later
more than 15 16 17 years later that
they'll make it even . for almost 20
years later that which they could they
come out
everybody thought well i mean i have a
good out and they had a really good year
and a couple of good songs but nobody
would have thought that they were they
were going to have it out
I will they probably get they probably
tore at this record and i will be well
for that making everyone and
they work slow they were kind of you
know part of what makes them cool for
visiting it can work on their own
schedule
there probably won't be on the Beastie
Boys records for five years
after a tracking holiday through Tibet
adam yauch was suddenly drawn to the
plight of the people there is cum trade
and culture was being occupied by China
he decided to stand up and do something
about it
resulting in the first Tibetan freedom
concerts held over two days into 1996
it was just this big interest in the
middle nineties in the United States
about 3 to bed and you will see it on a
bumper stickers on cars and you would
hear people talking about it became the
corner of like it was like a hipster
cause I'm the old and you're going I'm
going to hold and I don't know you need
to
like cool kids all of a sudden we're
taking this interest and you know
China's occupation of the bed and added
me out because one of the guys doing
like you know and I read about it and
use a week or something and he was like
yes this is important so he became this
sort of this very forward-thinking very
aggressive proponent of like Frank to
bed night
you really got beyond saying to bed
should be free but it kind of became
like is cause I don't know it's a girl
serious about our girls
I don't know i just got to get over that
should come along
jual beli love you out the valley love
it
ok ok you know what I get done because
you've got pounded in a piece by going
on the whole got me on that one
it's be off the bill come on do
something for us here what are you
giving us to pick you for these causes
weight gain would be security I mean
who's going to share like yeah well I
think China should be able to like Rob
these boxes of their color you always
going to disagree with freedom for the
bed yeah I just I just always think it's
funny whenever I see like a freaking bed
bumper sticker
I like a piece avoid future the Badgers
right well
I don't know how that's gonna manifest
itself in any freedom but you know it's
good you're thinking about it but to me
it was it was basically enjoying another
concert
you know I mean yeah I wanted to do it
for that calls so it was cool with me
and it was cool with everybody else to
support him and what he wanted to do
which it
what what should really be happening is
that all of us should be thanking the
Tibetan people and the Chinese people
who are here who are speaking out
you should be thanking down for
participating in this not violent
struggle education
just dance two minutes and Counting try
to a political rock
anytime we're trying to do something
with political is get all these big band
with you
it gets a lot of attention at first for
its political leanings think this
becomes like over all the good bands
were like it just becomes the Woodstock
and it's like you know you get people
going to that show who you know I
wouldn't care if like to bed got
attacked by Godzilla you know what do i
do you think it is
when I got on stage you know I thought
to do that
let's let's go to work do we supposed to
do so much with it when that concert was
going I just don't feel like wow what a
great show this is because it was like a
beastie boys program and hold you know
managerial other gags and then I think
something that struck by lightning guys
that was the main thing anyway
although the Beasties were extremely
successful
not everyone associated with the band
was happy I was saying the reason why
I'm our part it was because it was like
the Beastie would work like every five
six years and for me you know i got a
family I need to be constantly working
and you know it wasn't really benefit me
and my family
like work every five years I remember
like several times i'd be up there and
like you know what they were really
really be into it as much as I used to
be into it
financially I felt like I should make it
more than what i was getting you know
like if you go to work and you're not
happy with how much money you're making
when you have work you're not going to
be happy you know I mean no matter what
kind of job you doing
if you go to work and you like my own I
should be making some more money 1 i'm
making then you're not going to be
always concentrating all the way there
and that's how I felt I felt like I
should have didn't get making more money
than what I was making as far as how
long I was down after 12 years of loyal
service
DJ hurricane decided to leave the band
oh right sure
what are you don't what are you don't
have anyone who has spent time with the
bounds of always takes away special
memories always true personalities are
always hidden behind their comedic to e
gays but what are they really like I
first met my through my brother actually
because my brother was best friends with
Mike's older brother his oldest brother
David and so it just sort of naturally
happened that I became interested in my
plan B cross pads we gradually just got
more and more
and to use that between you know it's a
little child to recognize my DS to do
that
you know he's the guy that when Mike
comes on he wants to be to do is be
talking
he wants to take care of the business
part everything he wants to be spoken do
it at a group but not want to be is
basically for me Mike Dee was the quiet
when he was very smart though as well he
was very smart
quiet and in terms of the videos
he was the one that asked for the most
direction considering what he had four
trunks
he was a damn good drummer we had pretty
much
II the lowest form of just
bargain-basement drum set and
he worked it as well as he could
down down with this
I don't have it the actor of the blue he
was always the house he was the emotion
of a groupie
it was like the heart and soul and he
believed in this like this was his
life's work
this is what he had to do he believed in
the address that was his thing and I
really looked up to Adam orbits I
thought he was extremely funny and
he always wore like really cool clothes
his mom had a clothing store
I don't know whether we all dressed like
Adam or we all just stressed that way
ourselves but the whole like baseball
cap and you know t-shirt I don't know I
mean it just seemed like what we were
all wearing and then it became this
whole uniform in the nineties early late
eighties
yeah i was thought out of hilarious he
was just one of the funny to get my note
he enjoy being from there was a front
man to the beastie boys may be able o
damn with the Aqua be sexy guy Mike
diamond
he's good he's asked the manager
believer in the back bone in his own
bank but it would be a dark as though
the step afrika
you know he he was like the leader of
the young uses it was his band so and I
know because he was a couple years older
I mean those were just a big age
difference then
and you know I always looked up looked
up to him and thought he was saying like
you know whatever he thought was right
was probably right and you know he was
really funny and smart
you know so i always had this like kind
of little brother feeling around around
him
Adam or which was actually at the time
and probably although I knew all three
of them was when I was the closest to
he was the son of the famous playwright
and sometimes screenwriter Israel
harvests and we became pretty friendly
the minute
Adam told me that his father and covered
in an Italian gangster film with john
cassavetes which he didn't take credit
for Paul machine gun became that I love
or out of Horus was like you know that
right my like my favorite because the
he's the dude i would say like I can
relate to love the most because it's
just like so cool
I'm saying like he always called me and
you know so what's up K
he'll speak to my wife and I and you
know actually how the kids doing is I
would say i had work is definitely my
closest friend when it come down to be
the action the action beyond all dreams
add box definitely command harvests are
to me was like he was the actor or eat
at acting experience and faculty Pete
acted as a teenager as a very young
teenager I had acted on stage and they
said you know he's like a young Cagney
or something like that one would do
anything for a poor joke type guys
hillary was he was a jerry lewis of the
three
yeah
mca very cool very reserved very funny
guy
I was like hanging out with you because
you always reduce like crazy stuff you
know
five cells and hang out and talking you
know yup we're doing Scott and I would
be scotch with them and just talk stuff
pull off very reserved cool very very
clear
I can't do this moment i can't i can't
really do nothing around him that that
he's going to think is wrong but i have
like they'll do
this
cool time to do is just sold
so gentlemen now you know yeah it was a
little more was the most assertively
three in terms of wanting his
independence the most in terms of being
the most independence and most outspoken
and and he was sort of laid back was the
quietest 23 but he was he was he was
laid back he gave a lot of thought to
what he wanted to do and they all did in
fact I mean they work together but he
was usually the ringleader whatever idea
they came up with in terms of anything
that they came up with
I think he would sort of become the
spokesman at certain time one night only
pushing their records
you have this designation plunger see
the cartoons &
this plunger thing to detonate bombs and
you liked it you like to me close it's
one night we decided to blow up the name
is Michelle Parker
so he's not going over yet jumped over
the fence planted a bomb and click the
wire back trail that back up into his
room and set off a bomb
I don't know when
there are no but it went off at all we
just you know maniacally laughed and
yeah
losses
was it was fine you know it's just
there's no reason for you know what it
was just you know is silly
I think got a lot of trouble for that
actually despite an existence
that's bridged nearly two decades the
Beasties seem incapable of resting on
their laurels and just offering retreads
of their earlier work for a band that
was written off as a one joke novelty
acts the moment they came to mass
attention
they haven't done that badly they loom
pretty large in in rock and roll history
as probably as the first valid white
wrap
they have proved people wrong a lot
the no one thought that they would have
more than one market
Beastie Boys location we might say in
general year day during black sound
let's do it all they come across to mass
it to everybody to me
music music they're good people to their
they're always interested in another
band
helping very good things have been
around for this long first of all there
going on
what is that one in three years I mean
it's a huge accomplishment and they've
kept their heads you know they've really
survive so many years later they're not
really just a footnote in music
they actually are able to pack
you know like arenas in fact every white
act whether they want to believe it or
not including kid rocking guys like that
they may be door Eminem they may be
different but every white app that does
wrap or something to them just like
every white rock and roll guy owes
something to Elvis
I was some of this being one of those of
one of the greatest hip-hop group of our
lives
definitely one of the top the ability to
continue to grow and reinvent themselves
and staying you
yeah
they're still valid they're still doing
it and it's from doing it well and they
still got a sense of humor about
themselves as a very key think some of
their legacy will
large Lucy Biggers work with at least as
big as Michelangelo with you know if not
his biggest issue an order filled
yeah
ok
ways
yeah
no way