remembering out of the black silence you
were born in pain
easy easy does a little mother he'd
never lost her father
your job is done
you were born with hate and anger built
in took a slap on the back side to blast
out the screen and then you knew you
were alive eight pounds five ounces baby
boy Frankie bono father doing well
later you learn to hold back the screen
and let out the hate and anger another
way
you're coming to manhattan by dark
whether the time of day it is through
tunnels like sue is hidden under the
city but you don't mind that so is that
way whatever city it is
you're alone but you don't mind that
you're a loner that's the way it should
be you've always been alone by now it's
your trademark you like it that way
the railroad company makes sure you
don't forget they're coming to town on
Christmas it gives you the creeps but
that's all right everyone on the
goodwill kit maybe they'll leave you
alone
you hate cities especially at Christmas
but that's all right too when the Better
Business Bureau rings the Christmas fell
the suckers forget there's such a
business's murder and businessmen who
make it their exclusive line like you
baby boy Frankie bono out of Cleveland
nice view we have here Thank You mr.
Merry Christmas registered is Fred more
of Albany in town for a week or less on
business by the way mr. if you need
anything just ask for George okay at
noon you make contact the wind is cold
as you approach the ferry but the palms
of your hands start to sweat
this is the first bad moment there's
always a few on every job when you're
not alone you can depend on yourself no
one else you've learned the hard way
they all hate the gun they hire when
people look at you baby boy Frankie bono
they see death deaths across the counter
remembering
watch it Frankie you almost missed him
you'll known by the hate in his eye when
he asks for a light you got a match but
ever been in a while
yeah Cleveland
I got a friend at practices in Cleveland
you know him yeah I know fat Nick you
got my passport
after those in the envelope you get the
other half when the job is finished how
do I get in touch there's a number in
the envelope call after you make the hit
I'll let you know where to meet me for
the payoff okay one more thing
if you get spotted before the hit the
contracts off you understand me
yeah I understand you
now you're alone again you relax your
hands are cold now even with gloves on
on your own again nothing to worry about
the targets name is Troy yano you know
the type second-string silicate boss
with too much ambition and a mustache
tied the fact he has lips like a woman
the kind of face you hate
nice little home quiet little community
and our out in the suburbs every morning
he's picked up by two bodyguards hood
written all over them but when the
neighbors read the headlines mobster
killed they'll say but Mr Triano's
seemed like such a respectable man he
went to work every morning 9 30 on the
dot
you already know one thing they can't
make the kill at his house too easily
spotted 24 hours street lamps
it's a laugh you could afford a house
like that if you wanted it there in the
upper 5% income bracket killing pays
well for a reason you have the
experience and the know-how you're proud
of your reputation expert and thorough
you don't have to know a man to live
with them but you have to know a man
like a brother to kill him
watch it buddy guards slowing down could
be there watching for a tail pass them
don't ever take chances you're not a
gambler
now you know that pattern the job will
take a waiting job waiting to find where
troiano goes to be alone and you know
another thing to be quick and silent
while he's away from his bodyguards
it'll be a job for a gun that means
another pet moment another contact and
sweat a little on the wheel remembering
another Christmas running from the cops
watch it Frankie danger signal your
mind's wandering but you know why you
have to do business with a Ralphie and
he change his stomach
ah thank you ah ba ba Noi yeah come on
name Jesus good to see you he surprised
me i didn't expect nobody Cuba knocking
on the door they sign a bottom I just
have a mess that's excuse me to expect
no company about them I just had my
lunch here so how you been you making a
dollar store yeah yeah and you've always
did all right sit down Frank I with a
hurry Ralph hey come on him for me oh
yeah I heard you did little time huh
it's doing business Ralphie what can I
look I did for you I need a piece that's
no problem 38 with Santa silence that
that may be a little problem you know I
yeah I gotta worry about a machinist but
who work something out but it'll cost
you hey Nancy are you doing here coo coo
coo look I she knows me huh haha how you
doing sweetie how much she hasn't it no
they are we get it sometime he go he
goes free hey come on come on come on
come on yeah you like that don't you you
like that five hundred dollars Frank
I'll give you two I'd like to help you
out Frank but to come on Kevin here you
go there's an excellent
I'll tell what I do Frank four hundred
dollars but that's rock bottom three
yard and a half now and the restaurant I
get the piece Oh Frank may get another
50 come on what does it mean to you I
got to make something on with you just
another 50 come on please all right i'll
give you the other 50 but that's it you
understand sure sure Frank when I make a
deal it's a deal now I have a drink I'm
in a hurry Ralph where do I pick it up I
just won't for a new year right hey what
happened to that the girl used to go
with the redhead who was her name Sally
yeah hey Frank she she liked me then she
yeah she liked you yeah here's to uh mr.
Sally self what do I get the goods oh
yeah oh and east side the barge called
the Catherine el pier 21 after speak to
Joe Boniface tell Vinny centerra sent
you tell me from Cleveland he'll deliver
the goods where is that there between
twenty-third and twenty-fourth street
now I want this quick oh yeah anytime
after tomorrow Frank all right hey well
what's your rush right gotta run Ralphie
I stopped me your trouble road
hey but here liquid big Ralph got for
christmas and they're nice
you
now you're alone again in another entity
car you pick up the target where you
left off yesterday right on schedule
today the bugs are with you and you stay
with him while he makes this morning
rounds the streets of Harlem are busy
enough no one notices you you catch a
danger signal your hands are sweating
but that's all right because you know
what it is the hate of Harlem you hate
them and they hate you like another
Harlem where you grew up
watch it Frankie Savior age for troiano
he runs the girls and the dope in the
books and the numbers there's a guy
could really learn to hate you will
before the time comes you always do
somehow you always hate the targets
before you hit him
the sisters of the orphanage used to say
God moves in mysterious ways sometimes
we wonder if he moved you into rid the
world of men might try a no
he thinks it looks like the gentleman of
his shoes are shined you could kill him
right now with pleasure
you
knock it off for today pick him up
tomorrow when he leaves the restaurant
time to kill 24 hours to stay faceless
in the crowd get yourself lost in the
city lose yourself in the Christmas
spirit will be good little boys and
girls to go Santa's here with lots of
toys and goodies for all of you make
sure you all wanna sleep early Christmas
Eve because I'll be coming down your
chimney
Oh
funny the hands are cold when you think
of Christmas remembering
remembering other Christmases pushing
your nose against the plate glass door
windows till the cold of at major
headache wishing for something where was
it roller skates bike sled games nothing
like that something bigger more
important something special
alone at dinner your hands are hot
remembering the hot sweaty hands of the
Mother Superior holding you watch it
dangerous signal and now you catch it
another bad moment of all crummy times
the familiar face out of the past good
old Pete from the orphanage it has to
happen now and then you can handle it
but why now you feel hottie like they
were crowding in and pushing you who
anyone everyone Pete ya hate the type
you'd like to push his love muffin you
smile you're polite you don't even hear
the words yak yak yak like a parrot then
he's reminding you there was a girl his
sister Laurie you don't usually remember
names especially women's names but glory
there was something special a tell me
about yourself Frankie what are you been
doing pity I can't stay I've gotta take
off what are you kidding hey waiter
bring me two more here you're going no
place man
come on why if the layout like I used
come on up Frankie fill me in where the
hell did you disappear to well I've been
a moving on and I mean sure sure who
guys as for me maybe you remember I was
always pretty fair with the paintbrush
so when I came out of the army I studied
commercial art GI Bill and finally got
myself a job with an advertising agency
I guess I've been kind of lucky glad to
hear it Peter say what are you doing
tonight I mean Lori's given a party in
your coming no I can't make it kid I've
gotta go waiter Oh nonsense listen
Frankie it's it's Christmas Eve Oh
Frankie yeah you gotta come I can't
there'll be a lot of real swinging
people there you'll have a wonderful
time besides here she comes now hey
Laurie look who's here how about it I
Lori you recognize this guy love Frankie
hello
you sure have changed good why she has
changed a bit maybe a little longer wyd
of pets all hey Laurie we're gonna let
him have a lonely old beer on Christmas
Eve you know you're making a mistake but
you tell yourself maybe it's smarter to
play it cool go for one drink stay for a
dance maybe then get out you tell you
something like an suspicious if you turn
down the invite maybe you're right maybe
a smart maybe you're kidding yourself so
watch it
you hate parties you sit alone waiting
for a chance to blow the noisy crowd out
of he is wondering what you're doing
here if you want a woman by one in the
dark so she won't remember your face but
for some reason you stall around telling
yourself it's as good a way as any they
killed time
always wanted to dance with you Frankie
I'm go ahead we're all friends here go
ahead Frankie my sister only asked once
you know
you're not having a very good time are
you I guess I just don't mix a tie
that's more like it listen quiet down
with one of years ago I want a great
contest I'll never forget and just to
prove my manhood I'm gonna do so again
Frankie I hereby challenge you to
another peanut pushing contest with a
know what I have a slight advantage he
has to the camp I've been practicing for
years come on Frankie I'm giving you a
second chance where's your people get
that in their life
December 25th you have all of christmas
day to kill you hate Christmas so much
you can't stand the thought of sweating
it out alone in a crummy hotel room
hi hello you know I had such a funny
feeling I wasn't sure you'd come all
right here oh thanks Frankie merry
Christmas to you hey come on in no I
really was great I haven't even me like
this in years why not further case yeah
well you know I've moved around a lot
never settle in one place doing what you
certainly can be evasive where did you
go when you left Chillicothe Frankie
clean I was sick of that little burg I
wanted a big city and what did you do
I got a job in this big parking lot the
old guy who ran it he liked me treated
me like a father he made me manager and
I was doing pretty good till the whole
damn thing fell apart what do you mean
other were these local racket guys and
they try to shake the old man down they
bombed his house and they they killed
his wife why why you just don't ask
questions like that that's why all I
know is the old guy took off a flower
like a scared rabbit maybe I should have
gone with him what did you do I mean
what I do I look to stay alive that's
what I do now let's just forget the
whole thing shall we
I won't be dance
unless of course you'd rather push
another peanut across the floor
some dance that's her I'm not right so
you know
I'm sorry
I'm very sorry sometimes I just don't
know what the hell I'm doing
I think you better go Frank
oh boy please let me stay I I promise
you I won't get rough anymore I just got
carried away please Larry
please
suppose we have a warm up from the
coffee
Lori look I want to explain about what
happened over there Frankie look just
forget it really there's nothing to say
it's okay it's fine you know Frankie
you're really a very attractive guy how
come you're not married I don't know
well I think I think what you probably
need is a girl or someone you know
someone that you could feel good with
someone who could make you feel at home
that's all drink your coffee Frankie
and then you better leave I really am
very tired
december 26th troiano has had his day in
church in his back at work so are you
you're feeling better now you got
Christmas ideas system to begin to feel
the excitement that always comes as you
start to close in you have a crazy on
something new will happen today to break
the monotony of waiting and you're right
in the middle of the afternoon troiano
goes into a small brownstone he leaves
this protection outside now you know
where Triano goes alone but you still
don't know why
you should have figured triana was
strictly in character Christmas Day with
a family day after Christmas shacked up
with a dame four hours alone or almost
alone now you know where the target is
going to get shit the details will have
to be worked out but the generals setup
is perfect and you're learning to hate
for your know like you haven't dated
anyone since the old man
met a girl a year ago knew everything
there was to know her eyes were great a
hair was jet for my evil baby i can't
forget so i'm dressed in black all the
time dressed in black pullet our bear
cat tree i searched to care i pretend
what she did you see Ralphie you should
have spotted him before he spotted you
Ralphie with his pet sewer rats
why
love waiting on
my baby and killed himself to it broke
my heart I must confess
Oh
domestic black all the time dressed in
black Triana with his high-priced Damon
Ralphie and his rats two of a kind and
the conga drum beating your head till
you taste the heat on your tongue
times like this know who your real
friends
sky is claiming orange and the streets
of golden brown and I'm going to found
my baby in this horrid torrid time
she left me cross the border on a horse
tan and white gotta help me for my baby
others gonna be a fight she's here a
stranger told me she's there o Lord hold
me I'm here I'll do her harm the while
of her she ran off with another man and
I can't write think of her with a lover
if it's a cold my very dead skies bloody
purple now because the sun's gone down
upon my baby amidst our it now there's
no walls within me the sky is turning
red it it's time I left his car down the
both of them are dead i'm anton fucking
desert don't care what
are you doing Frankie you birthday party
outside I usually don't like birthday
parties you know I figure like it's bad
luck I mean like why tempt fate what are
you driving at fatty you know Frank I
may be fat over here but I'm not fat up
here you know I figure we're gonna have
to renegotiate the contract we negotiate
this made a deal I know we made a deal
Frank but I'd had no idea to have to
outfit the whole Safari out there and we
would have to be gained Frank hey you're
gonna have to pay luxury prices boy I'll
pay you nothing I'm warning you fatty
you're sticking your belly where it
doesn't belong don't threaten me without
a gun in your fist you nothing
no I will pay you in first place why
don't you go and feed your rats fire
Frank alcohol but if I just happen to
read the newspaper that our friend out
there and have no more birthday parties
or you come by it co Ralph I figure you
know a few bucks or something you're
over your head fette will see Frankie
we'll see I gotta run now I'm married
the iron sky is burning on the scalpel
looking down I'll soon be with my baby
far away from the storage
I
Oh
you
you're not mocked up that's a break
you're sweating all over your body you
tell yourself it's the steam heat but
you know the radiator has been cold all
night you know you'll stay in a sweat
till they find the body in the news
breaks that was a fine ballot from Gus
loan in advance bobble and now
yeah this is Cleveland listen I got to
talk to you talk I mean not on the phone
I want to meet with you check everything
know what I'm trying to tell you this
den some trouble do you see the papers I
couldn't help that he was trying to
shake me down all right his father no
but what I warhead interested in the
details but listen let me tell you you I
ain't interested we've got no time to
play with we're only interested in one
thing you get in that job and I'm gonna
tell you is I don't want to do the job
what I went out all right now listen
carefully item 14 just thinking what you
just said you're in real trouble and
they're gonna hear about this call I'm
all hidden to you made a contract with
us you'll do the job and you'll do it
right then we'll listen to your problems
you've got to New Year's Eve and
remember you're in trouble now
the worst trouble in your life but you
can't get the scream out of you had to
concentrate for the first time in your
life you don't want to be alone
hello Lori this is Frank Oh Lori I've
got to see you something wrong are you
in trouble no I know troubling I've just
got to see you it's important Frank I'm
sorry but it's just impossible for me to
get away from the next couple of days
Christmas we practically my whole family
comes to town on you tell me how fun no
boy I wanted to see you when I tell you
Frank if it's about the other night I'd
like you to know I have no hard feelings
and as far as I'm concerned we're still
the same friends ok ok Frank I did
really can't talk any longer now but why
don't you call me next week when things
won't be as hectic
alright Lori out I speak to you soon
okay my Frank ah my by the way I'd like
to wish you a happy new year
thanks
okay she doesn't know it but she just
did you a big favor you're alone the way
you were born your heads cooler and the
screams fading away Dan's is still hot
but you know why
another bad moment another contact to
pick up the gun fat Ralphie ordered and
you wonder how much the contact knows
about Ralphie's being whacked out and if
it means something to him hey where can
I find you a butterface what do you want
to know for I'm a friend of it he sent
terrorism he asked me to say hello I'm
Joe Boniface you got some merchandise
I'm interested in come on up
what do you want I can use a 38 special
with a silencer oh yeah add a lot of
trouble getting it they're not easy to
get dogs you know and pop you getting
paid
you're all right he doesn't know or
doesn't care you're relaxing now hands
cold again they'll be a gun in them soon
and your minds running clear and cool
expert as an engineer designing a bridge
you could have been an engineer
you're moving now smooth like a piece of
precision machinery before you hit the
target in this little love nest you have
to know everything about the flat and
the building as well as the architect
who built it you could have been an
architect to
you
hello hello mrs. Lana so good to see you
can never get through here there's so
much work I can never get through all I
staying dirty but you know the people
upstairs don't think I'm entitled to a
life of my own I have a right to my own
life
keeping watch on troiano you feel I hate
shaping up at the back Ian like where
the hair is short that's a good sign to
get a feeling this is how it was meant
to be like you are try a nose faith like
your God
now you know you have a free hour inside
the love nest
relax watch it steady Frankie boy so the
names phone rings well you get the crazy
idea was Laurie calling her head
concentrate no gun concentrate
concentrate a life depends on it no
neighbors to begin from any window
troiano want that is privacy okay not
just about wraps it up in a beautiful
package just a couple more details
before you tie the baby blue ribbon on
it
the last day in just a few more hours
your job will be done checked and
rechecked
you
nothing can go wrong no mistakes because
this is your last job you got that
figured out now you faced fact you know
you're through you killed fat Ralphie
and panic then you try to run out they
don't like that that people who hire you
they say a guy's cracking up when that
happens maybe that right watch it hold
on till it's over
how do you like that it's not in your
head at all an orphanage crummy
orphanage right under your nose
remember e
you
just one more killing Frankie than you
through one more to die and then you
won't have to be alone
you know Frankie you're really a very
attractive guy how come you're not
married but you probably need is a girl
or someone someone that you could feel
good with someone who could make you
feel at home
Frankie Laurie I want to talk to him oh
I'm terribly sorry Frank it's so early
it's important you know what we said the
other night about what you're told not
but needing somebody well I've been
thinking about it and you might I do
need somebody what I'm trying to say is
this sorry I need you Frank I'm sorry
Laurie sweetheart have you got one hello
Frank what the hell is this I'm I'm
terribly sorry Frankie you must have
misunderstood what it's just that you
were so lonely I just thought you
thought what well you really are a cold
shower what then nevermind nevermind I
understand Merry Christmas watch it
Frankie danger signals like electric
current like lightnings like fire in the
night and sirens screaming and add don't
think don't remember don't look ahead
concentrate you have a job to do when
you're an expert a kill Oh doesn't kill
gets killed
you
one last contact to pick up your money
only a few minutes and then you'll be
alone again the way you are meant to be
the way you like it
this is Cleveland
God moves in mysterious ways they said
maybe he is on your side the way it all
worked out remembering other Christmases
wishing for something something
important something special and this is
it baby boy Frankie bono you're alone
now all alone The Scream is dead there's
no pain you're home again back in the
cold black sands
you