California is a strong brand the place
of dreams movie stars and new beginnings
with a heavenly climate but the Golden
State is running out of money and so is
the city of Los Angeles public services
are being cut unemployment is rising and
many people that lost their homes in the
economic crisis but optimism and the
belief in the power of America seem
unaffected who are the pioneers of the
New America in the making and how do
they see the future like to donate he
donation firefighters muffins
I like to do now sir
quarters anything else Ernie hey
donations meant to the fire priors Los
Angeles County Fire Department and loose
change quarters anything he'll smell the
fire department needs money yes no we're
suffering through the massive budget
cuts LA County LA City we're basically
anywhere California there's lack of
equipment we're cutting back I mean
would you like to have a house burning
and nobody come to save you wouldn't be
too good like to donate he donation
firefighters lumber we faced a huge
deficit this year in the city at one
point close to a half a billion dollars
deficit in the upcoming year what we've
had to do is reduce many of the services
potential that would have look at how we
get back to the core services what a
municipality is supposed to provide we
were almost potentially going to get
down to zero on a reserve fund with that
would that means is if we had any kind
of emergency we had some natural
disaster which unfortunately Los Angeles
often has had an earthquake fires we
wouldn't have the cash to be able to
respond this is a crisis that we're
facing in this country and the state in
the city and that we don't want to
become a third world country we can be
eternally optimistic but if your
optimism is blinding you to necessarily
some of the problems that you face it
just it's going to be a revolving door
in a cycle that we can't get out of
la was a huge hotbed in regards to the
host of crime bars it's been a very
large amount of people that have been
millions of people i would say that been
affected by this so as you can see there
are a lot of people here asking for
assistance and these fairs are something
that are going on a monthly basis within
the alley area so this is still a
tremendous need out there where do
people go after they are thrown out of
their house work many people go either
they move in with family or they just
try to look for somewhere to go rent so
a lot of things were you seen is that
people have been moving in you have any
two or three families living in one unit
because a lot of people have either
maybe so if you haven't lost their home
today they've lost their jobs so we're
seeing a lot of kids coming back home to
the parents home we're seeing families
combine because the situation is very
difficult right now I think Oh Park has
always been one of my favorites and I
think that's why we started going over
there once we realize we could legally
park there because for me like that's
where I grew up so it feels very like
home to me I feel comfortable there I
just love it I love all the big oak
trees it just makes me feel like my
childhood so peaceful Hey Baby you want
hamburgers Justin ring about hot dogs
hot dog yeah I think the kids are prefer
hot tub watch out Justin you can't come
over here someone's gonna get really hot
we'd you doing today hi where'd you trek
though I was working at a hotel as a
reservations agent it was a really good
job and I loved it in school we learned
that California is I think it was the
seventh largest economy in the world not
just the country of America but just to
say to California when I started working
it was so easy to find jobs i mean i'd
walk in somewhere hey you hiring like
and they'd have work for you to do it
was no problem at all and since I've
been back it's incredible to me how much
the town has changed how much how many
more people are in their cars how many
more people are on the streets how many
more businesses are closed down you know
empty storefronts and it's just bad you
guys ready to eat yeah Taylor before we
actually uh we were living here in Santa
Barbara and a two bedroom apartment for
year and a half then know how long did
it take i mean you bought us your job it
was it was so fast it was i lost my job
in two weeks later she lost her job and
then and then it was tried two weeks
after that we were in a motel I mean it
was it was fast I'm an electrician and
when all the the housing market crashed
worked out really really hard to find
and just haven't really gotten any
better since will they give us food
stamps you can only buy food with it and
I think they give us 600 a month for
that so that's actually quite a bit of
food it's pretty much the only thing we
have is we have a lot of food but not
many places that cook it so this is the
only place that I found so far that we
can cook actual food our refrigerator an
RV doesn't work our heater doesn't work
burners don't worry Taylor I said stay
in sight Justin come on oh well that's
good honey but we're not gonna come back
and play here we're gonna go over to the
parking lot yeah yeah yeah nice well
it's either dinner or beds hailer yeah
we still gotta eat you're just tired
after as soon as we started thinking
about the idea of buying an RV but the
last of our money and everything we
started looking for where we could park
and we started noticing there's just a
ton of rvs in this town and they're on
the street and when you go by at two in
the morning they all have their
generators running clearly people are
living in them they're not like
therefore when people are on vacation
like you might think people are living
in them and I didn't realize how many
people until we started doing this
especially for families or people with
children who are living out of their car
and Santa Barbara has this great program
the safe parking program where they
provide people with a parking space like
this where it's off the road where we're
not going to get harassed by people
probably won't get broken into and we
won't get harassed by police or ticketed
or towed or anything like that we're
totally safe sleeping here so that's
basically the program I mean it has its
limitations of course it's only here
during the nighttime but it's a good
program so we can come here anytime
after 7pm but then we have to be gone by
7am you're angry at somebody for ending
up in this situation oh no um can you do
I mean he lost his job and then I lost
my job like I'm a little mad at us we're
not having more of a savings but we
never made me try and that was kind of
all we could scrounge together by the
time this happened to us but um I mean
everybody's hurting for jobs my
employers were so kind to me and they
let me go they were so nice they felt so
bad they just had to do it and his head
to too so I can't be mad at anybody I
just you know we just are trying to find
work you know if either one of us can
get a job then we should be a lot better
off
Rocco
well the class divisions are getting so
much further you know it used to be that
you really could be born with nothing
here and like work your way up the
ladder and I've been reading so much on
the middle ladder rungs are just like
not there anymore there's just becoming
more and more of a divided and we know
in history that it's never good for
countries and there's that much of a
divide between the people with money and
the people you know when the people
without are doing really you know the
worst of the people without money do the
angrier they're going to become the more
desperate they're going to become you
know they're just becomes more robberies
more crime you know eventually I mean in
history eventually they would just rise
up as I mean you know it could be very
problematic if that continues in Miami
Justin Christine
that's rise from the beginning safe
parking program
hi how are you doing good how are you
good and I saw you parked down here and
thought I'd come and check on you and
see what I could do there are a lot of
people who are losing their homes you
can see all the for lease for sale for
rent signs everywhere it wasn't like
this a few years ago some people are
very depressed I mean it's depressing to
lose your job in your home and maybe
some of your possessions you know it's a
very degrading thing for people to go
through when they start losing all the
things that they knew or and had worked
hard for Candice hi how are you doing
are you still over at Casa Esperanza
this is jess and he and his two sons who
were 14 and 15 live on the bus and
they've been in a program about four
years how are you doing good yeah you
need anything oh yeah six tires he has
six new tires for the boss huh yeah yeah
you need to get that money together I
talked to my boss and who doesn't have
any cash that's always his story well no
it's true I mean we didn't get very much
this year from the city or from any
people will usually donate yeah so
things have been pretty bad now while
food bank day is thursday so i'll come
by and see on thursday after the food
bank in the afternoon drop off some food
and stuff how did you end up in business
oh the dot-com bubble and i lost my
houses and everything eventually and
this is what we had left to live in
software engineering software
engineering and then you were fired no
then my company went on business I was
the CEO of a major com well professor
looks like there's a show today haha
testing we're having a problem though I
don't know if this microphone is working
it please young man the mother Teresa of
social work in California if you can say
glockens feel without smiling Don Pardo
what do they get they worked for CBS
News he was Dan Rather's film editor and
work for CBS LA you look familiar which
parking lot are you at you do have to
eat my box yah ah oh you're all ready to
do collections for flute and everything
huh I tried it once it didn't work do
you guys have spare change uh-huh give
you I don't have any sorry I'm sorry I
don't have a thing hey he's in love
firepower I that's brother 60 you don't
feel that the city governments should be
taking care of these people well the
city government and the city in many
cities across the country and especially
in the state of California is in the red
right now to the tune of several
millions of dollars and so don't think
it's up to the government and I think
we've just seen the tip of the iceberg
here in California there's going to be
less and less money so it's going to
take more people being creative thinking
outside of the box and doing something
to be a part of the solution and so the
problem
another puppy nah yeah lots of puppy
dogs around today hey yeah dog
I was working at a hotel I was working
at this hotel here the fess parker's
doubletree yeah it's a little
embarrassing to know me like parked
across the street in my RV and I always
hope I don't see some of the people that
I used to work with running around lon
did you ever I haven't no luckily yeah
you like to say hi
where we go in DJ what's your biggest
fear that the kids will and eventually
you know they will still be doing this
when the kids are old enough to realize
the situation we're in that it'll
somehow embarrass them it's cool
that's my fears that it embarrass them
that's on the embarrassing will be
ashamed of their parents or their home
hmm that make you cry um I don't like to
look at life like fears I like look as
just challenged this omari my biggest
challenge is to get us back out of this
situation
I'm in jobs Club which you know I go
every morning 830 in the morning I have
to be there i'm usually there for about
an hour hour and a half each other you
resumes and how to talk to him employee
they videotape you so you can see what
you look like when you're doing a resume
excuse me coming through guys with real
thank you
I feel frustrated just because I feel
like I'm letting my own family down I'm
posed to be the person that's taken care
of him there's so many jobs out there
that we don't eat opportunity to have um
in this in this state I can't be a cook
I used to be a cook when I was in high
school and if you don't speak Spanish
you don't get to be a cook the
immigration problem I think is one of
the largest problems to our to
California and California is upset right
you have to go back to way it's supposed
to be is hiring your own citizens for a
proper wage instead of having these
citizens that are coming from a
different country and working for half
that way
how often do you come here looking for
jobs every day every day what do you
look at usually craigslist monster com
just any job ads on the internet
anywhere i can find jobs well I've
putting out resumes and applications and
no returns it's the handbook for job
search I think that if you've actually
maybe graduated high school or had a
couple jobs this stuff would be pretty
repetitive and kind of insult you in
your intelligence in a way that they
wouldn't have now they got a teacher
there to teach you stuff but not really
teaching the normal person anything
that's going to help them in the real
day getting a job that says you have to
bathe and shower prior to interview
we're clothing that is clean pressed in
a well-fitted wear appropriate clothing
that footwear make sure your hair is
clean and combed hands are clean brush
your teeth stretching your breath no gum
we're supple perfume and cologne if any
tattoos you have to cover them if you
can I rarely get to take a shower as it
is right now or my suit is there but
it's not pressed you know I my polished
shoes probably aren't the most polished
but you know you do what you can and
that's just the hard with a job market
you
let's do a driving lesson nice so funny
well here's the thing is is that we're
getting in our car to drive two blocks
like if this is locked everything
because we could have walked two blocks
but know that we're gonna take two cars
to go a few hundred meters it's less
than 100 meters that's just wrong way
let's park here
we can leave it
public free it's true the crazy part is
how delicious it is smells really good
now that's talent hmm what we just did
pick public fruit from the streets of
Los Angeles in in in the neighborhood of
Silver Lake we all live in this
neighborhood and that's how we began we
just made a map of all the trees that
were like this one what's so great about
this particular neighborhood is that
these trees were planted a really long
time ago by we don't know who but the
public because there's no law about the
sidewalks about who owns a space this is
the city and behind the walls is the
people's property so in this area
there's no law that says that you can't
do this and so in the city of La they
say that it is not illegal to pick this
fruit people want locally produced and
nothing is more local than this right
combined with a terrible economic
situation so of course it's going to
change the way people live in the cities
everywhere this is like this is this
trees perfect for la carte car culture
because I have to do is drive by and
stick out your hand and then drive away
but I through fertilizer on this tree um
a few weeks ago you did yeah I did Thank
You Matias so the peach tree that we
just picked we call a drive-by fruit
because you can you can sit as you're
driving and just pick fruit from the
window of your car
here you have a very different kind of
public oh yeah here we go yeah the fruit
vendor was really yummy because they
puts like cup in salt and cayenne pepper
people that I know that have lost their
homes they they are okay in a way they
do lose their house they do lose the
money and the time they put into their
homes but the people i know have changed
they've moved to other cities they have
moved in with family they there's a
connectedness that wasn't there 10 years
ago we were very detached and people
were more interested in objects and now
people are more interested in experience
over there that's a dragon fruit right
there those cactus really ya know these
are the bananas yeah and there's a
little their flowers yeah these are the
bananas in the sea they're coming so
this is crazy because it'll it'll just
keep going to the sidewalk this one's
really good with it so public you know
what's so cool about this place on these
people is at these this is like the
epitome of you know like the generous
today yeah he planted all this stuff so
they could share it with his neighbors
yeah he planted an avocado incredible
yeah you guys share all your fruit
have you ever had the grapefruit from
around the corner on marathon no we
haven't really done too much foraging
around the neighborhood eat of people
here we have Meyer lemons and we have
Eureka lemon and we have bartender lime
and that's a navel orange and in the
back we have tangerine and blood orange
and on the other side of the yard we
have tomatoes and tomatillos we have
broccoli red cabbage brussels sprouts
artichokes
I think maybe one out of every three
people doesn't have a job right now in
Los Angeles it's pretty close to that
what about you yeah I lost my job last
year along with a bunch of my friends at
the same time the university system let
a lot of people go you were teaching
yeah I taught University for 16 years
since I was a kid and yeah that x over I
think
a lot of situations that happen in our
lives that we they seem insurmountable
and and and we just we get stuck in them
or we just can't see beyond them so so
what I want to encourage everybody to do
today is to think about not everything
that is faced can be changed that's true
these are certain things life that we
can't write but nothing can be changed
until it is face so try it try to face
it whatever it is however small or large
it is try it and take little baby steps
towards towards facing whatever
challenges whatever demons whatever we
hold within ourselves alright that's the
pop
all of these are going to be for today
yeah this side that side and this tube
okay these are added them because they
haven't confirmed but then they
confirmed do you all know of no files
mm-hmm I don't know let alone but I
don't know wasn't be here this guy's
gonna be here for sure Rafi shahi
Shannon too many good those yeah so
you're gonna be next okay you are my
face um I got this the first time I went
to jail um this one you Ernest by
killing somebody Kuala traces no no no
and then this one is for for love no
love the game love the game or no why do
you want to get them remove future I
don't want I don't want to told me back
when i get job you know and it makes
people look at you differently a lot
differently Lance I don't want that
trying to change my life she was a
little grouchy to
I'm progress since I've been out of
doors in all different directions yeah
I'll hang on oh boy I go to work come
home and that's it good for you she
congratulations that's a big deal did 14
years this piece federal return Stanford
took his case Stanford Law School
session after law school don't think
that there is that that group that does
that that specific they look at these
cases think so yeah that is a DNA and
all that's what they did for him did it
for me it took my case to them two years
given the cords they did a declaration
for my whole pass under control violence
they proved all that to the courts so
how long were you in 14 14 years for
something you didn't do well I did it
but it doesn't cost when he fires life I
like a radio you know oh right okay so
the judge had told a DA this man
observed 25 life for a radio he's a
repeat offender but for petty crimes and
25 years I'm letting this man go when I
walked out of the county jail not the
back door I walked up the street and
walk back towards the county cuz society
is differently I'm still adjusting I
don't go out as much because it's
dangerous out in society I always can
look all my surroundings the building's
the streets um surrounding people around
me on the cars the phones iPods
everything's different pretty working on
this to block this
this that till all the lot of it okay
and we doing this ideas that is we start
to fade or it okay and up here and all
this okay go to drop you remember how it
all works right here and how it feels
yeah you want to squeeze bowl
I got this tattoo and I was just a kid
and all the rest was done in prisons at
the time I wanted to be a gangster at
that time you know started drinking
really young age we stayed wherever I
could I was homeless mostly downtown
laid I caught up in LA to the streets
parks box had it hard
okay sound all right all right all right
good luck all right thank you you're
very welcome these games
so I live at home my mom and dad I'm own
room I got my own gym in the backyard I
got weights you know I got my fix it all
the way I wanted my room looks like
Circuit City I got teased and bone boxes
and walking out of the CD players and
nice clothes and stuff this is dubbed
under her head and I accomplished all
this in the year you know it's luxury
bud and I worked for to what he was
growing up he was a good kid and now i'm
glad he's back on course again that he
paid for his mistakes but he / page of
mistakes anyway but thing is that now
then but now he's warded his 40s now and
he lost all his or his youth being
locked up to miss it's not fair at all
so somebody owes him but he can't get
his life back that he took from him
that's what's that
let's do it
when I was in prison and you know they
talked about the deficit how people lost
their houses and everything because of
the crisis I gotta look I find a job so
I hold on to that job and I you know and
I just like you know I try not you know
yes sir no sir and do my job you know
and there on time actually I'm opposed
to be I work at three I'm they're about
to 215 just sitting there and start work
I sit in my car and read my Bible and
then I go in there having a little cup
of noodle soup and start work and I
worked 48 hours a week six days a week I
make 300 almost 400 a week and with that
I pay bills with it and I go pay the
bills right away soon as i get them I
never wait I get them and I go pay the
bills the next day soon as I get my
check I go pay bills so all we have to
worry about anything like that here
around here this is all filling up with
new stuff sweatshirts jeans brand new
jeans socks t-shirts you know you got a
lot of stuff yeah but yeah stuff that I
never had you know and that's not it
there's more all new stuff and t-shirts
and so tight tank tops and t-shirts and
stuff like that and and I see something
i'll buy it bank card checking and Bing
card so it's late I don't have to worry
little more you know i was like i can
buy it if i wanted you know i don't have
to robber still one more
hey
I think the only certainty in today's
day and age that is that things are
going to be in a state of constant flux
and uncertainties so my own philosophy
with what's raising my own children is
that you know the most important
capacity is to be adaptive and to know
how to learn but the fact that you know
these economic crises the fact that you
know jobs are moving between countries
in a way that's completely unpredictable
that we really don't know what the
future holds in terms of the sort of
opportunities that are out there that to
me seems like the one certainty that we
have for today's kids
I work at the University of California
so we have felt the economic crisis for
sure there's been huge budget cuts but
this idea that that public university is
going to be there is one of the finest
educational institutions that supplies
education at low cost this model is
coming under challenge as the University
of California is facing these budget
shortfalls having to raise tuition and
increasingly relying on private money
for funding for my own kids I'm
extremely hopeful because I think that
for them they're really able to take
advantage of a lot of the opportunities
that the new media environment has to
offer so much of this access to
knowledge is happening in very private
settings if you have a family that
doesn't have a computer going to the
school library for an hour every other
day is not the same as having a
smartphone always connected to the
internet being able to be on myspace and
facebook with your friend all the time
that gap is really huge and the school
is not really a context that can mediate
that disparity anymore
um these two computers are connected
well I can go to both at the same time
and my mouth can connect between for
your real s or your virtual bit girl
yeah what well cuz I can play with her
however I want but these big guy down
there only yeah I can only do what the
computer program I think what we're
moving towards is towards digital
technology becoming a very sort of
pervasive part of everyday life so that
we don't really think about the
distinction between the real and virtual
as something radically different
I think the worst case scenario is that
these sort of technologies that will
accelerate the divide between the more
privileged and less privileged and I
think a city like la is a place where
you might see that happening so I think
that is the worst case scenario i think
the best case scenario is that it will
actually help bridge them of those
divides
you
my name is Laura Burkhalter I'm an
architect and I've been thinking about
the urban paradigm my whole life because
I believe that there's another way my
dream is that the city becomes a city
for people instead of a city for cars
and money and power that the city is
built by people for people I envision
infrastructure for people for example
bicycle freeways where you could cross
the city from one end to the other with
a without a single traffic light I guess
the crisis helped us out we had a baby
on the way and we were looking to move
into an apartment to rent and it was so
expensive reason you can't afford it you
know we started thinking well maybe now
it's the time to look at all the stuff
that foreclosed on and bank owned and no
one wants it so we were lucky to get
this place for less than half of what it
would have been two years before can we
get to share it with our friends with
our community and grow food I think a
lot of people are starting to turn on to
the idea of growing their own food too
because it's really probably better for
you obviously the things that you buy
from the supermarket that are from out
of the country or grown a lot of
pesticides or something thousands of
next really cost-effective oh yeah it's
much more cost effective and I think
that's why people are also getting
behind it right now because not you I
read something I forget it's like a
sixth time you use six-fold ear money
mmm right like let's say you buy tomato
client for three dollars the amount of
tomatoes you get from it is like only
six times more than what it would cost
you to buy the tomatoes right it is also
making people aware that they can do it
in their apart
it because know everyone is fortunate I
have like an amazing space like this and
like I'd love to be able to learn how to
grow like little plants on my balcony or
you know something like that I would do
that when we have the space on my
balcony and it's absolutely the case
that produce is expensive now way more
than it used to be for right is being
more conscious and doing it again yeah
yeah I mean well is it expensive it's
the enough can afford to go to Whole
Foods exactly this is what I'm saying I
think after the crisis I think in
anyone's mind whether you're an
entrepreneur or a person a citizen of
any nation status is how do you become
empowered and self-sufficient because we
have this crisis and people were
dependent upon a system and now I think
there's a lot of a lot of people are
lost and trying to figure what happened
and what's going on I think the best
cure I guess or what I think is action
and how do you be self-sustainable how
do you empower yourself I think the
system has made us believe that very
powerless that were just at the mercy of
the system but we're not because the
system can only exist with us buying
into the system and if we don't and we
start creating our own reality then the
system can no longer exists that way
this is our workout for the day
what I think it takes to get anything
done is first of all for people to start
bearing to imagine what would a cool
City be like what would it be like to
live in a really awesome City what would
that look like and then step two is to
start taking some action just a door
right here no that's too how friend this
is a half bro let's maybe let's find out
what the door yeah that's good all right
here sister that looks rectangular right
I could take it this way kind of toss it
i'll toss it up okay the sense of
community is becoming much more
important than it used to be people
depend on each other they didn't used to
depend at all everyone was like off to
themselves and looking for their own
interest and now people need each other
this is a bedroom and lauren will live
here first i think one of these this one
might be getting it up which one is the
long one this one's longer if it's you
you don't have a bedroom now I do but
I'm moving out of place so and then to
be offered to live here and I would
definitely look here yeah oh one is
super long this one this one you like I
grew up in a commune and we were very
much on top of each other and I think
this one will take care of some of the
issues that I think happened in the more
typical commune setups so I want to find
out if it's possible to have a you know
kind of a more modern version of how to
live in a city communally in the
seventies people they felt like everyone
has to follow one thing is I'm a
vegetarian you all have to be
vegetarians if I don't drive a car one
has to not drive a car it was more
ideological and now I think it's more
practical in a way
you know about farming I'm learning
learning as I go six beautiful and so
meditated kind of go on my zone I think
that gold rush is over yes people don't
have the possibility to go after it
because there's no nothing of value that
you can just like flip and make quick
cash so that's the whole premise of gold
rush is that the end of the American
dream no I think the American Dream is
bigger than that I think that's just one
part of the American dream that's been
the expression of the American dream in
the past you know couple decades but I
don't think that's the whole American
dream I think the American Dream has to
do with a self expression to freedom and
it's been caught up in this kind of want
to have you know materialistic aspect of
the American dream but I think Americans
are very optimistic people and they they
will get back up so I think the freedom
is now being redefined and I think
that's still the American Dream is
freedom but maybe its freedom from the
system maybe it's you know having your
own solar cells and your own power and
not having to pay into the system and
having ways to gather round that's not
part of the gasoline company's profit
it's another kind of freedom
one thing about Americans is that
they're very flexible I think it's going
to take longer for the rest of the world
to accept a new identity for America
than it is going to be for Americans to
accept the new identity because people
change their lives all the time here and
that it's kind of the way it is and oh
this is over what's next you know let's
start over
you