all the children
understand
kids
and some
pretty
Oh
Casper
this
Oh
God
this isn't happening this isn't
happening this is not happening I
thought people only fooling dreams
that's it I'm having a nightmare whew
wake up Casper come on snap out of it
hey mister what's going on what happened
to me yeah scram Debbie I'm in a grave
move he what's his problem um why you
strangle a lady the processing station
now let me rest in peace excuse me but
uh where am I that's simple fog boy kiss
me
what are you trying to do kill me oh
wait
how do you do that
welcome to deedstown this excited quiet
place I hope someone here can help me
don't worry
pardon me sir I'm new hearing well
welcome to deedstown sunny a ghost where
what's going on what's everybody going
crazy for
I don't see any ghosts
mmm
bye
you
this is Captain Carson speaking
beautiful of the day ISM the x-files
t-shirt
g-money full minutes and Counting you go
to bed early to I am dad but I was
working on these sketches what do you
think nice we're going to see the alpha
5 hey just what this town needs fresh
blood out with the old in with the new
no what's the food Chris I'm on a diet
fine wool for me oh don't forget
tonight's my open how to school I really
want you to see my post as soon as I
tear down the old Applegate place I'm
not to mention I don't start it's the
first phase of my plans for the
renovation of the town and the mayor
loves it like an old mansion it's really
spooky no more supernatural stuff I'll
see you later oh don't forget Tory
you
smile on
No
barks for crass commercial eyesores
real Carson gets here
please ladies and gentlemen I have an
announcement today please ladies and
gentlemen just listen to me for one
second we are not the enemies we are
just here to improve our town and we're
gonna do that by giving you a brand new
mini mall please gentle the first thing
we've got to do is tear down this
dilapidated wreck this house survived
the decades and we'll make sure it
survives you look lady I mean cut me
some slack this place is falling apart
the best thing we can do is replace it
with something useful like what another
burger stand ladies and gentlemen
whether you like it or not about two
seconds this place is gonna become
killing would my apologies Stan
Louisville this puppy
I'm calling the show
anti it
ribbit oh gosh her
get it found back Oh God
run you better leave you better go in I
go
everything
coming back to fire up yo J
hey
let him go
Oh
miss me miss my skin i will eat them but
I count Fletcher your mind cuz
possession is nine to the law your body
manic we got a fleshie down coming
doctor I learned this trick for my buddy
it's a folder guys party
technicolor so how about Karami hey move
it pal
no parking zone
his face see what happens when he don't
set your own
sun rose now before you run off pal you
better check in today what's weird
exactly oh what a crack-up
oh my allergy
I told you reading too much Gary my job
boys the world is our oyster our
playground I'll oishi this day okay
everybody sheriff's on his way so you
wow he sure works fast hello snacky blog
oh but look creepy Chris Carson sure he
ranked you spiders as pets yeah probably
eats him too let's pay him a friendly
visit so you walk to another weirdo
convention truck check it out this is
written about himself you guys really
need new material shut up feet girl
pulverize pulverize well bracha
three-syllable word we're on earth the
Prince already holds back a grade
I'm gonna love taking you up wacko
definitely the work of ghostly trio this
I gotta see
damn it's Tim where's my crew hey adios
reservoir Dave I need this house down
well then you got two options Tim find
another outfit or start huffing and
puffing look you're the last demolition
crew in town if mayor hunt is not posing
in front of some rubble today I'm dead
tough we don't do ghosts union rules
Dave there are no such things as ghosts
we good or what yeah just like the u.s.
care for hey fatso lighten up huh and
don't turn on the lights oh yeah I knew
that did we ever scoop 10 pound bags
yeah they didn't even stand a ghost of a
chance then plushie sure can run I'll
say maybe they take extra vitamin E
maybe we're just the best you sure are
say cheese where
we'll take 38 by pins hey it's that
snoop again mommy rob was a nice touch
guys but the wedgie is sent a bit over
you don't you think who is you nosey
nice try oh it's mr. scare me not
looking how many times we got a failure
this is an exclusive club and you ain't
invited hey what's that aha this is a
condemned building and according to the
ectoplasmic botanica it's a public place
fleshies ain't suppose bad this where'd
you get it spook Ramage catalog how come
you guys decided to move here that's
sane our home don't what is a nice
location oh yes excellent view to
something of a fixer-upper though well
you know chef yeah yeah guys I know a
lot about ghosts wayang with you
you're a little late for that event kid
besides us house with a bone bag don't
make me laugh so make me puke don't eat
beans around the camp kill bad guys feed
it by pen you don't scare right Jos more
they know oh my gosh I'm late for school
ah
was fine meow
whoa you they come
all right all right everybody settle
down folks settle down I am sniffle and
welcome to our ghost train station in
other words the station where we train
you to be ghosts get it okay over the
next few weeks you the rookies will be
learning the abcs of the ghost life okay
again at which time you will be issued a
hunting license all right now you
deadbeats file through here ready March
all right everybody come on what are you
looking at move I Young's never like
target keep on moving but much much much
you didn't laugh at my jokes and the
grand total is 5 huh no who's missing
Casper oh did you say mr.
I'm in charge here in nobody skills
training especially little snack noses
named Carter la that's a Casper sir
Santa's what I want your help of course
pomelo one now about this caster Casper
and sigh how would it look if I the
mighty kibosh that some wide-eyed rookie
run loose without any schooling very
embarrassing sir embarrassing is
displaceable almost as bad as losing
track of those three worm-headed
deserters what would an inch stinky
stretch in fat soap sir when I find
those slackers I'll tie a sheepshank on
their bed sheet but your blood pressure
stupendous one I have no blood now find
me this Casper and bring his sorry
cookie playing twist back here
immediately
hi excuse me ma'am can you help me
please well of course but where are you
I'm over here just don't be scared okay
gracious may who'd be scared of a little
boy I wish someone would just talk to me
oh this reminds me I got to see my
dentist Tim the news is here to record
me giving a glorious speech in front of
a platen house and it is if I know mr.
mayor it's nuts one second my crew was
raring to go the next they're hauling
ghosts ghosts oh no he's just joking
around he's a kidder you know Tim ghost
rumors have been coming into my office
for the past month yes mr. mayor but
most of them are prank calls their their
kids they're drunks their nut cases my
wife and charming intelligent women oh
my wife is very intelligent it takes for
an hour and a half two hours 16 minutes
I have enough trouble keeping people
from leaving this air town so ixnay on
the ghosts yes sir I'm sorry about that
uh mr. mayor we're almost ready for you
oh I'm cool everything is cool now you
get that beat-up piece of lumber down by
tomorrow you're finished
you
hey listen sorry about this morning you
know guess I missed breakfast or
something whatever you know I really
liked your oral report about that alien
spaceship then why'd you throw a rock at
me that was Danny not me I mean I loved
your report right Leon oh yeah thanks
well of course you know mr. Pfister
graph liked it better than all of us put
together well I guess I got into it you
know my favorite part when that sold you
got slimed by that alien that was i
jested file imagine if that bad boy
dropped on you from the sky all right
who's responsible for this well she was
really just sort of standing there you
know good principal baby yeah go to my
office what excuse me I'll take care of
this one he was tardy this morning very
well thank you
the rest of you but it's okay Chris I
know you didn't do anything in fact I
know that broth is pals have been
picking on you for some time I know them
kill their losers no but you got to
stand up for your rights you can't let
people get away with that kind of
nonsense it's like applegate mansion we
don't stand up for it people are gonna
tear it down and build some new choke
and puke I shouldn't drag you into the
middle of my feud with your father hey
there he is how'd you know I'm dedicated
to breathing new life into deedstown and
what better way than building the
deedstown shopping gallery the dum-dum
donut and a stop and spend are gonna
save this town there there has been some
opposition to the destruction of these
old homes is that why applicate mansion
is still standing I think our talented
building contractor Tim Carson should
answer that one duh hi oh well TV
cameras aren't usually so flattering
plan to revitalize the town is to remove
all symbols of our stagnant past those
are historical landmarks our first
attempt was delayed by interference from
a few no ghosts right uh militant
reactionaries militant no need to worry
though the deedstown rejuvenation
project will soon be back on track
sweetly that weasel you can count on it
well Buster I'm gonna have another rally
see
you haven't heard the last of sheila mr.
Roth
I'm sorry no problem whoa he didn't
scream hey you didn't run away oh wow
ghost hi let me get your picture you
mean you're not scared of me are you
kidding I love goes Bennett's front
flying and vanishing all i know is
everybody just screams at me and runs
away sounds pretty lonely you don't know
how lonely let me guess you feel like no
one's on your side no one world cares
about you and no one really likes you I
feel like that every day hey we've got a
lot in common I'm press Casper swore do
you write huh you know go some places
they do of course didn't you go to spook
school no can I know just you need to
see come on all right
this is my hideout awesome huh yeah
really creepy so there are other ghosts
like me right they were here this
morning well till they get back I'll
teach him what about being scary but I
don't feel like scaring people it's your
job it says someone here okay then I I
guess I'll try good now this is how most
people think of ghosts whoa what that
they're blind just be one with the Sheep
for a minute let your ghostly instincts
guide you young spook walk okay I'll try
here goes Oh can't we cut some eye holes
in this oh oh man this is stupid Chris
try to be scared by standing still all
right I'll try boo powder whoo scarier
this kid has serious problems now he's
dressing up his friends like us he's
pathetic even by fleshy standards hey
you guys are just in time I could use
your help what's going on who's out
there it's a ghostly trio we know who we
are those fish the phantom of the white
sale no way he is honest say hi to cast
hello he's one of us well shrieking and
salutations Casper I'm stretch and this
is my brother stinky ask him how he got
his name how'd you get you I stink
therefore I am and this entire fog bank
over here there's a weather front name's
fatso I'm not really fat just big boned
so you guys can teach me how to change
shapes and stuff what's the matter kid
didn't I teach you not let the train
excite that he never went every ghost
goes through training ha oi stitch is a
golden opportunity that can is genuine
raw material unspoiled by kibosh hotcha
ChaCha Casper and the trio yeah here's a
chance how attendings abetting his then
maybe you'll stop hunting for us ok kiss
fit yeah
the screen thing now yeah and we're
gonna teach you all our tricks and
treats of the train I'll work really
hard honest that's the spirit spirit
wait through kibosh years about this
major brownie points for the snip leg
the first thing you gotta line it's hard
to go in that stealth amar yeah your
weight to construct to us otherwise oh
wow I gotta learn how to do this just
clean your mind think clear thoughts
what win or gasps gasps was it be okay
Casper high five bud no over here higher
gotcha this is so cool and that's just
the beginning short sheet but it's
suckers on a lab for the rest sorry
union rules well I've got important
stuff whoa all right wow thanks Chris
see you later so uh what's first guys
nighty but I only know how to hover just
give a shit Oh
couldn't we start with the step ladder
or something nonsense the best way to
learn is this fair away what's that good
this teaching business is hard Luck's
gotta be someone else Angie well there
is one place we haven't tried who's that
I'm getting demolition get him on the
phone Armageddon now sergeant bill case
yeah hi this is a Tim Carson over here
in deedstown sir I've got a building I
need torn down I volunteer you haven't
seen yet nothing mattered natural and
man-made I make it gone hold on please
junior face what was that just a little
extermination job pockemon has a gopher
problem correction had Missy so when can
we meet tomorrow 1300 hours your HQ eat
your Wheaties and be sharp soldier are
we insured well the flying went over
like a lead coffin now I want you to go
through this wall right here how about I
start with tissue paper and work my way
out no listen up champ say I am
invincible I am in a heap of trouble
stop that now look at this one and
concentrate see the wall I see the wall
now bait a wall I
and the walls now go through the wall I
am going through that's what the public
wants no faces okay okay forget boys try
for a good visual and watch me heads up
bone bag
sorry Kiera have limitations are out
this year ah rats keep trying
this better be important Casperson
deedstown you'll never guess who I hate
guessing snare oh I'm sorry your playful
one how foolish of me the answer is the
ghostly trio you'd better not be wrong
Casper their own unorthodox open may I
say illegal ghostly techniques the
hokies Casper de gym in your place don't
even say those words
luigi's can't out teach me check on that
progress on a full report tomorrow good
thing I'm already dead or that would've
killed me
so she's not a genius but she moves like
a gazelle I mean if Maggie doesn't get
into this dance club it could ruin her
chances forever of getting into incest
Alfred I myself wanted to go to Stanford
it didn't work out so she could use a
little extra help you know what I'm
telling you yes of course we excuse me
hi how are you still no dad huh you
promised you'd be here well it's still
early got some punch I already had three
gallons Thanks don't worry he'll show
and got a bit trash and burnt through it
I thought you liked it back ah thanks
Jennifer solution source right there
so you really believe it all this ghost
stuff sure don't you dare real ghosts
are all around you just got to know
where to look well maybe you can you
show me one someday sure sorry I gotta
go
one two three four five say something
all right Jim I'm not again uh-huh
uh-huh hey Tim the Martians have just
escaped from my pencil sharpener oh
that's nice Tim what you know you really
should go home and take a break away the
kid you know you probably misses you
chris is fine okay I've got that handled
and he knows that I'm up to my teeth and
work and it is not as easy to be a dad
and a mom who take it easy I'm sorry I
asked and I apologize sorry no problem
just this applicate thing has got me so
wound up I know I know but you know you
you really should take a break wish I
could I just got officially sketches for
the man all right I'll see you tomorrow
josh day
we got in spades up so here's a flyer
we're having a rally to say about the
gate match tomorrow so I hope you can
make it and Josh keep up the good work
I'll see you tomorrow okay so much there
you go here's your flyer you're doing
very well this semester thanks a lot for
come on night how you doing I knew we'd
flake out well something probably came
up something always comes up hmmm
phantoms poltergeist which one is your
favorite the and cheese then make a lot
of noise and nobody can understand what
they're saying they're Irish you know
they usually appear just before my dad
thinks I have an overactive imagination
Oh a good imagination is a powerful tool
it allows us to do great things like
saving a landmark against all odds I
like the way you think no you work
almost a charge from my dad mm-hmm well
I'll take that as a compliment come on
let me walk you to the door
hey why don't you have your dad come for
a private conference tomorrow at four
this way we can all meet sure but a
problem this bag it again sometimes I
think he likes us draw more than me well
we may surprise you my name is mr.
Graham by chris i'll see you tomorrow
okay oh great kid crummy dad mm no no
chivalry shrieks I gotta come from deep
inside you sixty vanden try again boo
good shit i'm thankful stuff wouldn't
even give a fleshie goosebumps I'm doing
the best I can oh boy George he's got it
oh sorry I said oh no ghosting spring Oh
Janet you guys we've been in it all day
why changing dismemberment Casper just
ain't getting it well I'm trying my
hardest you okay but you got a little
style it's cuz your motives are all
wrong basically you don't want to scare
you Minh what's wrong with being nice to
them ah I'm not hearing this huh I
they're gonna be sick now look what
you've done you breathing life and going
look little guy we know deep down inside
you're really gruesome and horrible but
we're just not seeing it besides if you
don't line it makes us look bad I'll
work harder sorry runt we've come
through a parting at the waves there's
no place in this world for a friendly
ghost dad lost get going get a life
I know I know I'm late I'm gonna grab a
bite at work Chris Chris Christmas ma'am
da you 12 we missed my open house hey
was that last night was the orchid deal
without appearing Oh buddy I'm so sorry
look there's pressure me hard right now
it's important to me I'm gonna make it
up to you pal whoa do you know what
today is huh huh do you know what today
is it's wild and crazy guy day you're
right yes it is says it right here you
and I are supposed to have a guys only
sit down dinner with no interruptions
you read my mind heist uh-huh and later
after that you and I can go to the
batting cage and this time I'll raviga
yeah still deal gotta go wait since you
didn't show up last night I've kind of
had a set up and doesn't mean for today
you know a parent-teacher one at 44 but
I have Chris buddy you can count on me
see you later
yeah well I'm glad one of us is happy
hey Casper did you hear dad might have
gone to the batting cage tonight then
it's good i stopped by now I just got
the boot so I'm leaving town for good
you can't leave what's ready I'm a lousy
ghost no you're not look you know how to
go into stealth mode big whoop that's
the only trick I know did the tree will
help you know they dumped me seems I'm
too nice to learn anything so I'm not a
human well not a ghost I'm a nothing
stop it look at those three losses won't
help you think I will oh why waste your
time cuz you look cow I am really yeah
and what's gonna help each other right
you couldn't help a dead alien fall over
very fine marshmallow head
the coast is clear are you sure about
this yeah I'm gonna teach you to be both
even if it kills you mmm no offense sure
pick on the living impaired skip over
the session I'm scary and stick with the
basics lesson one going through walls
hey no problem I've got that wire
I think you're gonna need this right
about now
yep this must be the place
right now
smooth move exlax so how did I do a
fourth Uzi azum but d-minus for control
follow me Casper
you really need to clean this thing out
we can play knee does listen to changing
shapes hey you're right thanks teach
okay lesson three invisibility I know
that one already yeah now I want you to
carry something heavy as well traffic
out the blue book you got it
I ghost taking lessons from a human
sorry Reese I'm surprised at you books
are our friends you must treat them
nicely oh sorry that was me be more
careful and I'm invisible I can't see
where I'm going library are you talking
to space cadet your imaginary pals
that's only because they dreamers don't
have any real friends mm-hmm don't you
have someplace to go like attention hey
come on guys let's go he's not bothering
us you think you're so smart don't you
freak crops talking to you keep ya geek
better watch out
they say this library is haunted by who
Ernest haunting way
no William Shakespeare
hey this is some sort of trick right
darn Hardy messing with
scuze me Brock finished chill off make
me run first the buckhead York Africa
alright was reading my editorial section
where I always do well all of a sudden
this is going on your permanent record
nothing like overkill oh he had it
coming this is going on his permanent
record way to go Casper I think you're
ready for the big time high five bud
yeah I want to go out and try my new
powers happy horny
oh I'm sorry I think I lost him you must
be built case hi I'm Tim Carson nice to
meet you ditto so what kind of ordnance
you're looking for here fragmentation
grenades c4 explosives missiles
plastique TNT cherry bombs help me out
here I don't know this oughta do the
trick hey you can detonate this with a
plunger a timer or simple open flame
that isn't real is it primitive is that
the target there yeah yeah this is a
very few problems it can't be solved
with a suitable application of high
explosives tomorrow that place will be
bite-sized is if you put this out please
huh ah don't worry about that doesn't go
boom without this that harmless is a
statement except one thing my office is
on fire control truck
now that I'm a real ghost I gotta try
out my new tenants on someone
hmm
whoa if I can scare him I can scare
anyone here goes hello how may I help is
a stick-up girls uh I'm sorry I didn't
mean to hey wait wait look I know you're
a ghost but you just saved my life thank
you really sure how about some jerky he
hates me wow this is great finally I
feel so alive mr. Graff high time for a
conference yeah Chris come on in I was
just getting ready for my big rally hey
maybe I could get you to carry one of
these signs tomorrow oh no there I go
again I'm sorry is my daddy here yet no
but he has a few minutes anything he's
coming this time no it come on I don't
want you to be late right okay the
teacher the teacher's name is faster or
mr. fuss Mr Graham right okay no really
bye bye hey would that be Sheila mr.
grass yeah I think so she's the one
behind the save the mansion movement
Christmas teacher mm-hmm I should have
known parent teacher conference huh my
Aunt Sally hey that's really good you're
a good artist excuse me Sheila Pfister
graph
but miss Lyons these conferences are
essential to the students what this is
school business no it has nothing to do
with the mansion will you tell mr.
Carson if he keeps dodging these
meetings the next call he'll get will be
from the Board of Education Chris I'm
sorry I'm afraid that your father isn't
gonna show hi I'm sure it's not your
fault I'm sure he's just under a lot of
pressure with his job well
Chris you should have seen me I was
awesome people all over town liked me
yeah now on I'm gonna use my powers to
help people I want to be their friend
I'm so happy for you What's Wrong dad he
flaked out again he forgets everything
about me hey parents don't like going to
school anymore and kids do but I'm sure
he'll remember your baseball thing hey
yeah the batting cages and we're
supposed to have dinner too well alright
get pumped dude and then I'll top it off
by introducing them to my best friend
who's that shoot two fists you'll have a
hard time forgetting that my teacher hi
mr. Rath hi he left us at school and I
thought you might want it back oh thanks
do you want us over anything oh um sure
alright cool man I'll be right back hey
I didn't know your dad like Frank Lloyd
Wright oh yeah he's a big fan huh
there's hope for him yet
what's this piece um that's to a coat
rack oh that's so cute just a mist no
here I'll get it you look round
oh here's me as a Klingon oh I love Star
Trek did you see the Wrath of Khan that
was a classic yeah you know I was really
hoping to talk to your dad about the
mansion did you know that nadine 05 the
applegates found at this town without
them none of us would even be living
here how interesting I didn't know that
yeah it's true well guess I better get
going big rally tomorrow luck
thank you hey your porch lights out i'll
see you tomorrow at school goodnight hmm
close call I don't think she likes me
mom we've got a dinner to make so let's
do it better keep your head down nosy
neighbors losing Casper how about some
music all right
Oh
you
what
now Casper's the fleshy slave it's time
to report in to my master what perfectly
safe all done by remote control no wires
no fuss and you mr. mayor you are a hero
okay okay but how you gonna steep the
tea and tea and without those protestors
knowing it's already in mr. mayor so
already
you
ah battle worn yet
de mañana boys
right human teaching haunting techniques
it's unorthodox it's it's unheard of
it's an American disgusting keep your
eye on I'm on my way can you believe
this bad store owner thanks go so
friendly he was Casper right now yeah
he's going around town doing good deeds
for everyone revolting the kids are
menace I don't know I kinda liked him
around it was sort of like a family am i
hearing this I can't help it I feel
stuff yeah well feel this family ghost
is a threat to all ghosts so spread out
and find that little poking geek and
self a coach in all about it
looks good pal you've gotta play I want
you to join us really gee thanks
sad now listen I'm gonna introduce you
to him so whip on my window all right
okay but uh what should I say well just
be friendly Chris no go Chris Chris I'm
not supposed to open the door for
strangers look I'm sorry about this
conference thing I had an emergency my
office caught on fire yeah and the groom
will make my homework look charbroiled
medium well you forgot well I didn't
forget about wild and crazy guy night
whoa chris is great well thanks I hell
yeah I had a friend oh yeah new kid in
fact he's coming home for dinner oh you
know did you that was go to a restaurant
maybe that that that Chinese restaurant
or something you tore down not to oh
yeah I did but I put up a yogurt hut
very sense of their dad why do you like
to tear everything down I like that old
Applegate place you're starting to sound
like your teacher and your teacher is
gonna get me fired then you and I we
gotta live under a freeway bad though Oh
alishan listens to me what's that
supposed to mean you never pay attention
to me I mean you don't come to my
baseball games or take me to the movies
or listen to what I say Chris Chris
that's ridiculous
Chris you know that when you promised no
one eruption can I take a phone call the
phone is ringing where my foot hello yes
mr. mayor sure uh the memo of course I
saw no dad the batting cage you promised
that was the mayor I'm your son Chris
don't do this at least meet my friends
first okay when's he gonna show I think
he's here right now oh yeah oh really
really well I will hear the doorbell
trust me hello sir I'm Casper yo dude
big see here brain it's bald head your
fishy friendly things are really kind of
difference be nice ok dad me Casper
where is he well he's a ghost Oh Chris I
don't have time for games it's not a
game ghosts are real Casper oh I know we
probably wanted the Applegate mansion
let's go that she loved fish DeGraff put
you up to this right I'm gonna talk this
is ridiculous that's it you have an
overactive imagination it is time to
grow up this goes
and this this look at this stuff
this is trash
you clean this up
I don't see the matter you can wear our
dinner and the Betty King I don't want
to hear it Kris bear
me
you
come on guys have gone to bed to home
Chris we don't give a flying in Banshee
this fleshy stuff has got to stop it's
ruining our reputations you've been a
goody-goody too long and now it's time
to pay the price pay the piper hey the
requested look Elvis ghost stupid
everyone knows Elvis is still alive find
him
wow you really clobbered him tonight
absolutely why should we tell mom
you got me a month of detention eek so
good i'm here for you yeah we think
you're doing come on you've had your fun
you're not standing up for this worm are
you know that I think she likes to win
so do you huh Chuck god stop it why
don't you beat it you know I never liked
you hanging around anyway you're come
with us alphaville mansion weird out
yeah to me
yeah you are gonna die
looks like you're staying don't let me
get on site
hmm no look you know a Wimpy ghost is
lotion it's our fault what could be
worse oh it's worse count see I told you
they were here I got him red-handed so
where's Chrysler Casper oh um he's a
find him yeah yes you're back handedness
okay yeah what a surprise you're looking
good trip silence I decision for you
slackers far too long
now to find your little protégé can
yeah you're mr. Carson is this line
secure yeah who is this it's bill case
sir bill yeah yeah what time is it it's
over 600 you don't sound good have you
been tortured no I just was working late
must have conked out on the couch so we
are still on target for operation
sawdust yeah sure you mean the
demolition yeah first class Oh are there
any demonstrators there ah permit a
small platoon but they're well outside
Ritter but they can't get to the
detonator can they have to worry sir i'm
unstoppable that Shack is newt waxed
history okay look I'll be there soon if
I'm not there by 6 30 on the dot the
miles the place Roger that over now
oh well
I have my orders
yes Chris Chris Chris Chris Chris Chris
Chris
sorry I'm always bothering you so I ran
away now you'll have all the time you
need for your work I'm sorry last night
was my phone careful mr. Carson it's
okay really I got blue here this is
better
you here boy Chris was right you really
don't have an imagination Chris you
where my son is I swear if you've done
something to my son latts mr. Carson I'm
Chris's best friend in fact I'm his only
friend you are cast me in the flesh or
so to speak where's Chris hmm you ran
away seems is it come always pushing
with people alone he's only 10 mr.
Carson and very lonely it's lonely how
could it be lonely I'm always there no
you're always working
said that find him you need each other
you're right password
we do need each other and we love each
other will you help me find him Casper
sure I bet he's at the Applegate place
chris loves it there the Applegate place
I feel blow in 15 minutes what I gotta
warn Chris I gotta stop at that nation
Phil dangerous yeah you know yeah get it
right to obligate place
hey your shit off mr. Graff you've got
it bucko Chris this time forget his
birthday chuckle you always shall hit
conclusions about me or my work
just just so stubborn you don't
understand without change the dead
young you
chili
Chris Chris where are you
chris kasper Chris help me out here
buddy and here come on Chris we got to
get out of here fast weren't you call
last night never mind that there's a
bomb in the house let's go nibbler miss
Newberg his finest never once I grab
that rad kappa its back to processing
for all of you was a radical retreating
more left-wing protestors well they
shall not pass
guy who's blown up this house well
there's a bomb in the house we've got to
stop him the first thing you said that I
agree with soldier dad am I sector you
bleeding-heart Libertines mission is
aborted ah yo you freak it's me Tim how
do I know you're not Sam master of
disguise imposter it's me I hired you
I'm firing you you're done it's finished
it's over
Tim are you all right
I'll be right back
i'm not gonna get out am I don't give up
Chris but maybe I can find the bomb in
and disarm it
yes going on they're gonna blow up the
mansion
stop the countdown
now what think Casper think
must save reputation
No
let's pass 630 you're okay I am I am yes
negatory is sniveling liberal pansies my
bombs got a default mechanism on it and
wave bye-bye to that rat trapping one
minute
my only signs in there
goodbye
ha
okay yeah but we can't take it outside
that'll hurt the people out there your
dad's right go okay care is great now
what do I do
okay to work
hey
I got you
Oh
soldier you have failed 30 days in the
stockade
some insanely long we must deserve a
historic landmark
would you like it as borin sir how did
you do that they taught me sir we did
yeah yeah we did Tom gin we had great
techniques hmm then I was wrong to spit
you three are a family is scary as you
has my permission to haunt where you
want but you still need to go through
basic training give me drop out hey the
little guy stood up for us now it's our
turn sorry you can't take Casper yeah
you said yourself that you can't split
up a family but he's not related to you
yes but you see no resemblance we're
sure you wanna you got him but remember
the rooms a family has to stick together
for all time yeah you're stuck with cat
oh that's Casper make sure you for never
darken my tomb again
oh my step oh oh sorry sorry oh it
stinks hey Chris I'm sorry for ignoring
you
I didn't mean to doubt you it's okay dad
dad I love you sir
and you got a great teacher
so so my guess you wanna last now yeah
like a family will have a home and a
rumpus room and everything yeah my
training we can start from the beginning
we got am I here in a home a rumpus room
fatso you got covering your ears didn't
you hear that little fleshies old man's
gonna demolish this place ferret sounds
good thank you fix Gaspar's it's Horton
the streets for us we got bupkis hmm mr.
Pfister graph Sheila Sheila so Sheila I
was wondering if we reclassified this
place as a historical building how can
we spice it up what if it had a gimmick
like it was haunted me that would bring
in tourists right but don't we need goes
for that
you mean yes the place of our own a to
one of you and from a flashy hey this
breaks all the rules but I love you will
miss you almost got Chris kills cool
cock truth but you'll always be a but
just know your old man's okay if you
ever need a favor just ask see those
guys over there there isn't one to lock
me in here with the ball nuff said no no
no now that we're family you guys have
to try to behave yourselves oh we will
short sing we will rock our hearts and
hope the live show cutter what do you
say boys oh my god it's Jennifer hi
listen and that last night those guys
were jerks e so as I for hanging event
sorry don't go
I didn't know they lock you in here were
you scared it is haunted you know right
don't you like to meet a real ghost say
hi to cast hi you're me please don't
stutter ghost casper i like this you
have on people yeah I think I'll be a
good influence on the ghostly trio
that's cuz you're friendly Casper hey I
like the sound of that Casper the
Friendly rape no Jasper the pleasant
poltergeist let's just stick Casper the
Friendly Ghost
don't go change am the Avenger
geez
bye
reelin please
we
look
check
Josh I
Oh
that's what it's gonna be
that's what is done
Shakespeare
too many that you
you and me
can you meet your my best
you