funny
yeah
not quite
ok
yeah
like a normal person
lighten up face calling me that I'm sick
of it oh yeah we'll go puff up your hair
yeah yeah okay okay put your collars on
the slots try and act like it and this
time we're gonna stay together
alright alright alright okay we're gonna
go in we could all use some meat r and r
sweetheart
hey Rox let's get this toilet
keep going hey come on after what
happened candy in the last town who
needs the hassles you do don't cross me
ok bad hey Rox eight brides on the rag
what are you gonna do
yeah
I could have to drag you want to go get
some meat
what's the problem it's just another
stupid
yeah no problem
alright i'm hungry elite will be outta
here in two hours
yeah
anybody else coming no other can tell me
i guess we can dispense with the
scriptures we should all know by now huh
well let's get to it
we're here to say goodbye to con con was
the butcher now he's dead but
whatta fuck why dwell on it
yeah
ok
welcome to zariah lady cool because the
jello
yeah
that you
come on we're dying out here
yeah do you want us to do it shut up
Lance we've got better things to do than
take care of a bunch of bump reading
bastards said it not me
got it for such a burden why don't you
just move on to your next well intention
cause good idea we'll pack right up for
your parents
nice what you would expect from a guy
who carries an Uzi for sentimental
reasons
yeah
he go
ok
yeah
what kind of get with black
no gotta get me the means to get what
you want to watch it would be gone 15
minutes an hour
what could possibly happen
yeah
surprise your friends
I
Bosh pick up anything with them
yeah actually picked up to you on awards
whoa boy radio yeah cool
look like hardware store you
hey so what do you need nail file torque
wrench
maybe i'm using well maybe we can work
something out
bring back the deck you're mad they said
in mind this was the United States
government
the closest I left
yes I've been a bad boy i will get those
whores I want you dead asses in that
mind by tomorrow
Bob if you don't do it then I'll have to
do it
don't make me do it Bob
now what's the Bob model God wanted me
to do normal stuff i cannot hear you
if God had wanted me to do normal stuff
it would have made me look like normal
people like one
normal people but wipe
yeah
where you been around we don't have had
any since you left
you haven't fucked for six years
alright a couple of times
listen don't you come on
I don't want you okay baby come on home
with me know
yeah
speaking to me Bob happy birthday baby
its mama
well its momma Dee me bump
oh boy school sure stinks city countries
relax but I didn't and she asked for an
inhale send me a present outside normal
sea monkeys they just each other and
honey is your daddy there any she's not
your aunt honey how can we shake it mama
mamas don't run away they just wednesday
we can Obama possible that what Jesus
it's it's one of those things that they
put in the road to keep the cows
continent doesn't tell me about mom's
gotta go now okay we'll send you your
present tell that tell your daddy that I
called
t-bob ask you daily with the word
impotent me a hot impotent
that's right
how about home my love you
yeah you're running all mama
yeah fuck you owe
yeah
ok
somewhere down the line with my love
yeah
go away get out of my face want to do
and do you read me
down and take it with you I take it you
can take it and leave me
yeah
and you know what TV work
ok
yeah
professional
Big Mama
yeah
mama
oh my gosh i was getting afraid you were
going to be a virgin forever now maybe
you'll move out of the house
yeah you know a lot of town there's
always somebody wants to get out so so
we take them and then we just right
around $TIME right around must be nice
and riding around
yeah it's called so why not come with us
nobody ever get that here you go to
school here you get married in breeding
die from you guys call yourself slut
well rocks and that's what we're going
to call it anyway so I might as well
beaten to the punch but the kind of
music you want to play play
no no produce you know bring up the
baseline control stuff that's what I'm
gonna do
so how come you're just riding around
and no I was following this band for a
while and well I thought I had a chance
but all they wanted was you don't just
walk in and say hi I'm a producer you
know you gotta work up to it okay okay i
gotta i gotta close up you want to come
over and listen to some records or
something
many still around
hey TC for Toms Christopher my folks
wanted a boy
my parents wanted somebody smart oh well
. them so I this place got a back room
or something
Wow
they fucking hate me but i know im a
bitch but fucking AI gotta be to keep
these little pussies together give an
engine maybe running home to play dead
sit around waiting for them to dry up
and fall off
they're just never gonna be like me
you know I think I'd just hang it up and
let someone else to go baby
yeah d you know sometimes I think
there's a spark there but most of the
time is just push and she's down just
like the rest of you but you guys all I
got
no but Jamie
it's such a bad down
I certainly hope you girls have all this
out of your systems for awhile sealed i
bet Lucille got ourselves some real good
toys do it because it's right to get
them in women my town now
gee I don't think that's such a good
idea that that look
here's a friend of ours
we'd like you to say something dorm say
something pretty
and you know what we'd like you to kiss
him goodbye
he'd like that site's up the pitch the
matter you would like or something
lady can't talk fuckface and for the
record I'm the dike below me whereas we
feel
hey yo face yet laid i know you want you
should we gotta get out of here with
rocks
yeah
man dead man store dead man's truck dead
man's wife
what kind of trash are you can't you see
we're in fucking morning here in you you
had sex
I remember that smell got no respect for
the dead got no respect for property
because some kind of rebels but you just
whores and now you gonna make amends got
any money bitch
lousy knots on well aren't you gonna
introduce your husband to your little
friends that's it
your homecoming queen the face is
married
yo choose babe I don't need this shit
was around that right back off
and
on leave
yeah
I stay in here just going to come out
here and get us
bullshit i said we go back to town and
kick some butt
nobody runs me out of town you know i
would kind of like to go get my bike
back
somebody should go back and find the
seal no she took off thursday we did it
come on she could be in some kind of
trouble
I'm staying here what if they come out
here and get us you be safe mama
yeah
so you're pissed right how about a kid
you want to have a kid
what the hell you doing look at you just
want someone to poke their other women
in this town like God the one with the
bad teeth any take her she's dead
hunting accident chief well
Nadine used to like Nadine she drowned
ain't rabies Corey bad marriage
Raelynn bad pork all these people are
dead since the mine closed this town
just had a real streak of bad luck bad
luck but honey
things are looking up I mean you're home
i'm not home
do you put it away i want to show you
something right
I was drunk feeling mischief and I got
that you and I used to have fun
seemed like a good idea at the time we
leave that girl affected so it's kind of
like Donnie it's not you're right it's
me there's something wrong with me i
just don't hack it as normal and homes
and families and husbands are for normal
so I just what the hell you're talking
about like if you die down on me or
something you know I love you
stay
Lucy
you feel
yeah
are you doing here
so your box
something's wrong here
sure
yeah
you know
so
mmm
yeah
so you know Fred someday they'll say he
went too far
mad pursuit of knowledge immortality me
they'll say that about me that you do it
for science can do it for glory
I charge
yeah
let's get up
holy shit you're out 000 or you've been
a bad boy back but oh
yeah
really miss it
dad they're dead I'm the one who's a lot
i'm the one who stuck here cooking your
meals and day in and day out and care of
that baby just knock it off
our needs wood
yeah
down Jojo
you know you have your moments but right
now you are a pain in the air
all I'm saying is that what that guy
said we gotta go back and do something
about it
maybe he was right hey man I don't need
this
me and time your gonna blow this pussy
pop stand
mom give me that a gas can you been
carrying screw you
maybe I'm maybe I'm your lucky i don't
believe this shit
well you gotta go huh when I gotta go
job back to the army i wasn't a wall i
was just lost
did you fight real good but you always
fight for the wrong things
oh and sure I'm going on mama what are
you gonna do go back to your old man's
we can beat you with a belt some more so
you can raise little brat to be just
like his daddy haha and I little little
sweet rusty I little red gash gonna open
up for business again and TC gonna go
back to be the game bang queen of the
roadies i'm going to produce you know
you gotta stop live yourself kid you
bull dyke you get your ass mama I'm a
big bad wolf tank and my tongue has been
places you don't even though you've got
and it's great and I don't deal with it
I don't call but that's okay
brand on it I got fucking your grad up
huh
I wish you would all just be like dat
that this would just take off just right
home
that's it
we gotta get out of here yeah yeah
that's we are getting your fucking back
just like your old man huh
Your Dragon fucking
would that get you would get the corner
some
yeah
ok
Oh mom I had nothing you last round
yeah
Scott
color color is not quite
yeah
no I'll get those whores
no no just get out baby give her the
baby let's string him up right where the
role
maybe we can just shoot him with that
flare gun maybe do some rope and shit
you think that
Oh
yeah
my act box 11
it all
yeah
she's dead
them
yeah
not the teachers out we had to lock them
out and whatever is out there would have
gotten us to this gun line no parents
and now this
and they said there was no God Lance
game over
ok
we do come on are we fucking Shriners we
put our ass on the line for a bunch of
Punk's shut up jojo we gotta do
something what you mama around you
yeah
there
misty
yeah
ok
whoa bitch glass
never
yeah
what the fuck is all this
it's not me it's William shut up about
two years ago because it about the stuff
in the mine stuff radioactive stuff when
they did the underground nuclear test
nuclear whatever and well needed people
to get the stuff of mine but he could
you live people because they died so we
gotta get people how they get dead Bob
things happened and we'll have brought
him back and put them in the mine they
got the staff we get some of himself
until the best what drugs are you people
on something to who I don't know I just
went for it
why'd you do it Bob because i was
fucking sick of being cute
what he said he could make meet all your
small you're blind
pleased to meet you yeah she's blind
kids a midget dwarf dwarf dykes on bikes
we get started sideshow watch your mouth
little creek we save your butts and you
talk trash like that would really help
if you could be a little bit more ups
equus inspirational we knew our place
yeah like you I'm coming with you guys
we got enough problems and you got to
take care of them
go okay right pedal
yeah
look we're all in this together
come on their women you want money how
much you want 500 750 okay it's over
why don't you all just brought home
because I don't give a shit anymore what
rocks
I mean what we together enough back
there for you what do we have to do
anyway be just like you
we got families here we got businesses
you don't even have anything to lose
tell them they're fucking buy it it
looks like you've got company
yeah
rocks running now
do something dammit sure we can't their
us good people they're going to eat you
family you were homecoming princess
queen
yeah
oh shit
one
yeah
ed is water under the bus like you
me
yeah
rocks that like nothing's changed
if you only want to write they're all
back there waiting for you
I know that and I'm not going back there
starting to screw up I screwed up
Lucille that's good up with jewels yeah
you did but you could suck it doesn't
fall apart today it falls about tomorrow
you chicks just can't get it together
don't you understand sweet hard the slot
fucking we're meant
yeah
what
what about kids at the church they got a
gun you okay but William Henry stopping
the batteries out of the head how maybe
knock that off
ok
yeah
the heads of gotta come off whose heads
all right right because already dead
right
yep
yeah
you can keep talking made to your god
she's dead
you look and maybe if you don't eat
anybody no one will notice now I gotta
go but I'm gonna lock the door so you
don't get out okay and that there's
dinner in the refrigerator and see
what's on TV or some
yeah
I way to all and way too lazy to start
over okay
yeah
that's it
hey that was a that was easy
dr done better get off then a nice make
that picking it up
Kevin you're full of life still loaded
with warm look just right you're right
you're going out you gotta why I'm fired
up
well getting spires maybe forgetting
makers like it go away
what but you know the blood the week
William sucked
Wow
yeah
huh
we can't screw around along we gotta get
them together in one place where
sunday
we'll get them all in here above all
this damn place up the church
what about us you're the bait kid I'm
glad we're not slaves the petty morality
where the fuck do you think you go
taking the Holy out of this place i may
be a whore burning know he even you okay
we get out that way
sure clear
nothing gonna go off the supposed to go
out cool your jets huh
alright we get in there what you said 44
minutes
no three for three and a half minutes
and then get out get out get out all
right whatever you say homecoming queen
you're gonna need this
ok he said to get as much meat as shit
we
yeah
share their breeding well I guess so
waiting on
ok
yeah daddy look
yeah
Shh got no no no
come on
yeah
here
very cool
you got my jacket very makes it okay now
your slot tried act likein back-to-back
dugout
hey we didn't do it for money
we don't even do it for you hey don't
get carried away
yeah
great from chucker as well get a damn
you know the dog he gets a 3 seconds for
each leg table 1
yo anybody else
yeah
quite as we're gonna need more bikes
will get them in the next town
don't start with me
what about five
yeah
the
Oh
yeah
amazing things
I
yeah
and