let me tell you a story about a girl
named Debbie who loved her stuffed doll
dog and Little Miss Muffet she was
always dressing her up sometimes just
for fun but her fun nut muffins
I'm alive I can talk I can touch I can
feel look I just stuff oh darling I
gotta get out of here
hey my name's miles and I'm just doing
what I like best keeping time with the
blues before the student gets too
complicated I realize you folks might be
wondering what kind of place this is
welcome to tattoo town this is the place
where everything you've ever lost winds
up
can I do me wind up see here now Sonny
there'll be no loitering on the public
Holly texted a turn out like your
citation for this so be nervous know is
me public duty
Ted of town is the elephant's graveyard
for junk we're all forgotten objects
come to rest but as you can see nothing
rests around here an amazing thing
happens with some of the things to find
their way here they become
ah
get out of here you bum what do you
think this is a greasy spoon or
something yes sir tatort owls are cool
gig for everybody shame on you for
running away no I'm not good golly Eddie
look I've got a new dress for your dream
wants to
flibbertigibbet she got away again and
you weren't much help mosey thickness
and dutton oh no right left these can't
do that to me come on take it on baby
come over here let's step behind your
back oh nothing let me see your hands
goodness what have you done this time
now sit down here and we'll see what we
can do okay daddy hey if you caught the
doll of yours yet no she keeps running
away from me I can't understand
back in the real world what I can
remember when I got her for Christmas
what's a Christmas what you mean you
don't know what Christmas is with all
this junk lying around here you must
have seen some Christmas stuff ain't
joke its family well all we have to do
is start looking and I'm sure we'll find
something there your arms finished let's
go searching you do I don't give you
such a bitch this is getting to be fun
never be pure UK
got his little medlars a fix or his
wagons
get outta here you little rat Fink's
can't just see the spiders trying to
work Who am I why why I Muffet damn
merciless him take it over this dump now
scram night right wait a minute wait a
minute oh dal was great just great I've
been trying to take over Pat it down for
years but never like dag kind of a crazy
place is this anyway person be evil in
peace hey home with me where we going to
the dance does own the Dead stirs own
hangout for war toys TV sets and other
unsavory characters come on I watches to
meet the guys these are my texture
soldiers really impressed then these
rust buckets I've seen Jill would walk
back on any size
and I suppose you could do better you
better believe it handball I wouldn't
let him sit around on it oil pants all
day long I'm kicking ass stuffing down a
tattered town all day long week showing
those little squats who runs this place
Marshall
Christmas in Tanner town we'll be right
back after these messages you're
watching Nickelodeon and now back to
Christmas and tighter town on proper he
has all the town of town of scouring the
town from Christmas that's right yeah
ebuddy come here how'd you like to buy a
car that's not nice we have one of these
on our front door when friends and
relatives come over we'd open the door
and a little flurry of snow would fall
off the reef
somebody do something Eddie is leaking
life sorry I just thought about
Christmas got a little homesick that's
all you still haven't told me
Christmases well it can't be very nice
or she wouldn't be crying oh no
Christmas is the most wonderful time of
the year right now christmas is caroling
in the snow and candy canes decorating
the tree this morning we've run
downstairs and open up what are you all
standing around for let's have ourselves
a Christmas
Oh
meanwhile muffets emissary the fly with
the glass and hug and squeeze and oh
yeah I gotta stop it dad went oh come on
your mercilessness all right you poor
excuses for spies I want you to sneak in
the tattered town and find out what kind
of Christmas they're planning to have
good and we can waste some teddy bears
while we're at it Oh tisk tab don't be
so antisocial get going the woman
machines are rebuilt one more pill
the old geezers around here somewhere
Debbie who's around here Harvey why
Herbert cannibal that's who hi look at
man I'm not purchase on of history and
on soil to come on gone
I love our nation is all yours from our
epoxy no key hey use tenenbaum look
alive we got customers huh so your turn
mom I'm Debbie and this is Harvey and
dog we've got a proposition for you how
would you like to be the official
tattered town Christmas tree christmas
tree hey what do I know about Christmas
I'm a shopkeeper I sell comic books you
wanna buy a nice magazine but you are an
evergreen oh you just fine it's a little
pyramid but with some new soil plant hey
listen Buster I was a 10 foot pain since
before you buzz stuff hey just tell your
canine friend here not to get any low
key ideas okay look mr. Tannenbaum Bing
the official tree in the Town Square is
quite an honor Amish mother I'm a busy
man but there's no competition no worry
Harry help me see he'll talk me into it
where do I sign huh let me shake limbs
votruba I always wanted to be on
monopoly window
looking for debbie's be Christmas
explodes
there's a dis flower beautiful yeah
idiot yup moron you just blew our cover
come on
now before we have to decorate I'm gonna
waste oh my goodness oh my goodness it's
like an no
the guys go home see dis yeah I'll never
live it down not bad for a first attempt
not bad it's perfect Christmas in Tanner
town we'll be right back after these
messages you're watching Nickelodeon and
now back to Christmas in tighter town
it's the house
what done something wrong mum no but
someone jump out too
better be good news why oh look it's
from bad and Wendell it says penis
Muffet having a wonderful time why those
bumbling bimbos mu- Christmas
decorations on me ooh muffins you know
how I hate bad news fly why do you
always take such care got throw it in my
face
let me brush my head for a moment it's
so hard living with these lower life
forms oh listen to that amateur ranting
what a dead stirs own deserves the
talents of a master elocutionist like
what
shut up Oh a pavane doily fit for a
monologue ah it's royal garment I
wouldn't do that if I were you bad pipe
down oh no adult about it yester hello
is this mr. Maine and vice versa doesn't
up in your clothes when you're not home
how is this guy works for me uh wait you
see nothing I was just trying on this
role here you were to check it if it had
any more dommage anis good and I suppose
you put my crown on now plug that hole
in your head Oh correct accessible yes
what am I put this on Sydney it'll make
a new man out of you Hey well sir jimmy
sorting methods
hey nothing what sort of shoot is this
any hands you're gonna be my reindeer
Sydney all later them love it no I do
like hey Mike Santa enough the photostat
account wits to me
oh boy
he's coming now for a christmas carol
now the Christmas ever wanna know it is
time with jump him down
surely I guess you still don't get it
listen Christmas isn't about chopping
down trees or even about gifts it's a
very special time once a year when all
the people stop working and playing
yelling or fighting mr. Osmond all their
unkind deeds for this one special day
Christmas Day good stand back oh look
Debbie up in the sky Holy Smoke it must
be Santa hahaha close but no cigar mine
where troops let's take Derek down well
maybe the christmas poo
Merry Christmas well if it's a fight you
want already shaking its dash your goal
fatigue there must be a change in the
boy well I get it Muppet wants us to
attack each other rule that muffin such
a genius all right this is Christmas I
love aerial dogfights not exactly Harvey
show off sorry I can't play now so long
anyway
oh that was great Christmas some show
now when do we no no this is all wrong
it's here I just gotta find it this is
my last hope the head doesn't play I
give up
mer
nothing like the wall
are you
and children
well
through here
the river
first my
Oh
well n square hair gels it got about
sums up our christmas cake for the night
your friend I'm not yell it's a season
minus all monitored to mistletoe Britney
see them then you'll know it's Christmas
it's the time that comes each ear when
people want a special cheer designing
hear from you to hear it's Christmas
it's Christmas lights on the tree last
preparations are made