hey Benny you got to lose the boys awake
yeah I got the money but you ain't
coming to our bidding hey baby I got the
money I gotta pray yeah I got the 20 way
please the Commissioner Bill far
20 books up when he's fucked yeah that
shot go I'm gonna get you
look what we got here sure I didn't say
hello near lon mm-hmm two or three days
three days do you oh how come I've been
around before this what's your problem
do you do nothing very much well I'm not
gonna ask you the start of your life you
seem nice I wish you were I'm making you
know
got a nice cozy
I'm had any better offers that's great
wanna finish you drink a little bit good
boy big boy tonight yes ma'am I think
rottenness both
you come on will you mean by it
what do you mean by come up to my
it's a silly question for a big girl
like you what'd he do
musician
jazz musician I played trumpet
you didn't bring your instrument tonight
you guys are really something what do
you been sitting on me
huh I thought you knew
you want to get picked up lunch do you
like that I'd like to take you I bet you
have a great time what do you say all
right please baby please say I'm not
kidding I'm very serious would you like
huh all right what's your name Nancy
with you hi
if you don't play it cool still play you
for a fool how lollipop lollipop will
never make you sick for real magic is
like an ice cream cone she okay that's a
lousy agree I've been a singer in this
building for 10 years and I've never
introduced a Kaline in my life I can't
change you ue it's not a question of the
money it's just that my client feels
that it's beneath his dignity to have to
introduce a bunch of floozies we're
given the scale of the few guys where do
I'll take your place okay all right
okay okay okay cut it cut it all right
okay uh now there are 10 million people
in New York City now I have him a girl
and any one of them can sing the song
better than you bro any one of them a
real mad chick right a real mad chick
and shake your bodies around do
something weird let's try once more all
right what's more girls if you want real
mad chick but look I'm gonna feel like
an awful down those drones you're an
artist if you make up your mind and do
what you can do it I was an artist ten
years ago now that's when I was an
artist with the high during but you
wasn't for now yeah sure uh Benny women
ok what does it better you got a minute
yeah I am limiting something you know
these people want to do do to me it's
bad enough working in a third-rate
nightclub you know with package with the
strippers and the fuses are playing
second fiddle to they want me to
introduce the earlier that crazy they
can't even see fuck you i need 20 bucks
to pay a guy back i bought from for a
few beers are you ready frogged you now
well we're still making up on mine
where's your boy he's over there talking
to his brother I want to pay him back
now you got it hey here's my outfit i'll
go play two nights $35 night just to
know we'll take it Jack we've got no
problems we've gotten here you go hold
on we need the money you got it 20 bucks
from me let's go to boom uh look we have
decided we've decided
and he'll be there look nice or not yes
or no no your kid it's a lot of money
Rick shit and okay excuse me Benny now
mr. him and had no problems at all he's
got a little trouble with his kid
brother and it's gonna be taken care of
in just about another unit now as we
agreed we're gonna be there tonight you
philly right on time Benny look you've
got a subtle mustaine what's to do hey
who wants to give us thirty five dollars
a night in third Billy and you just
growing rivalry but we heard that
heartbeat floor what time do I leave
just be a brilliant time for the show
you're very lucky buck you know how
people wanted this job Eli yes well I
wouldn't say what's the matter its
medical almost never I forgot your tooth
crap look I by 10 hey hey how about
moving up there how you gonna get home I
gotta take a nice little walk no no look
I want you to take a cab oh please you
don't start that again I'm 20 years old
men live in this city all my life I
think I can manage yeah yeah and I know
look you don't know everything and
you're a baby I mean all you have to do
is read the papers a girl can't walk
safely down the streets at night and any
city without being hollowed out and
called named and pinched and abused and
I don't want my baby sister being
hurtful few pennies now you take a cab
nothing ever happens to me when I walk
home sriracha pulled up
look nothing's gonna not gonna make
nothing ever done I love you I'll take
care of yourself okay do a good show and
come on let's go and look okay ah I look
babylegs don't look at take care please
all right come here never our time but
we'll make it come on
no we gonna make it come on come on man
it's too late look look look he's
stopping come on man run after you
hey yeah thanks for letting us use this
pad man you like that Davis yeah members
one's gonna live you're sure Paul
villain and introduced a girly act now
that really burns me forget well yet
what I reduced a bunch of dumb broad
cool what's going to do so here dumb
buds so they can't live too yeah that's
gonna feel also that beef baked beans
with baby buddy Sam all right I'm a
singer and I sing a song now what am I
gonna say about a bunch of dumb broads
white ribbons going around singing a
pretty girl does that make sense but you
just can't say that exactly I doce a few
nice words about the audience like I
don't know just smile be yourself you
know I'm a singer nobody seems to get
that this thing is safe I mean that's it
that's all man oh man I told a couple of
jokes everybody likes jokes how many
people feel kind of good hey Sam what
time it's a matter of principle root
make them feel relaxed and easy like
Steve Allen you know jokes what jokes I
don't know any jokes look I don't even
know my own name come on baby let's go
yes hold on oh it don't you tell a joke
don't duh me don't you stop go you want
some jokes man yeah yeah okay uh how's
that what about the wittstock are you
kidding there's clothes and George I was
just thinking out loud i'll tell you
when a little bit a little bit worried
fine uh-huh you know you like that one
about the rabbit in the tree but a
mother you know that what about the
rabbit that fell on out of the tree and
says man that loved makings for the
birds as cute as like it oh that come on
wait a minute not only me but the man
hold it that's cute that's funny
everybody likes jokes that's right hang
or offend anybody you know it dates do
you think that's funny ad come on give
it a try well yeah i do man
come on look I can't Cheyenne you once
were you okay okay there you go uh
ladies in general did you overhear this
is stupid man what's to lose with us are
we gonna kill you if you're so smart you
do it yourself okay I will it's easy
though you know good evening ladies and
gentlemen on my way over here this
evening a very funny thing happened to
me got it I was walking out of street
looking up at this great big tree and
way up there on there and said our first
catch him off guard oh no you gotta send
them up man settle up your right in the
sleep and who you Steve Allen I got it I
got okay okay good I say good evening
ladies and gentlemen well you certainly
look like a refine audience we got here
tonight and I have a couple of refined
jokes to tell ya you
beautiful couple air ladies and
gentlemen there's a couple celebrating
their third drinks and 7 15
oh you're mine he asked if they're
married what a winner fella
here's the angle sister Ellen daddy maxi
delivered
I YouTube girls marry just like
the lamp over there I
I want you to meet us in Europe Hanukkah
singer right now a new II heard the
greatest thing I was all like take care
of a lot of applause please cousin
hello baby I had to call you on the
phone I said hello baby I had to call
you on the phone
wait cause your daddy's so long so and
he wants this
he's small step I if you read my little
baby what is this bring the girls and
what kind of a place are you running
here this is Karen buddy he'll also be
more no all good and introduce the girls
good evening ladies and gentlemen on my
way
well is everybody going to sit around
here all day Dennis knocked out when you
make me sick what's the matter with you
Tom I got a hangover that's what's the
matter angle that's what you get for
staying out all night who takes care of
your sister when you said all night man
I hire a babysitter not a hire a
babysitter be used to be on David's
riding a new novel all about you been
better not be any of that Beat
Generation just like the last night stop
it Janice it makes me sick right my
coffee time yeah take some dumb mean it
helps sometimes drama baywatch travel
agent it's a sigma dicin but not airsick
I'm ground sick but I'll take anything
if it helped me if it is the way I feel
this we do me a favor and get me some of
that stuff tennis what is it please will
you get me some of that Dramamine please
don't favorite writers I appreciate the
privilege Oh Charlie you guys
you never break a pattern you never go
anywhere with your life okay down we go
how many do I take take just this one
what did you do something learn
something there are thousands of things
to do in New York City like what why
don't you do something different you
want to meet new people you want to come
to a literary party I'm having tonight
don't invite them do they won't even
wear ties ladies coming what the hell is
littered or just where people interested
in books and other literary efforts got
together and discuss things well if
they're coming I'm not gonna be there
because they're gonna just act awful and
I'll be so embarrassed oh it's all right
oh hi what are you kidding you can come
just as you are you want to come yeah
I'll read a poem don't get excited honey
wants to make that think party anyone
all right something else a concert or a
museum museum I'm part Ben Tom I don't I
don't think you've ever even been in a
museum any of you why I've never been in
a few seen we've been in plenty of
museums I bet you can't even spell it Oh
will you stop teasing me yeah huh we
gonna lay liya has a very bright mind
Benny she's developing very rapidly oh I
don't want to sit around here and be
insulted by these creeps let's go then
you should eat something besides black
coffee David please don't start
lecturing me now
well come on David nevermind we're gone
now what will it be Dennis will it be
laundering or the Metropolitan let's go
to the Metropolitan they got mummies
there and everything okay you guys
kidding let's go let's go hey I know
what you want to come here for Dennis
this joint is nothing but a place for a
bunch of sexless women who don't have
any love in her life not a big deal
professor a lot of creeps trying to show
off how much they know you couldn't be
wrong I suppose professors don't come
here well I didn't say that all right
Dennis look that I suppose you can tell
me what he's about that genius he's a
statute I know he's a statute get it
what kind of a statue I know he's a
statue well Tom I don't know everything
you know something Dennis yeah you don't
know nothing oh yeah what do you know
about you yeah why'd you come here for
you know so much you have no respect for
on no respect at all ulysse tomatoes
you're nothing but an ignorant slob that
is a little ignorant slob I went to
college did you know I ever got out of
his dissipation a lot of early bells
disturbing my sleep
a lot of supercilious professor slob
professors shooting off their mouth
about something trying to teach me
something that they'd already failed out
in life themselves so don't tell me I
don't appreciate anything
sami know what I'm gonna do with that I
put it on a Christmas card just a mask
on a car that be wild don't someone to
me pal look Tom will you cool that you
know what you're talking about I suppose
you really understand that thing there's
not a question of understanding it man
if you're feeling your feelings so babe
that's I've been trying to tell you I
shut up there I shut up yourself say
you're sorry hey I'm sorry okay I'm
sorry Hey look it up without put it out
with man really say I'm really sorry
okay boss hey guys hey hey look at it
now look now look at this cat he really
had a sense of humor when he made this
that isn't supposed to be humorous Tom
what are we supposed to do get serious
with a can like that I'll tell you right
now tom don't get excited Dennis I'm not
gonna hurt it's made of iron chick like
that may destroy me Danny what's the
matter with tom is he crazy or something
I'm not Dennis someday you may marry a
girl that looks like that oh god forbid
drop funny dance that's funny wow this
joy gives me the creeps buddy let's go
come on where you gon get out ok
what happened hey I'm not trying to hurt
your feelings but if you're going to
write a story you have to do it
professionally David I don't want to be
a writer I didn't want to do this you
convinced me to do it and now all you
can do is criticize I just want you to
be honest yep look your story has some
pretty good things but it's very hard to
be honest well I don't understand your
viewpoint jean-paul Sartre has
absolutely nothing to do with
existential psychoanalysis cigarette no
thank you well it's all a bit vague
don't you think so John I do not the
trouble with you is you suffer from self
induced hysteria at the word
existentialism are you aware of their
can't fix you a drink I hear you I Dart
I know the article to which you refer
I've read it three times I couldn't even
find the basic precepts which article
was that if you can explain it I'd be
delighted well it's perfectly obvious
man in contrast to other animals is
conscious of his own existence therefore
conscious of the possibility of
non-existence ergo he has anxiety right
all right absolutely I couldn't agree
with you more well the trick is now this
girl here she has no control over
herself she's been deeply hurt and yet
she goes on as if nothing happened
living her life the same as before it
just doesn't make any sense I'm takes
more than imagination well the point is
that if you're yourself you won't get
hurt
you're right or two oh no do I look like
a writer oh I can't tell anymore I'm a
dancer really Oh a dancer well that's
that's great your ballet dancer oh no
exotic sorry oh you don't know what that
is do you not exactly it's a sort of
modern only more exotic it sounds
terrific listen would you mind if I came
to see you perform sometime oh no the
very next time I'll invite you great
when will that be oh I'm not dancing
right now oh no why not you're going to
have a baby knowledge York that's great
you're gonna have a baby baby that
sounds terrific congratulations that's
great news we think so don't be honey
huh yo let's well congratulations thank
you send a thud it's okay I'll just
excuse myself can fix my drink a little
bit
you don't know what else to be you can
only see it coming sometimes a person
could ruin your life and yet all he'd be
of times they say is I'm sorry I do i
interrupting something Tony lady
Carruthers Tony wrestler oh hello I was
just trying to come in this lady logic
riders today I've got to be realistic in
their approach what he's trying to say
is he hates my writing so are you being
a judge on you be the judge uh-uh first
day in New York this year ladies writing
by walk down Fifth Avenue she's stranger
standing and sunlight on a street corner
and she works up and kisses him this
perfect stranger it's revolting on a
Sunday afternoon no if I wanted to I
would i guess i have to change sides
David David you're getting some more
champagne it's even more revolting and
realized Smosh am page I think you've
had plenty what did you say your name
was laelia slowly parties
Junior you staring I'm hypnotizing thank
you who do you belong to Lillian well
I'm along to me what about David hmm no
more champagne later dude I was just
about to see Lily at home what do you
mean I'm taking their home well you're
both wrong because neither one of you
were taking me home I'm meeting Vicky
and she's spending the night at my house
I guess might not expose a little rusty
what about tomorrow tomorrow Leia and I
are going to the park oh well good good
I'll come along no daddy good don't be
so unfriendly
tell me that you know man David I know
mama hey baby give me one of those
mm-hmm in a strange and I sustain my mom
hi hello MA oh hi babe is it boy you
sure look like you got a hangover I've
got to go hey what's the story I'll talk
to you later about you and layer we're
making a scene hey Dave
I'm really not very happy I mean I'm
happy but I'm not as happy as everybody
thinks I am why not oh because I feel
that I should be farther ahead than I am
everything is passing me by and older I
got 20 I don't ever get it oh don't
laugh i'm serious i have a feeling that
I'll never you know be smart and I'm
never gonna get the things that I want
and uh Oh what do you feel like don't
know what you feel like I feel like I'm
in up uh-oh nigga kuna you can't get out
that's why how did you know I didn't
think boys were supposed to understand
things like that you see I am far behind
fun whoo now you sound like David I hope
not why not David's were the most
intelligent people I've ever met my life
I'm not very romantic no he's not very
romantic
feel not a very nice person I mean I
have very romantic information before
warned that i'm not one of these
storybook characters is supposed to be
all noble and righteous when I see
someone I like and she likes me we
accept my romantic inclinations do you
happen to know where we are right now
now that's where I live right there
number seven
come on up for a drink you know you're
beautiful
don't you move
Oh
no you got the softest lips I've ever
dealt
hmm lucky well you don't want anything
to drink all right
love you love you
really if I'd known this was the first
time for you I wouldn't have touched you
I didn't know it could be so don't be so
upset sweetheart
baby be much easier next time on a
cigarette hmm come on have a cigarette
no I'm sorry if I disappointed you I
guess I did
I was so frightened I kept saying to
myself and mustn't cry love and Manish
yourself right you it's only natural
there isn't a girl in the world that
wouldn't feel the same way she's got
true what happens now what happens hmm
what what do you mean what happens now I
mean do I stay with you clearly just
stay with me I'm do you mean live with
me yes you want to
you know I wanna go home okay baby I
thought being with you would be it's so
important means so much afterwards to
people would be as close as it's
possible to get but instead we're just
two strangers no you tell you it's over
I know that much about life
Mariette you can come stay with me I I
want you to but when I say that you're
close to me that's all I can say because
that's the way I am but that does not
mean that I don't feel the same things
that you feel Tony please please don't
well yeah I love you please don't touch
me please don't touch me i want to go
home I want to get dressed now please
leave me alone okay sweetheart I'll take
you home okay sweet it's okay with you
I'll take any fire buddy look why don't
you just take the taxi wherever you
gonna go because I'm coming upstairs
with you folks come on it's my busy time
let's go yeah yeah just a second dude
look why don't we just end it right here
hmm make up your minds
because you don't want it that way
because I don't want it that way you go
with her or is it and you stay but come
on make up your mind hello como tell me
chime o'clock 75 I'm coming upstairs
with you know yet whether you like it or
not please don't make any seams I'll
make the biggest thing you ever saw
you're that important to me all right
all right you can come up but just for a
minute okay fine ain't love grand why
don't you mind your own business keep it
keep you are you what wow this is this
is why I've got to you any kind of do
suggesting any kinda juice yeah fuck you
does you open or what do I open 50 give
me two cars bang oh yeah yeah yeah tell
you what I'm gonna do it guys you need
the money so I'm gonna let you you gonna
let you have it as hand and very my
cards I don't want 20 more the call some
girls hey mom call a couple of shit I
have yo all ready come on then ha what
do you know but you should know a lot of
shit on you said you had said the man
you've been dragging all day about my
best Obama office Kennedy 1221
my boy a room 1221 uh Anita I don't know
her last name Sunita yeah room 1221
hello baby this is Claire that all true
flying I need it yeah Tom well how about
a couple drinks can you get that red
hair that works in the handshake alone
now there's three of us are you two
buddies yeah Benning and Dennis we're
feeling my little oh can you get another
girl all right i'll meet you about 20
minutes yes yeah let's go home yeah hey
chase whoa what'd I tell you huh you
didn't believe
Oh
just a dream and something
this
kiss me make this moment
snow
always
be mine
Oh
I spend it with your
my
register okay let's break it up Oh x-bar
like how you think I'm fine uh Tony
Russell this is my brother Hugh hot and
this is rough across bed not you are you
well well how does this thing go I mean
big crowds hmm fine the only one bad
spot no thing was his character he
decides to you know he's gonna rewrite
everything give me a jelly rolls son
like an opera Oh your songs not Joey
romance about a beautiful thing this
thing like a velvety haha sorry Elliot I
have an appointment I have to go
I have an appointment I told him where
are you going oh my appointment he
didn't tell me my little point in
earlier this remember about it a couple
of this card look bad ones tomorrow okay
after lunch after once will go to a
movie or something like that and then
have some drinks later late look
I want I want to fight shadow an odd
with you Smith her I wish to go why I
don't want you I don't you die don't you
just to hurt my sister I don't want to
hurt your sister look look look maybe I
can make you understand what I won't
tell ya I don't want to hurt you and I
want you to go what Edwin's tender but I
want you to go I mean it says as simple
as that oh I don't want you're wrong do
you want to have dinner with us far and
I don't wanna I think y'all take land
route to dinner but also all of us ago
look I care to make it clear you I don't
want you around hurting my sister I
don't you heard anything of mine I'll go
just go out you're telling me to get out
get out man what do you want me to do
now just get out remember you told me to
get out look will you leave me leave
before I do something I don't want to do
right now you just get out of here go
ahead but you know you can talk when you
get out of the house
you got me you all right baby good night
baby and get some sleep with you
hey
Oh
that would have better be hot this fan
oh wait that's it turnin out how you
managed to get here free minutes before
i do what you do work get up later diner
watch the lungs are too bad for us look
just don't slop it up in there okay some
people like water on them on i'll go
drown yourself hey baby how you feel
fine great looks like i'll have to go
out by your whole field at tobacco hi if
your life like talk to me about it maybe
I'll help me no you there's not much to
say anyway just possible for somebody to
get a towel on this oh I forgot to put
them up i'll get you one I don't drag it
out it's probably some place you know
simple like in a hi-fi set look I better
get it while it's hot Oh alinea look I
got some cats coming up tonight and uh
you know if you don't feel up to it
you're weak account no no you it's all
right really oh I'll he didn't order
some things it'll give me something to
do okay that's my baby
Oh
I'll told me a story yesterday about
bird and bird had this big limousine
that had been like assessed by the
Bureau of Internal Revenue and he was
driving it all over you know like a
block long and he was driving with two
other people in the car and I was like
the guy in the Senate who like told me
and the guy in the outside he didn't
like and they were going uptown they're
going down Broadway and they had to make
a left and another left to go uptown so
as they stopped at the light bird's head
man would you mind getting out of the
car I have to make a left turn and so
the guy said okay bird and he got out of
the car and bird made his left turning
one on time without see that's sick very
better you get off of me yeah thanks
maybe I'll just join a smaller group in
Vegas ready what's this I hear about you
getting a job I mean that really really
upsets me you're kidding aren't you hey
funny very lady can I get you a cup of
coffee or something no here what's the
matter with you are you sick
you look awful you ought to get some
rest at night we're sure what I say just
just be good don't forget it what did I
say what's the matter with her nothing
you'd be interested in it wouldn't have
look she's my sister too i want to know
what's the matter with it nothing baby
just a little problem that came up last
night a little problem what is the
little problem look Benny it's just just
a problem two races so like I said that
look you be interested in who else carry
this party tonight oh just some people
you know what you need you need a guy to
take care of you and protective value
you know homeless little baby honey
that's what you need Oh Daisy chocolates
save me Oh Vicki oh baby he's wonderful
your love nicky no Amy danger Vicki baby
thanks oh yeah what's gonna meet later
Davy went to the same school you know
the brother school dynasty I Vicky um
how long have you known Vicki what'd you
do all day sorry pain Marcus maybe I
could drop by one afternoon taking a
movie s1 I don't like the movies well
they're over the place with the double
event a good club there how about that
far we got an offer hey I'm not drop
upon asking you maybe we can go for
water to the park are I don't like the
park even look at that break
are you I'm not interrupting am I 50
will you help me out put in a good word
here or there somewhere wow you talk to
let my baby are you doing hi have
wonderful of painters they haven't been
kind of thing over at Cooper Union she'd
love that oh I wouldn't take that off
well that's the kind of thing I enjoy
well we'll go then I'd like to see it
for a second can I know it's about Tony
say uh excuse me can I talk to the lady
for just a second something important
shit come on David I'm Robin not honey
it's okay honey please just come with me
free David please well he called me you
know he was very upset about tell me
that happened here the other day and he
got me upset about it I know this yeah
but I feel I'm involved in it I just
want to tell you that I didn't know at
all what he was like when no hay hay day
Thanks think of one come on baby bison
I'll see you later all right come on and
have a drink with us then join any party
and forget about your move hey y-you
know I was still out there thank you you
really really want to join in the party
but maybe we don't know how you want to
be cultivating nearly feeling me I
prefer be coats but don't you coax me
okay but there are the way you wanted
race me to get you a drink no thanks so
much you'll find that it's good for what
ails you just pull yourself together
because you're not kidding anybody but
yourself you know you have your sense of
values all mixed up so I don't touch me
come on just a little taste
mary had little Lance Bass white itself
everywhere to Mary went the lamb be sure
to go
geez your brother and I I find it hard
to believe you can't talk to him I don't
know right now I just be satisfied with
a home a few kids you know simple thing
I envy you he's a pretty unhappy kid you
know he loves you bad you can mixed up
and for some reason I don't know he
doesn't either goes want to is afraid to
okay he let her off the hook way yeah
the night's almost over let's end it off
with a little smile rather than all this
what's with this why don't you leave the
girl alone why don't you leave me alone
yeah I was only attempting to remind you
that we invited her here to have a good
time that's all she obviously wants to
hear what I have to say why did I talk
if we weren't getting a big argument why
don't you put it yeah I'd run if I want
a fight over to kill each other that's
my business okay every time I turn
around its you behind me pushing me
interfering with me you know you know
you said would be me thank you thank you
let's knock it over all right Hey look
I'm thinking if you're afraid the other
day it filled up when I'm when we're
singing you know I don't appreciate that
at all oh yeah i'm getting ready to sing
the song in the middle of song for what
reason I don't know what the hell why
you did it you decide to change it this
don't make sense at all right does that
make any kind of sense no I don't think
it's fair to sort of at the last minute
sort of thing no that look bright idea
is without interfering in with you I
think what you feel more is my attitude
towards life maybe that it bugs you but
don't hold it against me festively i am
sane i'm ashlyn are you planning on a
state here what time is it now I'm fine
after five key where the hell have you
been what the hell are you kid what do
you mean what the hell do i hear keys
where's Lillian's she's awesome mesum
that's play thank you look Ben I want to
talk to you know you're not gonna talk
to me now get out of my want to talk to
you
take your hands off yes Betty you're not
bro oh god you got the whole thing over
again no baby doesn't have to baby i'ma
tell you about Manson look wait a minute
will you I'm granny will you listen baby
i love you what the hell am I supposed
to say Benny Benny for God's take take
take the keys please baby be friends
buddies brothers hi already know where's
my flowers well I was late thought I
didn't have a chance to get up you know
I just right right although I just don't
think that's very nice of you at all
after all don't you think you should
bring a lady something when you beg to
take her out I can go back and get them
if you want me to no just go make
yourself comfortable this drink Celyn go
well be long honey as long as I am hi
there oh and Avia I'm taking layer to
the dance tonight okay how is meet you
uh one chiggers have a drink with my
brother and uh group Thanks inches you
should stop romantic huh and if it
doesn't even make sense with singer
what's all I don't want to talk what
what's up hey what's up dude Lanie
what's that yeah you want to sort of
think of one good tip it over
and not your post oh the whole song
sorry to just the other way you know I
want to leave good lady well wait stop
don't say I'm gonna sing all things like
that but close cuz it's not were you
just doing lucky day yeah oh I know that
song I'm doing in my nightclub oh really
all right oh boy that's terrific good no
but really uh I know it in his doing it
wrong oh really yeah what a show that I
do it that's wrong name if you're
dragging it through the mail it's all up
to me yo Ella will you tell now you know
you know you know you know you know oh
wow horseshoe I couldn't go along hey
Benny give me a smash what do you think
you're doing here I've only played even
thinking it rolling in a wrong view to
come in here and serve my relative okay
we sit down be quiet
what you mind is shaking it up Leia I've
been waiting for exactly two and a half
hours do you wanna go out with rec
always like to leave look nice I want
your look of it I want you to shake it
up your mind are you wanting bro the
dance with me it wouldn't be if I didn't
want to go to the dances well then you
wait I'm not finished yet hey hey what's
with you two yeah yeah you have to talk
to my bag I'll talk do I have to talk to
him that way yeah I wouldn't blame the
fellas he got off to the left hello
there was the whole wouldn't let anybody
talk to me like that you tell me look
I'm just happy to see Lexi burn out how
I look why did you be good boy good boy
I see arrest me okay right
hey what are you doing here I was a
tough hilaria but you can't talk to lady
I don't want you in here no I only to
talk let's get out of your fucking tell
me I don't have anything you gotta stay
will you go please Leo just don't know I
don't want to hear any pleases will you
go I don't really like a good on relays
for me wait a minute wait wait a minute
it's my problem this is our problem ah
problem okay but where you want this
mont you to tell her that I'm sorry all
right which is okay sorry okay okay you
tell her that yes I will most definitely
we tell her I realize now there's no
difference between us anything else
she'll always mean a great deal to me
anything else just tell her that Tony
said I'm sorry there's no difference
between you and Layla she means a great
deal to you and you're sorry thank you
you must like to find yourself a man
special people ya see ya okay what are
you doing get ready to go to Chicago
buddy how about you well I'll cracking
on I'll be right with okay so you be
honest
you're very good dancer sure you know I
believe you so that I know I'm a good
day oh wow what did he go you come here
often yes I like this place its wings
well maybe you can take you next but I
didn't ask well if I want to go i'm sure
you'll take me i'm with tenure or i come
from the mend of asking the girls just
go yes or no well i guess i just don't
fit into that pattern now to do I know
you don't it's a matter of fact you just
a little too much well then why don't
you take me home oh why did you ask me
in the first place Oh II girl do you
always shout down your boyfriend's that
I never shout well it would seem that
way to me look do you always go around
embarrassing people in front of
strangers I mean left them in front of
your family you keep on waiting for
hours just too short how masculine you
are darling but it would seem that way
to me why do you want me to behave well
just dance and D as lovely as you look
look David I am what I am and nobody
tells me what to do look I know who you
think you're fighting you know I saw the
way he looked at you back there and I
also for the way you looked at me
my
tell me
Oh
is
I
notice i chose horrible styria you i
like
ooh I got some bad news three move now
so I take all that telephone services no
point nuts going to Cincinnati because
the job is closed out what about Chicago
still there what happened Ackerman
Ackerman call sis gnatty at his own
expense and total and that you are being
difficult so that means no Cincinnati so
that means that we go to Chicago for a
week spilling and come back here and
maybe some cheap mangy cur Bowman will
give us a job introducing the here early
lioness well maybe you can sync your
ruco equations but we've been in this
business for a long time I supposed to
be a manager you're supposed to be a
singer right how old I ever managed
besides you and what have you ever done
are you able to get for you as Anna
black rose in Tucson Arizona from animal
is great wait no now I've had this rat
race by Pettit I'm busted I'm 46 and
I've been insulted by these pigs where's
that and what's in it for you or for me
but we gotta be failure let's do so in
our own City or get the hell out of here
where ma'am here the safe will go to
Paris France Africa I don't care
we got it wait a minute wait a minute
you believe in me rubadoux you believe
in me how I mean what what those other
people think of me I mean when we give
each other yeah what comes out of both
of us your talent my boys now when
you're on time you're still not on time
no do you believe this the course move
it I believe that you're the greatest
manager in the world and we're together
rogue you're the greatest manager in the
world x week eastland oh well yeah come
on
hey this is gonna get Shelly almost time
to see me almost hit me hey making out
girls the happiness boy singing up on
the Moonbeam girls the happiness boys up
on the moon be knew it little bump on
the Moonbeam boom boom up on the moon
bay Moonbeam boys what makes my head go
round while my heart so what's start you
need ice go there we just came to you
with clowns come on around we'll go
climb out somewhere else out buddy I'll
take it oh wait we've chilled out a punk
take it easy
ok
how about it you honey tell him her baby
is he wants the one he's all shook up no
more that's jazz for me baby they can go
home for a weekend cool it so what are
you gonna do we went out to have a ball
didn't we that's what we did so you
gotta pay the price man like you get
beat up to get beat up I don't know why
we do this man and you can go around try
to pick up girls it with broad you think
we have girls are on my area normal type
guy so so I'm do it anymore and it would
want to be me to be corny and say this
has taught me a lesson or it's taught me
less I get about huh okay forget about
um yes ok we have them I'm gonna shovel
okay Benny okay all right I see so long
I'll see it the house yeah used to so
long I gotta get a pack of cigarettes
you