hey
what do you mean you don't remember what
you did with the can of gas how do we
get back sure we spin the tank fuck you
wasn't my fault you'd left me on the
beach oh you're such a dork you guys it
finishes in the driveway Frank the
sucker but nobody complained until the
motor went did we're all alone out here
we're live hey this is no time to panic
here hadn't told us
well the shore is it that way
hey guys we're tired BTW speak for
yourself i can keep it up all night I
just knew this was going to happen
whadda you haven't even seen it yet
attacked by a shark that only happens in
the movie what if there's a storm
Dorothy his dogs don't happen during the
summer
come on
hey guys I'm worn out I got an idea I'll
lighten the load
don't get any higher it's only a summer
storm it should end soon right now
you're a goddamn weapon what are you
complaining about Leisha life stories to
tell you children if I live through this
shit I hit something
I can't breathe it I don't the damn
thing eat this
you
look there's something there
yacht
Oh
I'm gonna border like steak I'll go
be careful yeah
alright
hey Nick seem quiet up here come on
aboard
hello hello anybody here
since we got this far
let's go in
hey anybody around thank God we made it
I'm sorry I slapped you before its own
darling it stops raining we'll go man
wonder what they're studying hey where
the hell is everybody hey guys check
this out it's a lab to study marine life
it's an oceanographic research ship what
a weird yes they must have caught them
with a dive in the bed certain fish you
can only get way down deep Wow are they
dead of course they're preserved in a
special liquid so they can be studied
later one of them wasn't dead how do you
know
look over here so the wave not the face
onto the floor big deal maybe one of
them suddenly come to life tweet us all
don't listen to him after what we've
been through he still wants to get
around
well what do we do now not breathing oh
you guys are out of gas to wait you're
not gonna leave us alone you stay here
don't touch anything and nothing will
happen to you we'll be right back
what are you looking at those disgusting
creatures for but Dorothy they're only
fish they frighten me they have an evil
expression
strange that our night like this there's
nobody in the pilothouse weird shit
hello hello can you hear me
terrific that's all we needed we're
stuck in the middle of the ocean it's
storming and we're on a ghost ship yep
Jason yacht like this abandoned on the
high seas I can't believe it let's go
down right
hey guys what's happening up there nada
well huh well nothing there's no one in
the pilothouse we can call for help by
radio the radio is busted they must have
left my lifeboat no well maybe the
motors bus uh-uh come on they went away
leaving all the lights on I don't know
maybe we're expecting dinner guests Wow
home and garden beats the hell out of
the game here haha mm-hmm hey check out
that unit this is strange something's
going on look aquatic Banzai Oh terrific
I always dreamed Nevada yacht like this
yeah I could definitely hang here for a
while the kitchen it's empty come on no
way
if they're not in the cabins they're
nowhere hey this cabins empty yeah so is
this one hi I'm just corollas i give
good time what the hell is that QT time
Bobby Bobby what is it makes just a joke
idiot no really tell me you quit it huh
can't believe you people have no sense
of humor it's full of clothes hey what
size for men
I don't like the situation it's party
time
yeah if we're forced to spend the night
it's a good idea yeah Hey look at this
these guys are loaded
really Nicholson guys a chemist I think
it's time to buy a new bra
this must be the wives are one of the
sailors I was just thinking that man we
saw in the water could he have been one
of the crew
he could have been the owner of these
shoes
what were they do to this fish it really
looks like an operating table
your operational total anesthesia but
this is all absurd it's like in a
hospital when the doctors go out for a
coffee break during an operation this
one is lit up to there are images
what are those there are some fish sales
who knows where they went
who the chemists of course
I bet this is an electronic microscope
how do you know I studied biology in
school
this must be a refrigerator it looks
like a hibernation cell it's full of
frozen fish my brother runs a nautical
maintenance company he wouldn't cost
much to change the yacht's registration
number paint over the name make a place
to party in this lab huh what do you
think I take you already own this place
the drug dealers just left the ship
could tell by the day's marked off on
this calendar and the man we saw in the
water was knocked off by the gang drug
dealers what drug dealers Bobby is
convinced the yacht was used to refine
drugs everything else on the yacht was
to fool the Coast Guard what do you
think the only thing that certain it is
that we're safe as for the rest of it I
don't know there are some details which
puzzle me the man we saw in the water do
as part of the crew was in pretty bad
shape almost as though he was by
piranhas but we all know piranha live in
river water and as for the lab there
might be a way to find out if it's true
or not we check the computer yeah but
what do you know about computers the one
in the lab isn't like the toll you have
at home well I can try I'm telling you
the stuff in the lab is drugs
meanwhile why don't you cook up
something to eat instead of being is
your sister is busy with John Travolta
lets you and me see what's in the fridge
I'm really not hungry I think I'm coming
down with a cold after what we've been
through it's no wonder you don't have
been low yeah they have enough supplies
to last for weeks whoever they were
there's even fish here everything is so
fresh the crew must have abandoned shift
in summary which is our good luck hey
and let's hope they don't come back here
try to fish I'll take care of the rest
of it
are you crazy the fish is on fire god
damn it are you okay but the fish moved
in the pan sure oh this burning get
another pan there's only one fish left
all my life I've been alone oh boy but
now I got something to hold on oh baby
nobody don't worry honey for the rest
your life you can stay that way oh boy I
got something you can really sink your
teeth in a way but evident a bit finally
that's now
too bad for what we did you're gonna
give her Betty Crocker right and I'm
awesome huh my god you really like a pig
all right nope note the differences
between a blowjob and a half gramlich no
give up okay what look I've dinner
tonight i'll show you guys you can have
a great time on this yacht we fight our
friends at night oh what oh geez
forgot my friends tonight we tango hey
you hear that the sound came from below
what was it it's only mice no way they
got to be giant mice to make that noise
didn't you check it out below please
take a look below come on Bobby oh
alright there goes my sex life seamless
that light switch this fucking ship is
lame it's the storm take a look over
here anything on that shelf would say oh
yeah yeah I guess some i'll take a look
with this you wait here okay but be
careful hello anyone down here you see
anything yeah drats fucking get serious
Bobby Bobby
Bobby you find anything
don't play games
I'm coming down
please be careful
Oh
Bobby if you're playing fucking games to
be able to kick your ass
Oh
Bobby
where are you
body
haha scares the crap out of you you son
of a bitch follow me I'll show you what
I found look this stuff is gonna make us
rich god damn it but it research drugs
if you really want to know yes I've
tried everything in my life you'll see
I'll fix myself a dose later in fact
we'll all have some by the way the girls
could really see what we're made of
tonight I think you're nuts I don't need
that to make love just once look at this
give me some light man what is this
stuff kind of animals are these they're
horny ones come on will you drop this
shit or go get laid it's got here man
secret of your best unknown animals pick
theology interesting now don't tell me
you're gonna read that crap what's wrong
with reading it then I'm gonna take a
look at the computer in the lab you know
i'm not sure that your virgin is right
okay okay sweet she's home you take the
keyboard take the brats you hear that
what was it let's take a look
oh Christ Mike there's a man here is he
still alive no I don't think so what do
you think he is wherever he is silly I
think he's alive look come on Bobby
let's take him up above okay okay girls
look what we found he's got to be one of
the crew this guy's a really bad shape
why did he sting he must have peed his
pants she's right god it's nauseating
for baby somebody changes diapers will
you calm down well we just want to help
you oh my God he's freaking out
God he's one of the scientists his name
is Clark Duerson and he's a chemist ya
dumb chemist won't be tell us a damn
thing until he comes to and that could
take weeks what could have happened to
him it's a pain in the ass now we can
forget the yacht what's he trying to say
let's toss him into the ocean I was
kidding around aren't you I think he's
serious oh he bit me don't you get it so
obvious didn't need the chemist anymore
they gave him an overdose and left him
to die on the ship he's not dying all he
needs is some rest we all do I suggest
you all go to sleep I'm gonna take a
look in the lab you guys are here oh no
that this room only has two beds so why
you and me only need one bed good deal
this room is reserved for girls only
don't do that to me don't leave me alone
out here all night I'm afraid
Julie Julie the fish was bad
Christ hey hey Jesus what is it okay
thanks what happened she's all right hey
are you making jokes no trace was
whacking off sighs resting alone in my
room I doubt it oh I'm down tell me what
happened it's okay calm down tell me
what happened I'm swimming suddenly and
stomach pain went to the bathroom I'm
take me away from here I said little
animal like the ones in the lap gonna
wanna stand this bone another minute
major usual lullaby nightmare wasn't a
nightmare II dumb jerk cut of the
bathroom and see for yourself if you
don't believe me all right all right
calm down go take a look shut the fuck
up it's too
I'm Susie how would you like a shot
again how'd you like me to wash you with
my shampoo what kind of vision hey honey
i prefer with tits do you want harmoo
faster soon soft or hard tranny all I
can see is the vomit told you I want to
scare to the night gives her nightmares
she dreamed about those little monsters
in the lab oh there baby there well what
happened uh well you see see what
nothing only vomit bah and I don't give
a damn ur house of weather alright
alright I'll take you away just calm
down
goodies on
Mike be careful
oh fuck the boat is flooded the lifeboat
it's full of water we have to bail it
out
shit there's another step up here
we won't get out of your life
stay with your sister if she wakes call
me come on
I have to find out what happened here
something is really wrong the lifeboat
has a hole in it made by an ax there's a
professor shirt in it what are you
planning on doing I want to find out
they were researching on this ship we're
stuck here for the night anyway good it
works index marine biology presentation
margot this stuff is way out there it's
way over mine
it's like
wild stuff
I'm sr stepped on something soft
I don't see anything
hey Mike look at this what the hell is
it I accidentally touched his labor I
get it now this is a control console for
a distant teluk amber where are they I
believe they're in a bell at the bottom
of the sea along with the rest of the
crew it's attached by cables to a crane
I have the feeling that the secret of
this ship is somehow tied to these
strange fish they found fish thought to
be extinct God their work was amazing
dozens of different species
I mean
thousands of years old thousands my god
Oh
this is a real scientific lab not the
kind Bobby things I'll have to refine
drugs these fish bone to a group called
cross of temper kitchen
until today they were only known as
fossils dating from the devonian and
carboniferous period especially true
living fossils the underside is striated
furrowed or the structure is raised
they're carnivorous and live on plankton
and they have mobile eyes and a wide
field of vision they also live out of
water
carnivorous fish that live out of water
you know what that means
come on oh no house like Margaret we're
in the lab let's go oh my god here I'll
take care of come on out join you soon
I'm still get it do you
dammit where the hell did it go
Bobby shut the door I don't want it out
of here trying to convince me that one
of those fish that belongs in a museum
bit Margaret fuck the fish you idiot
these animals they fished are different
than the others damn it
the careful body
see
let me see it but it's here
now you see why this ship has no clue
strike audio
ah
you
it's over Mike it's over I'm not sure
it's pointing where that animal is that
it's missing from its container would
you care important thing is that we
killed those monsters Margot damn I
forgot
it's a whole other state of mind
what happened to his people
the rapture of the deep
bizarre
Freud would probably have a field day
good stuff
the hatchetfish kleptomania sajuk aren't
dead with exceptionally developed
genitalia in the rajma zone that is a
great depths neck two pd's given the
absence of the female are carnivorous
and game this is which shit
the name plankton includes both
vegetable mineral and animal organism
that live in the water though preferring
jacuzzis and they're transported by full
stretch limo cards
plankton prime source of food for fish
but above all the crustacean lost
Medusa's at cedar
professor do that how long have you been
fuckin fish yeah they were old enough I
world uh no I understand these things
happen
you
I knew you'd come sooner or later Shh
she just can't resist the big guy
well you were bribing so much
you worried about my virginity
so what are you worried about you're so
wrong not worried about anything you're
a sheep in my flock you can't escape me
fuck now you're talking you bastard let
me out give me the key which one this
one mutated species the erogenous Hamid
I fidy the harmless and Placid and it's
normal environment has been known to
become sexually aggressive when he
radically stimulated by inquisitive
minds plankton contaminated plankton
that's what's causing mutation professor
do listen the man who is below damn it
Margaret you almost gave me a heart
attack I'm sorry I didn't mean to
frighten you I woke up didn't see you in
your bunk I was worried Margaret I want
you to go below it's not safe in here no
way you stay I stay the fish you're dead
right sure stubborn how's your neck it
burns a little better much
Oh
fire in my veins
these fish went through a genetic
mutation caused by the plankton plankton
what's that plankton is the major source
of nutrient for fish it was contaminated
by radioactive waste dumped by a ship in
this area it contaminate the bottom of
this part of the sea contaminated the
plankton eaten by the fish and so they
became contaminated that explains their
strange properties these fish are
mutants creatures which because that's
incredible strength and vitality like
that damn fish that attacked you
professor do listen after having fished
them and put them under glass thought
they were dead evidently one of them
wasn't and ended up killing the whole
crew somehow it affected him here it is
after every discovery the professor put
them into the memory bank it's
horrendous I'm sure it's not in one of
the containers this is the last animal
recorded by the professor you remember
the broken container you mean it was
that thing who I think so and the most
worrisome thing is that it's probably
still on the ship why is the professor
dad I don't know but he's lost his mind
with sexual obsession that substance
Bobby thinks as if drug his life at eyes
plankton
oh ok
Oh
ah
we gotta tell him if it just touches the
stuff it's gonna be deep shit it'll be
fatal
due to radioactivity the plankton was
transformed into cancer cells and if it
comes into contact with human cells it
develops with incredible speed as soon
as it stops raining we'll get our rubber
boat and leave tomorrow will be one year
that we're engaged and I certainly don't
want to spend it here oh damn I didn't
even buy you a present really I'm glad
why because you would have never guessed
what kind of present you should have
bought well what kind a wedding dress a
wedding dress for what to get married
right I'm a month pregnant baby that's
great oh right I'm so glad you said that
I thought you'd be shocked huh Mike
Mike
huh
Oh
Jesus
oh my god fuck I'm gonna get it now
where to go like God be careful Mike
quick we have to get out of here wake up
Julie she must have fainted Julie Julie
we have to go Julie we be Julie you have
to get dressed understand we have to go
no Bobby not again ah Julie I'll give
you two minutes Dorothy wake up why did
you strip me you were making love to
Bobby what if he laid one thin anywhere
on me I'll make him swallow one of the
fish in the lab
we have to go it's nothing
the door just fell off the closet
Mike you crazy you say I'm the one who
does dumb things you could have killed
me okay guys that's hit the sack you're
upset you know I'm gonna go take a
shower drain the old dragon god I'm
losing my mind I almost killed him was a
host nation before don't you remember
what happened between you and Bobby no
sleeping yeah you have a strange way of
sleeping with your legs apart no panties
on I have to drink something it's
midnight it's midnight I would be
careful if I were you
damn it just won't stop raining tonight
I can't wait to get off this damn ship
what are we gonna do Mike
I don't know I have to relax a bit I'm
very very confused
professor deuce bricks something to
drink what are you doing as soon as it
gets light will take you off the ship
okay
I feel sorry for me he's in such bad
shape I have some pains on my gut like
it's boiling bubbling do you have your
period no here what could it be here
could be painful but it's not the
bubbling you described but it's not the
kind of pain you get when you have your
period I've had those it's almost like
something whittling and I've never felt
it before Mike what is it there's
something back there I don't see
anything will you tell me what's wrong
with both of you you've been acting
strange for some time maybe you're right
let's just a while it'll be done in a
couple of hours and we'll get out of
this sisters lucky being able to sleep
so peacefully I have to lie down his
legs are killing me you have any problem
i do you know what time it is Mike I'm
going to the bathroom I'll be right back
I'll leave the door open all right back
I'm not telling oh he's still in the
bathroom please can be seen
what's your ass down consultative am
don't you Myron worthy but please please
substitute hey granny tissue car
dogville you say
Oh
come on Poochie
please
what
duh
you're gonna be okay baby come on let's
go to the cabin we've got a quick but
now take her to the solano get life
jackets if we stay here all night quick
put these on the professor to I'll go
wit Dorothy Dorothy wake up we have to
go wake up Dorothy left leave the ship
hey hey if we don't get out of here
it'll be your last dream wake up Dorothy
you know damn come on Dorothy
Oh
you
you have no more sister my name is
Jessica Jessica please let's go first I
have to do something something important
destroy these monsters or we'll all
become like them no please don't leave
us alone here use it if you have to I'll
be right back
what is it
they're all over the fucking place
they're multiplying it's a thousand
funny invisible rotten son of a bitch Oh
black out malfunction malfunction on my
crippled short short Margaret it's Mike
don't worry professor we're going to
leave where are you Margaret it's Mike
Margaret where are you it's Mike
Danger Danger p 30-5 you have five
minutes to evacuate evacuate Red Alert
play Oh mark is anyone listening I still
hear footsteps evacuate evacuate you
have four minutes 30 seconds to evacuate
the time is now what you doing here
Anthony
Mike I swear I'll kill you
get it I'm okay and I'm loosening my
name is mike allton this time went
it's gonna blow up soon I wanted to make
sure nothing strange happened to you
come on professor we're going what
happened I don't know on the mic sorry L
or it'll be too late
Margaret what is it
my god two pages
take you away from here
Oh
beyond danger zone
wake up leave her alone there's more
pussy in the planet if we can save it
come on wake up
Oh
the radioactive potato
this is the last fucking I'll ever take
you