What do you want?
- Where are the jewels?
- Downstairs, at the vault.
- Gimme the key!
- What key? I don't have it!
The key or you're dead!
- In the drawer!
- Which one?
- I recognize your voice...
- Turn around and you're a dead man!
Please, don't!
- It's locked!
- I have no key for that!
- Give it to me!
- Be careful!
- It's in my pocket!
- Give it to me! Fast!
- Please!
- Give it to me!
- You'll regret that!
- I'll kill you!
Let's go!...
Let's go downstairs!
- You're opening up early, Mr. Vaziri.
- What are you doing here?
- Get in here!
- Help! Thief!
The old man rang the alarm!
What have you done, Hussein?
Why did you shoot?
He's with him!
Help! He killed him!
Get away from here! Bastards!
Go away!
Bastards!
Go to hell!
- [Text missing]
Get away, you bastards!
I'll shoot!
What's your problem?
Asshole!
I waited for 2 hours.
They wanted you there, personally.
- You got it or not?
- Of course I did.
Who do you think you're talking to?
- I was almost desperate.
- I waited for 2 hours. It sucks!
You said that without the money you
wouldn't marry my sister.
- I don't get it.
- Neither do I.
Doc says, it's ok.
Smile!
What's that?
I found a bag.
I haven't looked inside it yet.
In front if you, I don't hear you...
Yes, in front of you.
And this is for us.
Why is it torn?
Seems like marrying got her fat.
[Text missing]
It says "75", followed by... six zeros!
- How much is that?
- 75 million.
Are you kidding me?
Of course not! It's
a receipt for 75 million.
"Italian necklace.
For Ms. Roxanne Mazaheri."
You wanna humiliate me?
You know my situation.
I would never do that...
Especially to you.
Anyway, she paid for it.
Let's not argue about that.
How many months of hard
work equals to that?
Depends.
It seems you won the lottery!
"Expensive" is the key word
for every job.
Otherwise, everything goes wrong.
You need to be professional
and sometimes more than that.
- Ethics.
- Exactly.
- Honesty, I would say.
It's the same thing.
- Do I bother you?
- No, we enjoy hearing from you.
Honesty is the basis
of all professions.
Even yours.
It's a common profession.
There are many people
like you all over the world.
Last year, in Europe,
a colleague of yours...
...a colleague of ours,
I would say...
Took my wallet.
Seems he needed it badly.
He stole it you mean.
Everything was here before us.
Everything will be still here after we're gone.
Frm the ones that do it,
some are really affected.
Start to feel
guilty.
It's not so common to see
people like you. Open minded ones.
But you're not alone
in this profession.
Add me to the list.
It's easier to count the
ones that are outside the list.
"You wanna catch a thief? Arrest everybody."
From all our coleagues, only
the honest ones make it.
These are strong fags!
Some days ago, someone
stole a bag.
Found some change and
4 bus tickets.
I insulted them
the worst way that I could.
They hurt that lady
for some change.
Now, everytime she hears a
bike, she's freaking out.
She didn't let that bag.
She was drawn for 50 metres.
You must know exactly what
you're doing, before you do it.
Calculate the consequences.
Don't make so much damage
for just some change.
A woman, ouside
a bank...
Guess what's in the bag.
Choose the right time.
Divide good and bad
neighborhoods.
- How?
- That's art.
Bastard! Is he preaching us?
I'm totally broke!
He was talkin to me.
I have the dirty face around.
- How is a thief?
- Like him.
He thinks we're all the same.
Guess what's his profession.
He ain't robbing bags.
He plays with people's minds.
Keep your own!
If I had one
I wouldn't be in this mess right now!
If we were professionals,
we wouldn't be here.
- What's his speciallity?
- Crook. Charlatan.
You saw how he entered
in our conversation?
I hope you're not angry.
No. You're the
most experienced of all.
Specially with bags.
My office is right across the
street, if you need anything.
It's my treat.
See ya.
You don't seem that kind.
- Keep that, in any case. -
- Tear it.
Keep it, Hussein.
You never know.
What an idiot! "It's my treat"!
Two teas please!
Let's go. You bike
must be ready by now.
- You've seen that?
- What?
You've seen her bag? Is she
entering a bank?
Thieves need a
sixth sense. That's what he said.
Guess what's in the bag.
- What have you done to it?
- It's here, it's here.
Smells nice.
Lemme tell you this...
He was talking about bags...
...and now I'm looking the
bags, instead of looking the women!
You've seen that? She was holding the bag
firmly! What's inside damn it?
Some change and 4 bus tickets.
Look at her!
What the fuck is happening today?
- She didn't have a bag.
- I'm not talking about the bag!
If my siter finds out that I point
women at you, she'll be mad!
It's here.
The good neighborhood.
Lets go see how a 75,000,000
worth necklace looks like.
Lok at her!...
No, it's underneath it.
- You've finsh?
- No, I have some more.
And me, I have a feeling!
It musrt be here...
It's here, allright.
If she had a good body,
she'll be awesome!
I got a question.
- Shall we go in?
- I hear allright.
- I'll explain everything inside.
- Tell me.
This ring...
was his wedding ring.
He got fat and he
had to cut it off.
I'm getting married now.
Can you fix that?
We don't "fix" things.
You must go somewhere else.
In Galubandak.
Someone will "fix" it there.
Come on, smile!
To look at women
again!
How was it at your time?
Did women go out naked?
Without all these veils?
- How old were you then?
- 17 or 18 years old.
May I ask something else?
- Were you really insulted?
- Weren't you?
Not as much as you were.
You're very sensitive after all.
We're not good enough for customers.
That's what hurt me more.
The way he was looking at us!
Did he have to do that?
He was so ignorrant! Forget it!
I'll do a fag.
I'm not smoking in front of you.
I respect you too much.
A fag will do
good. Trust me.
I really like you, you know.
I know you too good.
He doesn't know you.
He's always counting money.
Does he has anyone in his life?
44 people at most.
Everyone he has can barely fill a bus.
Don't get mad.
Respect him and he'll
respect you back. That's the it goes.
Are you defending him?
Did you noticed the way he looked at me?
I'm not defending him! Don't
be so hard on yourself!
All I got is you
and my sister.
I'm so glad you two are getting
married. I was worried about her.
It's not that you couldn't
find someone better...
...but, no way you could find
a better brother-in-law!
As for him,
I will take care of him.
The one that pissed you off.
I'll teach him a lesson.
- What are you gonna do?
- You'll see.
- I mean with the bag.
- I'll give it to my sister.
Throw it somewhere.
It's a pity, the bag is nice.
Would you throw money?
It's not the same.
Money goes around.
But a bag can easily
be recognized.
You're right... She doesn't
like black colour anyway.
She prefers white colour.
A white bag for the marriage!
You must be reliable.
I must scream 10 times before she's here.
He's is in his own world.
I sceam his name
all the time.
You're right. Medicine
makes him a bit slow.
It's not his fault. Doctor says
he'll be allright, someday.
Number 33! Hussein
Emandendin! The order?
You see?
He's not coming.
If there's a problem,
I can arrange that.
He's a good kid.
Everybody likes him.
Even the boss.
They told him to work in the
kitchen, if he has problems elsewhere.
- But he doesnt't want to.
- He's claustrophobic.
He can't be closed
somewhere.
He likes riding a
bike. Makes him feel free.
He says it's
clear-minding.
He never wears a helmet.
I keep telling him to.
If something happens to him,
he'll be left with no brains at all!
You talk to him.
He's sensitive.
See you later.
This is for Vozara.
Then leave this to Alvand.
Mr. Sageste,
your order.
The levator is broken.
Forth flour.
Can you come down?
You see I have my bike...
- Nothing will happen to it.
- Open up.
Thanks.
Sorry about the elevator.
- What do I owe you?
- 18,500.
Here's 19,000.
Keep the change.
- It's you Mr. Sageste?
- Yes. It's me.
It's me, Hussein.
From Salemse...
At the Signals...
AT Communications!...
You've changed, I didn't recognized you.
It's cortizone to blame. I can't
recognize myself either.
- You've changed so much!
- You've changed yourself.
You were a holy man!
Aren't you in heaven yet?
You got a bike in the street?
Go! Here you are.
I insist... Don't get lost again.
I must go now.
Wait! What do you want?
Mr. Izandi...
Third floor.
Stay here. Park
the bike in that corner.
- I must deliver.
- Wait. I'm coming.
- Will we wait a long time?
- Until your daughter comes downstairs.
- When?
- Well, I wouldn't know. It's your daughter after all.
Please...
I'm a mother...
This is the last time...
She won't do it again.
Please wait in the car.
- The delivery boy?
- He has nothing to do with the party.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Boss told you allready. Just park.
- I got pizzas to deliver.
- Watch your mouth!
- I got work to do!
- Ask the boss.
I'm sorry but I've got work to do.
What can I do?
What were you told to?
- There's a car coming!
- Hide in the trees!
- Where are you going?
- In that house.
- In which floor?
- Second floor. Let me pass.
Are you goinf to the party?
- We're not up yet!
- You look suspicious!
- Put her in the car!
- We're not up yet!
Don't talk...
Just keep moving. Cooperate!
- You'll come to our tiny littly party.
- But we're not up yet!
Put her inside!
I don't care about second floor!
I must go the third one!
- So?
- They have ordered!
They must be hungry.
Don't you worry about them.
It's my job!
Let me do it!
Put the bike on
the sidewalk.
- Let me go!
- Do as I say!
How long do I have to wait?
As long as it's necessary!
- Come over here!
- What's wrong?
But we're married!
Let me explain!
- Aras, do something!
- Move!
How old are you?
Aren't you a bit young
for a soldier?
- How old are you?
- 15. No, 18.
- What do you want?
- I'm looking for my daughter.
- In which floor?
- Second floor.
Wait here.
She will come down
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. Wait.
- She's waiting for me in the midnight.
- You got a cellphone?
- Should I call from there?
Call her. She'll come down...
nothing is wrong. Just call.
- Lutenant!
- What's wrong?
You'll get afterwards.
Wait in the car.
Fast!
Can I call the restaurant so i
know what to do?
You cannot go.
Make way, I need some fresh air.
That's good...
Boss can perform miracles.
He needed some air.
He got him!
What's going on up there?
- I don't know.
- They're dancing.
- Just dancing?
- I don't know.
Put the gun down.
I'm still young.
- And why you are here?
- To watch out.
So noone escapes.
- And if someone does?
- I'll get him.
- You're so young. How you're gonna do that?
- With my gun.
At least you got a
reason for being here.
Has that ever happen to you?
- To have fan?
- What does that mean?
Have you ever danced
witha girl before?
No.
Look, they're gonna stop
that car.
What do you want?
I brought 2 girls before.
I'm here to pick them up.
- Name? Floor?
- Afsani. Second floor.
You can ring. Nothing else.
A taxi for Ms. Asfani is here.
Get in the car
and just go.
They are having all the
fan and I'm stuck here waiting.
It's wrong to deliver in
this neighborhood.
- Why should I wait?
- Don't you know?
If you leave, you can
tell them.
They won't come down and
we'll wait till morning.
Exactly. We are waiting.
We ain't eating or drinking.
Do you wait for everyone to come out?
They are done.
They are coming out.
- Done with what?
- Dunno, whatever they were doing.
- This way, ladies.
- Why? We didn't do anything!
Don't you touch me!
I'm coming!
Come. The party goes on
there.
I can smell their perfume.
Even from here.
You're lucky.
I can't smell a thing.
How long?
Last time we were through
at 4 o'clock.
They sleeping in the morning.
They do all that stuff at night.
- What stuff?
- I don't know. Getting drunk.
Have you eaten anything?
It's my treat then.
- You have not eaten. Take this.
- Thanks, but I can't.
- Come on!
- No, thanks.
Get some!
What's that?
- A gift from above.
- Is it raining pizzas?
Get some, so the others dare
to get some also.
- Only if I pay for that.
- One of your men has paid allready.
- One of my men?
- Figure of speech. Look...
Really, I can?
Share it.
Get some. It's for free.
The boss goty some himself.
You can get some also.
- How old are you?
- Will you tell the others?
- Fifteen.
- Too young for the army.
My big brother died.
I took his identity card.
- What's going on here?
- A party.
May I get the kids?
- That's what's happening every night?
- I don't know.
Look at Hussein!
So stylish!
- Why is he dressed like that?
- I'll tell you afterwards.
- Will we be allowed to go in?
- Trust me.
Allright.
You look like rich people.
May I help you?
- There was an old man...
- Mr. Vaziri is downstairs.
I want gold for
my fiance.
What can I do to help you?
- I would like a set, with necklace, please.
- One moment please.
- Is mr. Vaziri here?
- Coming right up.
- We're in a hurry.
- Would you like to drink something?
Mozafarians are here!
- What can I do to help you?
- A nicklace, please.
You have a price in mind,
so I can help you easier?
- Something between one...
- Two million please.
Let me show you
some of our items here.
The blue ones,
that's what I like most.
They are much more expensive
than you told me.
Come this way.
I'll show you some more.
I suggest these.
They are Italian made...
Or this.
In crimson gold...
What's your favourite?
Crimson or white gold?
Gold from India or
Pakistan are really nice.
We don't have that kind.
Italian and Iran made are
in fashion nowdays.
We don't import from
anywhere else.
You prefer something from the
ones I show you?
What are we doing now?
You pay. You choose.
How are you?
Your order is ready.
I hope you like it.
May I see it?
You want a mirror?
We're in a hurry.
What do we owe you?
It was a pleasure helping you.
9,600,000.
He didn't even looked us!
- Bye. Come back soon!
- The pleasure is all ours.
- I'll try this one.
- Do you like that?
- What is it?
- Diamond on white gold.
- It's price?
- It's in your limits.
- What do you say? ...The necklace.
- It's nice.
Do you want to try
the earrings also?
- Yes, give them to her, please.
- They must be expensive.
Give her the ring please.
Are the ones I asked
more expensive?
I have no idea.
We don't have anything like this.
I can't help you, I'm sorry.
They must be more expensive.
They are bigger.
- Is this nice?
- Yes, wear the one too.
They are not shoes!
- How much do they cost?
- 250,000.
250,000 is the price
for this pair of earrings.
And the necklace
costs 1,550,000.
Total price, 1,800,000.
That's less than you were willing to give.
May I give you one advise?
You've chosen something Italian.
Buy something you can easily
refund.
We want to keep our
customers happy.
Buy something handmade
from Iran.
- Can we see something?
- I don't have anything here.
You'll find somethiong in the Bazaar,
in Galoumbandak.
If he was to marry my daughter,
i'd advise him to invest.
And don't buy jewels.
Gold can be
easily refunded.
Bye.
And congratulations.
What got into you?
- What's wrong?
- It's Ali's fault!
He told me to get dressed like
that. I didn't want in the first place.
He has no idea with whom
he's dealing with.
- Wanna fag?
- No. I'm cold.
I'll get your jacket.
- It's my fault you got upset?
- No. Let's go.
Your cap.
- Do you want me to take you somewhere?
- No, go.
- Will you bring my sister?
- Yes, go!
You're mad because I
raised my veil?
I wanted you to see the necklace.
I was so glad to see you like that.
With a costume and a tie.
You were good.
We'll get married soon.
I didn't want to come.
I only came cause you asked me to.
I don't care about the jewels.
We can rent some.
To keep the pretexts.
We'll return them afterwards.
I don't need them.
Are you mad at me?
Tell me, are you?
- No, I'm not.
- Why we went there?
- There must be a reason.
- Nothing really.
It was veryu expensive. I was thinking
something around 200, 250.
Ali said 1,500,000
and you said 2,000,000.
Is it my fault now?
What have I done?
Are you mad at me?
Because I raised my vail? Is
that what bothered you? What?
- Nothing. Just don't talk.
- I wanna know what.
As you wish. I just
don't wanna see you upset.
Is tie's fault?
You don't wanna wear a
tie in our wedding?
There must be something wrong.
- Tell me what you want.
- Goodbye.
I didn'do anything!
I didn't do anything!
Why are you taking me?
Stop! Take
the kids inside!
Hello, Hussein.
One moment.
I'll bring the box.
Can I have a light please?
Go out of the way,
you skinny bastard!
How you're doing?
With all this cold?
I'm tough.
I can tolerate anything!
- Nice shoes.
- Very stylish right?
- Aren't they a bit small?
- A bit large you mean.
Have you tried them on?
Reza said, the bigger
the better.
Small shoes and small
women are always bad news!
- Are they expensive?
- Do you like them?
- How much did the cost?
- Not much.
If you paid a bit more you
could buy a pair like mine.
Really?
Let me see...
You bought them from the bazaar?
- You can't find another pair.
- Take them out! They're dirty!
The more expensive,
the better.
- The look nice on you.
- Thanks.
I'm late. I'm gone.
Have you seen his girlfriend?...
very beautiful.
She came by last night,
Everybody went crazy!
They were so surpised!
He came on his bike.
A ferrari would be more suitable for her!
What a pity!
Some people are more lucky than others.
One in a million is as worthy.
- Men also!
- One in a million is a positive thought!
Ali is so lucky that
has you as a groom.
- Are you kidding me?
- Not at all.
Is that my order?
Don't you forget the money.
Thanks. I'm off.
I told you to write better.
I can't read a damn thing.
Zaferani, Building A.
You want me to read the number for you too?
Yes. How many?...
Hussein. Wait.
How many, you said?
Once more for
Zaferani.
I didn't see that. I was there
when they were taking him away.
- What did they say?
- He's in a bad situation.
I'll go visit him
after work.
Where are you taking this?
Give me that shoe!
Show some mercy!
- A delivery for Mr. Nakahi.
- He's waiting. 18th floor.
The elevator?
- To the right.
Mr. Nakahi?...
I brought the pizzas.
Bu the girls are gone.
- I came as soon as you called me.
- What am I supposed to do with them?
- You ordered them?
- Yes, for two sluts!
The city of madness!
Are they gone?
The two girls I mean...
Are you sure? You've seen them?
Sorry. I don't get it...
what do I owe you?
It's the city of madness!
That slut came, but she
brought a friend with her.
The came and the left...
I don't get it.
That's for you.
I don't want them.
You can keep them.
- Three pizzas for me alone?
- I'm alone too.
Let's eat together then.
I can't. I've got work to do.
- In the midnight?
Everything is closed. I'm hungry
myself. Let's eat together.
I wanna talk.
I'm so depressed.
Come on in.
Don't be shy.
How fo you live in this damn city?
That's the city of madness.
Μη βγάζεις τα παπούτσια!
Unbelievable! I just seen her a couple of times
and she was preparing for a wedding allready.
She's nuts! I was with someone
for 5 years, when I was there.
Five years and never talked
about getting married!
I put so much effort
in cooking something.
And what does she say?
"Let's order some pizzas!"
Don't stand in the way.
Let them fuck themselves! Sit down.
- Here? Like this?
- Just forget it. Make yourself comfortable.
- Bathroom?
- On the back, to your right.
She wanted to be here.
And she showed up with a friend of hers!
They got themselves locked in the bathroom
and then they just left...
Why did they come after all? I was so
damn tired trying to make a proper meal!
- Are they here?
- Why? What's wrong?
- There is blood.
- Where?
You damn dump fucks! They left the
moment they got out of that fucking bathroom.
They can't even solve a
biological problem!
They fill their bag with
cosmetics, instead of...
...filling them with something
usefull for their shitty lives!
Go to the bathroom upstairs.
I must clean here.
Plus, they're gone!
"My parents don't approve
this kind of contacts."
Sorry. I used
your stuff.
- I was so dirty.
- Don't you worry.
- Is this your appartment?
- Of course not.
It's my parents.
I just live here.
To be exact, I just "rot" in here...
Sit donw, let's get to know each other.
What's your name?...
My name is Purang.
- Where are your parents?
- In the US. I was there too.
But I got nostalgia. I'm back
now, and I'm feeling a total stranger.
Noone understands me. They
are different, weird.
Doing the simplest of the conversations...
...while trying to talk, I feel
I am talking to a wall.
Everyone is pervert here.
You are pervert!
- Why don't you eat something?
- You?
I lost my appetite.
I'd rather talk.
As for the bathroom...
We made a mistake.
I wish it was what I believed in the
first place. It'd made some sense.
Now... My head is
gonna burst!
- What was it?
- Red nail varnish.
She did her nails!
I don't get it.
It's horrible. You get it now?
They are horrible!
- You got some water?
- I'll get some.
I'm glad you listen to me.
Someone is marrying and his
wife ain't a virgin.
He pretends nothing is wrong.
The marriage isn't ruined...
Next morning she hears her
screaming out loud.
She goes up to her to check what's wrong.
Her ears are getting pierced.
It wasn't exactly the place
that needed "piercing".
Should she do her
nails in my bathroom?
- Do you listen to me, Hussein?
- Yes.
You didn't laugh.
My mouth was full.
You find something interesting?
I'm looking for my house.
I've never seen the city from this high.
It must be somewhere there.
You stop hearring.
It's ok.
You wanna see the city?
Go upstairs.
I was exactly like that
the first time.
Nice view! My father
was building the house for 4 years.
He stayed for 4 months
and then he left us.
This is what I mean
when I say you're weird.
So many rooms...
For two people only...
It's her. I can feel it.
She calls and she doesn't talk at all.
I can't believe it!
They call and they don't talk.
- Eat!
- I lost my apettite!
I'm definite it's her.
Say something!
Why don't you say something?...
I know it's you.
If you're not talking, hang up.
Why don't you say something.
Say something!
Listen to me!
I beg you...
Stop calling me...
Or talk! It's you!
Do you hear me?...
Why are you doing this?
What's this game?
I know it's you.
Your pizzas are here.
I didn't eat them.
Do you hear me?
Take a cab and come over.
Do you want to sent one?
Do you hear me?
Fuck! She hung up!
- Can I smoke?
- Yeah, I'll do a fag myself.
- What kinda cigarettes are these?
- '57 brand
- They're heavy.
- Yeah, for me too.
- You want something lighter?
Nah, it's ok.
I forgot to offer you before...
I've got some booze on the fridge.
I don't drink. You?
Here, men do drink... a lot.
They drink just for the idea.
I need environment,
some occasion.
I don't get it...
You can find almost everything in this fridge!
Wait.
She's talking at last!
No. No-one is here.
I'm alone, yes.
I told you. Get
the pizza out of the fridge.
You talk too much. Let's not argue any
more... Come back here.
We'll talk when you're here.
I haven't invited you before,
you came by yourself.
Come back and we'll talk...
Come back, I said!
Ok, it was me.
I invited your friend.
I told you, it was me.
Forget about it...
You didn't eat. Neither did I.
Let's eat together.
Come back.
Let's talk about it.
Listen...
Why don't you just listen?
The night I met you...
I was about to shave
my beard.
But you said I
look like Shakespeare.
I kept one for you.
- Who are you?
- Where are the jewels?
- What jewels?
- The ones in the window upfront...
What do you want? Why
are you doing this?
- Where are the jewels?
- What are you doing?
- I'll kill you!
- Why? Don't do it, please!
Where do you think you're going?...
Where are they?
The blue ring...
from the window upfront.
- Stop!
- Where is it?
- Where have you put it?
- In the vault!
- And where is that vault?
- Downstairs!
- Let's go downstairs then!
- You're making a terrible mistake!