the incredible legends of the abominable
dr. phibes began a few short years ago
all of them are unfortunately true it
was here in London's fashionable mall
Dean square whence Phibes ventured out
to work his diabolical revenge against
those responsible for the death of his
beloved wife Victoria and the
destruction of his own face making it
necessary to talk through an ingenious
mechanism in his neck my wife existed
only six minutes on the operating table
you murdered her when the acid reaches
him he will have a face back
the most brilliant minds of Scotland
Yard were battled as the amazing murders
continued each more fiendish than the
last and in this soundproof basement of
his mansion none could hear his
flamboyant songs of triumph and revenge
played on his organ and by his ingenious
clockwork musicians we have got to find
times only by a stroke of amazing luck
did the police seek out mall Dean square
but the fiendish dr. Phibes was prepared
for such an emergency and building his
face a new he entered the crypt where he
had enshrined his beloved wife
incredibly maintained neither alive no
completely dead and there Phibes placed
himself in suspended life like her until
it would be time for Phibes to rise
again
dad it's as if you disappeared off the
face of the earth Vybz lay in darkness
three years until the moon coming into
proper conjunction with the eternal
planets shone upon the golden moon of
the Crypt pulsing with a fantastic life
of its own
lifeblood then flowed back into Phibes
great wheels and motors strong into
motion and dr. Phibes once more what
upon the earth
Oh
Victoria for three years I have rested
beside you tonight the glorious moon has
risen to the exact position which last
occurred two thousand years ago
signaling the opening of this script and
the beginning of our greatest adventure
we shall embark to the land of Egypt
where years ago in a mountain
overlooking the valley of the Pharaohs I
did prepare for us a wondrous shrine
unknown by any living man there my
beloved awaits the key to resurrection
for you and eternal life for both of us
and once again I call on you for Naevia
come one more time my trusted aide join
me and my beloved for we have work to do
to bring her back to life
Oh
thank you my dear for answering my call
upstairs in my safe is a most precious
map of papyrus the way to a Pharaoh's
tomb beneath which flows each 2,000
years the river of life we must make
haste and find the river at its flood
let us go upstairs and prepare for our
journey no no while I slept in sweet
oblivion who dare destroy my house the
safe the safe could it still be here
there
patna themed has taken it only one who
seeks eternal life as how you do my
derbeck the papyrus we are paradoxically
worthless here's Ambrose worthless but
without my knowledge or my
interpretation of the translations it
has no value of significance three years
it took me to come upon this grand and
final realization it was the one the one
piece I'd searched for my whole life may
are you paid a bitch ah so this is a
papyrus that I've read so much about
I've made no secret of it it seems that
when they demolished some old house in
malden squared came into the hands of a
dealer who contacted me knowing of my
interest as it seems to be was a matter
of life and death to you you're a
strange man acclaimed as one of the most
brilliant minds in the Western
Hemisphere and yet you seem obsessed
with yes the spiritual the mythical
aspect of life of course I'm obsessed
with life somewhere in Egypt that
obsession will be answered this this is
all hypotheses five years ago I toured
the whole area indeed Ambrose and
nothing well I remember looking down
upon the whole valley that my friend was
your greatest mistake you looked down he
didn't ever occur to you to look out who
Sky exactly that's where the answer lies
the stars
the moon the sky is the key while you
look down I look up the rings around
Saturn when were they discovered will
beginning of the 18th century exactly
and yet look here see plainly marked
that map is 5,000 years old and this
only a frightened but of what
significance it's a page from the
logbook of the Phoenician trading ship
notice the positioning of the stars a
chart far more sophisticated than
anything we allowed for in our
calculations and finally this the temple
of hibiscus that's where we're going
what do you hope to find if there's
treasure gold Ambrose it's yours i'm
seeking something more what more do you
want i like to think he wants me I can
tell by your face you've forgotten we're
dining with Princess Rica I'm sorry I'll
go up and change may God was a drink
with you
when are you two going to get married we
better our star is that perhaps after
this trip you know sometimes it's like
well as it is going to Egypt for my
benefit every day grows more preoccupied
with something I only wish I knew what
it was though ambriz I don't want to go
I thought you wanted to go oh no telling
i wasn't talking about tonight don't
worry well are we ready here we go then
come along my dear what at least the
mail should be interesting oh you
greater good claret anyhow Darius we
can't keep the princess waiting blue
blood you know I'm always josef pc we
Lloyd
No
so once more I have been forced to kill
for you Victoria only that you may live
again oh here where mystic lines
converge we'll find the door that
separates the living from the dead I say
um has he any known relatives in this
country sir it would seem most unlikely
hmm well may I ask how long has you been
in your employment these questions are
academic inspector the papaya that may
if you don't interrupt me it damn well
is so the papyrus is missing and that's
all that I'm concerned about not this
prolonged postmortem Wow no now let's
just get our priorities right a man has
been senselessly killed murdered all
right so he has but I have been
senselessly robbed now curious as that
may seem to your police mentality the
ladder is all that I care about you
understand find the papyrus and
doubtless that will lead you to the
killer but find the papyrus first I got
24 hours to complete your investigation
well papyrus who exactly would know that
it was in your possession any interested
party I made no secret of its purchase
but it would be of interest only a
handful of international scholars all I
assure you completely above suspicion no
trout what you are looking for is a
common thief who was surprised her man
who pierces the skull of another man
with a golden snake it's not a common
thief sir with respect with respect just
what then are you suggesting that it was
a calculated act by a man who knows the
true value of the papyrus yes sir no
foreskin all the world can stop us now
for in
mountain range where pharaohs once
reside a palace I have built beneath the
stone and there will wait until the
great appointed tide reviews a secret
door through which will find new life
and now both why ours to all of us with
you victorious safe in your sealed abode
we drive to Southampton then channel
then the open sea come volnay via we
sail
a sweet Victoria what happy times of
years ago I think of now it won't be
long my love before we've reached our
goal and moving breathing you in my arms
again and I and yours in Egypt I frying
the key the key to the elixir of life
June first at sea bound for Egypt and
taking three drops of my elixir of life
the vials are almost empty if I fail in
Egypt I am doomed
you
awaken old sick one nice flat they have
lifted Dane head tortilla ridin appear
now it justified against those that
sought to do the harm one of my favorite
passages from the book of the dead or
relating to the divine incarnation of
the phenomenon of rebirth singularly
appropriate Ambrose
our voyage has now become bonet via
though brief the time aboard this ship
will seem too long I know so eager are
we to arrive in Egypt and complete the
preparations I began long years ago here
in the mountain marked on this papyrus
beyond corridors which led once to a
Pharaoh's hidden tomb awaits the key to
resurrection and life I shall decipher
it nothing nothing will stop me now I
must tell Victoria hidden safe below
away from curious eyes we have but three
short weeks until that glorious day how
would you pinpoint the most important
part of the globe Ambrose rocks a road
for San changes daily only rivers flood
twist for new courses topographically
the world is in a perpetual flux with
the sky the sky remains the one constant
factor wonder only theory of your
leading app to my theories alone
evidence ancient civilizations knew
about this capitalized on it to what end
the return of the life force
as I say they're not my theories a 3,000
years old let me show you another
fascinating aspect of this affair
where's that model of the mountain ute
in the hole then it can wait i'll tell
you tomorrow but Fanta break I won't be
able to sleep I must know tonight hey I
go down and get it hey you haven't
discussed this with anybody else have
you of course not and Ambrose I forbid
you to tell anyone of this conversation
probably one of these let's see now oh
no no that's not it huh I'll quite the
kind that model I'm looking for hey
might just be stored in here sir mt I
suppose pity ah I took small like it
yeah well thank you very much officer
and I mustn't keep you from your duties
like as you said I could quite easily
just oh I can magnify myself I wish as
you say should thank you good night
without you but hell
Oh
come in by the day yes captain I'm sorry
to be the bearer of bad news I have made
two complete sweeps of the area and
found no trace of your friend very well
then that's that I'm afraid that we must
face up to the fact that well time is
running out mr. bata dick and not out
you'll resume your normal course kept
got heavens no naturally I tend to use
my every part of find him he's continued
with certain till dawn if necessary you
said yourself there's no hope it's been
two hours this delay is intolerable
please bring your ship around cat I
would remind you said that the
navigation of this ship is my
responsibility I shall of course bear
your suggestion Mike what are you a good
swimmer I have no idea captain I suppose
he never how can I put this I suppose he
never touched the bottle then how the
hell did you get in there in the first
place rider must have branches by here
I come back from me even the first thing
I find on my desk is this Oh set enter
the Gloucester squirt murder the
Gloucester square man I can hardly read
your writing mr. on arrival i discovered
the man's body surrounded by balls okay
plug on the snooker table sir what who
balls on sook devil cause of death was
apparently by a small gold snake which
entered the man's left here a great
speed and having pierced the scowl
reappeared through the right in my owner
the other cell death it would appear was
instantaneous a brilliant now just why
was his employer the principal witness
allowed to leave the country tell me
that well it was a very delicate matter
CERN I was studying with a very
difficult gentleman well I've got news
for you charge or dealing with even more
difficult but now do you know what time
it is uh just after one sir I've been
waiting for you since nine well I was
cooled out last night sir where to sit
called Fawley never heard of it except
the mouth of southampton water sir the
man's body had been washed up fallen
overboard incense yes sir men fall
overboard all the time that's what the
locals of all that's what I complain
about in his department this one was
inside a pulsar doer he was inside a
bottle glass it was about seven feet
long talked to Egypt and our arrival
here
my compliments to you Val Naevia you
have done wonders with the local fish
but we must not dally while Victoria
safely sleeps we must hasten to the
caves within and learn what time has
wrought since last I ventured there
you
see panavia mother a has been disturbed
some minor decorating some touching up
and it will seem like home lights music
Palladia a song of celebration unveiled
the ban
we're looking for a madman sir well you
bloody well found one do you realize
this is Saturday afternoon we'd have a
little talk with you in private says
you're the shipping agent Larry do
appreciate you coming along at such
short notice mr. Lombardi wasn't a very
much option did I with a radical a
police car rolling up outside my club
frightful intrusion and as I say on a
Saturday afternoon well it is a rather
delicate matter sir hmm we've we found
the body well I didn't know you miss
labor who's Ambrose is the man who fell
off him ah him yes sir well look if it's
about insurance it's much too early for
me to commit I mean well it seemed for
the office that he was said yes we are
loose I big one who live to involve
anybody else at this juncture well we
have a strong reason to believe that he
was murdered her killed yeah yeah I got
her sapne oh boy okay did you know the
gentleman well not intimately but I knew
him of course professionally because he
was always getting on these cruises out
the Middle East it was an archaeologist
no Dean around in the dirt now you chaps
Yeah right this may seem a rather
obvious question said but on this
particular passenger list what is there
anyone who described as a tall house I
put it odd no ready lot of us well no
that's a slight exaggeration now I I
wouldn't say exceptionally odd odd ish
well is that it for the time being thank
you of course if you should have second
thought sir by even the smallest thing
we would like to hear from you or I
probably would allow me I'll think about
it course we do have a lot of eccentric
people as i said before on these tours
but a textual sources incident last
earlier there was a woman oh well I'll
saw another dad well whatever they ask
for we as I say we tried to keep them
happy yeah we get chefs wanting pianos
in their suite really like imagine has
been no still thing along moonlight
sonata guys are good we are grateful to
you for coming along stop you're now on
this last ship a fellow added an organ
well are we are I'm sure would you just
say that again sir well I'll be off
never noticed before oh the organ to
mean that's it so yeah oh I didn't think
was anything about it I think he's
probably an organist I remember the girl
stipulated that a cinema which go the
girl who did the booking what's her
employer's name Phibes finds no Smith
get hell of a lot of Smith's Smith thank
God for that well thank you again mr.
Lombardo's and asking moment trucks this
girl who did the wastelands time cloud
we've all got our jobs to do did you see
the man at all no no no I didn't see the
man I just saw the girl she was a very
beautiful girl very tall you'd have
liked her there was I thinking on the
strange about I especially was probably
any entertainer or something about of
course there's the answer fellows on the
boards one is a bit of practice on the
way over did you take anything else
Williams organ music far to go down well
with all those Arabs talk with musicians
life-sized clockwork musicians an
incident to that isn't all all we took I
remember they took a lot of sons matter
and I got all the details over my office
I'd like to come along take the house
true I know you didn't see you the man
no I didn't see the man I just saw the
girl as I told you she did the whole lot
she did the paying and every defect did
you pay by check no I ain't no no cash
return fare no single single one way
maybe he won't come back oh it's fives
Eliza and he always comes back
you
well you near the st. John build a
better mousetrap in the world will beat
a path to your door every time we built
a better mousetrap survivors build a
better mouse damn else that nothing to
do with me sir you sure it's not one of
your do you mean one of mine
oh there sorry I must have dropped right
off yeah but may we ask why you're here
I've come to see mr. Waverly would you
like me to go sir I'm Wibbly it wasn't
that nice such a sweet man showed me and
I man Ambrose you know Ambrose your it
cousin of the late Harry we were very
sorry about that it he must have been
great shock not all that close i'm
afraid we kept in touch occasionally i
thought he was a mysterious old bird can
you tell us anything that might be of
any help mr. been Embree rose did
anybody bear him I'm sure and if
anything it was hardly luck is it I've
been you spent most of time leaping
around the world it's possible I suppose
though hmm just before you came your
night took the liberty of looking at
this map that's not where they're going
at all you know who abide it back and
that lot now here this is much more
likely
where the devil is everybody mr. von
domek I'm Hackett well I imagine the
others on the Hale instructions work for
everyone to wait until I arrived at the
base camp everyone hmm well uh Stewart
and Baker couldn't wait they've gone off
to explore the mountain they've gone off
to do what what they were getting a min
impatient and shavers oh he's around
packet well come on come on where I'm
sorry darling you stay here and rest
come on dammit hack and no man should go
near that mound alone nobody really
knows what's in there sleep on my sweet
victoria for regal claws of sacred birds
god well your place of rest for those
poor fools that dare intrude the penalty
is death
you
if you have a good dinner
do you realize what this is a secret
room hidden from view so long as it is
flooded but now as the moon rises
towards a Zenith the waters have receded
and they flow underground perhaps into
the hidden river of life itself
somewhere through there vulnavia awaits
our answer
what Pharaoh of what forgotten dynasty
arrested here before he drifted on the
bosom of what stream beneath these
stones to find eternal life
a secret compartment beneath the
sarcophagus large enough to hold
Victoria what other secrets lie within
the key and actual key how ironic and
Hulk never when I find the locket fits
i'll have the shavers Baker where are
you straight ahead fighter back just
what the devil you think you're doing oh
oh well it's just a preliminary sorties
on whose authority we didn't realize we
needed permission Stuart when you're
older and more experienced perhaps
you'll learn to have some respect for
authority you might do well to keep in
mind that you're a member of my team
working for me and is this your Mountain
sir I regarded as such yes are we to
take that literally sir it may take it
however you wish but understand that I
give the orders any explorations will be
planned and led by me understood
Oh
but you know we're not exactly amateurs
here if discoveries are to be made it
will require individual effort and a
certain amount of intellectual freedom
Hackett there are no prima donnas here
discoveries will be made by the team
under my directions well then perhaps
you'll be so kind as to enlightens just
where is all this leading to in good
time Daris I'm not another heads usual
for all information to be pool sir I
found out it's rather urgent what is it
done I have a little discovery of my own
that I think you ought to see
you mustn't let this upset you upset me
so matt has just been killed in the
desert my dear not taking tea and
mayfair curious is it me seem you don't
have to remind me of that I've drunk
lots of tea & mather without planning
dead bodies at my feet would you just
trust me trust yes trust how far is that
gonna get me or us I mean how can I you
don't trust me what's that supposed to
mean that supposed to mean anything
she's perfectly clear to me you don't
trust me you won't tell me your attitude
has changed suddenly human life means
nothing to you anymore have I ever said
that no but I just have so callous now
is that what you really think do you
want to see care what I really think do
you of course I do it's just the night
but he says I can't explain it what's
holding you back I mean it's that isn't
it why does that big mountain have so
much hold over you I mean just what is
it that goes on in there
how lovely she looks my darling on her
way to her last brief sleep before
awakening she shall rest well none can
find her
you
I am protecting you Victoria from those
who would discover us I shall eliminate
them all one by one yes even Beiderbecke
himself if need be my beloved in this
secret compartment made by partisans
millenniums ago you shall rest like the
princess you are for when the moon next
comes full the waters of the Nile and
the tides within the Seas will somehow
meet and life will flow within your
veins and love within our hearts
yeah um we've got enough trouble around
here without you're dreaming out more
that kind of trouble I can take any time
yes well she belongs to buy the Big M
your bears were some more than others
ice it seems you gentlemen have nothing
better to do this evening perhaps you'll
unload the other truck what truck
Hackett's trunk
get a good night's sleep you still
haven't told me what to expect to find
tomorrow no Doris I'd like to know now
tomorrow
you
my
you're bloody mad forgot but I
if music be the food of love
give me excess of it no yeah with a loaf
of bread beneath the bar book of verse
glass of beer that's that so Mike I am
sure yeah you know I'm a bit
apprehensive about finding the other sir
do you think you know where we are to
chart I don't think I now I don't think
you know either sir keep your place
tried right
out it Caro um do it there by the same
token the Red Sea is over there that
direction trod yes sir England yeah yeah
quite so sir but how do we find this
mountain range where by Tibetan Phibes
are headed there are times chat when I
worry about you all we have to do is to
ask someone else here sir why not
Barnaby somebody oh there there's
somebody where sir um three dunes East
up to it man stop attack
how could I need you what's all this
about why are we taking the truck Getty
and I sent Baker and the Arab workmen up
there why are we taking Eddie on we
broke through a wall found a gold
sarcophagus already underground waters
have begun to rise somewhere within this
maze of tunnels a new river will crest
along which we will glide through gates
which will be reviewed to us panavia the
gaze which can be unlocked only with the
silver key come I must tell Victoria
those Devils to take from me the two
treasures of my life I shall get them
back who tries to stop me will die
it suddenly as a remarkable fun how he
knew it was their business me you went
straight to it I think it calls for
celebrate y aquí no I don't know but
something's been biting him
listen Darius Stewart's back I don't let
him go away i had the Alpha moment it's
not going anywhere please you must come
now I suppose we better take him down
why I don't understand whose mind could
conceive of such a bizarre way to kill a
man called five sir dr. Anton Phibes
they have taken you from me my sweet
victoria but fear not for I shall
recover huge and they will suffer for
this outrage with their lives so with it
up Stewart he's now killed four men yeah
recently sure if you could go further
back that yes but why what possible
reason could he have well barovik the
papyrus but if he stole it means we have
the same goal same purpose no that's
impossible impossible impossible or not
we must all get back to civilization at
once yeah especially the young lady yes
I'm afraid you're right make your first
thing tomorrow morning I want you to
take dial out of here the rest and
follow later and your good self sir
there's one thing more I must do before
I leave here if you value your life oh
that's precisely why I'm staying
remarkable man I hardly know him but I
I've never met anyone more completely
dedicated that poor girl what she must
have gone through in the past few days
why the hell did he bring her out
curiously enough Waverly I think she was
the reason he came here in the first
place listen dialing I'm listen you're
my whole life everything please darling
please if nothing else you must know
that I'm beginning to wonder if I do
know anything about him I can't tell you
anymore I mean not that you'll
understand but the mountain must be the
key to it all sir possibly tried
possibly but it's all purely academic
you know we only got as far as an inner
chamber but they looked as though
there's a warren of tunnels on to that
mountain every move I make everything
this whole affair concerns our future
together but if it's anything like now
it's going to be pretty old it will I
promise you it's just that what what
were you going to sing all right say it
it's just that these next few hours are
of desperate importance to me this
expedition isn't really the reason we
came out here is it I mean there's
something else well we could search the
mountain and look for a method one needs
a warrant to make a search trout you
should know that by now yes I know sir
ben this are you charging into somebody
else's mountain this isn't Hyde Park you
know try Baker I want you to sleep on
the sarcophagus 10 tonight be sure
packed and ready to leave in the morning
with Diana
yeah Boise Shakespeare so sir thus
unconscious does make strange bedfellows
of us all it don't worry truck
you know what I'm dying for Wilson a
nice big warm wool glass of milk well
would you would you like me to go get
one sir no that's all I tried dear girl
and the machine
Oh
but at least we're short of one thing
hmm nothing must can happen on a night
like this
you
Victoria those who have tried to take
you from me so have they paid the
terrible price this water Placid now is
but a calm deception for beneath this
mountain when moon and water reconcile
the secret River of Life will be a
review a key where is the key
what's the matter where's Baker Baker
poor devil quiet he's taken the
sarcophagus but I still have the key
that storm last night fires must have
used that as cover used it he probably
summoned it all the Arabs are gone I
don't blame them i said i don't blame
them it's obvious thing to do i found a
truck abandoned not by the mount and the
sarcophagus oh well that's gone just
expected but what were their doing that
I mean who drove the truck up there in
the first place where's big he had a bad
night sir come along by the Vic I'm
still staying oh now look here sir I
have a responsibility I appreciate you
have a moral responsibility Waverly but
as far as I'm concerned no actual
jurisdiction I'm staying here but no
one's ever got a better a5 sure to our
certain knowledge he's already killed 15
men you can't hope to win I don't speak
of hope to meet route I mean to win hack
it with Baker gone you'll have to take
Diane out of here if you'll excuse me
gentlemen I'd like a word with her
before she leaves
darling to come I could put a suitcase
on the truck hello long time strike camp
yeah we ought to get these tents down to
CERN be on our way what about Baker
should we dispose of his body around his
body I think we should give his head a
decent burial
you
listen it's the Scottish Fusiliers my
god it makes you proud to be British
good here how marvelous house it's
probably some desert patrol where
Tonya's cloak covers a large section of
the globe you know well we must tell him
about the others I mean that way they'll
be safe yes let's try not but um I
mustn't leave you oh I'll go with you
mr. agate huh uh no no but you're
absolutely right
now platoon of that love all the put
fives in his place don't go anywhere
you
hackett he has nothing to say it where's
Diana my god fides must have her but you
haven't got a chance you chop you down I
can rest of them I would like the rest
of them now fighting for the fear of God
in you but not me now stay out of my way
really is being a truck for heavy hand
insane by the offensive it wasn't the
Miss Trowbridge in there Adam come on by
the back wait after him
five so we meet at last Beiderbecke
we're waiting as we all must wait play
of all games with me fives if ever a man
deserves to die as you you cannot
threaten the dead with death my friend
only with life eternal life so that's it
the key by key no I've searched for
years the temple of Ephesus the river of
life it's mine Phibes then you're pinned
of it will die for only the key can save
her now you lie the T controls the gates
nothing more the key controls the gates
and much more the life of your Diana and
you have only three minutes to use it
now save your guy Hanna
Diana
observe my sweet victoria that as the
sacred waters drain away the final
revelation is before us the dates to
eternity go vulnavia and if our victim
know the full measure of our love
amazing thing don't do that drop sure
let us turn it
what we really need sir is a rare you
have so little time Beiderbecke what
kind of fiend on a kind that wins my
friend it is a pity in a way we have so
much in common you funny yourself I
think not for years I have had one
terrible obsession to find the river of
life once used by the Pharaohs of Egypt
it lies beyond those gates a river that
gives new life again and again and again
why do you think I came here you have
all the life you eat no both eyes the
elixir that gave me you for a hundred
years is gone this file is file a
sustaining for many years to spend a
time and age but no long how long how
many years too long to remember to log
throw it all the way now I too have
searched right of it but not for myself
for my Victoria
I offer you the same goal the life of
your beloved but hurry when the bough
breaks my friend could be a trick why
should I trust you evolving that me the
ancient artisans who built these
chambers when those games are unlocked
the waters from Diana's poo will drain
out and she will be free safe don't be a
fool soon it will be too late for who
for us all especially Diana free second
brings her closer to a terrible death
can you pay that price beiderbecke patty
the devil take you Phibes step will take
me not for some considerable time but I
trust
now if I de Becque went through there
and he was running pretty fast well and
then now a minute fives must be out
first otherwise we would have yes I
think I think I've got it
don't worry sir we're gonna round all
right 52 finally fail they know he's one
daughter gumbo Maivia your work is done
join us on the other side nothing fine
55 I thank you let me come with you
birthday don't worry die it's not the
end of the world over the rainbow
the frame
you
Oh
I
you