finished it's finished nearly finished
it must be nearly finished rain upon
grain one by one and one day suddenly
there's a heap a little heap the
impossible heap it can be punished
anymore I'll go now to my kitchen ten
feet by ten feet by ten feet and wait
for himself whistle me nice dimensions
nice proportions I lead on the table and
look at the wall and wait for him to
whistle me
you
need to play old staunch are
can there be misery love the ER than
mine no Tyrus formally but now my father
my mother my dog oh I willing to believe
they've suffered as much as such
creatures can suffer what does that mean
they're suffering equals mine no does
now always absolute the bigger man is
the foolery is and the emptier clothed
now hello what dreams those forests
enough it's time it ended in the refuge
to and yet I hesitate I hesitate to to
end yes there it is it's time it ended
and yet I hesitate to to hand good I'm
tired I'd be better off in bad
you pollute the air get me ready i'm
going to bed let's just cut you up and
what hours well i can't begin your
imported about every five minutes so
it's things to do did you ever see my
eyes now did you never have the
curiosity why that is steeping to take
off my glasses and look at my eyes Flynn
battle it's no one of these days I'll
show them to you it seems they've gone
always what x is same as usual have you
looked yes well 0 it'll need to rain the
wall grain apart from that how do you
feel I don't complain you feel normal I
tell you I don't complain I feel a
little queer clothed yes have you not
had enough yes of what a dish this thing
I always had not you then there's no
reason for change to make and our
lifelong the same questions the same
answers get me ready don't get the sheet
oh yes I've given you nothing more to
ease then we'll do it I'll give you just
enough to keep you from dying you'll be
hungry all the time and I shan't I are
you gonna get this Esen no I give you
one biscuit Friday one man why do you
stay with me would you keep me there's
no one else is no where else but you're
leaving me all the same I'm trying you
don't love me know you loved me once
once I've made you suffer too much
haven't I it's not that I haven't made
you suffer too much yes I gave me a
fright forgive me
I said forgive me I heard you have you
bled less it's not time for my
painkiller know how are your eyes Val
are your legs bad did you move where are
you here come back where are you here
why don't you kill me I don't know the
combination of the ladder don't get to
bicycle wheels and I know more by
certain waves what if you Tom which our
boys are killing I never had a bicycle
thing is impossible and the way of still
boys suppose I wept to have one i
growled at your feet you told me to get
outta hell now there are non and your
rounds when you inspect my paupers
always on foot sometimes in horse yeah I
things to do in your kitchen yes outside
of here its death ideal we're getting
home beep out Akerson throw Jenna the
tap the old folks at home no decency
left guzzle guzzle that's all they think
of well I thought you were leaving me oh
not just yet no just yes repop Kipnis
path there's no more time you hear that
there's no more path you'll never get
any more path huy fong profound give me
biscuit a corset fornicator
oh yes stumps there are already stomps
I'm done with this is well is it spats
medium it's hard I can't tatlim Eddie's
put new shit on them they can't sit true
and I can't stand so it is every man his
speciality no phone calls don't we
laughs I don't feel like no right glove
yes Nature has forgotten us there's no
more nature no more nature you
exaggerate in the vicinity we breed we
change we lose our hair or teeth out
bloom her ideals and she hasn't
forgotten us but you say there's none no
one that ever lived at our thoughts so
crooked sweet we do or we can we
shouldn't you're a bit of all rise I do
smithereen this is slow work is it no
time for my painkiller now I leave you
right things to do in your kitchen yes
what I'd like to know I look at the
world the world what do you see a new
world many many naked parties I see my
life dying the idol died do I listen to
that where they can go just as well hear
your lies take a look at me and come
back and tell me what they think of you
are lying you shouldn't speak to me like
that forgive me i sent forgive me I
heard you
did your seeds come up now did you
scratch round them to see if there's
browser they haven't spares it perhaps
it's still too early if they were going
to sprout they would have sprouted
they'll never sprout this is not much
form but there's always the way at the
end of the day isn't it 12 hours it's
the end of the day like any other day
isn't it though looks like it what's
happening what's happening sunsun is
taking its course all right be off I
thought I told you to be of our train
ever since I was flipped we're getting
on
what is it my pêche time for love we're
here sleep Oh No kiss me we can't try
oh why this fuss day after day we've
lost v2 it when having yesterday ah
yesterday can you see me how did and you
what can you see me hardly so much the
better so much the better oh don't say
that our site was failed this can you
hear me yes and you yes our here in
hasn't failed of what our hearing no
have you anything else to say to me do
you remember know when we crashed our
tandem and lost our shacks if you seen
the old dear on the road to see Dad you
cold yes perished and you are you freeze
it do you want to go in yes Bengal
why don't you go in I don't know as he
changed your sawdust it isn't sawdust
can you not be a little accurist neg
your sand then it's not important it is
important twas sawdust once once now
it's sand from the shore now it's and he
fetches from the shore now it's sent
well as he changed yours no ah nor Liza
I won't have it you want a bit nope what
biscuit I kept you half three quarters
for you he know you don't you well I as
class keeping me awake talks after if I
could sleep I might make love I go to
the woods my eyes would see the sky of
the earth I'd run and wrong they
wouldn't catch me nature to something
dripping in my head I heard how did my
head kill you you a heart in his head
well muscled up at these things neg why
do you always laugh at them that's so
loud nothing is funnier than unhappiness
I grant you that oh yes yes it's the
most comical thing in the world and be
lost with off with a will in the
beginning is it's always the same thing
it yes it's like the funny story we've
heard too often we still find it funny
but we don't laugh anymore
have you anything else to say to me Bob
are you quite sure then I'll leave you
do you I want you biscuit I'll keep it
for you I thought you were going to
leave me I am going to leave you could
you give me a scratch before you go no
where is the back no rub yourself
against the rim oh it's laurie doubt
that that in the holo holo holo could
you not yesterday you stretch me there
ah yesterday good here that would you
like me distract you you crying again I
was trying ass little vain what was
lettuce it perhaps it's a little vain
what does that feat that'd be stuff it
but I tell you a story of the tailor and
know what Thor to cheer you are it's not
funny must always made you laugh first
time I thought you'd died it was on Lake
Como one April afternoon can you believe
it what this way once went out rowing on
Lake Como one April afternoon we got
engaged the day before engaged did you
worried such fits we capsized by rights
we shall have a round it was because I
felt happy it was not it was not it was
my story or nothing else happy don't you
laugh at it sailed
every time I tell it happy it is deep
deep and you can see down to the bottom
so white so clean let me tell it again
an Englishman needed a pair of striped
trousers in a hurry for the new year
festivities goes to his tailor who takes
his measurements that's a lot come back
in four days they'll have it ready good
four days later so sorry come back in a
week I've made a mess of a seat good
that's all right and beat seat could be
very ticklish a week later frightfully
sorry come back in ten days admit a hash
of the crotch God can't be helped a snub
crutches always a teaser two days later
dead Feliz ani come back in the Far my
tummy the balls of the fly but at a
pitch a spouse flies a stiff proposition
I've never told it was a totally story
worse and worse I will to make it
shorter the bluebells are blowing and he
bulks is the bundles god damn you to
hell sir no it's indecent that are
limits its sixties do you hear me six
days God made the one owed yes sir no
lesser the world and you're not bloody
little capable of making me a pair of
trousers in three months oh but if Sir
her My dear sir look at the world look
up IE trousers haha
hahahaha hey you could see down to the
bottom have you not finished will you
never finish will get better finish my
kingdom for a night man get away this
muck chuck it in the sea so white what
what's he getting about desert she has
no pulse what was she dribbling a boat
you told me to go away into the desert
damn busy buddy is that all know what as
we didn't understand your partner s they
both but alas screw down there it's time
enough my anger subsides I'd like to pee
well go and get the catheter far enough
give me my painkiller it's too soon
though soon on top of your tonic it
wouldn't act in the morning they brace
you up and then the evening they calm
you down and this is the other way
around that old doctor is dead naturally
it was an old but he's dead naturally
you ask me that take me four digit on
not too fast right round the world hug
the walls and back to the center again I
was right the Santa Rosa yes we need a
proper wheelchair big wheels bicycle
wheels are you hugging yes shall I what
do you lie to me there there stop old
well beyond is the other hand toss our
toes over here tickle you ham
you hear you here hollow bricks oh
that's Hollow that's enough back hand on
the round right this is that my players
yes that's your place am i right in the
center will measure it good morning
that's more or less there I'm already s
in the center they say so it says so
probably right now Center let's go and
get the 10 expressly roughly batheson
there I feel a little too far to the
left now I feel a little too far to the
rice I feel a little too far forward now
I feel little too far back don't stay
there give me the shivers if I could
kill him and I happy what's the weather
like as usual look at the earth looks
with it last no need it a glass deliver
the class going at the glass no need for
the glass
I back again with the glass I need the
stats boy have you shrunk I don't like
that don't like that fuck you get over
the steps I need the glass do you have
the glass oh I haven't a glass this is
deadly things are no even enough I get
it on purpose
I say a multitude and transports of joy
and that's what I call an egg the fire
yeah don't we laughs oh you don't all
right let's say 0 0 and 0 nothing stirs
all is yeah wait you're spoken to all is
all is Alice watch I'll just wash what
all is in a word that's what you want to
know just a moment corpse well content
look at the see the same look at the
ocean
seen anything like that what a sale a
thin smoke loiter sulk how we all knew
that let's make left the base yes no oh
god no girls does and I rise nothing on
the horizon what in God's name to go
beyond the horizon the waves how the
waves ways let and the sound 0 but it
should be sinking again down the Sun is
it not already there no then what is it
hey gray gray did I hear you say gray
light black from pole to pole you
exaggerate don't stay there you give me
the shivers
with his first day after day routine one
never knows last night I saw inside my
breast there was a big sore if SIA has
no it was living close ask what's
happening something is taking its course
close why say we're not beginning to to
mean something mean something you know I
mean something that's a good one I
wonder imagines a rational being came
back to earth wouldn't he be liable to
get ideas into his head if he observed
us long enough ah good now I see what it
is yes now I understand what they're
asked when that gone as far as that we
ourselves we ourselves at certain
moments the pink perhaps it won't always
be for nothing I have a flame a free are
the cities Samir's one this is a crab
lips humanity my start and they're all
over again catch them with another God
don't get the powder see this is all
full what a day my back again with the
x-axis oi let him have us
bastard did you get him looks like it
that's his land other Lane lying I mean
this is lying tell go Oh once this lying
one doesn't say lame Jewish your head
can't you if he was laying we'd be
bitched I'll they've let p I'm having it
that's the spirit that's the spinet this
cow from here the 2 verse out you can
make a raft and the current will carry
us away far away to other nom on this
God for this alone I'll embarking on get
working on the raft immediately tomorrow
I'll be gone forever well start straight
away the Sharks you think shacks I don't
know dad it will be wait it's not yet
time for my painkiller now wait how are
your eyes bad but you can see all I want
how your lives bad are you gonna walk I
come and go in my house one day you'll
be blind like me you'll be sitting there
a specking the void in the dark forever
like me one day you'll say Joseph I'm
tired us sit down and you go and sit
down then you'll say I'm hungry I'll get
up and get something to leave but you
won't get off and you won't get anything
to eat you look at the wall a while and
you'll say I close my eyes perhaps have
a little sleep after that I feel better
and you close them and when you open
them again there'll be no wall anymore
infinite emptiness will be all around
you all the resurrected dead of all the
ages wouldn't fill it and there you'll
be like a little bit of grit in the
middle of the
one day you'll know what it is you'll be
like me except that you won't have
anyone with you because you won't have
had pity on anyone because there won't
be anyone left our pity on it's not
certain and there's one thing you forget
ah I can't sit down well you know down
then what the hell oh you'll come to a
standstill simply stop and stand still
the way you are now one day you'll say
I'm tired i stop what is the attitude
matter so you all want me to leave you
naturally you don't leave you you can't
leave us then I shan't leave you why
don't you finish us I tell you the
combination of the ladder if you promise
to finish me I couldn't finish you it is
shan't finish me and leave your things
to do you remember when you came here
now too small you told me you remember
your father same answer if asked with
these questions millions of times I love
the old questions are the old questions
the old answers there's nothing like
them it was I it was a father to you yes
you were that to me my house our home
for you yeah this was that for me but
for me no farmer but fam mom I'll leave
you did you ever think of one thing
never but here we're down in a hole but
beyond Hills a patsy greenie flora
pomona carry who's perhaps you won't
need to go very far I can't go very far
I leave him is my dog ready relax alec
is his silky it's a kind of
pomeranian go get him relax a leg don't
care we're dealing on the dogs are here
he's why isn't he nearly I didn't II
nearly is he why there isn't he he
hasn't you forgotten the sex but he
isn't finished the sex goes on at the
end you havin piranhas ribbon what he
isn't finished though he tell you a
forest you finish the dog then you put
on his rhythm can you stand I don't know
try well wait well you sounded / where
where is he there is it gazing at me yes
as if he were asking me to take him for
a walk if you look or is a huge begging
me for a bone leave him like that
standing there imploring me believe you
have you had your visions bless his
mother pegs lies haha nice hell anyone's
might be on extinguish naturally its
extinguished if it's not on its
extinguished no I mean mother pig what
actually she's extinguished what's the
matter with you today I am taking my
course she buried Barris who would have
bet her you know me I'm know enough to
do without burying people you bury me no
I Shan bury you she was bunny once like
a flare of the field and a great one for
the men way to a Bonnie once it's a rare
thing not to have been Bonnie once go
get a gaff
do this do that and I do it we never
refuse why you're not able to sue no he
won't do it anymore you won't be able to
anymore ah the creatures are creatures
everything has to be explained to them
yeah she got stick it off did I move no
don't get the I've can before tie the
casters I all of them yesterday
yesterday whether that mean yesterday
that means that bloody awful day long
ago before this bloody awful day or use
the words you taught me they don't mean
anything anymore that teach me others I
let me be silent I once knew a madman
who thought the end of the world come he
was a painter and engraver I had a great
fondness for him I used to go and see
him in the asylum I take you by the hand
and dragged him to the window the Tarot
that rising corn I dare look the same
seriously all that lovely in us he
snatched you as hand to go back to his
corner appalled all he had seen was
ashes he alone had been spared forgotten
it appears the case is was not so so
unusual the mammoth it was done oh way
back way back you weren't in the land of
the living god be with today's I had a
great fondness for him she was a painter
and engraver yeah so many terrible
things no no there are not so many now
clove yes you don't think this is going
on long enough yes what pierced
australis thought so you enough then
there's a day like any other day as long
as it lasts I'll lifelong the same
analogies I can't leave here I know and
you can't follow me if you leave me
after I know but you simply whistle me
and if I don't come running it means
I've left here you won't come and kiss
me goodbye oh I shouldn't think so but
you might be nearly dead in her kitchen
the result will be the same it's but how
would I know if you were merely dead in
your kitchen well sooner or later I'd
start to stink you stink already the
whole place stinks at corpses how
universe I got a universe think of
something what an idea have an idea a
prize idea ah good page my legs
unbelievable soon we won't be able to
think anymore you won't be able to leave
me what are you doing having an idea ah
what a brain well wait
yes I got it I said dealer this is
perhaps not one of my bride days but
frankly whistle me I don't come the
alarm raised I'm gone it doesn't really
like that is it working the alarm is
working why wouldn't it be working well
because it's worth too much miss hard
you worked at all and because it's worth
two little or you go and see
scituate to that did you hear it babe
and mr. eric i prefer the middle there's
not time for my painkiller now I leave
you it's time for my story do you want
to listen to my story now that's my
father if he wants to listen to my story
sleep wakeham mm-hmm he doesn't want to
listen to your story i'll give him a
blonde poem he wants to show the plum
he'll get her sugar plum it's do you
believe in the rush to come mine was
always there
got on that song I've listed scoundrel
why did you and gender me or to know
what what didn't you know but it'll be
you you'll give me a sugar plum after
the audition you swear yeah on what my
armor to one one for me and one for one
silence man while I it's finished we're
finished nearly finish there be no more
spinach something's dripping in my head
ever since the fontanelles splash splash
always on the same spot perhaps ascitic
vein little artery enough of this it's
story time where was I the man came
crawling towards me on his belly kale
wonderfully pale and thin he seemed on
the point of not on that path I calmly
filled my pipe the museum this is with
let's say a vesture drew a few puffs or
what is it you once it was an
extraordinarily bitter day I remember 0
by the thermometer but considering it
was Christmas Eve there was nothing
extraordinary about this seasonable
weather for once in a way well what ill
wind blows you my way he raised his face
to me black with mingled dirt and tears
that you too
no no don't look at me don't look at me
he dropped his eyes and mumbled
something apologies I presume I'm a busy
man you know the final touches before
the festivities you know what it is come
on now what is the object of this
invasion it was a glorious bright day I
remember 50 by the helium honor but
already the Sun was sinking down into
the down among the dead nicely put there
come on now come on present your
petition and let me resume my labors
there's English for him oh well it was
then he took the plunge it's my little
on his hair little one that's bad my
little pony said as of the sex mattered
where did he come from he named the
whole a good half day on whores what are
you insinuating that the case still
habited no no not a soul except himself
and the child assuming he existed god I
enquired about the situation of Cove
beyond the Gulf not a sinner good and
you expect me to believe that you have
left her little one back there all alone
and alive into the bargain come now it
was a howling wild day I remember a
hundred by the anemometer the wind was
tearing up the dead pines and sweeping
them away that's a bit feeble down well
come on man speak up what is his you one
for me I have to put our boy Harley but
to make it short it finally transpired
the what he wanted from me was bred for
his brass bread but I have no bread it
doesn't agree with me
good then perhaps a little corn don't
your dooms corneas I have corn it's true
in my Grenier is but use your head if I
give you some corn a pound a pound and a
half you bring it back to your child and
you make him if he's still alive a nice
pot of porridge a nice pot and a half of
porridge full of nourishment dude the
colors come back and his little cheeks
perhaps and then I lost patience use
your head can't you use your head you're
on earth there's no cure for last it was
an exceedingly dry day I remember 0 by
the hygrometer ideal weather for my
lumbago but what in God's name do you
imagine that the earth will awaken
spring that the rivers and seas will run
with fish again but there's money in
heaven still for him to seals like you
gradually I'd cool down sufficiently at
least to ask him how long he had taken
on the way three whole days good and
well conditionally left the child deep
in sleep but deep in what sleep deep in
what sleep already let's make its shores
I finally offered to take him into my
service he had touched a chord and then
I imagined already that I wasn't much
longer for this world well here if
you're careful you might die a nice
natural death in peace and come from
well in the end he asked me what i
consent to take in the child as well if
he was still alive it was the moment I
was waiting for him would i consent to
take in the child I can see him still
down on his knees his hands flat on the
ground glaring at me with his mad eyes
in defiance of my wishes I sooner finish
with the story unless I bring in other
characters where would I find them where
would i look for them let us pray to
drop their sure blogs surat in the
kitchen trash are there straps and the
kids in this one you haven't
exterminated him earth you distort us he
can't get away now you'll finish it
later let us pray to God can you
sugarplum God first are you right off we
go and you our Father which is in
silence where are your manners off we go
huh what a half new sweet damn all and
you wait nothing doing dumb bastard he
doesn't exist yeah you sugarplum there
ain't no more sugar plums it's natural
after all I'm your father it's true his
Envy beer to be someone else but that's
no excuse Turkish did like for example
we're so longer exists we all know that
but there is nothing in this world I
love war and one day I'll ask you for
some be in return for a kindness and
you'll promise it to me I must live with
the times whom did you call when you
were a tiny boy and were frightened in
the dark your mother no be and we'd let
you cry and then we moved you out of
earshot so we could sleep in peace I was
asleep happy as a king and you woke me
up to have me listen to you it was
dispensable it didn't really need to
have me listen to you besides I didn't
listen to you I hope that they will come
when you really need to have me listen
to you need to hear my voice any vice
yes I hope I live till then to hear you
calling me like when you want a tiny boy
and were frightened in the dark and I
was your only hope I revels now are
ended the dogs gone is not a real dog
can't go he's not there laying down give
up to me dirty brute what are you doing
putting days in order and then a clear
everything away Oh Don I love order my
dream the world where all will be silent
and still in each thing its last place
under the last dust what in God's name
do you think you're doing I'm doing my
best to create a little order Travis
there elsewhere challenger feast please
tramp tramp I must Apple army boots your
slippers were hurting you I leave you
know what has that actually be here the
dialogue I've got on with my story I've
got on with it well ask me where I got
to oh by the way your story your story
well you've been telling yourself all
your days ah you mean my Chronicle
that's the one keep going can't you keep
going you've got on with it I hope oh
not very far not very far there are days
like that one isn't inspired nothing you
can do about it just wait for it to come
no forcing no forcing its shape
I've got on with it a little all the
same technique you know I say I've got
on with it a little all the same well I
never in spite of everything you were
able to get on with her oh not very far
you know not very far but nevertheless
better than nothing that's another
nothing is it possible I'll tell you how
it goes he comes crawling on his belly
who what who do you mean he who do I
mean here another ah him I wasn't sure
crawling on his belly whining for bread
for this brass he's offered a job as
Gardner before what is it so funny about
that a job as Gardner is that what
tickles you must be that wouldn't be the
bread but the brass the whole thing is
comical I grant you that what about
having a good before the two of us
together I couldn't go far against they
know Roy I continue then before
accepting with gratitude he asks if he
may have his little boy with him for age
Oh tiny he would have cloned the trees
ALDOT large jobs and he would have grown
up very likely keep going can't you keep
going that's all I stop there do you see
how it goes on our own earth will it not
soon by the end I've afraid it will
you'll make up another I don't know I
fear I've drained the prolong creative
effort if I could drag myself down to
the sea I'd make a pillow of sand to my
head and the tide would come there's no
more toys go and see is she dead
looks like nine doesn't look like what's
he doing he's crying then he living did
you ever have an instant of happiness
not to my knowledge bring me on to the
window I want to feel the light on my
face you remember in the beginning when
you took me for used to hold the chair
too high let me stipulate accept me out
a great fond rehab to overspread front
and then we got into the wailers there
already is it lives it isn't that I'm
asking you that nice yes the carton
isn't closed now what window is the
earth I nealis there's no light daddy
order
that's what i call lies feels like a ray
of sunshine no no it isn't the ray of
sunshine I feel on my faith no am I very
wise I'm asking you am a very wise not
more so than usual open the window what
for I want to hear the sea you wouldn't
hear even as you open the window no and
it's none for Twila opening us nah in
albinus have you opened this yes you say
you've opened it gasps well it must be
very calm I'm asking you is it very calm
yes it's because there are no more
navigators you have much conversational
of a certain do not feel well I'm cold
what month are we close the window we're
going bad
don't stay there you give me the shivers
father father go and see did he hear me
yes both times once only the first
summer the second he doesn't know must
have been the second you'll never know
is he still crying now the dead go fast
what's he doing sucking his biscuit life
goes on give me a road I'm freezing no
more hooks kiss me we do not kiss me
know on the forehead they won't kiss you
anywhere it could be a hand at least we
not give me a hand I won't touch it give
me the doubt no you're not one he dog no
no leave it that's right we don't kill
that rat until I that's right me to play
we're getting on you weep and weep for
nothing so it's not to laugh and little
by little you begin to grieve all those
I might have helped helped saved saved
the place was crawling with them use
your head can't you use your head your
honor there's no cure for lass get out
of here in love one another lick your
neighbor as yourself when I wasn't bread
they wanted it was crumpets out of my
sight and better pairing patties I'll
dad Oh does not even a real dog the end
is in the beginning and yet you go on
perhaps if you go on with my story and
didn't begin another that's a control
myself out on the floor digging my nails
into the cracks and drag myself forward
with my fingers it will be the end and
there I'll be wondering what kind of
brought it on a wondering what kind of
why it was so long coming there are be
in the old refuge alone against the
silence and thus tumors if I can hold my
peace and sit quiet it will be all over
with sound and motion and all over and
done with I'll call my father and I'd
have called my my son even twice or
three times in case they shouldn't have
heard me the first time or the second
I'll say to myself he'll come back and
then
and then he couldn't he's gone too far
and then all kinds of fantasies but I
being watched a rat steps breath held
and then then bable bable words like a
solitary child it turns himself in to
children 23 supposed to be together and
whisper together in the dark moment upon
my homeland packet and down at the
millet grains of that old Greek and our
lifelong your way for that amount up to
a life ah let's get it over what leader
gone are dead spirit only wish both down
for me if he dead invoice awesome l sort
of here it's dead and their ass he's got
away he can't go far hey he doesn't need
to go fer there's no time for my
painkiller yes at last give me quick
there's no more painkiller good no more
pain no more pain killer you'll never
get any more banker what's the digit
round box it was full yes but now
attempt what I do what I do what are you
doing oh you know over the art yeah
since it's calling to you the third saw
would you like to lozenge now
is he mm-hmm well it hasn't the Reuter
saying anymore no and have it end you
want it to end I want to say I can't
prevent you what did i do that stats
didn't see that stuff oh I'm sorry
sometimes I wonder if I'm in me right
mind passes over 9 the sluices before
she cannot be that's great what am I am
on the wrong size yeah until you wonder
it up in my right senses and it passes
off my name is intelligent as ever any
particular sec to your fancy or nearly
the whole thing okay the general effect
mr. Bowman's love mmm you know what it
is hmm I was never there so what is it I
was never a dang lucky for you absent
always it all happened without me I
don't know what's happened do you know
what's happened drove want me to look at
this mockup yes or no answer me first
what do you know what's happened well
well when what's happened use your head
can't you what has happened what for I
say does it matter I don't know an old
mother pegged asked if royal for a lamp
when you told her to get out to hell you
knew what was happening then no
you know what he died off mother pan of
darkness I had a nanny yes you had did
address no it's clear enough as it is
don't care it one thing I would never
understand why always a barrier you
explain that to me no perhaps is
compassion a kind of great compassion
but you won't find it is it you won't
find it easy toy little goings are very
tired you're not sitting on it don't
leave me there for the right in the
center microscope to find this ah no
time give me the dog but you must hit
behavior with the accent with the gaff
hit me with the gaff not with the dog
with the guy with the axe that's star
hey never put me in my coffin no more
cause it'll end with a bang of Darkness
me did anyone ever happy your name what
let me you're referring to an aside ape
you never hear with a sigh before I warm
me up for my last Sevilla grid I warn
you i'm going to look at this filth
since it's an order it's the last time
let's see nothing nothing good good
nothing
bad more complication not an under playa
chest slide a small boy small boy Godsey
take the calf no no potential procurator
if he exists you'll die they will come
here and if he doesn't don't believe me
you take home in vetting it's the end
clove we've come to the end I don't need
you anymore lucky for you leave it again
believe before you go say something
nothing to say few words soponda in my
heart yea hath yes yes with a rest in
the end the shadows the murmurs all the
trouble to end up wouldn't close he
never spoke to me then in the end before
he went without my having asked him he
spoke to me he said something from your
heart my has a few words from your heart
they said to me that's love yes yes not
dead now you see how articulate help
easy it is they said to me that's
friendship yes yes no question you found
it they said to me here's the place stop
raise your head look at all that beauty
that order they said to be cool now
you're not a brute beasts think upon
these things and you'll see how all
becomes clear and simply they said to be
what scant attention at all is dying of
their wounds enough I say to myself
sometimes clovi must learn to suffer
better than that if you want them to
weary of punishing you one day I say to
myself sometimes claw he must be there
better than that if you want them to let
you go one day but I feel too old and
too far to form new habits good it'll
never end I'll never go
you one day suddenly it ends changes I
don't understand the toys or it's me I
don't understand that either I asked the
words that remain sleeping waking
morning evening they have nothing to say
we open the door of the cell and go I am
so bad i only see my feet if i open my
eyes and between my legs a little trail
of black dust i say to myself that the
earth is extinguished though I never saw
in it it's easy go when they fall I weep
for happiness cool nothing true this is
what we call naked an axis I'm obliged
to you low for your services paden it is
IM obliged to you it's we are obliged to
each other one thing more a last favor
cover me with the she's no good need to
play old end game last of old playing
lose and have done with losing let me
see yes
good discount take it easy and now raise
hat peace to our asses I'm for Anya
deals wipe
and put on again we're coming few more
squirms I dad Nicole a little poetry you
prayed you cried for nice it comes it
falls now crying darkness you cried for
nice it falls now cry in darkness nicely
put that and now moments for nothing now
as always time was never and time is
over reckoning clothes and story ended
if he could have child with him it was
the moment I was waiting for you don't
want to abandon him you want him to
bloom while your withering we did a
solace your last million last moments he
doesn't realize all he knows his hunger
and cold and death to crown it over to
you you ought to know what the artist
like now it is oh I put in before his
responsibilities well there we are there
I am that's enough
yes truly good so father good we're
coming and to end up with discard with
my compliments glove no yeah since
that's the way we're playing let's play
it that way and speak no more about it
speak no more old sponsor you remain
you