[Music]
Captain's Log space seems to go on and
on forever like your favorite TV show
and never got cancelled
not at all forcing you to make your own
half-assed episode after a thousand
light-years i'm about to complete my
15-year mission
this is the USB Aldridge buzz with a
fuel delivery for BB our base over your
coming in hot
abort mission / don't tell me and fly
this vessel over open the beer bade zor
pal
we have liftoff it is
[Music]
here's to another successful mission you
doing
[Music]
I hit that I have will fold that's not
on every box toe
oh it looks like alpha braids needs
another fuel delivery room
we're out of fuel Oh your guy what we do
what can we do not help more here and
introduce my earth in beer old fart ram
light extra-dark the first in my mind of
hostile and flavors all fortran needs
you tried the old for tram light
extra-dark jingle talented lazy slob
talking to you that writes the winning
jingle will take home lifetime supply of
all fortran latex dark spaces
dream-come-true stir once to trial for
translate extra-dark just walk one
are you thinking what I'm thinking
yeah it does with chicks their way hat
yeah nevermind breakfast and taking my
car and foghat broke up right
ok Nixon it's your old pal big and how
did you get my private deadfall number
it's classified
I wanted while playing Russian roulette
with President Putin so um what are you
walk
well there's this contest is giving away
a lifetime supply of free beer
all you have to do is write their
wedding cheap so you called me the
President on my birth to help your
write-up bear jungle go
I called you the president of Earth to
help me Rick that contest so that i
could win that free be all that sounds
interesting
I like a good rigging we could start
with a few and krimon aiding pictures of
the contact job yeah I'm anonymous call
to have ya wiretap here a death threat
there and the next thing you know next
time swimming and free beer
no I clearly said I'm getting that
freebie
haha i got a tricky day only looks out
for one person me are well fry bender I
was appreciated when you settle for me
and you know what this Jango could be my
own personal boost license I always
dreamed of winning a lifetime supply
something and what with my ability to
compute man arrives and your ability to
exist for issuing for that beer baby and
all I'm does exist in the 20th century
back
be
[Music]
South your harmony and about beer no
less
Admiral vendor I seek got a new mission
there will be no one to stop us this
time guys are still in your drinking
here
no we just ran out
yeah I can't believe you to let me load
the ship all by myself
you're right was told I'm sorry okay but
that doesn't change the fact that we
were supposed to leave two hours ago
and and how do you think this is gonna
take this who is everyone
I'm so glad you haven't left yet o Lord
before you drop that credit drives I
need you to deliver this old science
experiment / topic nine just sold for
twice as value on ebay we really want
those cute two rafts in the cargo hold
next to what looks like a leaky handmade
beryllium doomsday / no no it's too much
cheaper einsteinium 119 what about your
appt oh don't worry if they get too
close to the dorm state of ice just use
the spray bottle to give the merchant
correction it's filled with acid cool
oh and watch out for space pirates they
do love atomic atomizing apparatus
now off you go
come on don't make me do all the work
yeah right don't make her do all the
work you get Union get what youre
talking back
you need me stronger for not that I
enjoy yelling at you guys I really care
about you shut up baby i know it you're
bad influence on front oh you know
you'll do anything you tell him aren't
true
yesterday I told him to drop dead and
three would do it you're lucky suicide
boosts our expense
yeah that's why I bought him a gift card
haha bring any be free
last time
[Music]
not again
ok
[Music]
you did it again
Harry's sweet Condor of Gondor this
doomsday device of Teddy the green snake
or took implant haha
well obviously you don't seem too
concerned
well you know what they could do a whole
lot better with your sign one of these
it's an updated waiver absolving Planet
Express for gross negligence in the
likely event of you dying or
transporting this bomb
hey it may God sign one of those we
deliver that Brown of the Peace
celebration on sphere I now listen to
phone that was just mislabeled
nuclear-powered disco ball like
yourselves that Brandon came in wind it
up it wasn't the only thing he were I
don't know what to imply oh well let me
clear things up for you by not the only
thing I met you at x 1mm remember just
because two people were accidentally
locked alone in a sec swinging torium
for five hours and had to disrupt
because of a temperature malfunction
doesn't mean they waited functioning
harvest yeah i mean
whoa
oh what a beautiful day
just smell that fresh air
[Applause]
[Music]
Admiral better never kicked me for
insubordination you know a body
oh that reminds me that hellebore would
recommend a drink another beer to avoid
a hangover I've had enough of these
inebriation game games beers now gang
here is life
did you at least secure the cargo
yeah yeah that the professor's doomsday
device and seal the drafts in an
airtight container so stupid replicating
directly under the carpet
why am I not surprised you don't
normally let us handle the dangerous
cargo damn dressing sharp who pretty
shot
you think they would have made that
distinction by now in this new
regulations state that shouldn't be a
duplicate signal oh I was everyone doing
on this lovely day and whatnot doing
great dr. Z and my viewers for the
Hermes was the family
oh come on give me some claw even agree
i would recognize the for a designation
meaning it's a tricky to get report with
rudimentary fingerprints DNA and school
profiles in the addendum well
wow I just don't know what's going on
down there at the central bureaucracy
I mean everyone
What's Wrong professor I just remembered
I forgot replace that damaged owner
thruster on that rickety boo state of I
cytosol probably hydroponics lactation
there's nothing about their sentence I
didn't lie you will come to control
oh it's really not the problem is i got
to decide updated no-fault death waiver
Cummings if that piece of junk i built
explodes it'll destroy the merest solar
system and more importantly by am
actively berating understood professor I
will take care of this perilous mission
personally yes yes
seubert get that bomb back here
Wow an honor haha i really hate that
crab God's beer looking for dad's beer i
gotta find charge beer from my row five
that's me baby
[Music]
you're dr. Z on the vidphone initiate
boy broke protocol
oh yeah
post a photo with the Doomsday Device my
friends from an insight into my daily
routine
oh any cellphone Janek don't forgive
years ago music ensemble of the homeless
would you just please we stupid
somewhere else your mind if I do
we've got a beard regal to tingle yeah
Leela we're on a mission from sigh don't
judge me
you're unbelievable all the word can
weigh and their captors Sean you hey
well I think she's the best you will
never torture trash K the best part of
drinking and be it sold for trend like
it's through door when I want a coffee
so bad you know that makes me think of
buddy
it was good the way you held that thank
you just get out i can do to you
stupid selfie gave our position away
relax are probably just my adoring fans
conventional children morning sands
we're bold
rolling sir
well well well
Brannigan here captain Brannigan that
zapper I'm sure you're all upset as
millions of others were that I wasn't
included in this abomination fan film
unfortunately I was preoccupied with a
dupe emergency an alien planet sex
machine broke down and I had to fill in
if you know what I mean sexually
needless to say they won't be needing
that pathetic machine again you're
welcome in Palace 6.9 so as you can see
there was a legitimate reason I wasn't
included had nothing to do with Lila's
restraining order
you saw the episode you experience the
amazing disappointment that house
cliffhanger will the crew of the Planet
Express ship survived the looming
spaceback will Leela save her precious
miniature drives what did fries see in
that Dethklok what's the deal with that
tentacle thing but Lambie ever find
perfect color for her Donuts will the
professor save his impeccable ebay
rating will joy burger retrieved the
Doomsday Device these and many other
questions will be answered
never no one can plan dining area his
productions got no talent no rights no
money
[Music]
sponsored by dammit i told you i don't
care what the walks think like that too
busy
[Music]
what sweetheart my schedule just opened
up
I love you borrow our
Dethklok when you need to know when
you're gonna go
[Music]