you
[Music]
hi your bum must hurt my what your bum
you know from when you fell from heaven
did you actually just say oh that's so
sweet really wow can I buy you a drink
no let me buy you a drink okay I'll have
a pint of landlords colostomy bag oh I
love a man who smells of beer that's
amazing you're my dream girl no don't
kiss me like that like this I like you a
lot but if you want me to come home with
you you're going to need a pretty good
reason so yeah that's my video
collection wow I've never seen so many
box sets can I be honest with you it's
not essential I didn't bring you here to
look at videos I wanted to kiss you
again oh you sweet innocent boy
oh I want you to do what take me where I
want you to this is what
don't know much about woman are you
supposed to pose that was just a dream
nice oh and that's the door mum hello
Giles I was ringing the bell for ages
what were you doing I was dreaming about
a girl oh when are you going to meet a
real girl it's time for you to get ahead
and get on with life and tidy up your
room and mums um not again
[Music]
that was a dream too I don't even have a
mother no
this come is mr. headlock please Giles
just call me sir but what are you do you
I thought I'd give a lift to my favorite
junior designer Monica for legal reasons
I can't talk about her Giles I saw what
you did with the budget range nice what
would you say if I made you senior
junior designer I'd say I'm dreaming
you're not dreaming next year's range
and the next yours so this is a
promotion more of a side motion will i
get paid more you'll get a parking space
I don't have a car you can use the
executive toilets hmm i use them anyway
Giles I seem to be encountering some
resistance here the thing is mr. hit
luck just sir this is my dream so I can
call you what I want is that ok dickface
hmm now get out of my flat dickface you
stink of moral corruption I stink and I
hope your wife finds out about all those
girls you're chasing after my wife is
dead this isn't a dream is it I was
going to buy you lunch no no no
Oh
so I followed him outside smashed in the
window of his car and peed all over the
front seat that's when you walk up no
that's when I was sure I wasn't dreaming
Giles one of these days you're gonna get
yourself into real trouble real trouble
is there an echo in here just me
repeating myself maybe we've had enough
to drink drink or let snack these and
get tequila I've just lost my job oh
yeah what you're gonna do ah I've always
wanted to learn to play the guitar what
about finding work I don't know I've
become disillusioned with the whole
thing Harry have you ever heard of
Plato's cave the nightclub it's this
idea that we're all sitting in a cave
staring at the shadows on a wall and all
we have to do is turn around turn around
lad exactly nope Giles turn it's worth
it it's her I'm gonna shut her up that's
the girl of my dreams got dibs but but I
dreamt of her last night Giles last
night I dreamt I was a giant lizard
walking to the streets of London people
running screaming from me nobody would
let me in all I wanted was a hook
my point is just 23 Harry you're right I
wouldn't have even seen her if you
hadn't brought me here to cheer me up
she's yours made nice one by M so what's
your sign no entry fancy a drink no you
look like you could do with the long
stiff one you call the bouncer to kick
you out let's beach mm so how did it go
ah she's not really my type can I talk
to her go on but she's beautiful I don't
think I'd go there on Mon not coming
with you could talk to a friend what
friend you want me to jump on the
grenade hmm let's do it
lasers I wasn't talking to you I was
talking to you ignore him gema gema
you're beautiful that's just the drink
talking at least you're talking so
your bum must hurt my wart your bum you
know from when you fell from heaven did
you actually just say that's disgusting
wait up can I buy you a drink no let me
buy you a drink really wow I'll have a
pint of landlords colostomy bag I was
joking go away sure shoot but you're my
dream girl and no it's not a line I
dreamt of you last night me yeah it was
you you're beautiful you still are
what's your name Stephanie and I'm Giles
have you got a condom for me looks like
my one's ready to go Harry hello Harry
not a good time by Jordan uh sorry about
that it's ok where will your just about
to leave look miles Giles you're a sweet
boy but I'm sure you have to go home to
mommy and daddy uh no my parents are
killed by pirates what they were on a
cruise near Somalia don't don't don't
don't don't don't why don't don't don't
don't don't don't don't don't don't I'm
sorry for your loss but I think I should
leave what about us Giles you're a bit
weird weird in a good way hmm there is
no good way but you're the girl of my
dreams I'm sorry you're not the man of
mine I see I'm glad you're being mature
about this goodbye
yeah bye no not goodbye stephanie wait
I'm not gonna let you go help oi
and stay out and don't forget about our
two for one special on Mondays I walked
home alone that night you thinking of
all the things I should have said and
the things I shouldn't do that you have
a grin of my dreams a grin of my dreams
one regret led to another and i remember
the last time I'd spoken to my parents
okay bye they've given me that guitar
almost as if they'd known they would be
killed by Somalian pirates in the Indian
Ocean learning to play it wouldn't bring
them back but it would make me feel less
learning that night became the next day
and the next week became the week after
[Music]
it was only when I walked past a certain
coffee shop on a certain day and
recognized a certain person that I
realized there was more to life just
sitting in my bedroom playing with
myself my guitar Gemma um hello it's me
Giles ok Giles don't you remember you
had sex of my friend Harry Oh Giles hi
um I'd like you to meet my mother hello
oh hi I was just going darling i hope
you make the right decision about that
thing i will mum good mmm bye bye so um
what's happening you know your friend
never called me back Harry yeah he's um
sorry about him what do you want I
thought we could talk you know about
life politics sport Stephanie Oh
Stephanie what a surprise a boy wants to
talk about Stephanie it's not like that
I don't just want to sleep with her
rarely ok yeah I mean I'd love to sleep
with her cause there would be a for
awesome but I saw her in a dream so so I
want to love and protect her and all
that stuff but I can't even speak to her
what if she's not who you think she is
well she must be a good person if she
has a friend like you hmm we'll need to
get you a haircut and do something about
your clothes you'll help me you're not
the only romantic you know
fashion fashion fashion fashion fashion
fashion Oh fashion nope sorry just not
you passion passion
yuck that's not anyone
[Music]
how about this now we just need to get
you a job but not look start here in the
salon and I hear the hiring of the
estate agent I don't know anything about
safe houses just be honest hi so what
makes you want to be an estate agent I'm
trying to impress a beautiful girl so
money sex cult congratulations you've
got the job Wow was it my honesty it was
the tie well here's where the magic
happens nice are you a magician figure
of speech I knew that I was making fun
of you Oh Gemma yes um I've kind of done
something silly like falling in love
Britain you a song Oh interesting I'll
get my guitar you didn't tell me you
were a musician I'm not really but I'd
like to be
[Music]
star that's what you are too kind star I
like I
right but a light shining into the night
making
beautify strongly true how bad I'm
always friends with you know I'm never
late Wow would kill me to see Brown see
you from
[Music]
but of this hole
way
my day sorry that was embarrassing I'll
put this thing away no no one's ever
written me a song before I mean I'm
gonna spend more time obviously when I
do one for Stephanie Stephanie yeah
great whoo Gemma I want to thank you
you've given me the clothes the hair cut
the confidence and all you need now is
your dream girl yeah Wow completing each
other's sentences it's like we've been
friends for years yeah Giles if you want
to get Stephanie you're going to have to
join a gym am I out of shape trust me as
a friend I'll get my sports stuff
[Music]
Stephanie hey Stephanie hi oh it's you
what a coincidence I hope you're not
stalking me I'm working out mmm really
I've just been doing some bench squats
unit you know with the weights you yeah
I will cut all the time check this
[Music]
impressed yeah really no oh I'm more of
a cardio guy I hit the treadmills on my
lunch breaks you know I work over at
Wolf Pack you work at Wolf Pack you've
heard of them I handle their
conveyancing you're a lawyer junior
assistant legal secretary dreamgirls
have to work too you know at least until
they find their dream guy well you had
me thrown out of the bar so that rules
me out but you didn't tell me you were
in a state agent what difference does it
make Giles at the end of the day us
girls want security and I thought you
was something flaky like a graphic
designer wait you remember my name of
course I do Wow your parents died oh
yeah my parents died too what Oh in a
car accident in my first year of
university oh geez I'm sorry I blocked
it out but there was something about
your story Oh Stephanie I want to cheer
you up it's the least I could do let me
take you for a drink on Friday 630 the
same bar see you then bye bye wait
you're actually gonna go for a drink
with me yes bye babe
by Stephanie by Giles Wow hmm hmm you've
changed Giles huh have I maybe it's the
time oh that's it it's the tie you
shouldn't have I didn't it's for my date
you nervous no don't be there's plenty
of girls like her out there oh she's
already my god you'll never find another
girl like that Gemma's friend remember
Gemma oh yeah the one who keeps trying
to call me doesn't realize I'm a player
always on the go girls dripping off my
arms the ladies you get what I'm saying
here Giles yes so what are you gonna do
tonight I'll probably have a couple more
beers than head home with a takeaway why
don't you call Gemma tiegan release
Giles tag and release but she's really
nice you call her then I'm just not
ready to settle down and start family
who said anything about starting a
family boy you know what lasses alike
not really well just take care of
yourself with this one
goodbye hurry
hi hi Giles that wasn't that creep Harry
was it Harry no ah that's good he rarely
let my friend down well maybe I should
get us some drinks and after that what
you have planned well well I thought we
could have more drinks yes and go on go
back to my place to do what um look at
my video collection Giles i am not going
to sleep with you oh no no I wasn't
thinking about sex sex what's your
five-year plan Giles five-year plan yeah
I'm thinking and um I don't know well
not very impressed you know hang on this
feels a bit like a job interview what's
your five-year plan oh I like that
assertiveness it's not too much is it I
just want to hear your opinions ok what
would you like them to be Oh child's I
need a man uh I am a mad man I'm just a
bit nervous you know you hear it feels
like I'm still dreaming like we're in
Plato's cave Giles I came here to have
an honest and frank discussion about the
possibility of our future together and
hears you talking about night clubs
you're a sweet boy goodbye stephanie
wait I need your professional opinion
you need professional help the insurance
monies come through for my parents
remember I told you about them and um I
was money yeah lots of it whoa so
interesting yeah um yeah Oh Charles can
I get you a drink yeah okay and what
about later on can we check out your
Oh video collection um yeah I've got
some old sci-fi stuff you might like oh
let's get that drink first beer please
oh I love a man who smells of beer hmmmm
smooth like a smoothie wow it's such a
good night me too good to be honest I
was really trying to impress you what
did you think of the meal the kebab yeah
it's my favorite take away nice well
it's too late for a video oh I'll get a
taxi then okay goodbye oh okay bye um
hey um yes um I get a room what ignore
him he's not talking to us I'm talking
to you I can't block it out I'm sorry
Giles oh look at him it's some kind of
disgusting drunk disgusting drunk hey
it's Harry
revolting I'm glad you didn't call Joe
she's too old for you I'm sorry sorry
huh you should be ashamed of yourself
hmm hurry are you okay Giles leave him
let's go I I can't he's my best friend
just Tim or me him oh ouch ah he needs
help Stephanie sorry I hope you're not
planning on sharing any insurance money
with him huh what insurance your money
yes from Giles as parents I hope you
don't see a penny of that don't deserve
oh they haven't found the bodies
nobody's no money yeah that's the policy
you lied to me I was gonna tell you
after sex oh you losers hmm what do you
think she meant by losers Oh lad I just
found 50p in my vomit sweet
[Music]
hello hello hmm probably some religious
cult
ah coming coming coming oh hey Gemma
come in hi Giles you heard yes you
messed things up properly with Stephanie
oh I lied to her I know but if it's true
love you must go back she called me a
loser you're not a loser Giles thanks
Gemma yeah wonderful but you need to get
Stephanie back and I know just how to do
it okay I'm all ears open mic night at
the bar bring your guitar I'll bring
Stephanie Oh she'll be swept off her
feet amazed at the song you writer oh I
don't know in front of all those people
sounds a bit dangerous have you got a
better idea I'd rather go to Somalia and
confront the Pirates who killed my
parents wait that's not a bad idea no no
Giles they'll give me the proof I need
no to get the insurance money better
start packing okay thanks for coming
around bye bye bye bye
[Music]
hey see you come back i stoled they
might be pirates here are you a pirate
excuse me come back I'm not going to
hurt you I just want information I'm
starting to think this isn't a good idea
I know you're out there and I'm not
scared of you at all you hear me you
don't scare me one bit what are you
gonna do ah hmm can I help you yes I'm
looking for my parents they were
kidnapped and killed so you want revenge
at first yeah but now I just want their
remains our claims department San jun 17
that way Thanks maybe you and me aren't
so different yuck wait don't leave me
here please I don't know my way around
the desert
oh hello claims department mr. and mrs.
peacock please no please check again no
we have no record of them one more time
mr. peacock I don't know what you know
about modern piracy but we are
meticulous in our record keeping what
happened to my parents then if you ask
me I would say go back to the place they
were last seen mauritius were they on
holiday there yeah but now I wonder hmm
wait how do I know I can trust you
you're still alive aren't you hmm yeah
there's that okay bye bye bye oh no
money for a plane ticket I made a raft
thirsty tired sunburned and rarely itchy
I was drilled the Indian Ocean cat thing
hey buddy buddy huh yeah you dry land
Wow is this Mauritius yeah now move you
blocking the view oh sorry this here is
a private holiday camp oh can I get a
beer no alcohol allowed whoa I thought
you said it was a holiday camp it is
that it sounds like some kind of colors
church the Church of mental cult
whatever hey I'm actually looking for
mother all looking for something oh I
found it with the Church of mental you
betcha must be nice hell yeah how do you
join easy you give Reverend mantle all
your money oh no it's called freedom
away my old life goodbye now I sing in
the choir noni nani no evil I know
ah
[Music]
where'd you learn to drive dickface what
did you say um where did you learn to
drive quick pace thank you need a ride
yeah yeah nice one Thanks
so when are you headed the police rally
there's a religious cult out there a
cult you say wow yeah lunatics but I
think they might have killed my parents
whoa that's a wild allegation it's just
a theory mind if I put on some music
this music your mental name's Chris
mental okay bye where is that how do you
know my name you look just like your dad
so you knew my parents oh yeah but I
didn't hurt them Giles strange but I
believe you can you take me to their
final resting place hell you want to go
to the cemetery yeah if it's not too
much bother I I want to see this thing
through you know Giles you're a good son
no I'm a dick I am a dick I tell my
congregation give me all your money but
what I need is love but it must be nice
leading a cult yeah better than working
in an office yeah I can imagine want to
join nope I have to try it's my job come
on let's go to the cemetery that'll be
fun well here we are what's that noise
just ghosts come on your parents are
over here no markings no but you said
these were their graves they will be not
now hey whoa
my parents they're probably playing
bingo with the pool right now you mean
they're alive what they're not dere dun
dun dun dunna shoot left the car stereo
on let's go
[Music]
hello
what do you want who are you it's me
Giles Giles who Charles peacock my son
oh I missed you mum oh I I thought you
were dead I'm sorry Giles sorry I'm
sorry but why did you do it come into
the house Giles no I demand an
explanation come inside you stepping all
over my petunias oh sorry mum Giles say
something you two are the worst parents
ever Giles please don't say anything how
could you let me think you were dead I
mean you sent me that letter and
everything saying you've been killed son
we signed that letter surely that was a
tipple come on oh I don't know I was so
stricken by dream hmm since joining the
mentalists we are dead to the world but
in other ways we're more alive than ever
yes spiritually and financially we're
dead for taxation purposes so we keep
some of chris mentals assets I'm not
angry that you've joined a cult I'm just
disappointed oh ouch what made you come
here anyway after all this time I was
looking for your body's so so sweet um
yeah well I needed them for the
insurance money yes I see well I met a
girl and I thought I should be
financially independent you know so you
came over here for selfish reasons well
when you put it like that yeah I'll go
by Giles wait Giles please wait if you
go to the souvenir shop tell them you
with the mentalists you'll get ten
percent off oh thanks okay bye
so what's for dinner monkey we got
monkey last night you cook then no no
monkeys fine mum dad I'm leaving oh
you're still here yeah and I want to
apologize Giles we're the ones who are
sorry oh my boy come with me where to my
man room I've got something there for
you wait there give this ring to that
girl of yours well tell her it belonged
to your great grandmother oh did it no I
found it in the drawer but listen girls
love that stuff um ok thanks how about a
non-alcoholic whiskey thanks but I need
to go to the travel agent to arrange my
flight tell them you with the mentalists
you'll get ten percent off
um okay bye hmm Giles what this is how
you say goodbye Oh take climb what a
lovely boy yes what's for dinner piss
off
[Music]
so did you get the insurance money no
Giles you've got to pick yourself up and
get ready for the open mic night tonight
yeah why not I mean I've got nothing to
lose do it Wow oh sorry so excited I'm
excited too you always inspire me I do
yeah hang on its way down after that
something for you what could it be ah
it's just some old ring I've never been
given a ring before oh it's beautiful
can I wear it now yeah oh this is so
exciting oh it's a bit of a tight
squeeze no really it'll go on people go
on then what do you think beautiful
really oh thank you so much okay I think
a minute zone nicest thing anybody's
ever given me I need to work on my song
Thanks goodbye Jess by Creek did it
don't-don't-don't didn't don't intend
and don't it on didn't did you do don't
duh hey I thought that was you Harry how
are you ah good nice surprise you here
to support me I'm just here having quiet
drink you okay man just done a few too
many that's all okay so what's the
competition like then take a look man
really good I I'm embarrassed ah what's
the worst that can happen lad you could
fall over everyone laughs at you so what
a nice finished I'm on next aw go on lad
knock them dead oh you don't stand a
chance this song is called dream girl
boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
boom boom
so you just the other day wondered what
the world say I told you I met you
before for said it's you I adore I never
stopped to wonder why you're my dream
girl dream girl dream girl dream
you go Dre
thank you again diggy diggy diggy diggy
dong dong diggy diggy dong ding dong
ding dong dong dong dong dong oh here
you are I've been looking all over for
you Giles that was amazing oh thanks so
did you bring Stephanie oh yes Oh
brilliant I'll get her a drink do you
want something I'm gonna go bye okay bye
I'll have a pint of the Stephanie hey oh
hello Charles so so what did you think
of my song-song I just sang a song over
there oh I was in the toilet the whole
time it was a massive poo oh I wanted to
impress you I'm not 15 Giles I know I'm
sorry I just thought that you and me you
know where's Gemma um she left shoot she
was acting really strangely back how she
was looking at me like this Oh like this
oh yeah that's it she okay you really
don't understand women do you oh she's
sick she's in love with you you moron
what have I done Stephanie I I'd better
go and see if she's okay oh wait yeah
I've been thinking and and I think I
like you now because your friend likes
me yes oh jeez you're honest honesty
integrity money as a woman these are the
things I admire but I don't have money
you have ambition you're chasing after
me remember no no this doesn't feel
right you were supposed to like my song
and
Giles this is the real world what about
Gemma I I understand if you choose her I
can't do that no you can you can run
after her and say you love her as a
friend but but but you're my dream girl
oh no matter what I think we both need
some time to think about this yeah okay
I'm done me too that night we finally
made love how'd are you bastard oh but
it was a bittersweet triumph we both
lost our parents mine to a cult and hers
to an accident and now we were losing a
friend that we had made our choice Giles
each other stop talking to yourself was
I sorry just shocked me oh oh oh that's
better
[Music]
Oh
ok I need to pee Oh
[Music]
yep love was everywhere even at work hi
oh it's the estate agent so you're still
interested in the house yes it's
beautiful well I'm required to warn you
that it's next door to a drug
rehabilitation center oh that's handy I
can get my methadone there it's also
next door to a tire factory I love the
smell of burning rubber mmm and if you
ask me it's on for twenty thousand more
than it's worth Oh we'll pay forty
thousand more 50 60 no that's not how it
works eighty thousand okay I'll call the
seller ninety a hundred baby this is so
romantic let's do it in the car while
I'm in the shower okay my dream girl
hello Giles I want you I want you to
wait to stop seeing harry harry but he's
my best friend Giles he's holding you
back I don't understand hmm he's
immature irresponsible drinks too much
and says stupid jokes all the time what
about his bad qualities trials I'm sorry
you can't just ask me to stop seeing my
friend okay look at my phone I've seen
it just look at the last message mmm
messages let's have sex from Harry oh my
god I can't believe Harry left out the
apostrophe Giles go and talk to him now
am I understood okay I'll go and put
some clothes on he's my friend Giles lad
hurry tell me it isn't true what is
just tell me it's not true it's not true
Jesus is embarrassing about you and
Stephanie all that oh I don't know I
don't know what you're talking about
sounds like you do let me jog your
memory you what yeah 00 child's what was
that yeah yeah you like that there's
more where that came from I don't like
that why would I like that Giles you
texted my girlfriend oh is that what
you're on about so you did know I don't
even know which stephanie you were
talking about really Giles I would never
text your girlfriend why would I even
have a phone number I can't believe a
doubted you woman a war hey Giles yeah
why don't you get us a round of drinks
for medicinal purposes yeah okay oh
you'll have to pay for them I'm a bit
short ok no probs what are we having two
beers ok oh and get something for
yourself man woman woman man Giles yeah
could I ask you something you want fuck
ya tou Xiang same old Harry hi I'm just
upset that someone texted your
girlfriend that they want to have sex
what what did you say oh no you didn't
tell me what was in the message
no didn't did I I'm sorry Giles I could
explain everything no I don't think so
let's just have a drink and talk like
all times okay open your eyes come in
come in Oh Charles how did you for this
my bonus from work I'm going to give you
a little more bonus oh oh oh
oh oh oh Stephanie oh wow Oh dad hello
son nice to meet you hope you don't mind
they told me at your work you'd moved
here and well the door was open no I'm
glad to see me too son I'm afraid I'm
here for that ring Oh a ring turns out
it's diamond date the most valuable
substance on earth oh if I don't give it
back what will happen I'll be
excommunicated from the church of mental
oh no yes it turns out that ring was
more valuable than I realized Oh
valuable so just give it back I can't
why not oh it's keeping it for me uh
yeah oh you were going to propose what
um yeah yeah I've ruined the surprise oh
no you sure dad what are you gonna do
though about the church Oh your mother
and I'll have to go into hiding oh that
sounds terrible no big deal you sure yes
but they'll probably try and kill us so
I better get going oh okay um well it
was good seeing you dad it was really
good seeing you likewise so child's I
can't wait for you to propose I'm so
proud hello hello Gemma
hello can I help you yeah is Gemma home
hmm your child yes we met before friends
with Harry kind yo Gemma's beautiful
sister how charming I'm her mother oh
yes well you could have fooled me err
you I'm afraid she's not here ok we
rushing Brazil result thanks Angelica
excuse my cold hi I'd like a diamond
type ring please you mean diamond died
yes i have this how much 50 thousand
million trillion billion that's a bit
steep I have a diamond aight aight ring
ok how much is that 40 million billion
trillion do you have anything cheaper
mmm there's this diamond aight aight
aight how much 2,000 you'll take it yeah
looks great yes good good I'll wrap that
for you um she won't be able to tell the
difference will she mmm-hmm Stephanie Oh
must have fallen asleep hope I'm not too
sunburned no you look beautiful oh you
don't have to do that anymore I'm yours
I know but I want to make it official I
go like this Stephanie will you marry me
yes yes
okay where's the ring oh the ring yet
hang on a second so exciting Giles well
what do you think I love it trials this
isn't diamond died huh it's diamond
aight aight aight how could you oh um
where's my ring oh I gave it to Chema
Chema who moved to Brazil that Jenna I
thought it was just a cheap the one who
was in love with you my ex best friend
and I wanted to impress you with my
personality oh yeah I'm sorry oh that
makes everything better really Oh coming
great hey come in um I'm afraid I'm only
back for a holiday Giles but I just
thought I'd come and visit you oh that's
great how long does it being too long I
heard you bought a new place yeah it's
complicated hey you don't have that ring
I gave you to you oh no I lost it in the
Amazon oh well you know what it doesn't
matter yeah i'm just glad to see you 00
suppose it'll get that
Stephanie hello Giles you're probably
wondering what she's doing here Gemma
called me she wants us to get back
together you're my two best friends oh
how do I know you're not still in love
with him that doesn't matter I just want
you to be happy I'll take him back but
will you take me back of course hmm Wow
looks like i'm in for a threesome shut
up Giles you're on probation sorry so
when can I see the new place how about
now oh um Giles put on some clothes and
hurry up thanks for the tour the place
is beautiful oh thank you for coming
maybe I'll just not go back to Brazil oh
why did you go there in the first place
I wanted a fresh start oh how excited
you yeah tell you what why don't we meet
for coffee tomorrow okay are you all
about it I see you then so mr. you're
back yeah I really missed you you know
me too hmm I'm sorry I'm sorry too I'm
sorry that I lied to Giles I've learned
that there are things in life more
important than diamond night like what
dials peacock yeah that's me what is it
I've got bad news for you buddy you're
doing that exercise all wrong you should
straighten your back like this oh yeah
thanks don't mention it oh one more
thing yeah your fiancee was in a freak
acid attack Stephanie runs like a girl
huh baby I came as quick as I could I'm
okay trials you don't look okay I'm fine
really Stephanie let me see why not
leave me please I don't want you to see
me like this oh do you really think I
only like you for your looks no good now
let me see oh oh oh god what hmm it's
not so bad really no actually it's
pretty gross Oh Oh child what am I going
to do great what are we going to do but
I can't tell anyone who did this to me
why I just can't stephanie was it
someone you knew yes who please tell me
I can't she knows where we live was a
gem oh don't say that name to me ever
again I can't believe that we need to
tell the police no I don't want people
to see me like this Stephanie will find
justice I promise video dude where is
she whoo Flav Giles where's Gemma oh I
don't know you tell oh we're looking for
it okay would you like a cookie oh yes
please eat I'll go and fetch them from
the kitchen you sure it's not too much
trouble you're a family friend yeah I'll
just wait here then okay ding dong ding
ding dong ding ring hello Giles you
wanted to see me um yeah well looks like
you've caught me caught you mmm
I'm going back to Brazil yes I know and
when exactly are you going I was going
to leave tomorrow oh really oh I know
we've become friends again but a life
really is over there you're running away
aren't you I prefer to think of it as a
fresh start Stephanie babe get back to
bed I'll deal with this no I want her to
see what she's done is oh you tell me
what happened don't pretend come and
look well show me what you've got ok oh
she's dead oh oh I'm ok so now she's
dead child's what am I going to do
Stephanie what are we going to do for
the crime of murder I hereby sentence
you to 15 years in prison what do you
have to say for yourself Giles peacock
come is there Wi-Fi in prison of course
but we won't give you the password no
so I was stuck in jail but rather meet
and Stephanie because i'd watch TV I
knew how to survive
[Music]
armed and dangerous
or you yeah
Masha What's Wrong mate okay hbu to ask
him if you wanted to be my friend no
he's a big meanie isn't a ah come on now
I'll take you to the nurse let's get out
of here dickface
[Music]
why do you hurt people child and I don't
know does it give you pleasure what no
oh no no oh well have you ever heard of
Plato's cave yes really they do it mean
margarita no I mean the concept in that
well sometimes I feel that nothing's
real and we're all just shadows like
these shadows behind us and go on well
you're gonna think it's stupid Giles
nothing is stupid silly when you're
within the walls of this office the
truth is I think that in reality we're
all just finger faces
[Music]
like you make when you're a child yeah
oh by thinking of yourself is a finger
face a child's toy you're diverting your
responsibility then it's quite common
really
face mm-hmm I hope you don't tell anyone
Giles I'm a psychiatrist hmm boy finger
face Oh face like a finger Stephanie Oh
Giles you look amazing I had plastic
surgery you can't tell Wow yes it was
free because I was attacked well you
don't have to worry anymore Oh Giles
you're so brave I'd do anything for you
and in just 15 years you're out of here
yep and we're back together you wait for
me from this course i'll wait for you I
know I say this all the time but I know
I'm your dream girl hmm yep my dream
girl how was prison good yeah have you
made friends yeah loads but what's wrong
I miss you Oh Giles I'll always be with
you check the sale on now so see you
next week ok bye hmm so you just see
other day he wondered what the world
would say I told you I'd met you hello
finger face basher why do you look so
worried I stabbed your eye out with a
sharpened toothbrush oh I've got another
I huh i'm here to see if you want in
yeah yeah it's turning good the plan is
to kill all the gods and get out whoa
sorry I'm not the violent criminal you
think I am finger face they've cancelled
the prison disco oh ok let's do this
this way finger face well my dream girl
is that way
touching good luck Stephanie Stephanie
Stephanie hey Stephanie Stephanie sleep
buddy keep it down who are you who are
you um this is my house I bought it with
Stephanie her how do you know Steph
she's my girlfriend we're sort of
engaged sword of what does that even
mean Prague it's okay I'll handle it let
me give this joker a knuckle sandwich
with a side order of pain maybe I've got
it hello Giles who the hell is that
Stephanie what's going on and all that
time since they locked you away things
have changed I've changed I've only been
in jail for three days cool Giles I'm
sorry but I broke out of prison for you
I I'd do anything for you you're my
dream girl yes but you're not my dream
guy and Brock is when did you meet him
hmm last night in Plato's cave I went to
jail for you Stephanie I know but no one
girl could ever live up to your
expectations so that's it yes mmm oh but
but but Giles Brock has a sports car
it's red like an apple and I think what
I'm trying to say is it's time we all
grew up goodbye Giles and thank you for
the house Who am I supposed to turn to
know I don't know get out of my garden
bye oh I've only got one friend in the
world and I don't even know if you'll
take me back Oh
so this is Harry's place then I a left
it like it was not sure if I like the
day call oh where is he anyway did he
leave a forwarding address you haven't
heard heard what I saw it coming with
all the drinkie what he killed himself
huh hurry so this not just modern art Oh
Harry why I wish I'd listened more
closely to you I wish I'd been a better
friend did he leave anything like a note
oh you mean like a note yes like a note
well there was this note hmm take care
of her Giles what do you think he means
by that kill her but who is she look
there's something written on the back I
know that phone number Oh someone I need
to speak to Stephanie Stephanie
Stephanie come down here at once Giles
saw the news shouldn't you be back in
jail Stephanie I know the truth about
what don't play coy with me I know
exactly what happened oh you've worked
it out haven't you well I wanted plastic
surgery to look even more beautiful but
the Health Service wouldn't give it to
me for free can you believe that and you
couldn't afford it not after buying this
house so I had to turn to insurance I
had to fake an acid attack and who
better to blame then my old friend Jemma
just didn't like the way she looked at
you so there you have a child hmm
oh and we had to kill her because she
was a witness yes so there you have it
jell-o Stephanie I wasn't even talking
about that i was talking about the phone
number you gave to hurry yes I gave him
my number and told him to call me for
sex oh ouch I wanted you to catch him
out and see what a horrible drunk he was
he killed himself Stephanie I mean I
feel like it's partly my fault don't try
and blame me I did it to help you I'm
not but I wish I'd never met you oh that
hurts oh sorry mm-hmm no it isn't Giles
go back to jail go on we're no longer
you're a bad person Stephanie you have a
convicted murderer now go before I call
chad wait who's Chad what up to the
other guy chad has a motor bike trails
that's something you'll never understand
goodbye no no suppose I'd better get
back to jail so I was back in jail
[Music]
knock knock no boy finger face basha hi
what are you doing yo coom burke brought
a friend we got caught selling drugs
we're at a nursery school but no we're
back home yeah we're gonna have loads of
fun great i'm in a football yeah yeah
yeah good good oh fun cool Oh too much
too much fun oh oh good times good times
hang on what are you doing this is why
they called me Russia wait wait wait
yeah I've got an idea why don't we start
a band ooh oh you can play the drums
I'll play the guitar you could be quite
fun better than digging a tunnel with a
teaspoon and where you gonna get the
guitar oh you remember when you brought
in those cigarettes up your bum crikey
this is a guitar going day release
tomorrow do it well kill you when you
get back okay ooh we're gonna call our
burn ooh and whatever you want basheh
Wow burn in this is gonna be great guys
mmm hey jailbreakers you listen to teach
em prison radio and it's December so you
know what that means no no no don't step
under the mistletoe
right now it's time for our Christmas
number one riot riot riot riot kill kill
kill kill kill kill right right right
right kill kill kill no you have the
will
right right right kill kill
ride ride ride ride kill kill kill cry
well hey they finally let us out onde we
only had to serve 10 years yeah it would
have been less if you hadn't killed all
those gods oh my bird Oh bhasha o finger
foods ah oh he's still scare me so where
you gonna go I'm gonna start again in a
place with delusions and extreme
violence aren't just tolerated there a
way of life Oh 3 gun a gun howdy
neighbor hey the guitar run um hi hey so
you wanna play guitar in my club yeah
yeah I did all right show us what you
got ok stabbed a guy in the eye he
didn't die he just rolled away and cry
why why did you stab me and I
hey hey hey I'm gonna stop you there
what was that okay no that'll creep my
customers right out oh that's okay
thanks anyway bye have a nice day man
now where is that stripper gotta get the
paint off these walls so I became a
busker playing four quarters not washing
very much years went by
sometimes I got so lonely I even thought
about calling Stephanie
but I always resisted and kept playing
my guitar
playing my guitar
you
whew that was awesome oh thanks my name
is finger face I know I watch you
playing all the time Wow thought I
recognized you what's your name melody
say it's cold why don't you come back to
my place how do I know you're not an ax
murderer how do I know you're not well
actually I was jailed for murder oh yes
so funny um if you're thinking of
letting me in you should know that I
really am a convicted killer I'm sorry I
really appreciate your honesty but this
is goodbye no come on in but but I also
stabbed this guy in the eye and I think
my best friend is dead because of me
okay you got some issues but you got a
nice smile you're right I should stop
dwelling on the past and start focusing
on what's happening now mmm that's the
spirit come on did I mention that my
parents run away my parents died when I
was a baby oh I'm sorry you must think
I'm so selfish hmm focusing on the tiny
problems flickering in front of me when
there's a whole world out there hmm I
don't think you're selfish you just need
a friend melody thanks I don't know what
to say don't say anything just come with
me to my damn apartment already hmm
musicians so sensitive Wow nice place
don't be too impressed my grandmother
pays the rent oh where is she she's in
England hey maybe you've met her um it's
not that small yeah i know i was just
kidding sorry i haven't had much sleep
it's pretty noisy where I live I've seen
you there under the bridge well the
rents cheap say why don't you come stay
here I've got a spare room oh I see I
see what this is okay um here we go get
away from me sorry I thought you were a
droopy get back oh I feel really
embarrassed you're like twice my age and
dirty oh I see so this was all sympathy
you men in your pride maybe I just
wanted to hang out with you oh I'm sorry
and maybe I just don't know a good thing
I've got it uh well the offer still
stands you'd let me live you yeah why ah
I guess you're not the only one who
needs a friend but you're a beautiful
melody rarely inside and out oh um do
you want a cup of coffee I'll make them
I'll get them so how do you like your
coffee served um naked oh you're kidding
no uh while the kettle's boiling I'll
show you around okay great great and so
I spent my first day with melody she
didn't feel like a stranger more like an
old friend yeah just friends but then
that night after we'd gone to sleep I
heard a scream from her room ah melody
are you okay I'm fine it was just a bad
dream Oh what was it off oh you're gonna
laugh cuz I got scared melody I'd never
laugh at you well I dreamt that we're
all potato faces Oh like how like you
draw when you're a kid oh I used to do
something similar but the dream was so
real melody yeah yeah you are not a
potato face really no you're a finger
face like me oh thank you hmm finger
face yes have you ever heard of Plato's
cave the nightclub no never mind it's
silly no no wait I do know what you're
talking about you feel that nothing is
real that that we may as well be finger
faces you've got to fight it I don't
know if I can on my own but i'm with you
I'll stay with you tonight if you want
Oh will you yeah yeah oh I love them
sleep on the floor of course no stay in
my bed you mean I trust you mmm I think
I should just sleep on the floor oh okay
yeah um
good night good night finger face hmm
good night mmm finger face yes melody
can you switch off the light oh um yeah
okay night night do-do-do-do do-do-do-do
do-do-do-do do-do-do-do-do
do-do-do-do-do oh hey sleep your head
morning um hey what's that huh oh this
old ring my mom gave me it's diamond
dite is it what's diamond date the most
valuable substance on earth my
grandmother told me that it was given to
my mom by an old friend a friend yeah
and if it was special to my mom it's
special to me what was your mother's
name her name it was Gemma I had a
friend called Gemma what was your
father's name Harry what Harry what did
your grandmother say about your birth
when my mother found out she was
pregnant she told my father but he
didn't want anything to do with it so
mom ran away to Brazil when she had me
but then an old friend called it back to
England oh where she died yeah and my
father killed himself soon after that
you sound as if you knew him yeah well
what was he like he was a good person
but I think he just couldn't handle
growing up do you carry a lad take care
of her so melody are you dressed warmly
enough what why do you care um I feel
responsible for you finger face and are
you eating enough vegetables the only
person you should feel responsible for
how I turned out is the man who killed
my mother Oh who's the tiles peacock Oh
I've spent my life planning to kill him
oh but what if he didn't actually do it
and was innocent you know it's me don't
you yeah I know finger face we found out
you'd gone to America after prison and
you followed me here I left England as
soon as I was old enough and I've been
watching you ever since mmm why don't
you just kill me I was scared oh and
yesterday you finally got the courage up
yeah i was gonna stab you with the
kitchen knife nice but then you thought
i was maybe not so bad i'm not i mean
there's someone else melody I'm gonna
prove to you that I didn't kill your
mother okay I'll see you soon if I
finger face and I hope you're not just
trying to sneak off because I'll find
you beep beep beep beep hello Stephanie
it's me oh hi Mark no it's me Paul
listen I think marks coming home soon no
me daniel paul and marker in town I
don't think we can meet today your
ex-fiance oh Michael hi no the other one
just Stephanie I went to prison for you
Reuben no Francois no Gary for murder oh
I see well I'm sorry about everything
but you've just gotta hang in there
dinner ah Stephanie its Giles Giles
Murphy peacock oh I've been thinking
about you listen I've got something you
might want yes that diamond died ring
where are you America Stephanie
now arriving flight one from London
England child um hi it is you yep it's
me it's so good to see you ready I think
about you all the time child oh I think
about you too oh now where's that ring
boy yeah the ring it's a young friends
house hmm anytime well your rings yeah
where hello oh she looks just like Gemma
yeah except not in fact my mom's name is
Jim oh you must be her daughter this is
such a nice surprise did you know her
before she was killed telos Stephanie
tell me what we were best friends yeah
lovely not tell her what happened
Stephanie the truth must come out I was
there when she died yeah and Giles threw
her down the stairs and then punched her
in the face hey come on that's a lie he
killed her I didn't as a woman you have
to believe me so I should kill him no
she's messing with your head she did it
to me I'm gonna kill you anyway just to
be sure oh look at that gorgeous sunset
outside I love sunset johar romantic oh
oh come back so I can kill you where is
it it must be here somewhere ya got a
knife um I'll be two seconds come on ah
here it is ok coming
Greg Oh shiny my shiny shiny could you
move please I'd like to stab him it's my
shining SHINee okay Stephanie I'll give
you the ring good so shiny only if you
tell the truth I killed her you killed
my mom I wanted free plastic surgery to
look even more beautiful as a woman I'm
sure you understand yeah oh maybe you
don't ki ho oh oh I think she's dead no
okay still not too bad well she's dead
now and we're in a whole lot of trouble
let's get out of here come on Giles um
yeah you'll stay with me even though i
did that terrible thing of course but
you hardly know me I knew your parents
you know when I told you that nothing
feels real well things do feel real when
I'm with you like this is the life was
supposed to live like your family to me
and for once everything's so normal yeah
for me too but I know the body starting
to steam and we'd better disposed of
that murder weapon and so we went on the
run took place where we could be safe
and it wasn't long before love was in
the air
melody are you ready yes Chris do you
take this woman to be your lawfully
wedded wife I do to have and to hold to
death do you part oh yeah I do and you
melody take this man a man who never
thought he would find his dream girl to
be your husband Oh Chris I do well you
may now kiss the bride thank you hmm
felt like a proud parent giving melody
away and because we brought the ring
back my parents could come back to they
decided to renew their vows the Church
of mental everyone was happy
do me I know right now but everyone's
watching so um yeah you're probably
wondering about me well I didn't get
married or anything but I did join the
mentalists which is nice yeah it's nice
not to have to worry about philosophy
and questions of your own existence and
things like that Krista's all the
thinking for us he also put me in charge
of his quiet which is great I get to
sing all day and well the job as other
perks for example i get to shit hi
finger face oh hi candy you coming to
practice tonight is that what you call
it Oh finger face selin hi I think your
face hi Olivia I think of things hi
Ingrid so how are you ladies today he's
so dreamy so yeah instead of finding one
dream girl I'm with a few and it feels
like that's what I wanted all along who
would have thought it I think the face
oh hi Roxy let's start practice early oh
yeah get him girls Oh ladies I just want
to finish this film that I'm doing oh
never mind i Luke phase phase phase
phase phase phase phase bigger face face
face face face face face bigger face
face face face face face face face face
face face face
finger finger finger finger finger PPP
PPP PPP hope
[Music]
you