(soft guitar music)
- Jesus Christ.
What happened?
I just can't deal with him anymore.
- Don't even know what to do, eh?
Kill him.
You know who I miss?
- Who?
- John Paul.
- John Paul, like the pope?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Everybody liked him, seemed
like an alright dude.
- I guess.
But I'm not buying it, Alex,
you're not even religious.
- Just 'cause I'm not
religious doesn't mean that,
you know, I can't find somebody not cool.
- I don't know.
What, uh, Pope Francis
doesn't cut it for you?
- He does but he's no John Paul,
that's what I'm trying to say.
- Honestly, I don't give a fuck.
The only Paul I've ever
missed is Sean Paul.
- Well Pope Sean Paul,
now that's a good idea.
- Right, Pope Sean Paul.
Just Gimme the Light, you know.
- Yeah, you can make t-shirts.
You could vote for him.
- [Frank ] You'd vote for Paul?
- I'm pretty sure that's
how they weigh it, right?
- I don't know, I just
know they smoke and shit.
All of 'em.
- Oh, yeah.
(cheerful music)
- [Frank] Hey, can I
get a bacon and cheese?
- I'll take a Caesar salad.
- What the fuck?
- What?
I'm on a diet.
- So you ask the guy
that makes you sandwiches
for a Caesar salad?
- Well you never had his Caesar salads.
Trust me, they're killer.
- I guess so, still makes you a bitch.
- Well am I gonna be a bitch
when I'm on the beach with my six pack?
And you're gonna be here bitchin'.
- No.
- You should try.
You should have some of these salads.
- Yeah, we'll fucking see about that.
You and your six pack.
God, I mean, stop fucking dreaming.
Oh, what are you gonna do today?
- Eh, same old, get drunk.
- Christ, you're a fucking alcoholic.
- Well, you know, you love it.
- Your liver doesn't.
- Ah, fuck my liver.
I don't need 'em.
- I think you can't, they're important.
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Fuck, I gotta work today.
- Oh, oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- You work?
- What the fuck was that?
- What was what?
Work?
- Yeah.
- Nothing, don't worry about it.
- Fuck you man, work is work, you know.
- You give out flyers to people.
- Hey, I work in marketing.
- Oh, yeah?
You give out pieces of paper to people
that just throw it out immediately.
- Fuck you man, a job is a job, you know.
I'm on rough times.
- Oh yeah, 'cause your
girlfriend cheated on you, right?
And you lost your job, boohoo hoo.
- Hey, I don't complain that much.
You know, I'm just going
through rough times.
- Yeah you're not.
- I'm trying to get back on my feet.
- You're not going through rough times.
You know Sid Murphy, now he's
going through rough times.
- Who the fuck is Sid Murphy?
- Ah, my old friend from
high school, you know,
he's homeless, smokes a lot of dog shit.
- Dog shit?
- Too much.
It's dog shit.
- People do that?
They smoke dog shit?
- Well he does.
He's homeless.
- Ah, okay.
- What else is he gonna smoke?
- I guess that would be a
reason why he smokes dog shit.
- The only reason.
- Weird.
Thanks.
Man, I don't want to go to
work today, I'm exhausted.
- So don't.
- I have to, I have to make paper bro.
- Ah, alright, well, then go.
- Yeah, I'm gonna have to.
I'm just so fucking tired from yesterday.
- From all that drinking, all those 40s.
- Yeah, it's just those
40s were calling me.
- I don't know, yeah,
it's a good workout too,
holding those 40s all night.
- Ah, yeah, but then it's like a catch-22.
You're working out,
but then you're also
drinking a bunch of beer.
Calories, man.
- Ah, yes.
- Now, I'm sitting too?
- Empty calories.
Well you could have burned some calories
fingering that girl.
- What do you mean?
- You remember that girl?
- [Frank] Really?
- Yeah, remember.
She was like oh I totally
want Frank to finger me,
but you was doing 40 hands.
So she fell asleep, unsatisfied.
- Fuck.
You think she still wants to get fingered?
- Well, she's kind of sleeping right now.
- Well like, I could wake her and ask.
- Nah, you know, just
leave her, let her sleep.
- [Frank] Yeah, you know what?
When she's 100%.
- When she leaves.
- Yeah, you know what,
actually, when she wakes up,
you ask her, let me know,
'cause now I feel like quite an asshole.
- Yeah, you should.
- I could have provided, and I didn't.
Who is she anyway?
- I don't know, she came
with this guy right here.
- Who is that guy?
- Don't you know?
- No.
- Yeah, I don't know who that is.
- Maybe he fingered her.
- Maybe she fingered him.
- Maybe they fingered together.
That's why they're on the floor.
- Maybe they just laid
down and fell asleep.
You ever think about that?
- Well I only invited
people to this party.
Didn't you hear?
I was like hey we're
having a finger party.
- [Alex] Yeah, I didn't get fingered.
I didn't finger anybody either.
- It's about that time.
- Ah, about that time, huh?
- About that time.
- To go to work.
- Yeah.
- Eh.
- Fuck you.
- Oh, have fun.
(upbeat music)
- Nope, we don't sell beepers anymore.
Like phones and stuff.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry we don't fucking do it.
I mean we don't do that.
I'm sorry for saying, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Where you fucking first sent your bitch.
Hi.
- [Frank] Hey.
- Thanks for showing
up, you're fucking late.
- I'm not, what are you talking about?
It's 12 on the dot.
- 12 on the what?
- 12 on the dot.
- The fuck is that?
- It's an expression, like 12 on the dot,
I mean I'll be there.
- I've never heard that
in my fucking life.
- It's not my fault.
- 12 on the nose.
- On the nose?
- 12 on the head.
- Never heard of that.
- A needle in the head.
- Hit the needle on the head.
- Hit the needle on head?
- Needle in a haystack.
- That has nothing to do with time.
- I know phrases, I never
heard of the fucking dot shit.
- I don't think you know phrases,
'cause you never heard of on the dot.
Now you got lemons.
What's with the lemons?
- This is what life gave me.
I would love it.
I would love if I could just simply just
open up a lemonade stand and
not have to sell this shit.
But this is, this is what life gives me.
- Oh yeah, like the expression?
When life hands you lemons.
- [Escalon Boss] What happens?
- You make lemonade.
Are you gonna make lemonade?
- Life hands you lemons, you get laid.
You're fucking making shit up.
I never heard of that shit
in my fucking life man.
- [Frank] That's a thing.
- Alright.
Just hand out some flyers man.
If you could do that, that
would be fucking terrific.
- Alright, I'm gonna go.
- It would be like a
glass of fucking lemonade.
- Alright.
I'm gonna go give out.
- Extra sugar.
- I'm gonna go give out the flyer.
- Do that, thank you, thank you.
- I'll be back.
- Thank you.
Fucking shit man.
Fucking three o'clock,
I gotta fucking peel all these lemons.
Fuck!
I need the lemon.
Fucking shit.
Fuck it, fuck it.
It doesn't matter.
Kill me, just fucking kill me.
Just fucking kill me.
- [Frank] Can I have a cell phone?
- What?
("Tongue in the Dirt" by Generation Pill)
♫ Hey man can I get a ride home
♫ Acid on my eyes and in my bones
♫ Feeling dirty feeling people stare
♫ Care to take me almost anywhere but here
♫ Anywhere but here
♫ But here
- Hey man, what's this?
- Surprise.
- Fuck.
I haven't seen you in like forever,
and you lost a ton of weight.
- Yeah, well there's not too
many White Castles in Ohio.
- Well what's up, you don't
text me, you don't call.
- Well I tried calling you
but I guess I have your old number.
But I heard you were
giving out flyers again
so I'd thought I come check you out.
- Well it's not like this
is all I've been doing
for the past four years while
you were away at college.
You know, I've done other stuff.
It's just I fucking lost my job.
- Look, I didn't say anything.
- It's just really fucking
great to have you back.
Are you staying long?
- Uh, maybe, I don't know.
But where's Hailey?
I'd like to see her.
- Well, about that.
- So she just up and left you like that?
With who?
- Yo, fucking Danny.
It's 'cause he had a sweet car.
- Yeah, that's right, he did get
a lot of girls with that sweet car.
- Yeah, it was a sweet car,
and they drove out of the fucking state.
- Where'd they go?
- I believe they moved to Connecticut.
- Well, fuck her and her Connecticunt.
- [Frank] Oh, good one bro.
- Not my best.
- [Frank] Yeah, I think they're
pregnant now, well, she is.
- [Dave] Who'd you hear that from?
- Her mother, I ran
into her the other day.
- What?
It just doesn't seem like
something Hailey would do.
- Well, you know, it just.
- Well I don't know actually.
- Yeah, it's fine.
So, how was the college life?
Went to any interesting frats?
- Almost, but once they
found that I was gay,
they didn't want me
naked in their basement
getting paddled, so no frats for me.
- Ah, well there must have
been some cool parties.
- A few.
- No Project X style parties?
- No, I went to college, not high school.
- Well sorry, Mr. Harvard.
- Shut up.
- Well, what are you gonna do now?
- I don't know.
I mean, I applied to a few
jobs, maybe grad school,
but a lot of that stuff is really scary.
- I didn't mean like
in your fucking future.
I meant like right now.
What are you gonna do after this?
- Oh, um, well I gotta
say hi to my parents.
- Ah, fuck your parents.
- No, they're kind of cool.
- I guess.
Ah, well, we should do
this more, let's hang out.
- Yeah, definitely.
I mean, I gotta get
readjusted to city life so.
- I'll readjust you.
- Well, you have my number and just,
you know, call me when you wanna hang out.
- Yeah.
- But I gotta go now.
So, talk to you later.
- Yeah.
- All right, see ya.
Hug.
Okay, all right, all right, bye.
- I'll see you man.
- What's up?
- I saw Dave today.
- Matthews?
- No, Dave Matthews.
No, I saw my old friend.
I've told you about him.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, how is he?
- Oh, he's good, he
just got back from Ohio.
- Ah, Ohio.
What, is he gay?
- Actually, he is.
- Well I didn't mean it like that.
I'm not racist or anything.
- I think the term you're
looking for is homophobic.
- Well I'm not, all right.
It's cool that's he's gay.
It's probably the coolest.
- So kiss me.
- Ah, man, can you just finish your story
and stop trying to fuck me all the time?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Um, no, he was just
talking about how he's back
and he wants to get readjusted
to city life, you know.
- Yeah, that's cool.
- Yeah, I guess.
- What you mean by I guess?
- Nothing, it's just, you know,
we haven't hung out in a long time.
- [Alex] So isn't it a good
thing you guys are hanging out?
- Yeah, yeah, it's great,
I'm not complaining.
- Look, I understand, I was
like you're complaining.
Oh, yeah, yeah, by the way, the other girl
that wanted to get fingered.
- [Frank] Yeah.
- Yeah, don't worry about it.
- Oh, wait, you got it done?
- Ah, not me, I asked somebody else to.
- [Frank] Oh, the other guy that was here.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I've been meaning to bring up something.
- What?
- The other night I got in
my room, middle of the night,
and I heard something
coming from your room.
- Okay.
- I heard crying.
Were you crying?
- No, it wasn't me.
- I'm pretty sure I heard
you, I heard you crying.
There's nobody else in this apartment.
- Nah, it must have been
the TV, it wasn't me.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
The last time I cried was
at ending of Marmaduke.
You know that movie's too sad for me.
The ending kills me.
But no, wasn't me.
Well, I don't know.
I'm gonna head to bed.
- Oh, you mean you're
gonna go into bed and cry.
- Well, if I'm crying,
I'm watching Marmaduke.
You know that's my favorite movie man.
- I don't know why.
- [Alex] It's good.
- [Frank] Forgot something.
- [Alex] I like dogs.
- Yeah, I like dogs too.
- Ma, Amanda and her
sister are at it again.
Yeah, don't worry, I'll handle it.
Shoo, shoo.
Shoo, you two get out of
here, get out of here.
- The fuck, why'd you do that for?
- Man, trust me, don't worry about it.
- I am.
What, what was that?
- Those were my cousins.
Don't worry about it,
I'm just gonna go inside.
- Oh.
The fuck you do that for?
- 'Cause I fucking can, yo.
- You don't gotta be a dick man.
I'm just trying to work out here.
- This is what you call work?
- Yeah.
- You know how many six
figures I made last year?
- Six.
- 700,000 a year.
- Fucking congrats.
What you want me to say about that?
- Yo, you're making me
mad angry right now.
- You're not angry now.
- I'm about to give you a
fucking knuckle sandwich.
- Who the fuck even says knuckle sandwich?
- Oh, word.
(tense music)
- Who the fuck are you?
- I'm Will, your subconscious or whatever.
- Well I guess that's cool, whatever.
- What are you doing here?
- I got knocked out.
- Where?
- 47th and 7th.
- You better hope you don't get robbed.
- Yeah.
Wait, thinking about it now,
didn't you jump me a few times?
- Do you have hands?
- Ah, no problem, whatever.
- Who's that over there?
- Fuck you, Frank.
I'm fucking your girlfriend.
How does that feel?
Hanging out flyers while I
got the fucking Cadillac cash.
- That's Danny.
He ran off with my girlfriend Hailey.
Last I heard they're pregnant.
- Rough deal, man.
- Yeah.
- I got a fucking sweet car.
Me and your girlfriend
we ride around in it.
I already fucking bought like a baby seat
for the fucking baby.
His name's gonna be Hugo.
It's gonna be the fucking shit.
My life is awesome.
Your life sucks.
You have no balls.
Fuck you.
- Well, why is this my
subconscious anyway?
- Maybe because you
haven't gotten over it yet.
Seriously, how long has it been?
You're free to do whatever
and whomever you want.
Where are your balls?
- I don't know man, she took 'em.
- Exactly, get your balls back.
Get your balls back.
- I guess I better get
my balls back, right?
- Wow, they're really getting
hot and heavy over there.
- Oh, I can feel it kicking, oh.
Hailey's sucking my dick right now.
- And that's what a
prolapsed asshole looks like.
- So this is what you've
been doing since I left?
- Not exactly.
Aw fuck I hate this job.
- What happened?
- I don't know, some macho man came over
and clocked me in the face.
- Why?
- I don't know, maybe he don't like me
or maybe he just really wanted to fuck me
and all he knows is violence.
- Yeah, I doubt it.
- Well what are you doing here?
- Just going to the deli.
- To get what?
- Caesar salad.
- Why the fuck is everybody getting
Caesar salads from delis now, since when?
- So you wanna come over?
- Don't your parents like hate me?
- Doesn't everybody hate you?
- Yes, that's true.
- [Both] Ah, let's go.
- Hey, so who do you think
would win in a fight?
Sam Jackson in The Avengers,
or Sam Jackson in Jungle Fever?
- Oh, Jungle Fever, no question about it.
He's got that crazy
crackhead dancing going on,
and Nick Fury's blind.
- Yeah, like that never
comes up in the movie.
It's like you think somebody
would throw something
at Nick Fury and he wouldn't
be able to catch it.
- Well like, the Avengers
wanna go out one night
and see a 3D movie.
- Yeah, like fuck Nick Fury.
- He should just get a glass eye.
- Well, everybody should
just get a glass eye.
- I should see how much those cost.
- [Frank] Hey, have you ever
seen a prolapsed asshole?
- Dude, I'm eating.
- [Frank] What?
I'm just asking.
- Yeah.
- Ew, how?
- College party.
- Well, was there just
some girl running around
flaunting her prolapsed asshole?
- It's not too far from the truth.
- Ew.
- Could I ask you a question about Hailey?
- [Frank] Ask away.
- How long ago was it?
- [Frank] About seven months ago.
- It's just she never told me about it
and we were all best friends,
so I figured she would
text me or something.
- Dude, don't worry
about it, don't feel bad,
like she dropped everybody and just left.
- Let's just go to Connecticut
and slash her tires.
- Now that doesn't sound
like too bad of an idea.
- You guys were dating
for such a long time.
- Yeah, five years.
- Seems like forever.
- Yeah, I know Dave.
- Oh, sorry.
Touchy subject.
- Eh.
- But why though?
It was seven months ago.
Get your balls back.
- Huh, that's strange.
You're not the only person
who said that to me today.
- 'Cause it's true, that you
gotta get your balls back man.
Look, Saturday we'll go out.
You show me what I've been missing
and I'll get your balls back.
- I don't know, man.
I haven't seen those in ages.
They are probably all dusty and lonely.
- Lonely, lonely balls.
Are you watching porn?
- Dude, I really wanna
see a prolapsed asshole.
- What's with your new obsession
with prolapsed assholes?
- I don't know, it's intriguing.
- [Porn Actress] Fucking tease that shit.
- [Porn Actress] Uh-huh.
- So I guess my Mom doesn't like
prolapsed assholes as much as you do.
- Who knew?
- Anyways, Saturday still sounds cool?
- Yeah.
- All right.
We're gonna get your balls back.
- No matter what, my balls will be found.
- All right.
- I'll see you later.
("Sheet City" by Mannequin Pussy)
What the fuck are you doing?
- Oh, what's up, Frank?
- [Frank] Yeah, so what are you doing?
- I was just trying to
fit these in my mouth.
- Yeah, but why are you shoving fucking
toilet paper rolls in your mouth?
- All right, yesterday I was out,
I don't know if you know that or not.
- I don't care.
- Fair enough.
I was with some girl and you know,
we were just hanging out, all
of this, all that good stuff.
- Yeah man, okay.
- You know, I've known her
for a while, long enough.
- Long enough?
- Yeah, long enough.
So I paid for her, I paid for everything.
I paid for everything.
I just asked for a
simple and quick blowjob.
Didn't get anything.
- Ah, classic Alex.
You never get blowjobs.
- [Alex] You might have guessed that.
Probably from every other story.
- Every story you tell me,
it ends hey I didn't get that blowjob.
- So she was telling me.
- [Frank] Yeah.
- Well she was going on
a rant, first of all,
about how hard it was to give a blowjob.
Yeah, it was very annoying.
She was going on for five
minutes, felt like a whole night.
So she told me to get a
bunch of toilet paper rolls,
which is what I have right now,
and just shove it in my mouth.
- [Frank] Why?
- Well to show to see how it feels.
- [Frank] To give a blowjob?
- Yeah.
And it's probably one of the
hardest things I've ever done.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's very uncomfortable.
- That's probably why
they don't like to do it.
Like so you just got up in
the morning, decided hey.
- [Alex] Well I was up all night.
- All night just thinking?
- Thinking about it, it was killing me.
It was, it was bad.
Dude, do you wanna try it?
- I guess.
Nah.
Why don't you just give me a dry one?
I don't want one you just sucked off.
- All of them are.
- No, that's fucking weird man.
Just I don't wanna do that.
Why are you doing this?
- Okay, first of all,
you're making it weird.
Second of all, all of these are wet.
None of them are dry so
you're not gonna have any.
- Well, go fucking, why did you waste
all our toilet paper doing this?
- What else am I supposed to do?
- Not do this.
Watch the fucking TV.
Why are you sucking off?
You're just oh, I'm gonna
wake up this morning,
I'm gonna face fuck a
bunch of toilet paper.
- Yes.
I thought about this last night
when she blurted out, I thought about it,
and that's what I wanted
to do all day today.
- Well are you gonna text her
and let her know how it feels?
- Uh, no.
- Hey, so I finished up.
I'm gonna head out now.
- You're all done?
That was fucking quick.
- [Frank] Not that fast.
- Where's Guinness World Records?
'Cause I think I gotta
put a record on that.
- [Frank] What do you mean?
- Nobody hands out flyers that fast, man.
It's almost like you just
fucking threw them out.
- What are you talking about?
- Hm, look at this picture.
- What's, what's that?
- Oh (mumbles).
Look at this.
You wanna explain that?
- That wasn't me.
- It wasn't you, you're the only
fucking person handing out flyers.
- All right.
- Did you think I'm not gonna see?
You fucking threw them
out right in the corner.
I go to lunch on that corner,
on that fucking block.
I see a garbage can full of our flyers.
- I had something
important to do that day.
- Important, you have something important.
Have you seen what I've fucking been
through this whole fucking week?
I got a lot of important things to do.
I got deadly shit to do.
This is not fucking like,
this is your job, bro.
This is what you have to fucking do.
You gotta take responsibility man.
You know what?
- I'll pay for the stack.
- That's not the fucking point man.
If I could just pay off my fucking,
fucking problems, my
issues, we're done son,
I wouldn't have to deal with shit.
But I got shit to deal with,
and you're not involved in
it, so just fucking leave.
Just take a few days, just take a few days
and just get out of my fucking face man.
- Are you firing me?
- No, I'm not.
I'm just giving you fucking time off.
If I need you, I'll call you.
- Dude, I won't do it again, I promise.
- Take some time, all right?
- Fuck.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
Yes, they're okay, they're good.
Okay, all right.
Yes, you'll have the lemons ready.
They're fucking peeled.
You have them three, three on the head.
It's an impression.
Mm-hmm, infection, I don't know.
Listen, I'm sorry, okay, fuck, fuck.
We need hand chop.
We got like a fucking
shitload of lemons coming in.
Fuck man, I don't know what
to fucking do with this shit.
Fuck!
- Fuck.
- Fuck what?
- I think I just got fired.
- What do you mean you
think you got fired?
- I mean he told me, "Hey, don't come in
"for a couple of days,
I don't want you here."
Fuck, which means no money,
which means I'm fucking jobless man.
- Yeah, well, what are you gonna do now?
- I guess nothing, just hang around here
fucking doing what you do.
What do you fucking do?
- I do a lot.
- Yes, suck on fucking toilet paper rolls.
- It's productive, it's better than
what you're doing right now.
You're just sitting here bitching.
- Fuck.
Yeah, sorry.
It's just fucking, you know, like Dave
came back from college and I can't even.
He has a fucking degree.
I can't even fucking hand out paper.
- Well, giving out paper
is not for everybody.
- Fucking homeless people
can give out flyers, man.
- Well, if it makes you feel
any better, Torrie stopped by.
- Oh yeah?
- She was looking for you.
She looks pretty good.
- What does that even mean?
- Well, she looked nice,
she looked all dressed up.
She looked like she was
going out, you know.
- Man, I haven't seen her in forever.
- Well, maybe then you
should give her a call,
see what she's up to.
- Yeah, maybe.
- How about we, we walk to the park?
Take a little walk.
You know, that used to calm you down.
- Yeah, sure, whatever.
- Yeah, let's go.
You smell like lemon.
- Ah, it's a long story.
(screaming)
- I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
How's it going man?
- Alex, man.
- How's it going guys?
- [Jimmy] As I live and breathe.
- [Alex] I went to high
school with these two guys.
- Oh.
- Yeah, we used to be best friends.
- Best friends, man.
- Best.
I am Jimmy.
- [Frank] And this is.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Tommy.
- [Frank] I'm Frank.
- Nice to meet you Frank.
- Do you guys live around here?
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
- We live here.
- [Frank] Oh, you live in the park.
- [Tommy] Yeah, we're homeless.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- [Frank] Well like
the world is your home.
- It's everyone's home.
- That's true.
- Some people have homes as well.
- Yeah, we have an apartment.
- Yeah, it's cool, man.
- Why is it that all
your friends are bums?
- Hey, we're not bums!
- No, Tommy, no.
- We're not bums!
- Tommy, Tommy, no!
Safe place.
Dude, I'm sorry for that.
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't look at him yet.
- Oh.
- It's fine.
You know, just be a little careful, okay.
He's a diabetic.
He kind of gets worked up.
- Low blood sugar.
Low blood sugar.
- Low blood sugar, man.
- We'll get you some Krispy
Kreme later, we're good.
- It's all right.
- It's cool, we're all buddies here.
- [Jimmy] Yeah.
- So, how'd this happen?
How'd you get homeless?
- You know, story's old as time.
You know, we were hanging
out with Sid Murphy,
starts smoking dog shit
like 24/6 minus Lord's day.
- Is that dog shit really that good?
- Dude, it is fucking God.
- Dude, it takes you on
a fucking roller coaster.
Like one day you just
graduate high school,
the next moment you're
fucking smoking dog shit
in the gazebo next to
hipsters fucking each other.
- Yeah, but man get off that true.
- It's true.
It's true.
- It's good.
- We've been sober, dog shit's over.
- [Tommy] About like.
- [Jimmy] What was it, three months?
- [Tommy] Four.
- Four months.
- In dog years?
- Fuck you.
Dog years, this is my life
you're talking about, man.
And yes, dog years.
- He was correct.
- He was right, yeah.
- Well, how's Sid doing?
- I don't really know, man.
We haven't really seen him since
he took our shoes and ran off on us.
- Dude, we don't have shoes anymore.
- [Frank] Oh, you're not
wearing any shoes right now?
- No, we just painted our feet.
- Optical illusion.
- [Frank] Oh, good.
- [Alex] You got me, fooled me.
- Yeah, but we know.
So what are you guys
doing around here anyway?
You're doing the girls tour or something?
- [Alex] Just walking around.
- [Frank] Taking a
stroll through the park.
You know, taking in the sights.
- He got fired from his job so yeah.
- You know why I think I got
fired, it sounded like that.
I mean I've just been so fucking confused.
(Jimmy gagging)
- Really?
You're gonna complain about your life?
- Yeah, dude, we're fucking homeless.
- [Tommy] You all right, man?
- Yeah.
So like what do you guys
plan for the evenings?
- Nothing really, we're just walking.
- Nothing.
- Yeah, nothing.
- Guys.
You guys wanna smoke some weed?
- Yeah, I guess so, as long
as there's no dog shit.
- Oh.
Oh, this mother.
- One, two, three.
- [Alex] Hold up.
Hold up guys.
- I'm exhausted.
I'm just gonna go to sleep.
Yeah?
- Torrie's at the door.
- [Frank] Really?
- Yeah, well she never
comes just to see me.
- Well can you tell her
to give me a minute?
- [Alex] Why don't you go tell her?
- I can't.
- [Alex] Why not?
- Alex, I have morning wood.
- Oh, okay.
Give Frank a fucking
minute, he has morning wood.
- [Frank] What the fuck?
- Fuck you too bitch.
- [Frank] Hey.
Oh, yeah, sorry about Alex.
- Yup.
- [Frank] You wanna come in?
- Yeah.
- So welcome to my humble home.
Well how's everything been?
I don't get a call, no text.
What's up?
- [Torrie] I've just
been really busy lately.
- Yeah, doing what?
- Uh, I got a job at MTV.
- Wow, look at you.
Have you met Carson Daly yet?
- Carson Daly is not on MTV anymore.
- Oh, fuck it, I don't watch TV,
but I guess I'll try to tune
in more now since you're on it.
- Yeah, thanks.
I hear you're back to handing out flyers.
- Yeah, that is a thing.
I'm not really sure
about it anymore though.
I think I got fired.
- [Torrie] Why?
- I wasn't handing them out.
- Well, that'll do it.
- [Frank] I guess.
- How long have you been living with Alex?
- [Frank] It's been about like two months.
Not very long.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah, it's fun.
He's a bit of a weird guy though.
Like the other morning, I
walk into the living room
and he's just stuffing toilet
paper rolls in his mouth.
He tells me that some girl told him
that's how it feels to give a blowjob.
- Yeah, girls do that all
the time in high school.
You didn't know that?
- [Frank] Really?
- No, not really, that's fucking stupid.
- So you're telling me you've never
put a toilet paper roll in your mouth?
- I've never even thought about it.
- Yeah.
- Alex is weird.
- I love him though.
- Speaking of guys you love, how's Dave?
- Well, he's back.
- [Torrie] For good?
- I guess, he's all graduated and stuff.
- Great, have you seen him?
- Yeah, we've hung out.
I'm actually gonna go
out tonight with him.
Have a bit of a night out of town.
- Boys only?
- [Frank] Not necessarily, why?
- I was gonna invite you out tonight.
- [Frank] Where?
- Just to some party.
You guys should come,
you should bring Dave, and invite Alex.
- Um, I don't know, I'll
see, 'cause I gotta ask Dave
if that's what he wants to do.
- Okay.
It's been a while.
You should really come.
We can catch up and stuff.
- Aren't we catching up right now?
- Kind of.
I have to go to work.
- [Frank] Oh.
- But text me and let me know.
- Uh, sure, will do.
- [Torrie] See ya.
- I'll be here.
(phone ringing)
Hey, what's up man?
Uh, oh you got time now.
Um, yeah I'll come down.
You wanna hang around the park and drink
for a bit before we go to the party?
- Sure, sounds good.
- Cool.
Yeah, I'll see you in a bit, see ya.
Hey, um, Alex, you wanna come meet Dave?
We're gonna go drink
before we go to the party.
- Nah, just go, just head out.
- [Frank] Why, are you
gonna meet us there?
- Yeah, later, later on.
- Well then why don't you just come now?
- 'Cause I gotta brush my teeth.
I got a whole bunch of things to do.
- By brush your teeth, do you mean
you're gonna jerk off
now that I'm not here?
- Yeah, mostly likely, yeah.
- [Frank] All right,
well have fun, okay, go.
- Oh, thanks.
- [Frank] See ya.
- So, do you take all your dates here?
- Now that I'm thinking about
it, it's kind of creepy.
- And it's probably why
Hailey broke up with you.
- Could be.
- Can you not start that?
Why are you smiling?
- Hey, I'm just appreciating the moment.
It's not every day I get to see you.
- Well I'm here now.
- Yeah, you are.
- So tell me.
What's been really going
on in the life of Frank?
- Well you know pretty much all of it.
I got dumped by Hailey and
I got fired from my job.
- [Dave] Where did you work?
- I actually had a pretty sweet gig.
I was working at Galaxy Comics.
- [Dave] Really?
- Yeah, it was fucking awesome.
I just got to sit around
and read comics all day.
- Well, why'd you get fired?
- I didn't really get fired per se.
I just kind of went into my job
and my manager wasn't there.
Instead there was just this
really tall big Russian dude.
And when I asked him,
"Hey, where's my manager?",
he said, "He moved to Las Vegas."
- Sounds kind of fishy.
- Yeah, no one's ever,
no one's seen him since.
- He's probably dead.
- He did have a really
big gambling problem.
- So, what else?
- Nothing much.
I just kinda drink a lot
and watch Wahlburgers.
- Wahlburgers?
- [Frank] You don't know
what Wahlburgers is?
- No.
- It's awesome.
It's this reality show
about a burger restaurant
owned and managed by the Wahlbergs.
So it's Mark, Donnie, and
the whole Wahlberg clan,
just selling burgers in Boston.
- Who would have guessed
that the underwear model
would be in a show called Wahlburgers now?
- So, how was, how was
your four years at college?
You hardly ever came
down and visit anyone.
- Yeah, I mean, I was really busy.
- Well, when was your graduation?
- [Dave] In May, but it was small
and just my family came up.
- I would have came.
- Well thanks, but you didn't have to.
Like I said, it was just
my family pretty much so.
- Yeah.
- So, let's talk about something else.
How about the Broncos?
- I don't even know what that means.
Is that like a gay thing?
- Kind of.
(Frank farts)
Is that what we're doing?
Fart noises?
- Hey, was that not clever and/or quirky?
- Yes, that's what I
love about you the most.
Your quirkiness.
- Hey, it's hard to
keep up this character.
Man, it's not easy being
so cynical and cute.
- [Dave] Yeah, but you're
neither of those things.
I guess you can be a little bit cynical,
but you don't have to be a
cynical asshole all the time.
- But I do have to be cute.
- I thought I was the gay one here.
- Hey, well I don't, you know,
like take dicks up my butt,
so I think you still have
the cake on that one.
- Well, I've never actually
had a dick there, dick.
- Really, you've never had
like a dick in the thing?
Nothing?
- [Dave] No.
- Strange, so like what
do you do like sex-wise?
- I don't know, mouth stuff.
- Interesting.
What is it, like no one's ever offered?
Or is it just something
you don't wanna do?
- No, I get a lot of
offers, but I don't know.
I might let the guy I'm seeing now do it.
- You like him that much?
- I guess.
- Hey, well if anybody's gonna
be taking your virginity,
I gotta meet them first, Dave.
I gotta approve.
- [Dave] Hey, you don't
have to police my asshole.
- Oh, I guess not anymore since
you got a college degree and all.
- So, we gonna talk about
my asshole all night
or we're gonna go to the party?
- I guess we should go.
- Hey, is there something
you wanna talk about?
I mean, I don't know, but it seems
like there's something on your mind.
- So we're gonna do this now?
- What?
I wanna talk.
You seem like you wanna talk.
- It's nothing important.
- Frank, stop being a
little bitch, just tell me.
- It's just you never visited me, is all.
Even when you were fucking
down here, I never saw you.
That's what I'm thinking about.
- Really, that's the issue?
- Yeah, that's the issue.
- I mean, I don't know
what you want me to say.
I have other friends.
I'm sorry I didn't center
my visits around you.
- Don't be a fucking dick.
A call, a text, would have sufficed.
It's like you went up to college
and got all fancy and dropped me.
- Well I'm here now,
so what's the big deal?
- So you were trying to drop me?
- No one was trying to drop you, Frank.
What are you talking about?
I went to college and I
wanted to make new friends.
I wanted to grow up.
Sorry if you took it as a personal attack.
- Fuck you man.
It's just not the same anymore.
- No, no, it's not, I know that.
You're the one who seems to be
having trouble realizing that.
- Fuck you.
- Oh, that's right, that's how
you solve all your problems.
Fuck you, this is bullshit.
Stop being a baby.
I mean, yeah, we're not
best friends anymore,
but that's not bad.
I mean, you have your
people and I have mine.
- Can we just go to this
fucking party already?
- Frank, I'm not trying to fight.
- [Frank] Yeah.
(electronic dance music)
- Yeah so I was at Subway's.
I tried to get a meatball marinara.
No more meatballs.
- [Torrie] How does that even happen?
- That's what I was thinking.
- [Torrie] Shouldn't they just
have meatballs all the time?
- No, they just put the sauce on the bread
and they just gave it to me like that.
- Dave.
- Hey, it's been forever.
- Yeah.
- Hey, I'm Dave, nice to finally meet you.
- What's wrong?
You guys look like shit.
- [Torrie] How was your date?
- Fine.
- It was great, he's having a fit.
- Frank, come here.
Wanna try?
- What's that?
- Drugs.
- [Frank] But like what does it do?
- It makes you feel like a rainbow.
- Oh what the hell.
- Well, do we get some?
- [Torrie] Everybody gets one.
- I've never done this before.
- Well there's a first
time for everything.
- Yeah, well like how long
does it take to kick in?
- Usually about 45 minutes.
- So what happens now?
- Well you can go dance.
- Nah, I don't dance.
- Believe me, after
tonight you're gonna dance.
- I already regret this decision.
- Well, you've already done it.
So let's go dance.
- So did you know that
Torrie was gonna drug us?
- Nope, I had no idea.
- Classic Torrie.
- I guess.
It's the first I'm hearing of any of it.
- I mean it's not a bad thing.
It looks like she's having fun.
- I don't know man.
It's just like everybody's
doing their own shit,
and here I am, spending
my days giving out flyers,
smoking and drinking Four Lokos.
- Gotta stop being so hard on yourself.
You're 22.
You have plenty of time to grow up.
- No.
I guess I just want to grow up.
- I miss the old you.
I come back and you're
crying over some girl.
- Some girl.
- Yeah, I mean okay, we were
best friends a long time ago,
but I mean she broke your heart, fuck her.
She's just some girl.
- Just some girl.
- Just some dumb girl.
- You know what the thing is?
- What?
- I haven't had sex since her.
- Nope.
Could have fingered some
girl the other night,
but some guy beat me to it.
- That's weird.
- That's my life, Dave.
- So, nothing physical since her?
- Nope, not even a kiss.
- Ah.
- Yeah, and you know what I'm afraid of,
is that when I do eventually get a girl,
I'm just gonna end up crying
and fucking moping all over her.
- You're not gonna cry.
- I don't know man, I
can't have that shit.
What if she gives me
some bad review on Lulu?
- Lulu?
- Yeah, it's this app
where like girls rate guys.
- Did someone give you a bad review?
- Yeah, Hailey.
She said I make too much noise during sex.
- Do you?
- No, I make like regular noise.
- Like what?
- Like (moans).
- Do you make that face?
- I don't know man.
- It's nothing to be ashamed of.
- I guess.
You wanna get out for a bit?
- Yeah, sure.
("Rookie Card" by Meth Dad)
- [Torrie] Hey guys.
- Fuck, getting out felt really weird.
- What is this?
- [Torrie] Have fun.
("Swimmers" by Meth Dad)
♫ Talking to tigers and
wishing the wardrobe
♫ To take out the garbage
to clean up this place
♫ Whooping and craning
we'll quit our complaining
♫ We're growing up faster
adding fat to our face
♫ Testing and learning
and books about burning
♫ They're asking too much so
let's burn down the school
♫ Dim down the lighting
and quiet the thunder
♫ Hush mother nature let
me bathe in your pools
♫ I want to want you
to want to want me too
♫ Talking to tigers and
wishing the wardrobe
♫ To take out the garbage
to clean up this place
♫ Whooping and craning
we'll quit our complaining
♫ We're growing up faster
adding fat to our face
♫ Testing and learning
and books about burning
♫ They're asking too much so
let's burn down the school
♫ Dim down the lighting
and quiet the thunder
♫ Hush mother nature let
me bathe in your pools
♫ I want to want you
to want to want me too
- Hey, don't I know you?
- Oh shit.
Hey Frank.
- Melissa, right?
- Yeah, yeah you were a junior
when I was a senior, right?
- Yeah.
- Weren't you the guy that took
a shit in the urinal as a prank?
- No, that wasn't me.
- Common mistake.
- Aren't you Danny's cousin?
- Danny.
Look I'm sorry he got your
girlfriend all pregnant and shit.
If it's any consolation,
I hate the fucking guy so.
- Well, hate's a strong word.
- Okay, then I really, really dislike him.
- As do I.
- [Melissa] So, what are you doing here?
Were you inside the party?
- Yeah.
- Oh, I didn't see you.
Do you come to these parties often?
- No, this is my first one actually.
You?
- I dabble.
- I was actually here with
Dave, from high school.
- Dave.
Dave was the one who shat
in the urinal, right?
- Nobody took a shit in the urinal.
- Look, I distinctly remember fecal matter
being a big part of my
high school experience.
That and my cousin fucking
everyone in the entire school.
- [Frank] Well who could forget that?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry about that girl.
Hailey, right?
Well, fuck her.
She can't be that smart anyways.
- Why, 'cause she left me?
- No, 'cause she's dating my cousin.
- Well, he does have that sweet car.
- Yeah, it's a pretty sweet car.
- [Frank] Well, what have you
been up to since high school?
- School, partying, stuff, I guess.
I'm studying economics.
- Oh, so you're a beauty
with a brain, huh.
- Are you trying to flirt with me?
- [Frank] Yeah, kind of.
- Oh, so you're flirting
with the enemy, huh.
- Enemy?
- I'm sorry.
I guess I just thought you'd have
some sort of like gypsy curse over me
and my family or something.
- No, believe me, there's no
curse coming from this way.
- Shit.
Since when did you get so forgiving?
- God, I have no fucking clue.
- Well it's good to hear.
I hate people that sit around moping
about relationships months
after they've ended.
- Yeah, those people are crazy, right?
- Yeah.
Well, I'ma head home, Frank.
I have a nice Puerto Rican
fellow waiting for me.
- Whoa.
- Whoa, whoa, I am a free bitch, Frank.
I am a free bitch.
- [Frank] Um, maybe text me sometime.
- Uh, I don't have your number.
Maybe I'll see you at the next party.
- Maybe.
That's good to hear.
See ya later, Frank.
- [Frank] See ya.
(electronic dance music)
- You okay?
Do you need any water?
- No, I think I'm okay.
- Sure.
How do you feel?
- Kind of like the Grinch.
- What does that mean?
- You know in How the
Grinch Stole Christmas,
he gets the Christmas spirit,
so it zooms in on his tiny little heart
and then it grows three times its size,
that's how I feel right now.
- Oh, I'm glad.
- So what happens now?
- You just enjoy the comedown.
Eat some beef jerky.
- Why?
- I just think you'd really
enjoy some beef jerky.
- Sure, I guess.
- I'm gonna go dance for
a bit, you should join.
- Nah, I think I'm gonna relax here.
- Okay.
- Torrie.
(electronic dance music)
- Crazy.
Right?
- Holy moly.
- Shit.
I actually saw Melissa outside.
- Danny's cousin, Melissa?
- Yeah, the hot one.
- How's she doing?
- She looks good.
- What do you mean by good?
- I don't know man, like good.
- Looks like Alex is having a good time.
(electronic dance music)
- That's weird.
You know the time?
- What, it's 3:30?
- Fuck, time went super fast.
- So what, do you wanna
like get out of here?
- Kind of, I was thinking of getting
a drink before we head home.
- All right, sure, we'll do that.
- Are you sure you guys
are gonna head out?
- [Frank] Yeah, it's a bit late.
- You had fun though.
- Yeah, oh my god, so much fun.
- And Alex looks like he had
a really good time tonight.
- Oh, bro, I don't even know
what's going on right now.
- I don't know why we
haven't been hanging out
until lately, but I really miss you guys
and we should definitely
start hanging out more.
- [Frank] Yeah, let's do that.
Drive safe.
- So you still want that drink?
- Oh god no.
Alcohol does not seem like
a good idea right now.
- Yeah, I hear you.
- You know, man, like I
feel kind of different.
- How?
- I just spent so much time,
in the past seven months,
I've been so angry with Hailey.
I don't know, I feel like kind of lighter.
Happier maybe.
- That's good.
You should take that
into your everyday life.
- I guess I'm gonna try.
Fuck, I forgot I don't have a job.
- Go get it back.
- I guess that is what I'm
gonna have to do tomorrow.
I'm gonna go in the
morning and to Escalon,
beg and plead for my job back.
Man, I gotta do something
with my life, dude.
- Do you have any hidden talents?
- Nah, I'm pretty average.
- Well, I'm sure you'll find something.
- Hopefully.
Holy shit.
- What?
- It's Sid Murphy.
- Sid Murphy?
- [Frank] Sid Murphy is
an old friend of Alex.
They used to go to school together.
Guy has been living on the streets.
- Are you gonna say hi to him?
- I'm gonna go do something old
Frank would have never done.
- Sure.
- Hey, what is that you're
smoking in that pipe?
- Dog shit.
- You're Sid Murphy, aren't you?
- Yeah.
Who are you?
- I'm Frank, I'm actually
friends with Alex.
You guys went to high school together.
- Yeah, yeah, I haven't
seen that guy in ages.
- Yeah, well, he misses you man,
and we actually ran into
Tommy and Jimmy the other day.
They said you stole their shoes.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Like what happened, Sid?
I'm sure Alex would wanna know.
Like after high school
you just ended up here?
- By the way, welcome to my home.
I don't know man, I was just.
I was just smoking dog shit.
My parents couldn't get down with it.
They kicked me out.
- So you were smoking dog
shit before you were homeless?
- Yeah, I just I like
to get down, you know.
What, are you judging me?
- Kind of, it's like there's other drugs.
Dog shit isn't even a drug.
- You know it's like they say,
don't knock until you try it.
Don't not smoke it until you smoked it.
- [Frank] Well I'm not gonna smoke that.
- Dog shit's not just for
picking up and throwing away.
They're perfectly good resource.
It's like not using solar power.
We're just throwing that resource away.
If I could smoke solar energy, I would.
But I can't so I smoke dog shit.
Ha, they're like getting
that sweet steaming nug
from that dog's bum-bum.
God, you're just like hitting that pipe.
There's just nothing better.
- So you were just walking
down the street one day,
saw some dog shit, thought to yourself,
hey, I wonder if that gets you high.
- No, I just knew it would.
I don't know, there was like a,
they say it's like a sixth sense
but I call it my second sense.
It's number two.
And I just saw it and I was
like I gotta light that up.
I gotta put it in my lungs.
I'm gonna get it straight to my brain.
- [Frank] And it was
all downhill from there?
- I mean uphill, like
I've been living high.
- Well I wanna help you out, Sid.
I wanna see you in a better situation.
Can I give you some money?
- You don't have to do that.
- [Frank] I want to.
- Okay.
- Here's.
- [Sid] Hey, thanks man.
- Well you know what,
just take that money.
When you get up in the morning, go out,
buy some jeans, get a nice shirt.
You know, go out there
and try to get a job.
I'm pretty sure there has to
be something you could do.
- Now by jeans, did you
mean alcohol and ecstasy?
- No, no, I did not.
I meant shirt and jeans.
- Shrooms and whiskey.
- [Frank] Nope.
I hate your anatomy standing there.
- There's dog shit everywhere in my brain.
It sounds like you want
me to go out and buy it.
Malt liquor and crank.
- Ah, well you shouldn't.
I hope you don't, 'cause
I just gave you that money
and I can't ask for it back now.
- We'll see.
- [Frank] I hope you do the right thing.
- I hope the right thing
makes me feel great.
- I have faith.
You, you know, you're going places, Sid.
And I hope to see you again.
- I'll be right here or
getting high somewhere.
- [Frank] Well, I'll see you around.
- All right.
- That was a nice thing you did for him.
- Well I did it for Alex, you
know, they grew up together.
- But either way, I'm starting
to like the new Frank already.
- Yeah, I don't know what
the fuck is going on with me.
- So I gotta get on the F train.
- I know.
- But I had fun tonight and it looks like
you got more than just your balls back.
- Oh, I definitely did.
- Frank, listen, you know
you can talk to me, right?
I mean, I'm here.
I might not always be
here, but you can text me.
- Yeah, I'll do that.
- All right.
Um, I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
See you.
- See you.
("Grand Navy Plaza" by Silent Partner)
- Well, good morning.
- Alright, what are you up to?
- I'm gonna go try and get my job back.
- [Alex] Cool, cool.
- What are you up to?
- I don't know, I'm
watching Face the Death,
on Blu-ray right now.
I heard very good things about
it, so I checked that out.
- Yeah, sure, whatever.
I'll see you later.
- [Alex] All right, good luck.
- [Frank] Thanks.
- It's just one left,
please, just one left.
Fuck, he killed them, you fucking.
Wait.
Josh?
Josh, you fucking asshole.
I've been peeling lemons
for like two weeks, dude.
I thought you were gonna kill my family.
Oh, you fucking asshole, you owe me.
Fuck dude, that was fucking,
that's a good prank, I'll give him that.
I'll give him that.
Fuck.
Yo.
- Hey.
- Lemons don't mean shit to me now.
- Oh, that's good.
- Mm-hmm.
How you doing man?
What you doing here?
- I was wondering if we could like talk
about me getting the job back,
to be working here again.
I know I fucked up before
but I wanna have more responsibilities.
I could take a pay cut if necessary.
I just need, I think this is
the best place for me right now.
- Frank.
I kind of gave it to someone else man.
- [Frank] Already?
- Guy came in here.
He's fucking pretty bummy.
He smelled like shit.
And like, he just look
like he needed to work,
so like, you know, he helped
me peel some fucking lemons,
and then I gave him
flyers to hand them out.
He's doing a great job here man.
I can't get rid of him.
- Nah.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, I think, I think
I know what happened.
- But um, you know what?
I love you, man.
I respect you.
You can do fucking way better than this.
I believe in you.
Things are gonna fucking work out, man.
We're gonna fucking,
we're gonna get it right on the spot.
- Right on the spot.
Ah, well, yeah, don't
worry about it, it's okay.
I'll try to find something.
- [Escalon Boss] I believe you, man.
- All right.
- You're a good guy.
See you dude.
Fucking shit.
Fucking lemons man.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey man, Frank, right?
- Yeah.
- So you did it, you got the job.
- Yeah, yeah, there's this
phone shop down the street
that pay me to pass out flyers.
It's a good start, right?
- Yes, it's definitely a good start.
Um, I actually just had this job.
- Yeah, no kidding.
Where are you now?
- Jobless.
- [Sid] Huh.
- Don't have a job.
- You know I lost a job cumming
in the fry seasoning at McDonald's.
- [Frank] You lost it, you had it?
- I had the job and they fired me
because I just filled up the fry seasoning
with dried out cum.
So it was like a salted granular.
Anyways, hey, hey,
I had some leftover money from earlier.
- Oh, don't worry about it, keep it.
Buy some more stuff with it.
Buy some more jeans.
A man can never have too many jeans.
- Dad used to say that.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, then he left us.
- [Frank] Did he at least leave you jeans?
- No, just with a legacy of trannies.
Tranny block, that's what
we kids used to call it.
Anyways, but yeah, he,
he never bought me jeans
before, but you have.
- So I bought you more
jeans than your dad.
I'm like, I'm better
than your, I'm like dad.
- You're like, you're like new dad.
New dad, give me a hug.
I've been looking for you.
- [Frank] Well, yeah.
Yeah, new dad.
- Anyways, hey, do you have a dad?
- [Frank] Yeah.
- [Sid] You should give him a flyer.
You should give him two flyers.
- Yeah, next time I see him.
- On me.
- [Frank] I'll give it to him on you.
- Yeah, like the old days.
You know what, next time
you see Alex, say hi for me.
- Yeah.
- [Sid] And give him a flyer.
- All right, I live with him,
so we're just gonna have
these around the house.
- That's great.
You can give him probably
a couple other flyers.
I'll give you one for the other side too.
Hey, we should hang out.
You, and me, and Alex.
Mix it up.
Pass out some flyers.
- Do something.
- [Sid] You guys can come over.
We can empty out some condoms.
- Don't wanna do that.
- [Sid] Okay.
- Yeah.
- [Sid] Anyways, well I
need to get back to my job.
- Yeah, I'm gonna go back home.
- That's cute, rubbing it in.
- [Frank] Well, yeah.
I'm just gonna go home.
Not trying to rub it in.
- Yeah, just gonna go, just gonna go
masturbate into some couch cushions again.
- Yeah, 'cause I can.
- Yeah?
- [Frank] Yeah.
- Hey, when you're at home, sitting naked
on your couch in the
living room, masturbating,
why don't you take some pictures
and shoot a little video for me?
You can show me.
- I'm not gonna do that.
No.
- Yeah, but the next time we
hang out, you could show 'em.
- [Frank] No, that's weird.
Why would I do that?
- [Sid] You're the best.
- I'm not your new dad.
I am the best though.
I'll see you later.
- [Sid] Cool.
- Have fun with the new job.
- I will.
Have fun with the jerking off.
I'll be thinking about you.
- [Frank] Ah, okay.
- Morning.
What's up?
- Hey man, I wanted to come
over and talk a little bit.
- About last night?
I'm still kind of recovering.
- This is hard.
I've never I don't really do this a lot.
I wanted to apologize for last night.
- It's okay, I mean.
- No, it's not.
That's the thing, that it's not okay.
I've been such an asshole to you.
It's just you went to college
and I was just afraid of
like being my own person
and I blamed you for
it and I wasn't right,
and then the thing with Hailey happened.
And I'm just I don't know, I've just been
really upset past couple of years,
and I took it out on you, I'm sorry.
It was never your responsibility.
- It's okay.
I mean, things are getting
better and they're looking up.
- Yeah, maybe.
I've just felt like a piece of shit, man.
- Well, you might be a piece of shit,
but you're my piece of
shit, and I love you.
- I love you too.
- How'd that job thing go?
- Sid Murphy got it.
- That's funny.
You didn't need that place anyways.
You'll be fine.
- Thanks.
- I was gonna go on in and
watch the Wahlburgers marathon.
Do you wanna come?
- Nah, I think I'm gonna head
home, but some time soon.
- All right, I'll see you later.
- Yeah, see ya.
- How'd the whole try to
get your job back work out?
- It didn't.
He already gave the job away.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Sorry man.
- But you'll never guess who got it.
- I don't know, who?
- Fucking Sid Murphy.
- Really?
Get the fuck out of here.
That's, that's cool.
- Yeah, it's pretty, pretty cool.
- But it still leaves you jobless.
- Yeah, pretty jobless.
- Yeah, and do you have any
clue what you wanna do next?
- Nah.
- No ideas?
- Nope.
- Don't worry about it.
- Yeah.
- You'll be fine.
- Yeah, I should be okay.
It's not like it's the end of the world.
- Well, not that we know of.
- Yeah.
Uh, so what do you wanna do now?
- I don't know.
Wanna go to the movies?
- Yeah we do.
- All right, so let's go.
My treat with the jobless ass.
- [Frank] Thank you.
("The Flames" by Meth Dad)
♫ Woke up to the flames and fire
♫ A leap of faith to escape death
- We're just gonna do a documentary
about how this film is falling apart.
- [Woman] Shit, again.
- I'll sue Flubber Boy.
When I first heard of the
idea, it sounded cool.
Thought it'd be a little fun experiment
with Roberto, here, Carlos,
couple of friends from school.
Days go by as filming,
starts, you know, getting into action.
I don't know, maybe I just realized
that Roberto has no talent.
♫ Of the untold nightmare too
♫ We all wish we knew what happen
♫ We all wish we had a clue
♫ The flames they burn,
they burn much faster
♫ Than you ever think they could
♫ These half-ass walls, they have fallen
♫ Way before we wished they would
♫ I was scared as hell
♫ But you were all I felt
♫ As you jumped I fell
♫ I wish I didn't leave
♫ I wish I never crossed the sea
♫ I know it's not my fault
♫ I know it's no one's fault
♫ Woke up to the flames and fire
♫ A leap of faith to escape death
♫ Now death is one step closer
♫ So let us live this life that's left
♫ All of the others were the witness
♫ Of the untold nightmare too
♫ We all wish we knew what happen
♫ We all wish we had a clue
♫ The flames they burn,
they burn much faster
♫ Than you ever think they could
♫ These half-ass walls, they have fallen
♫ Way before we wished they would
♫ I was scared as hell
♫ But you were all I felt
♫ As you jumped I fell
♫ I wish I didn't leave
♫ I wish I never crossed the sea
♫ I know it's not my fault
♫ I know it's no one's fault
♫ I was scared as hell
♫ But you were all I felt
♫ As you jumped I fell