my name is Dylan hunt my story begins
the day on which I died
my last look at my world was to be from
inside a pressure chamber at NASA's
underground laboratory in Carlsbad
Caverns Department doreen only one of
them telephone support mystery output
nearly check telemetry William
marketability good thank you they'll let
you last chance Dylan I can still have a
girl waiting here to revive you I don't
think Nessa's ready for that method yet
I wish there were good luck see you
Tuesday
he not because you're ready
pressurizing our goal was the
development of a form of suspended
animation which would allow our
astronauts to make longer voyages
through our solar system it had been my
decision that our method was ready to
test on a human so it seemed that any
risk should be mine too I had guided the
basic research since being appointed
chief of the project on februari 14 1979
I arrived from Washington DC on the
newly completed underground sub shovel
perhaps my confidence in our experiment
dated from that trip
within five years of developing a
nuclear drilling device the sub shuttle
now bridged his first continent it
seemed to me that mankind's ingenuity
was capable of anything from out there
okay thanks for letting me watch
okay thank oh
hold that meeting as soon as I get back
yeah that's pretty impressive yeah at
least the war scare did some good they
finally recognized that surface and air
transports got them too vulnerable let's
hope that with the Chinese Alliance
working so well you people will soon be
out of a job I can't say that I mind
yeah looks like humanity's finally
growing up carlsbad six minutes arriving
carlsbad in six minutes
now writing Megan handless stand by
the Continental Defense Command in
Carlsbad Caverns had permitted NASA to
build our laboratory in a deep grotto
where constant temperatures were ideal
for our experiments by mid year we had
slowed the aging process and test
animals to the equivalent of less than
one day for every ten years of sleep our
problem in reviving the animals was
solved when we discovered a strong
relationship between the will to survive
and the need to reproduce after the
inevitable jokes are for the possibility
of male and female astronaut teams
massive injections of brains stimulants
were found to work as well by every
measurement when you love the experiment
should have gone perfectly what we did
not know was that a fault a flaw existed
in the rock strata directly over our
heads and that the slightest ground
tremor would be enough to dislodge it
please come on
when I press this here a small green
night went on inside Oh only a battery
power it had been developed bunny and
his rock slide occurred Primus the altar
free inside pressure must be holding the
door closed body must have been
preserved by some sort of gas in there
hey sir Ganymede project xenon pressure
chamber do you see mergency decompress
anywhere and emerging calm
try the donor
remarkable perfectly preserved he must
have been a handsome man
i miss the flesh is soft
you breathe so now you must get it out
of you good to get something to put him
on
he sees me
hmm
I think he's asking how many days he
believes that we are of his century Oh
Oh
who
he's wondering who we are a rockfall
buried this whole section of the caverns
they gave up looking for you a long time
ago
it is the year 21 33
20 133
no summer time every time of year to my
shop
to injure is intravenous to inject
inject an alien substance into his body
kini brain excited there is nothing like
that here
Oh
good morning
are you feeling better
oh hey Dave you asked the same question
each day don't you remember
do you remember being found this is a
year 21 21 33 good lord do you remember
how I cared for you 154 years what is
this place they call themselves packs
piece to fool others actually they're
descendants of the soldiers who made war
from here youtube same day you yeah not
packs he was promised not to give me
away I was sent here and pretended to
join them so that I can warn others who
packs might attack
this has effects much like the medicines
you called for going through your old
medical books I discovered how to make
their equivalent for mutated plants my
people youth so they put you in my care
mutated the bomb and we did have war
that was long ago it's only history now
that happened there are some new forms
of life but you'll find your not
interfere unless you fear me I'm a
mutant
we trained Ian's have two hearts greater
strength superior to humans in almost
every way
you don't say
as security Primus it is my duty to
voice my concern Isaac the men from the
past has been in Lyra a scare for 15
days now yes I have seen him daily and
each time I've seen him he's grown
stronger but everything she learns of us
and our world is from the lips of a
geranium from a fellow member of pax
even like many others she left her
people to Gareth freely Oh Isaac and
Noth means nothing to a mutant but Lyra
eyes only half mutant her mother was as
human as yours or mine Primus when she
lived in turanian my agents found no
evidence of humanity in her however we
owe her our gratitude the man from the
past is alive more than simply a man
from the past a scientist his brain
contains knowledge that would take the
world centuries to discover again all
the more reason they must be separated
the moment he no longer needs her care
Isaac I must regretfully support Primus
you'll often this we must remember her
people practice deceit as a virtue and
believe only by my excuse me fine line a
man from the past is out of his quarters
he's with Lyra our communications
equipment from the old military storage
room
deeper in the caverns they have armory
workshops gunsmiths I'll find a way
later to show you those good Lord and go
but a jelly and bread it's incredible
they've looted the whole world no one is
safe from them well they sure shall lot
of taste of what they steal
lyra when they were wheeling me here I'm
sure I remember hearing singing children
singing perhaps it was a dream you were
having no one sings here without being
ordered to
what is the power source your old
nuclear generators still operate
fortunately for the world packs doesn't
fully understand the principle sunlight
a whole new medicine
what beautiful than ever
look every way in or out of here is
watched constantly
if we're about the caverns here then
it's gone the highway the airport theres
a river now there are what else is gone
I mean how much did the bombs destroy
less than it was believed what happened
many years of fighting each side fear
the death bombs of the other too much
when they were finally used the
scientists revolted didn't last we did
show some guts hmm but the ancestors of
pax men took power many scientists were
killed as traitors your teachers and
technicians tried to save them in a
great frenzy of killing again without
scientists and teachers who machines
began to rust and began to fight for
water and food your great technology had
been too too complex too fragile
without oil the wheels stop without
wheels the factories stopped without
factories food transport studs earth
isn't finished Dylan it's only different
in some ways perhaps even better oh I
was hoping to welcome you to our century
in a different fashion Dylan hunt I am
Primus Cambridge who found you and this
is prime miss youla is pax security
chief there are told me I've been
needing you all pax is grateful for the
care she has given you but unfortunately
now she has other duties equally
pressing I must respect Primus you
laughs authority we have so many
questions to ask you the first question
must be what dr r has told your facts by
is there something I'm not supposed to
know we are naturally concerned with the
knowledge you carry your not unlike a
death bomb yourself the power of your
knowledge could have great value but it
could also destroy us all we hope you
will use it in our cause once you
understand us fully
I think you'll find him a fairly quick
study
I'm Harper's mine I have been assigned
either oz duty that's a tall order
there is a girl under that what
importance is that with the shape of my
liver or pancreas interest you perhaps I
hate surprises I know why you ask that
because all the people in your century
were ruled by lust I thought you were
taking over my nurses duties there are
always tough to be in you are a
scientist and yet you do not understand
that must destroyed your world that is
an interesting theory it is a fact most
of your world's problems were caused by
aggression between male and female your
own st. Freud wardrobe at st. Sigmund
Freud a witness which kept even your
leaders from clear thought and wisdom
thus in the end it was animal lust that
caused your civilization to fall it's
just how many of you people feel this
way great part of taxes of the unisex
persuasion outside of course primitives
and barbarians continuing the same old
errors well I'm saying Kevin I'm safe
here
good night oh that better
neither is injured you loft now suspects
why I'm here I must leave can you get us
both out of you if you're willing to
risk it I was hoping you'd say what are
we going to the freest most beautiful
place on earth if you wish my city
terranea rule
what are you doing it only fires the
dart which causes unconsciousness so
they did go on to cover the world yeah
so sup shuttle is taxes greatest weapons
from here the team can go anywhere
attacking and murdering get in here I'll
get clearance for hurry
things sure puts you away this is the
pact sword art they hit you in
little hypo
this doesn't make them seem very
bloodthirsty it's only because they
wanted you alive I've said it to start
for an old maintenance station orbit is
the closest the suck shuttle comes to
terranea from here we travel above
ground
can't fax traced this car to hear no I'm
sending it on exciting
extra horses and pack us some food yes
mr.
villain rest while you can need your
strength
eat this we have a long ride
one of you bring me my riding clothes
were they they breed our horses their
ancestors live in the city which was
destroyed here you called the region
Arizona
it's called the position of respect
which also makes it much more difficult
them to put a lance in our backs you
have much to learn about earth as it is
now Dylan hunt
don't be afraid it's all right
the fortress now controlled by warlord
so I beerus has been given a second
chance in disguise
video water fish what else much more my
century has many surprises for you
turanians nuclear generator plan where's
your city well over days ride yeah we're
not as fortunate as packs it's beginning
to fail perhaps the distance to our city
makes it weaker do you understand such
things ah more likely the nuclear core
elements need rearranging killin
kyrenia lovely
you
you must have been gone a long time and
yet no one is surprised to see you we
would consider that undignified who are
they they're called our helper where do
they come from some of them from far
away it's considered an honor to be here
these are supplicants who have come here
hoping to be accepted as helpers the two
are Carolinian scholars you'd do well to
avoid the woman's country Dillon males
are tolerated they are only as pets
the stim my people believe it confers
dignity this is my guest Dylan hunt he
used to be treated as a Tyrannian Astrid
will show you to your quarters I must
prepare a proper welcome for you
it was quite simple to win the trust of
most of them and I could soon go where I
wished but when the man from the past
was discovered I realized this to be of
even greater importance than my study of
their sub shuttle system this human
could also be a clever trick a spy
planted here no I saw him found he's a
scientist of Old Earth with a knowledge
of machines that fly of old weapons and
of nuclear fusion I will require more
time to win his full loyalty as a mere
human he is of course ruled by his
emotions and superstitions then he must
be trained as with all humans I am
certain he will help us freely if he
feels at ease among us I asked that all
inter aenea must be commanded to help me
convince him of our friendship agreed
but we must soon see evidence that he's
willing to serve us if not he's to be
placed in training school
don't let a stupid Astrid she's done
very well show is served food now
mistress yes I'm starving get me my robe
please dilim sit down I'll be with you
in a moment take my hair down Astrid
if you don't see a delicacy would might
just ask and they'll get it Lloyd
you see our nuclear generator plant
grows weaker almost with each day
repairing it or when you Walter ainias
friendship
I continues to trouble you Dylan but
they serve us so well it's their damned
eagerness to please they love us just as
an animal pet returns love given it
their human's Lyra are Astrid are you
happy here happy master I was ill and
starving until I came here they're
fortunate humans Dylan and they
recognized
you
you can I
by my SIA max will you keep silent
i'm doctor tell him pax and this is
saying team communications and you at
the payment man from the past were
swallowed every lie that his first
mutant tried on him we've heard that you
repairing their nuclear generator
tomorrow why it is there some objection
to their City having a reliable power
supply to have you not seen this is evil
place it was a few doubts that brought
me out looking around tonight but I'm
not exactly in love with your auntie
leader so it is true what she told that
Thompson she used your illness to keep
you secluded you saw practically nothing
of pax pax was founded by people alive
in your time people who revolted against
the great conflict they took over the
caverns to preserve the books music and
art and and decent ideals for when the
world might try to rebuild again and why
the secret teams of agents everywhere
are you asking me to believe you are
here in trading good books and culture
from show you why this team is here
oh those are new helpers recently
captured this is what one acts team is
doing two of us have already died
planning a rebellion if necessary all a
sweet we can save them and several
thousands like them
here's why these new england fishermen
take alka seltzer plus coal model you
will find it profitless to lie to us
human will you repair our nuclear
generator yes or no now you listen to me
I came into your century ill and that's
been used against me very cleverly but
I'm not sick now and I'm getting tired
of being pushed around you don't
understand what this means tell them
you'll join us gladly and I've had the
last advice I one from you Florence
Nightingale training is decree
human welcome to the ranks of the
helpless
we'll take the position of respect and
express gratitude it'll be a cold day in
hell when I kneel at your feet
that was the lightest pain setting there
are eight higher you will take the
position of respect
hi
the position of respect human usual I
had to use the seventh settings the next
moment should be even more effective
see the stem is capable of pleasure or
do you prefer the final level of pain
wha
no doc your student what's happening
here get the setup get hold of him take
this ass 25 how does your wife do people
keep popping out of the woodwork don't
you
it's tim thing what is that I'm from
your time it uses Sonics wavelengths
that stimulate the brains pain and
pleasure centers we invented that oh
yeah it was used to control troops and
civilian populations oh really schools
just play that you will never be inside
one teachers back to training school
quickly do whatever we ask
stronger with us
is this the human from the past yes
basta arnon I will exchange you three
female students for him he interests me
master i love you i love terrain here I
thank you for taking me in as a help
done mercy on us you said that yesterday
up y'all
shall the new student how cooperative
really gummy but yeah tell me tell me
how else to please please help replace a
helper duty to find ways you must
constantly be thinking of ways you'll
find this interesting him no physical
injury you can't die
but you will risk
Master
hmm I didn't storage area the others are
waiting there
well it isn't miss Harper smileth you
had to wear a skirt more often well then
the devil are you doing here we were
sent here to take away Collins wissen
also but he was killed in a blight in
ambush this morning Collins good man
good team leader we were sent here to
tell you to forget the revolt to use all
your efforts to find Dylan hunt and get
him safely away from you forget human
slaves they can't order that two of us
have already given our lives to get us
this close to the default and now
columns Oh close we are ready just as
soon as we can locate where the mutants
store their sins then I'm not going
anywhere gentlemen the turanians getting
a dose of their own stims I don't want
to see that listen to me Dylan hunt if
packs orders us to forget the revolt and
get you out of here then that's the way
it will be X doesn't only duck please a
revolt is not possible now there are saw
me crossing there more this morning and
I'm sure she recognized me
a glimpse of her but I'm certain it was
a female on you at pats engine either
with a pax team or joining one here any
helper who finds them will be rewarded
for the maid and a leap of still sent
for pleasure you'll have them before
dark business but six months ago i was
using this very same circuit am I
talking about a hundred and fifty-four
years ago thanks has good communications
equipment from your century Dylan Kevin
storage was ideal for electronics
sundown in three hours hurry all right
then it's time to leave doctor if you'll
just give me a few more minutes with
this equipment i'll have it ready do we
need this time to get through the
tunnels you're coming sing tells me you
were a white Comanche warrior isaia a
leader of your tribe but I am up packs
now and sworn to obey did you swear to
forget everything you know about tactics
about warfare the turanians will be
watching every exit they know your team
is here and you know how badly they want
me we need the revolt as a diversion we
must leave
now look I never met anyone in my life I
wanted to fight less than him but I
promise you I will that's how strongly I
feel about this Dylan the antenna is
directional now
now the other receiver can be adjusted
in exactly the same way with enough
students toured together we'll pick up a
signal from 30 or 40 meters away are you
certain of all this yes
you there what's that you've got there
helper he brings me an ancient device I
wish to study
admit of your century acknowledge debts
Dylan I saved your life twice now you
also lied to me about pax what do you
want from me this time perhaps my human
half doesn't want you broken in training
what is the Turanian F want I need the
status here that you cost me repair our
nuclear generator
unwatched and I'll help you escape
afterwards Lyra aah this device says you
lie do you think I'm a fool that's one
of the old radios used by packs but it
has other uses your century hasn't
learned I'll prove it to you tell me
your name here are of course no signal
you spoke the truth do you love terranea
yes do you love me Lyra don't be a fool
it mistakes are a small interest
but I'm incapable of feeling love is you
understand it
good
I don't know but I can't love you
I'd be human then I the weak and foolish
like them that's why I'm superior I know
self-interest is the natural order of
life
I own welfare much
it's much stronger now
must be a pressure plate somewhere
we don't have time to look for it
perhaps two pivots looks like it opens
along here I sire if you're as strong as
you look get a grip here
I'll go faster
understand joke number the mutants ten
to one you can be breathe here take it
Oh
something's got them running turanians
there between us and the old Phoenix
station Dillon is there another one at
leaves only the maintenance station
where in Lyra I brought you in very bad
turanians knows that well
frisky they know you came in this way
there's not feel good there's way down
from side
hurry I thought
Oh
inside
I can save your light a third time if I
can talk to you privately dealing
optional doors closed that don't control
saket it's kissing see if you can force
the doors I've gotta hear what she has
to say don't mr. Dillon don't believe
her know what will happen to them if
they're caught what do you want the
power station or this time my people
will destroy me to get all right
beginning together
with this your film is can escape great
you're close the door
why do I thank you now
as we know six days ago the man from the
past unfortunately agreed to repair the
terranea nuclear generator but he agreed
to help them in order to save the lives
of the team who rescued him because of
this Dominic was asked to immediately
dispatch a second team to the area Fran
I have just received a report from that
team I'm afraid it's much worse than was
feared they've discovered a missile site
which with full generator power they
will be able to use against us
these missiles are capable of carrying a
bomb designed to penetrate and destroy
soldiers who once fought from here we
have a few weeks perhaps before they
learn to use them no more
for you mean I have a math to
investigate we must make immediate plans
to get all our people to safety what is
coming from the two Sounion station but
very erratic
it'll never stop at that speed they're
just stuff
I wondered if it could be you thanks for
self in their thing the fact you are
safe pleases us promise you do know what
I did we've had a complete report Primus
Cambridge and the cows you are most
anxious to meet with you please get in
all the way let me show you our backs
you haven't seen yet
our young are breaking away from the
older unisex beliefs would it surprise
you to know that taxes turns security
primers approves
it was our dream to preserve the best
from the past let the worst be forgotten
there's so much more our new form of
gymnastics ballet artists who paint with
light Newport the libraries the
paintings the ideals you people
represent i'm very happy i had a chance
to save it save it by using the warhead
i found there when i realized they were
studying it you said you had a full
report didn't you central see the flash
this evening
Primus I set a nuclear warhead on a
delayed fuse it should have lit up the
whole sky % nurse reported nothing
that's impossible I thought you were
showing me all this are you what we have
to lose the mutants needed their
generator repaired not further city but
for an old missile site they have
discovered but that's exactly what I'm
talking about it should've blown can we
check with your sentinels
nothing I can't believe it I don't
understand what could have gone wrong
I'm going back you escaped or them twice
before capturing time save what you have
here it's my only link with my world
we're all very pleased you're safe but
also very frightened Primus I've got to
go back gosh you're trying to set off
the war here that they have generator
but something went wrong your only
chance now is if I can blow up that
missile silo I'll need a tea first you
must understand a few things about banks
Vera I uh she said she was going back to
the city if she was being honest with me
she's safe come on huh
good question we must ask you did you
take lives a couple of technicians
certainly more if they were there
hooking power to the silos there were
thousands of lives at stake right here
trade one life for a thousand could we
justify a hundred for more perhaps
10,000 for still more that same
reasoning we destroyed your world Dylan
hunt I've just saved everything you
fought over a hundred and fifty years
for you join us Dylan hunt I swear to
give your life or any of our lives
rather than take another well I'm not
sure I've got that kind of guts premise
we all must this time forgive me Prime I
we heard there were so many stars
visible tonight and my little brother
yes yes beautiful they should be enjoyed
you
it's just the wind
it's all open mind it's all over
all right only the best of the past let
hope I'm up to it
how are you as a guy drop person i'd i'd
like to see more of facts now do you
like children's outcomes why is it Ozil
i was going course not Eddie that you've
got a great pancreas
Oh
you