she's alive incredible
you
human alright thanks ed how about the
brain reserved under those conditions
now that's got it look he's coming out
of torpor hello my name is EDA you have
a name after all this time she's not
likely to remember but I think I can
restore most you'll be keeping her then
yeah I think so here eita huh Thank You
Kelly how do you feel today galley have
you adapted to your new body yet yes mr.
GaN wonderful zan was about so freely
well it was the best fiber doctor in
town you know now I wouldn't go that far
megelli wandering off by yourself can be
dangerous especially at night with that
killer stalking young girls for their
brains and that's not even mentioning
the spine zzzz that's the fact where did
it move thanks iris you see with cyborg
technology most body parts can be
replaced with synthetics everything
except the human spine and that means
that there's a thriving black market of
ruthless organ brokers who will take the
back from under your shirt hey Doc huh
this is giving me more trouble than I
expected I'll come back and finish it
tomorrow well thanks for trying would
you like something to drink before you
go you go bad no thanks I've still got
another 30 houses or so to hit today
well see you tomorrow bye courteous and
hard-working rare qualities in a young
man these days am i right ito mm-hmm yes
sadly true
[Music]
not a little chips of neighbor this go
don't worry I'm not at the point of
starvation yet you can pay me when you
get the fun good mining either oh good
morning Delhi what happened here on this
guy guess I must a trip
can't you see I'm we're gonna do it
doing something up here all right hey
you live here with the dark don't you
that's right ringing Dalli Dalli fragile
pretty strange names I just um I think
it's a pretty name you're right it suits
you by the way my name is you now isn't
it huh you knew it already mm-hmm you
got huh he has a family here nope that
you can make a living all by yourself
you think so that's impressive wait oh
come on i'm talking about solemn of
course hey why don't you come with me to
wear to a better place come on hey Doc I
got it working now come on homie
it's off this way oh my god here take my
hand you may toe it felt like you wait a
son they had your strong dude yeah
really I think the view is all them from
here is just the greatest sometimes I
keep staring at it I can feel it calling
to my soul what kind of people live
there i want my brother wanted to go to
zalem once he even broke the law and
built an illegal airship as for me I'll
just make lots and lots of money until
finally i can go there myself
hmm just why are you looking at me so
look on your face is more interesting
than zone must be real I mean look at
this place what a disgusting cesspool of
humanity it's nothing but the dumping
grounds for zelim you know these people
are nothing but vultures feeding on the
trash and carrion that falls from the
sky you really don't understand anything
do you are you from the Outlands or
something I really don't know I have no
memory no past even my name galley is
something made up I see but in a way
it's not so bad not having a pash means
that you've got no memories to haunt you
a clean slate for your soul but why
should win why do you want to go back to
zalem so badly I have to there are
things that I didn't get a chance to
finish now wait a second do you really
think you can manage it why else would I
be in scrap iron city the only work for
someone of my skill in this dump is
repairing crippled cyborg so what's
wrong with fixing cyborg it's a crime
squandering a talent like yours in this
backwater you know you could do much
better up in xela does it amuse you to
play fallen angels these insects an
angel of mercy you know you have no idea
how low you've fallen yours albums fine
it's the best cybernetics doctor ever I
don't understand where is your pride my
pride is not a problem what has become
of yours shahram I'm not going to spend
the rest of my life here I'll find a way
back to zalem somehow I'll claw my way
back with my bare hands if I have to
I'll do whatever it takes Shirin I know
it's no longer my business but if your
former partner please press me on this
you mustn't get involved with the
factory you know this is the last time
I'll ask will you help me return no I
see I'm sorry
[Music]
he's done it another victory for the
rookie with the disappearance of the
great Karissa he is inarguably the new
champion unbeatable
[Music]
I'm a hunter warrior oh right random
raised a ring even if they belong to a
man but if you wait i'll chop them up
ha
yummy
[Music]
you
Garrett are you all right is your body
damage tally yeah I'm fine does moo shu
me very impressive I didn't know you
could find my body move by itself that's
a great call it inside me and I can't
believe it you say your bounty is
100,000 chip of course this part where
does it work 10 times that ring eating
mutants are bad for business so are you
in the market for some new body parts
today
I need to find out eventually and what
they call a hunter warrior he once there
was something called the police his
purpose was to prevent crime these days
factor ages for the bounty on had one in
criminals and less hunter warriors like
me
[Music]
what's wrong galley
I want to don't be stupid you don't know
what you're saying I didn't give you
limbs to do things like this you don't
have to work all you have to do is be
beautiful if you want money I can this
isn't about money this is nothing for me
this is for you yes tonight I felt
something new like I was really alive
for the first time you don't know what
you're saying I don't want to sailing
your perfect hands with blood
and you'll really get me too darlin I
said so didn't I really enough don't
worry your pretty head about it your job
is to upgrade the gladiators for the
Colosseum how soon you go to zalem will
be determined by the quality of your
work and the size of my topic dr.
Ianelli my whole body is on fire you're
not the pampered star of the Colosseum
anymore why should I work on a
brain-eating junkie with a price on his
head Roger ito and where did he get a
little cyber bitch
[Applause]
sorry absolutely right you're not my
totally life is your own but why the
hunter visit some demon hidden in your
empty memory using the laser we will now
improve your registration number on your
brain tissue clink OH still great swing
fingerprints voice prints and retina
patterns can be changed can you think of
a better way to tell one side board from
another group starting the procedures
now
[Music]
to cause this much damage but the single
impact would require an unbelievable
amount of power only ito could
accomplish such a feat the risk I'll not
only rebuild I'll make you more than a
match for itõs little toy I'll use
every skill and dirty trick I know
sounds pretty completed that was
personal yes because the hard part is
the job is done oh I really like the
official answer to that is no comment
I just registered myself as a hunter
warrior glorious victory for the record
was where are we going uh hunters hang
up I'll need to introduce you
it's from the tubes that connect the
factory with solemn officially it's
caused by the new title pole give me
your son come to pay you back
hahahahahahahaha baby are you ready to
play with me Callie someone give us a
hand are you going to run away I accept
daddy what a good trim don't tell me you
rebuilt X monster mutt with a bounty on
his head but still I can't help but
wonder which one will win suffer ito I
want to see your face when your little
toy is broken but such elephant pain
belongs on a more suitable stage when a
broken steel and iron
what up buddy ladies la-dee-da
now let's really get
[Music]
selling your Conner's rookies you just
say with some down
[Applause]
Wow
Callie did it yeah I lost again ito
nothing I do seems to have any effect at
all garbage you're in solid cast off
scrap someday I'll get back to Solomon
and I'll be the one looking down Ben yo
I swear that I'll make you look up to me
kelly your powers and abilities are
still growing which is fine I know what
you're worried about that you have to
trust me from this point forward no
matter how much I seem to change your
gallery he don't always see your gallery
I believe you you can only be
we got it look yeah I hear ya so boys
how's business hmm mr. vector you didn't
have to kill him if you keep leaving
live witnesses if you won't last long
come I want to talk with you
[Music]
you go who knows where that young fools
gone off to I know that's right the way
he talks about going to Solomon visors
of credits if he's funny in the head all
right he really thinks solemn I let him
in what a little fool now what was it I
told you three years ago give me 10
million chips and I'll make sure you get
to zalem yes sir normally it would take
a lifetime to acquire that kind of
capital put you you want to do it in
three years I must say I'm proud that
difficult you've got a lot of untapped
potential whore I'm not that special
here try this it's the real thing
straight off the tube for solemn not
that junk they send us oh just a piece
their essence of lolla you go I don't
have to tell you this but most of the
goods collected refined and packaged
here in scrap iron city just get
exported to zalem through the factory to
the crap we get to keep for ourselves is
just that now seeing as I'm in a
position to oversee those exports why
shouldn't i share in the benefit say you
go why don't you join my operation but I
want I want to go solemn follow you out
of your mind do you really want to be
homeless and friendless in a place like
solemn trust me you wouldn't like it on
the other hand by helping me deliver my
shipments to zalem you could achieve
real wealth and two are you could live
in the lap of luxury just like the
citizens of solemn think it over you go
what do they make you drink you and the
color I don't care who you are if you've
hurt you go you answer to me you go I'll
be waiting for your answer canyon there
you go Oh some water see what happens
when you drink I'm not a kid and it was
only one drink you're not acting like
yourself what happened just what are you
doing here anyway uh well um I just
really wanted to see who I guess I don't
know y le do you have a secret dream
though I'm not just a fantasy of wealth
and power to me I want to see what's
like up there so high and far away do
you fear they'll be sites I've never
seen waiting for me wonders I can't even
imagine that's what I want
[Music]
look up look up Grisha gears with high
grade oil and Teflon events lose jobs in
town I'll take a squeeze that kid thank
you sir
hey kid oh hey so that's your little
game is it right your hands on my fine
no luck now let's take a look at your
place the master you go quick thinking
little bastard but I'll bet there's
already a price on your head you go oh
you go with you what trouble under
warrior disguised as a customer he
killed Dungey and he knows my name calm
down it over nothing you can do now will
make any difference don't you bring all
the money you save to my office you mean
you'll send me to zalem Java hmm look
we'll talk about that when you get here
you go you don't have much time Oh
30 ng o Ricky's no head damn I guess
it's time to rebuild the Ricky again dr.
Sharon that's your department why should
I even bother I've used everything all
my tricks and techniques I can't win
what was that so when am I going to go
to zalem hey take a look at the number
of bounties this get is collected her
name's galley this could be a hot ticket
a female gladiator hey wait a minute
this is the girl from you goes play
itõs Kelly hmm you mean you know her oh
it's like that is it now wait a second
you want galley to fight in the Coliseum
absolutely it'll be a smash we could
call her the battle angel you don't
really think galley will fight for you
of course she will she'll do anything I
asked to keep her boyfriend from losing
his head doctor I want you to find
Dahlia why should I do this for me
picnic and then i'll send you to zalem
14 bodies in seven days what was a
sudden mercenary veal galley when you
became a hunter warrior you said it
wasn't for the money that was before I'm
saving so I can go to zalem with you
girl who dies who said that you could go
to zalem
and he told him how you see you know and
how did you go feel about you well it is
amazing it's just now believe it
bouncing animalism numbers nor a google
wanted for spine theft and murder bounty
80,000 he repeats number seven hugo
wanted for spine theft and murder
Wow
record him to the factory as soon as II
cited
or 68 69 million five hundred thousand
ships just a few more Kelly I'm not
going I'll sneak back into town back to
mr. vectors place I'm not going to give
up on Dom it's crazy looking for you
don't you understand going two thousand
more than just an escape from this scrap
metal present for me it's a war a war
between me and this garbage heap no
matter how insignificant i maybe I still
have my dream my pride I won't let his
corroded metal monster throwing me into
the dark I'll be leaving as soon as it
gets dark go home before you get
involved any further by
you go listen not to do that and I have
to know how you feel about me why are
you bringing up something stupid like
this now go home galley so now we're
partners in crime early
my mouth is tingling it's like I get the
battery it's the lightning I'm Dave like
this my body pics and recharge i blended
about the car any event the scar it's
sort of a keepsake of my brother Pete
week I used to have a brother might
older than myself he had a wife my
sister-in-law and they raised me
together the two of them cared for me is
if they were really my own parents we
had a good life together my brother was
an engineer for the factory and he
enjoyed his work and my sister-in-law
was loving and generous but it wasn't
enough for my brother he'd look up at
solemn yearnings I want to go to zalem
someday he must have said that a million
times finally he acted he could get to
zalem he decided by balloon the factory
of course had prohibited the creation of
any kind of flying machine and put a
heavy bounty on the head of anyone who
built one my brother knew what the
consequences could be but he followed
his heart anyway when I was ten years
old the airship was completed but on
that very nice the hunter warrior king
my sister-in-law I betrayed my brother
reporting in to the factory my haven't
assistant I don't know suppose she must
be living somewhere with someone I think
I know what used to store my life at the
series I think hitless to my lover was
obsessed with something I couldn't
understand you're scaring me first I
think I'd go along with it but after
he's so long that might come to believe
that he'd even read me if I couldn't
have him myself and hating him killing
it I'd be easy but that's kind of
drastic what I suppose you'd have to
kill me to keep me away from solid what
am I disease should I kill you freeze
how much more do you need to get
developme of about five hundred thousand
ships okay i'll take you to vector what
could not taking my eyes off someone
who's so important to me but joey is
hitting some tips myself it should be
about 600,000 go to zalem with it and
then if everything goes right see if I
can have to follow you oh right don't
worry go gather your chips
ah there you are too little too late ya
li you beat me to every kill since
Russia but this time the head and a
bounty belong to me just like his
brother oh so that's the way it is don't
you know there's no room by things like
love or mercy and a hundred code if you
want him so badly come and take him I'd
rather have your head anyway prepare
yourself all right this will stop your
flitting about
[Music]
hahahaha do you really think this death
forever can delay me forever
[Music]
Callie ito if you go for me
don't worry galley the operation was a
success well the reason he lived was
because of you Kelly if you hadn't
bypassed your own life-support system
feeding your blood into his arteries his
brain would have died of oxygen
starvation that was really quick then I
was the one who did the bypass it was
Shimon sure lemme so she's the one what
you goes dead yes killed by a hunter and
then struck by lightning well there goes
bad meal ticket what about galley I have
no clue as to her current whereabouts
scrap iron city is a big place it may
take me quite a while to find her you
know what I'm leave hey wait a minute I
think it's time to send you to za it's
not possible for someone from Iron City
to go to zalem I ought to know gali the
brand of my forehead means that I was
once a citizen assalam it's all
[Music]
got it get out there and find you go
what who and the hell are you so you're
the one who died there you go assuming
that solemn thing hey it's not my fault
if someone's an easy mark and you need
the money so badly all right then right
jack you go to split into mine because
of you go ruined his life stealing money
for line why why why you what have you
done with Serena over there blah my god
organ replacements this mr. Riddick the
order comes down from solemn every month
I don't know what they do
[Music]
I'm coming wait for me solemn I'll be
with you soon
you
you can a boy come through here they
just climbed out all to do this is a
restricted area please keep out
what's that ring for its the defense
ring I can't score just another vermin
volim Johnson periodically to keep rats
from climbing the zoo
[Music]
yeah it's olive I'm almost there huh
galley go let's go home forget it I'm
never going back to that filthy garbage
heap solemn is my destiny until this
moment my life was a cosmic joke my
entire existence pointless and
unnecessary oh there's my delight
described by insidious solemn don't you
know your mind he could dream you go we
can find a way began a new life we could
[Music]
Oh
you
[Music]
Oh
you