Hello Vikash
Hi Karan
What is your plan for tomorrow?
Nothing Special. tell me, did you make any?
yes, tomorrow i am throwing party at home
when to come?
Come at evening
Dad going to Pune on tomorrow morning
I will come and do you have something special?
yes, i have. Wahid had new DVD "Big Bang"
Film looking very sexy. It is in HD format
Who is in film?
Mia Khalifa
Don't have Sunny Leone's DVD?
ohh.. Sunny leone's DVDs are old now
We watched every film about ten times
Thought, let's watch something new
Now she is most popular in market
ok. and are Monti and Neuton also coming?
yes, i am going to invite both of them
ok. See you tomorrow
and listen, bring few packets of cigarettes with you
okay, I will. and tell monti to bring beer bottles
yes, I will tell him
Now I hang up phone to call both of them
ok dude, bye
Let's meet tomorrow
bye
Hello Monti
Speak Rascal
Tomorrow i am throwing party at home
Is your dad going out?
yes. and listen, It is your duty to bring some beer bottles
No Way. I will not even touch any beer bottle
Godman told me to Stay away from hazardous items made by glass
you fucker. Godman didn't told you to stop drinking? Freeloader
when you get them free, you drink 3 bottles simultaneously
Now saying, you will not bring any bottle
Try to understand my friend
don't make excuses. Vikash brought last time
Now it is your turn
it is on you if you don't want to drink
OK, I will bring it. anything else?
Nothing more
ok dude, bye
ok, bye
from morning to evening, you stick with TV and Mobile.
what will be your future?
Dad, you started just arriving at home
what should I do else? look to sharmaji's son
he is of your age but always comes top in college exams
Mukesh ambani(Bill Gates) is also of your age, he comes top in earning
but you are still stuck here
You worthless, shameless
arguing unapologetically
Please dad
then don't compare me with anyone
I will be what I am
Well done son
Father have to do hard work at this age
and my prince seating useless all day
Dad, I was studying for hours
Fool, don't tell me lie
if you was studying
then you never get such low marks
everyday i received your complaint from school
they complain, your child is very weak in study
I have to give lot of donation to admit you in good collage
thought, you will improve your behavior
But the result is zero
i feel stressful
how will you manage if something happen with me
last warning for you
if you not be able to do well in collage
then I will force you to join my business
DAD, till my study complete
I will not do anything
KARAN
son has been spoiled because of so much affection
never listen and talk to me rudely
I am very much worried about his future
please, calm down Sir
Karan is in his adolescence and immature
let him grow first
and he will understand you very well
when will he mature?
I disturb every time thinking about his future
If his mother kosaliya is alive today
I don't need to worry about anything
but now no one is here to let him understand things better
you know my situation very well
Sir
please don't take any kind of tension
I am here
I will talk to him
Dear karan
are you angry on your dad?
Dear, you must try to understand your dad
He scold me every time
so what
He love you too much
and He is very much concern about you
He will
you must behave first
Give proper respect to your father
don't give any chance for complain
Will you follow my rules?
yes
Good
I will talk to your father for you
OK
Take Care and enjoy your life
Sir,
Please, Stop worrying anything
karan is very much intelligent boy
I explained him everything
Now please stop worrying
and take care about your health
Child is stepping in adolescent age
Let him live his life as he wish
so who is stopping him to live free life?
I know one day he will make big name
just need to leave his childish behavior
Don't worry
One day, karan will sure make you proud
you are such a famous businessman
one day, he will sure be a famous personality like you
WTF
I will be a Plumber after grow up
I will too be a Pizza delivery boy after grow
How much golden chances they are getting
everyday, a new undressed beautiful girl waiting for them
I will become porn-star after shifting in USA
after then will get new sexy girls everyday like sunny leone
just need to complete my 21 years
My life will be heaven after then
free to do everything
psycho, mend your ways
this is just a porn film
whatever showing in it is not real
Never do these things in real life
or you will get two tight slaps
just shut up
We are flying in fantasy land
let us fly
If you don't like to fly
then Fuck yourself with the stinky books
(laugh...)
You have all the fun
No one is in your house to say anything
I am living a pathetic life
just leave this talk
My dad is most dangerous
this is story of all
parents are like coconut
hard from shell, soft inside
just leave this talk
leave what?
Monti is correct
you are very lucky
your father left whole house trusting you
you can start with your girlfriend whenever you want
never friend
don't think to make any girlfriend now
bitches are so much arrogant
she will apart you from your friends
and also transform you to like her pet dog
exactly
I too got a girlfriend
the witch make my life hell
every time there was questions list
where you go? what you eat? what you drink?
with whom you are?
and she was so much demanding
that when I started ignoring her
the bitch run away with someone else
NO GIRLFRIEND, NO TENSION
enjoy your life with your friends
watch films
and whenever you want satisfy yourself by hand
our hand is worth then bitches attitudes
Stop your nonsense
do you have any experience of girlfriend
watch your face in mirror
forget girl even eunuch will reject you
fucker, leave it
do you think yourself smart as salman's father(brad pitt)?
whole world knows arrogance of girls
and once you will get a girlfriend
you will know everything
I already have girlfriend
and my thinking is not like you
No girls means No life
I am soon going to propose her
and will take her in corner and will do thakathak(fuck)
friend, be little careful while proposing
or thakathak(fuck) will happen on your face instead on your dick
don't worry about me
my life is set
Great friend,
his life is set
so I will drink one more bottle on this happy occasion
rush to your girlfriend and propose her
or someone else will fly with her
(laughing...)
Hi item(Sexy), listen..
Dog, what you want?
why are you showing such arrogance?
ok, speak what you want
I am mad in your love
I love you darling
WHAT?
I LOVE YOU
shut up and get out from here
you looks so beautiful in anger
anything else?
and.. from morning to evening
I imagine only you
hmmm... and?
and.. I want to marry you
and?
and... I want to give you French kiss
and I want to do thakathak(fuck) with you
and let you pregnant and make mother of my children
dad
Dad, it is paining hard
it is paining hard
oh.. how much paining to my son
now see, how I will teach lesion to the spoil boys
by calling to their home
if I will not be able to teach them lesson,
I will change my name from thakur chail singh
(phone ring..)
karan, give me my phone
KARAN
how much time you take in bathing...
come on my leone
just come out by breaking my mobile
just once
just come one time
Hello
are you karan's father?
yes, speak
I am vikash's father thakur chailsingh
I have complain about your son
what happened?
your son is spoiling my son
just after you leave home
he calls all his crook friends and throw parties
all gather and watches naked films(porn)
drink alcohols and smoke cigarettes
and do all wrong works
in your son's company my son also spoiled
and started harassing our neighborhood girls
My son is little naughty
but not so much spoiled as you saying
how can I trust you?
do you have any proof?
Listen, whatever I am saying is absolute truth
you can search in your son's room
you will find out by yourself
that your son is white as milk or dirty like mud
please talk in correct manner
I will not tolerate any lie about my son
if your son committed mistake
you have to tolerate my manner
Maybe you have lots of money to spoil your son
but we don't have
we are descent and family class people
it is my last warning
to keep your son distance away from my son
or I will complain directly to police and under arrest him
GOT IT
bastard
DAD
DAD, I am going
DAD, I was calling you for long time
but you didn't give response
what happened?
Worthless, Moron
am I teaching you to do all the wrong things?
what happened, will you explain me?
I got call from your friend vikash's father
you are spoiling his son
he threatened me
if any day he seen you with his son then.....
chill dad
why are you trusting him?
Don't you trust me?
I trusted so i am disappointed now
I give you everything whatever you want
I give you so much love but what did you done?
you misuse everything
please dad, don't overreact
i searched your entire room
I find out everything what you do after I leave the house
DAD, how dare you to search my room?
Moron
first you done wrong and now showing arrogance
DAD
please don't beat me
unworthy, will you teach me?
will you teach me?
today I will pull out all your arrogance
DAD
you are beating your dad
hey, look him. what is he doing? go and ask him
hey dog, what are you watching for long time?
shut up monkey, is she your sister?
don't try to be over smart
don't hit me
what do you think about yourself?
I will slap you, get out from here
get away from here
go away
first you get away from here
get out you fucker
(phone ring..)
Hello Karan
Yes, Speak
What happened?
nothing
i had fight with my dad
He got call from vikash's father
i too got call from vikash's father
my dad drove me out from house
he told me not to come back till improve myself
so where are you now?
at bus stop
where are you?
I am at home
if your father also get you out from house
then you come at bus stop giving me your company
I will spend whole night here
No, dad yet not kicked me out
lucky
tomorrow I will go back to my house and apologize
and swear not to do any mistake again
you also need to apologize to your father
my story is little complex
are you mad?
why do you stretch things so much?
what should I do?
situation gone out of control
I am been saved by babaji(godman)'s thread
all troubles goes quickly
this trouble too will vanish tomorrow
one day I will take you to the babaji's place too
you will never get troubles again
by the way
ask your dad for forgiveness in early morning
don't stretch things too much
I will see tomorrow
ok, I will call you tomorrow
if you need any help, just call me
bye, good night
Good Night
you are beating to your father
DAD
I am apologetic for whatever happened yesterday
Sorry dad, it will not happen again
DAD
DAD, Please open your eyes
Please open your eyes, dad
DAD, please open your eyes
DAD, What happened with you?
please dad, open your eyes
please dad, at least one time open your eyes
I love you dad
Dad, I ask you for forgiveness
Dear Karan
never think yourself alone
wherever you will need any help
just call me
and
your father's partnership in company will remain same
whenever you wish, you can join the company
I will send you bank cheque every month
ok
and don't take any kind of tension
dad
please dad come back once
please dad
dad, come back please. one last time
dad, i was totally wrong
dad
dad, come back please
come back please, one last time
you was correct
i was wrong
dad, i will never do anything what you don't like
never, i will never do it again
i will destroy everything
dad, i will destroy everything what you don't like
I will destroy
look dad, i destroyed everything
dad, now nothing is here
please dad, now come back
dad, come back please
come back please
dad, i will never do anything wrong again
dad, please come back
look dad, i am breaking everything
dad, i broke everything
dad, come back
DAD
Monti, I need your help
tell me friend,what help you need?
My whole life is for you
I want to call one last time
I too was thinking same
I will not spare that asshole Vikash
If i meet him again
I will tie rocket in his ass
and drop him in Pakistan(terrorist nation)
I am calling to vikash
give him two more abuses from me
it all happened because of him
What is our fault? If he caught red handed
Fucker
did we ever pressurize him to watch porn films?
bastard
every time this dog come wagging his tail
please monti, don't talk about him
I will not spare him easily
I want to talk to my DAD
OK, give me his cell phone number
WHAT?
do you want to talk to your dad?
yes
Friend, did you start drinking alcohol again?
huh.. you want to talk to your dad!
Friend, how can it be possible to talk with a dead person?
Monti, i am serious
if there is any way to talk to dad
It is tough job like to put on saree(dress) on sunny leone
let me think for solution...
there is a way to talk to him
but not sure if it work
tell me the way...
there is a bopi(bishop), her name is Kamini Devi
people says, she goes in hades every New Moon
and talk to dead people
are you sure?
i heard it
Never got opportunity to test the claim
Will she talk to my dad?
people use to praise her
hope it is true
ok
let's try her once
if you are interested then i bring her home
if you find her genuine, continue with her
ok, bring her home
greeting
tell me boy, what is your problem?
I want to talk to my father, one last time
your wish will sure be fulfilled
i goes to hades every new moon night
and talk to dead people
give me your message
I will sure deliver your message to your father
i had fight with him on the day of his death
i want to say sorry to him
it was all my fault
i must understand him
i am missing him alot
please tell him
if anyhow he come back to earth
i will never give him any chance of complaint, promise
boy
dead people can never come back to earth
but i can deliver your message to him
if he is suffering
or if he is in trouble
then i will solve his problem
please aunt, let him know
your son is feeling guilty
he can't live without you
Sure
Sure, i will deliver your message to him
we can go beyond the reach of science and technology
I am giving you a list
buy all the materials written on it
and remember, tomorrow is new moon night
so buy these materials soon
so that tomorrow i will go to hades and talk to your father
10 kg. rice
10 kg. wheat
10 kg. sugar
coconut, Flower garland...
why is this all?
boy
tomorrow I will do Mantra meditation
these materials are necessary
with help of these materials i can go to hades
will you sure deliver my message to my dad?
of course boy
That's why I'm here
ok
Thank you aunt
your fees?
boy, i don't take any fees
i accept whatever people give me with affection
you can give me only 5001 rupees(200 $)
your wish must complete, it is my main motive
ok aunt
i will buy all these materials before tomorrow
Very Good
so now i am leaving
at tomorrow night, i will come back
yes
now relax, your wish is soon going to fulfill
will she sure deliver my message to my dad?
what do you think?
i am totally confused
My mind stopped working
try at least once, if you want
let's go to buy all the materials
Now?
yes, now
TAXI
as you wish goddess
At the time of hypnotic
don't try to awaken me
yes
(chanting magical spells...)
wake up boy, wake up
it's morning
aunt, did you meet to my dad?
what did he tell?
keep calm boy
Why are you so much anxious?
please tell me fast
what did father tell?
did he forgive me?
will he come back to meet me?
your excitement is justifiable
but first take bath and make pure and clean yourself
after then i will tell you whole story
As you wish goddess
Monti
Greeting
please tell me fast, what did dad tell to you?
your dad is very much angry on you
at the time, when i meet him
and told him that your son send me to meet you
he reacted furiously
he told me to get out from here
and tell to my son that i don't want to talk to him
i calmed him down
asked him why are you reacting angrily?
he's your son and you are his father
and father have to bow at front of child wishes
why will you not talk to your child?
did dad agree?
how can he not agree?
i was there to convince him
I insisted
to low down his anger
and told him your son accepting his guilty
just forgive your son
but he was firm
he told me that my son harassed me very much
i convinced him to low down his anger and forgive you
and let me know if you have any demand here
i promised him that i will not disappoint you
and will be in touch with your son
I will meet all your needs with help of your son
did i reply correctly?
yes
so dad has no issue in hades?
dear, I made list of his requirement
take this
i wrote things that your father need desperately
2 ton AC
Refrigerator
why are these all?
Dear, there is extremely hot climate
so he need it badly
but how will you send these materials in hades?
don't think too much
just give me the materials written in the list
i will send it
10 kg. sweets
10 kg. dessert
sweets are written in it
but dad never eat it
dad had diabetes
Dear, the hades is totally different
a person who doesn't take interest in the things here
start to take interest in the hades
don't go deep in this matter
do whatever I command you
because if you make even a small mistake
And dad become angry
then i will not be able to convince him again
he is also correct from his side
You're only son of him
all the money, wealth he left for you
now if you will not care about your father
then who will?
try to understand
and it will not worse
if you spend some amount for dad.
buy all the materials in the list
i will come back on next new moon night
ok
take care of yourself
and dear
keep this Amulet
tie it in your neck all day
No trouble will come near you
i never go to any place
but your friend urged me so much
that i accept it without hesitation
your friend is truly loyal to you
take this amulet, especially for you
ok
now i am leaving
long live our goddess
Goddess
let me do it
ok dear
i will drop you at taxi stand
karan, i am leaving
ok, bye..
will you buy all the materials written in the list?
he has no other option to talk to his dad
don't be a fool
what have she proof that she meet to his dad?
she made stories
and you started arranging her household demands
in modern era, how can you believe in witchcraft
he has no other options
Can scientific technologies let people talk to dead man?
if no then shut your mouth
Yes, by Electronic Voice Phenomena
and  electromagnetic pulse technologies
you can talk to spirit
many similar gadgets are present
just shut up
EVP or EMP just let you know about the presence of spirit
they will not help you to talk to spirits
and no gadget is scientifically 100% full proof
that it will give correct information
does your technic give 100% full proof surety?
they are making you emotional fool
at least she is giving some peace to his mind
he is getting some relief by talk to her, let him continue
i don't believe in her nonsense
you are free to decide
What do next?
i am totally confused
if the woman was true or not
tell me solution
I have plan
i know a famous tantrik baba(godman)
let's meet him
he is very famous
his advertisements come on TV, Newspapers..
people calls him baba bangali
he give 100% surety to solve problems
let's meet him and confirm if the lady is true or false
he settled all problems of my neighbor uncle quickly
I'll bring him home
he will differentiate between truth and lie
bring him. let's see if it works
(Chanting magical spell..)
Greeting
I don't accept greeting by shaking hands
you must completely bow at front of me
Kowtow to babaji so your work will done perfectly
Long live our Magical Godman
long live
Godman,what will you take? cold water,tea or cold drink?
it is very hot here. bring a glass of cold drink
(chanting spells..)
tell me boy, what is your problem?
my father died some days ago
I wanted to apologize him
kamini devi came here
she told me that she spoke to my dad
but we have doubt on his intention
so we call you
we want to know if she is saying correct or not
Who? Kamini Bhopi?
yes godman. she is
she is not witch but bitch
She trap innocent children like you and make money by them
She is biggest liar and fraud woman
did everything she tell was lie?
lie? completely lie
I told you, it is her job to trap people
Because of these kind of people, No one believe on us easily
don't be fool, how can a living human can go to hades?
what should we do next?
I can understand
Baba Bangali is only option who have no option
I will definitely solve your problem
How?
by sacrifice
whom?
by sacrifice a human
I will convey your message to him and at the end sacrifice him
so your message will reach directly to your dad
Whom will you sacrifice?
I will sacrifice a human infant
No, it is crime to sacrifice human being
I can understand
chanting magical spells..
I have elusive power
and gain supernatural power
that in present time i can talk to animals also
and i decided
to help you by sacrifice a magical cock for it
by this method your message will reach to your dad
your work will be done without sacrificing any human
but how will i know if dad got message or not?
SILLY BOY
you are now in front of Baba Bangali
who is excellent in black magic
many popular godman come to bow me
No one ever dare to rise finger against my magic power
but you are innocent
I can understand
OK, If your work will not done
i will not take a single penny from you
it is maximum what i can do to erase your doubt
how much money will need?
it will require 1 lekh(2000 $) rupees
and a 16 years old virgin girl for offering
What?
virgin girl? from where should i take her?
and you are asking too much money
the required work is also too much
else go to some other godman and goddesses like kamini devi
who takes money and tell lies
and make money by people like you
you will lose all your money and your work will also undone
I am doing work with 100% guarantee card
but how will i arrange this much amount in short time?
I can understand
ok
I will arrange a 16 years old virgin girl
you just arrange 51000 rupees(1000 $)
What are you thinking?
I reduce whatever i can
and you are still thinking
godman, but...
don't think too much
talk to your friends
talk to your relatives
talk to your beloved
when will they help you if not now?
you will also come to know, who is taking care about you
think about your father
he is worried in heaven
his soul must be free from all worries
and it is your duty to free him
Monti, come here
yes
What?
what should i do?
take a look around if you can arrange from somewhere
should i talk to sharma uncle?
yes, ask him
Godman, cold drink
Hello
Hello. uncle, I am karan
yes dear
uncle, i need some help
tell me dear, don't hesitate
talk me like as you talk to your father
uncle, i need 51000 rupees(1000 $) urgent
it is just a little thing
i will send you in evening, anything else?
nothing, thank you uncle
are you starting something new?
no, i am completing just some old works
good-good. a person always must to do something
but i am interested to know what old work are you going to complete
just nothing
tell me dear. why are you shying from your uncle
uncle, tomorrow, i am going to talk to dad
with whom? your dad?
yes
How?
uncle, baba bangali is miraculous person
tomorrow, he will deliver my message to dad
Baba Bangali
I heard his name somewhere
it is great news if he is helping you
yes uncle. he is wonderful man
first he asked me 1 lekh rupees(2000 $)
and a virgin girl for offering
but after my request, he ready for only 51000 rupees(1000 $)
looking as he is very gentleman
yes uncle,if you too want to talk to dad.come here tomorrow
Sure. i will reach here tomorrow
you give me great news
yes uncle, i am very much excited to talk to dad
so i will meet you tomorrow. ok, take care, bye..
thank you uncle. bye..
Monti, i talked. uncle is ready
he is also coming tomorrow
wow, good. Congratulation
Godman, please come here tomorrow
as you wish
(chanting magical spell..)
long live our godman
See miracle of Baba Bangali
(chanting magical spells...)
Shiv Kumar, Come back..
Shiv kumar came... Shiv kumar came...
DAD.. Dad I love you dad
My Son
Dad, I love you. please dad, never leave me alone
Dad, please promise me you will never left me alone
I love you dad
I will never annoy you
please dad, never leave me alone
please always remain with me dad
tell me dad, talk to me...
long live our godman
(chanting magical spells..)
long live
today, i will over your all problems
put your money here, cock will be happy
Uncle will soon reach here and give you money
OK, till i begin praying of magical power
(chanting magical spells...)
is he miraculous godman?
yes, he solved problems of many people
Give me your introduction
i am business partner of shiv kumarji
but he treated me like his younger brother
very good
and who is she?
she is working in our office
she has deep interest in black magic and devotee of godman
she is here to see your black magic
she want promotion
Sure
this is my business card
I do work with 100% guarantee
one of the finest godman of black magic
no one can escape by my magic ability
I am Baba Bangali
if you have any problem in business
or have trouble in promotion
every problems have only one solution
and it is baba bangali
looking as he is most miraculous person
keep the money here, i will show you my miraculous power
Sure
but will you sure talk to our sir?
definitely
How?
This is a magical cock
First i will convey your message to this magical cock
after then i will sacrifice it
this cock will then go in other world by my magical power
and this is how your message will deliver directly to your sir
May be you are correct but there is a small question
our sir done many noble works so he will be in heaven
but if this cock go in hell then how will message reach to sir?
don't worry
it is a magical cock
and by my supernatural power
it will directly reach to heaven and meet your sir
ok
as you wish
but i thought why should we take even small risk?
you are such a biggest miraculous godman
why don't you call sir on earth and talk directly to him?
i will give you double amount for this act
and this lady meera is happily ready to serve you
tell meera
Sure, long live miraculous godman
your request make some sense
but it will need lot of hard work to call him on earth
and it is most toughest job
it will need lot of extra magical power
also it is expensive
expense will rise to about 2 lakh rupees(5000 $)
and i will be tired after this hard work
for this,lady have to come my place to serve me for one week
don't mind about anything
call to our sir here
keep this lady as much time as you want
and i will pay you whatever amount you want
Very Good
but godman
you told me alive person can never go and come back from hades
Silly boy, you have no idea about my super magical power
I have immense supernatural power
i will not go in other world to talk to your father
but i will bring your father from different world to this world
Shiv Kumar, Come Back...
(chanting magical spells...)
shiv kumar, come back...
shiv kumar came back
but why can't i see him?
silly boy, it is his spirit
ordinary person can't see him
only person with miraculous magical power can see him
Ask him, whatever you want?
ask him, how did he suddenly died?
tell me shiv kumar, why did you suddenly died?
Speak Shiv Kumar
he telling me that he is sorrowful by behavior of his son
It hurt him alot and it was reason for his death
He is the reason of his death
ohhh... Sir
Karan, did you hear him? it is you
you are responsible for death of our sir
NO, I loved dad so much, I never thought to hurt him
Dad, I love you
Dad, i will never annoy you again
Dad, come back please
Dad, I will never hurt you again. please dad come back
IDIOT. just shut up
i told you earlier, don't hurt sentiments of your dad
but you didn't understand
first you send him up and now you are calling him down
Godman, is his dad still angry on him?
he is very much angry on him
because of him, he is not getting peace in heaven
so what should we do to bring peace to his soul?
to bring peace to his soul and atone sins
He need to give food everyday to a godman for one month
also need to take care a godman for one year
and in every new moon night
he need to offer a 16 years old virgin girl to godman
by this method he can bring peace to his father's soul
are you listening Karan?
It is only you, who drop us in this situation
now we have to do everything whatever godman suggest us
Uncle, i don't understand, why does dad need all this?
What do you need to understand?
If you done mistake, you have to pay for it
for peace of his soul, i will not consider about money
even i can sell this house for his soul
isn't it?
his soul must achieve peace by agony
will it enough or need some more?
Godman, please make it clear
My Sir is everything for me
I can't see him in sorrowful condition
by the way, if you want to make happy him forever
then you must give 10 lakh rs.(20000$)to any miraculous godman
so he will take care of your sir's soul for lifetime
why someone else?
who is most miraculous godman on the earth except you?
and i know you will take care of sir very well
don't worry
i will take care him forever
I will promote him in heaven as god
He will never face any trouble in heaven
excellent
if it all are true then your reward must not be limited to 10 lakh(20000$)
but you are equally partner of his half wealth
you are taking so much care of him
so you are equally entitled in his property and assets
as you wish. shiv kumarji is like my father
i will never let him disappointed ever
I will shift his place near god
he will be in true heaven
god bless you
i knew your miraculous power
so i bring this flat papers with me
today i will sell this property and give you half shares
so you will take care our sir from today
Is it fine Karan?
but uncle, if you sell this flat then where will i live?
Why are you worrying?
My brother-in-law is purchasing this flat
today he is giving 50 lekh(100000 $)
you will receive half shares
enjoy your life living in hotel with your friends.don't take tension
but uncle, flat approximate value is 3 crore(600000 $)
shut up.don't use your mind too much
no one is willing to buy property at such high price
sell it at whatever price we getting
Urgently we need to give half money to godman also
am i correct godman? please explain him
you are absolutely correct
Nothing can be better than this
you are truly honest and loyal man
sir is very happy watching you are caring him even after his death
long live godman
today i will give you your half shares
let's go to property registration office
i am calling my brother-in-law there
let's go
let's go pupil
let's go Karan
ohh.. godman... i forgot to ask a question to sir
ask him. today he is very happy on you
he will answer your each and every question
ask him, how much money he had given to mehta ji?
He don't remember it
oh.. it will create a big problem
ok,ask him how much amount bank draft given to paras enterprises?
He is angry by hearing all these questions
He forgot everything related to business
ask him about his health, about heaven's atmosphere
he is angry on questions related to business
Sorry, then ask him what is name of his grandfather?
don't ask him such stupid questions
did you bring him from heaven to ask these useless questions?
if you again ask stupid questions,he will left this place in anger
sorry godman, forgive me
i want to confirm with whom you are talking is our sir or someone else
Don't doubt, he is your sir
ok so ask him is his wife savitri devi is happy in heaven?
yes, he is happy by this question
ask him question like this
he is telling his wife is happy with him, he met him
and how is his sister kausalya devi died recently? is she also fine?
yes, she is also fine. now let's go
wrong. i told you something wrong is happening here
he didn't had any sister
I just want to confirm you are true or telling lie about shiv kumar
fool, what you want to confirm? am i lying?
Godman, you are great
first you talked politely but when you got exposed,you reacting angrily
Shameless, Hypocrite. what you want to prove?
Don't make me angry or there will be Holocaust.you will waste completely.
what is your level against me?
if i curse you, your whole generation will destroy
Still you have option. bow on my foot and i will forgive you
or you will be destroyed
Godman, boon yourself before cursing someone
stop making fool to innocent people
Do some good work for society and for country
How dare you to give me lecture? whole world comes to teach from me
I will destroy you
Stop making fool to innocent people
a immature kid is in trouble and you want to make money by him
Stop or I will kill you
Stop this drama. you are completely exposed
Police is waiting you outside
thank you ma'am
we are gratitude. because of you,we can catch a fraud godman
we received many complaints earlier but today we catch him red handed
let's go to police station, i will fulfill your all wishes there
I caught the culprit. I collect and record all the evidences
Send Vijay at the flat
Bitch, you are also involved in this plan
No one will be spared
and you, your house will destroy
and?
your whole generation will finish. you will remember me
(chanting magical spells..)
you mess with Baba Bangali
No one can win from Baba Bangali
Vijay, arrest him
Now shout with your full strength
I tell you, I will be back and curse you
(chanting magical spells..)
remember me, I will not forgive you
Do you have any brain or not? What kind of friend are you?
your friend is in trouble and you showing him wrong path
did your parents teach you something or not?
Sorry uncle. i just want to help him
help by these impersonators? didn't you see how did they help?
Sorry uncle,i will never fall prey by these kind of fraud people again
Good. focus in your bright future
Now leave
thank you uncle. today you opened my eyes
Karan, why are you doing all this?
If your dad was alive, he would be very sad
I just want to talk to dad one last time
by this, did you talk to dad?
Dear, you are not kid anymore
take care while taking any step ahead
father and son relation is different, need no word to express feeling
what do you think? does your father not aware about your feeling?
uncle, it is all my fault
I was reason behind my father's death
I will never forgive myself. Never
So what do you think, you are only reason of his death?
This situation may never rise if you can understand him
Come with me, i show you whole story
Come, come here
read it
did you ever care about your father?
did you ever ask him why are you always remain in tension?
why are you sad every time?
if you ever rise these questions to him, you will never confront this situation
your father got cancer. and he want to hide this illness from you
so you can live your life freely
focus in your goal and make a good life
you are not behind his death
but if you are feeling guilty full and want to rectify your error
then go to some cancer hospital and served to needy people
Still you have lots of time to choose correct path
either you can continue your study or can join business with me
but please, don't waste your precious time in these kind of things
just forget whatever happened in past
If you will remember your father by true heart,he will sure listen your voice
you will need no proxy to Deliver your message to him
Think wisely whatever i told you
Decide carefully
i am leaving now
tomorrow, I will come again