a beginning is a very delicate time
know then that it is the year 10,000 191
something sleeps inside us and seldom
awakens
the sleeper must awaken my father had
acquired the rights to the book and the
book was one of my favorite books of all
times I i had read at the time i think
there were only three out and so I very
much wanted to be involved I thought it
was a good book but more important I
thought David was a good it was a good
director and these two things said well
I love this something good was come or
when I read the book I didn't really see
Arthur we're going to make a movie out
of it then I read the script and saw the
David done a pretty good job at sort of
narrowing it down but to still keeping
it pretty complicated when David Lynch
got dune I think it was generally
perceived that he got it because he was
he was coming off the success of the
Elephant Man which in turn was a was a
big surprise to to lynch fans because
before that all he done was this very
strange cult underground movie
eraserhead so it was perceived as risky
but exciting and people kind of their
hats were off to Dino De Laurentiis for
taking a chance with with this sort of
almost avant-garde director but he had
proven himself as a commercial director
with the Elephant Man there was a lot of
excitement about this movie because well
for one thing from all the Frank Herbert
fans mean dune was a was an enormous
cult science fiction novel that people
have been trying to make into a movie
for years and years and years and now
they were finally going to do it so the
anticipation was very high I see the
truth of it could he be the one maybe
it would he be ours to control there are
some books that should never be made
into movies Moby Dick is one of its been
made several times now and it's never
made well Moby Dick is one of those
things that is a book leave it as a book
so we say in Yiddish wasn't gain let be
don't mess with it there's some things
you just don't screw with well I always
thought that about doing I thought dude
was one of those books that read well
and in the theater of your mind your
imagination could make it far more abune
sexier more adventurous more dark and
many layered than you ever could in a
film you know I always felt that one of
the problems or one of the mistakes
maybe that we made was to try and be too
faithful to the book you know it was
such an incredible undertaking to just
try and be and tell that story with all
those characters all those planets all
those words in the worlds and you know
but but we did it somehow
you have to go with Lynch's movies on an
honest unconscious level they're really
about imagery and it's I remember the
images of that movie twenty years later
much more vividly than I remember say
Superman which was a huge commercial hit
and was a lot of fun but it doesn't
stick with you the way that the dune
sticks with you and it's not about
storytelling because the storytelling
isn't particularly great in the movie
and that's one of the reasons why it
wasn't a commercial hit but but boy you
know as a visionary thing even for all
its flaws I think it's much more
interesting than most of the Hollywood
science fiction fair and one of the
interesting things about it is how it
the the iconography of it goes into the
past well it's actually wildly eclectic
because you've got some people dressed
as if they were in like a Shakespearean
play and you've got other people dressed
as sort of Nazi storm troopers and
you've got Venetian architecture and
you've got Victorian trappings you've
got 1930s telephones it's the most
eclectic from a design point of view and
that's one of the things that's
fascinating about it is that it but
there's very little that's actually
futuristic about it and we generally
assume that science fiction is going to
be futuristic and it is said in the
future but you wouldn't know it
it was a difficult road to cast because
he had to be young he had to be princely
this is the Reverend Mother guys Helen
mo him she's going to observe you and
Kyle kind of you know worked after we
saw many many many many different people
he he he he had that charisma precise
control june and i actually have a
history before the film i was a big fan
of the books by frank herbert when i was
i guess i discovered them around 15 when
i was 15 years old and took to them
immediately i had never been a
science-fiction fan really but i just
something about it maybe it was because
the age of the character in the book was
similar to my age 15 or so that i really
really responded to it um I'll cut to
about I guess eight years later I was
working in seattle on a plate just
graduated from school earlier that year
from my training and and i got a call i
received a call on my message machine in
seattle from a casting agent who had
come to Seattle and was looking for
unknown actors at that time to to
audition for the role of Paul and she
had called around to various theaters
and as I was performing there I was sort
of known at that time in seattle i'll be
in a very small capacity and so my name
came up as a potential you know audition
eat and so there I was met with casting
Lady Elizabeth Lustig is her name and
she recorded me and doing this very odd
audition because of that to that point
I'd only been really stage trained and
didn't really understand this
relationship to the camera and but she
was very encouraging and helpful and she
took my tape down to David Lynch and
Rafaella De Laurentiis at universal
studios in LA and a few days later they
called and said we'd like to screen test
you so I found myself on a plane all
expenses paid it from Seattle to LA
first time had been to LA in fact and
that's how it started stop fear fear is
the mind-killer and here's a little
tentative brings total obliteration face
my fear I'm over me and mommy McLaughlin
is not a great thespian he is not Gil
good he is not sir ralph richardson he's
a perfectly competent actor and in this
case he was young and I think a little
frightened and did a perfectly yeoman
job but Francisca anise and Max von
Sydow and and everybody else in the cast
that the characters are so individual
even sting sting really I will kill you
all of them were just the most wonderful
kind of repertory company
Frank Herbert was around a good deal I
remember and always just again boy you
know kind of that adage of poison this
great you know this is this is so much
fun to be a part of this and to see this
happening and you know he would help
with pronunciations you know from time
to time and but he really as I recall
didn't impose or you know him cell phone
in any way he's like just very happy to
see his vision you don't come to life
and in whatever form I mean obviously
this book had to be altered a great deal
and he just seemed to be quite fine with
you know whatever form it took he was
always fascinated by the schedule well
you know I spent our scheduling with
those little strips you know and he was
always he was fascinated by the fact
that his book was turned into these
colorful strips Frank was a strange man
but he must have been he vote you didn't
he I said to him once or twice explain
something about her to me and he'd say
oh look at the index you'll find it all
in there so I said no but tell me what
you think about it and I don't think he
could
I remember doing 16 or 18 budgets for
all over the world we were trying the
third that the things we needed we're
big stages because we had all these sets
that we needed to build and we need a
desert so I did a lot of different we
did it early in Morocco we did England
and I can't even remember how many
versions of budgets we did and Mexico
Churubusco had these huge stages often
with dirt floors but you know big empty
rooms and you know we went in and we
just put sets and every one of them I
mean we just filled them completely once
and then basically knocked them all down
and filled them again we had so many
scents it had everything it really did
have everything that we needed to make
the film the fact that it took so long
was it was so complicated thee when you
come to consider it the script was so
complicated you know doing his uh he's a
story that's created in someone's head
there's nothing real you know there's
not a prop in the film that was a real
thing you could buy in a store
everything had to be made so everything
from the smallest you know weapon to the
you know the largest set had to be built
from scratch
when we were in Juarez in the desert in
high summer and it was not so much a
problem for us we we decided to work
very early in the morning from about
five until Hoppus one and that was what
we called it a day but that's mainly
because the actors were wearing rubber
suits and they were falling down like
ninepins and the crowd and so it was
were very unbearable for him for them
for that period of about two weeks in
Juarez in the high summer some images or
I'll never forget the one was working
with Max von Sydow on a stage on the
soundstage churubusco studios and he's
we're all dressed in these rubber suits
and which were very uncomfortable
designed by Bob ringwood who is known
for using a lot of leather he did the
Batman stuff and among many others but
they look great and I remember max
standing there talking to Jurgen and I
looked down and his hands there were
just sweat was sort of dripping off all
of his finger says he when it was out of
the frame but it was just this that's
not to myself I ought to make his max
it's very imposing you know he's like 66
or something and you know fantastic
voice a very wonderful presence you
don't hear he was you know working
concentrating and yet under great you
know under great stress as it is he's a
trooper you know I said that's way to go
max
I'm sorry granny not sorry enough
what's wrong with gurney he's not making
this now got yourself a true
is this what you seek God the saw blade
penetrates this year but look down we
have joined each other if then you can
see finally to get the moment
I worked for six months kind of parallel
with the main unit but doing my own
thing sometimes you know very special
sometimes you know very very small
occasionally very very big but a fair
number of special effects things that
today would be done as a digital optical
we did them for real as mechanical
effects and took a little longer but but
you know we were pretty good at it one
of the stages we turned into a desert
set but the sand was made with micro
balloons which is balloons made of glass
but there any microscopic to keep the
scale and then we had all these worms
that were model worms that you know and
we had to shoot very high speed you know
to make it look I me it was at the time
groundbreaking I thought the worm was
horrible I did and we had all sorts of
sections of it of course but they were
also had the annoyed at it the full
thing I thought it was a hideous thing
maybe it was done as you know by Carlo
Rambaldi who had done et and that was a
sweet little thing the little thing in
ET the worm wasn't there was nothing
affectionate about it at all as far as I
could see nothing at all one thing that
was so hard was to make those eyes blue
we had to rotoscope each I of every of
the friend today that would be so simple
I remember you're going to bar now
you'll remember mine I can kill with a
word we tried to contact lenses and they
were horrible I mean it was really hard
the actors because there was a complete
contact lens they look like one of those
1940 pictures with the giant ants you
know it didn't look good the other
challenge that we had was that you know
in the book Frank Herbert says that
Iraqis had no blue skies because there
was no water and that seems simple but
you know that meant that even when we
were outside we could never really shoot
just to see the sky we always had to
make sure that we could take the sky out
and change it I devised a thing called
the light flex which was a it's a very
straight for peace is like a piece of
glass in front of the camera which you
illuminate you light up the glass so it
adds a spark of the whole thing and you
can control it and after June I used in
every movie but Bishop this was the
first picture I used it with and I think
it added a lot to the look of the proof
the picture my role was really not so
much the big shot with the real people
it was the it was the the moments
moments of a dream that were you know we
were interpreting differently and often
it was very abstract the other thing
that was that was really important in
the film was water I mean the images of
water were very very important to Frank
Herbert and intense to David so we would
try to find ways to capture water but in
a very abstract way so so all the the
water drops in the film you know the
rings of water and all those things are
images that we created it with our
little little second unit I gotta say
David Lynch was was was brilliant he was
so composed during the filming I mean I
know we've spoken since and I think at a
certain point in time he just I think he
just felt like um he was you know there
was the light that he entered the tunnel
and but and there was no light yet at
the end that he could see so he was just
in a sort of a period of time that was
seemed to go on forever I mean you
remember he was there are almost two
years i think i was there seven months
but they decided to do a lot of second
unit and special effects shooting there
as well so he was there for at least a
year and a half perhaps longer we had
the advantage of having a lot of
pre-production time out there doing
tests and so i was able to see all the
sets being built the development of each
set and stages of the movie so we were
we had a lot on board before we actually
started filming more so than any other
film normally we would get Freddy would
get four weeks preparation i would get
about a week testing so you're living
the movie before you actually start and
all the departments are coming together
they were building the sets and the
special effects something like two years
before we started filming it was huge
david is such an artist study where he
lives in as little work that never
bothered him you know the the 2,000
people in the back he was worried about
what was in front of his lens and then
sometimes that's what we had problems
with because you know I would have two
thousand extras instant suits in the
desert and he was trying to shoot the
close-up of kyle's I and I said David
you can shoot that I you know in the
studio anytime you want but we gotta
shoot that's what you know that's why
we're here out in the desert David never
really worried himself about that David
had one of his black smoke and the way
to get the most the best look of this
smoke is to burn these tires which I
guess you can do in Mexico you can't do
in America but if you caught any of this
in your lungs as you were sort of round
you you it froze your vocal cords or
something or you couldn't your you
couldn't breathe I mean it wasn't the
strangest thing so I remember doing a
sequence with Patrick Stewart where you
know we come up and and you know give
each other a big hug and on on one take
I remembered some of this the wind
shifted in some of this black smoke came
right past us I remember i'm going to
speak to him and I was like nothing was
coming I could not get it to work I said
oh she's Scott what am I just done we
had our own ways of working and we
continued to work the English Way the
british way we wouldn't let we wouldn't
let the Americans take over I have a
certain approach where I stay very close
to the director and expect my operator
to be at my side and in my mind all the
time and this was the way I was I always
operated and it's the way Gordon goes
the better so we operate exactly the
same way I don't say put the camera here
Gordon
the camera there Gordon as a result of
Gordon listening to the director of
myself he knows exactly what to do so
the moment we finished discussing this
shot with the director he's getting a
camera mind up and everything connected
with that while I am getting all the
lighting sorted out pretty Francis the
DP was a real character he was helpful
but he wasn't really sort of the warm
cuddly friendly type you know his first
was Roy Roy learner i think freddie took
perverse pleasure in sort of you know
shouting out across the set to roid it
you know to fix something you know and
Roy was you know pipe up you know right
away you know it's like done you know
and it was kind of like I don't know
what I would imagine you know turn of
the century or before you know they're
on a ship he's a captain his first mate
could be that scenario they could have
been somewhere in India you know the
relationship because it certainly was it
felt to me military in the best way in
that great English tradition
I went on from March through til
November of 84 so that seven or eight
months David wanted a three hour movie
and Dino wanted a two hour movie and
indeed 01 it was fight to get it down
there and David was very reluctant to
give stuff up and I could understand why
but I think we found a good way out of
it and i think the picture stands up in
the way it was finally worked out but i
know it was a heartbreaking for david
for it to come down to that name the
failure is probably one of the very best
two juicers I've ever known oh she was
very she was a very knowledgeable and
very efficient you know she'd been
keeping build ball in a film studio
almost and you know she just went along
with the run of things that she was very
efficient and a great friend at her of
all the unit that was the thing about
any film on which you work that has
rafaela with you there was the greatest
camaraderie in the world they're really
and truly was she is an astonishing
person she really is and people will
work their guts off because she's doing
the same thing she never expects anyone
to do anything that she won't do herself
I think when you're young ignorance of
sometimes make you achieve greatness
because you just don't know any better
and so you say okay well so sure I'll
produce do I want to produce dude then
you know it's only ten years later that
I found out that no woman had ever had
ever produced before dune I'm anything
moving hood that the budget was
over 5 million dollars i had no idea the
first time I met Dino was at the Beverly
Hills Hotel and I went to the bungalow
and Dino came to the door and he was
eating pasta or something was having a
late meal or an early dinner perhaps and
he had low pasta there's an a stuck
around I felt bad for disturbing him but
and I could tell the person I was with
was a little nervous but he was very
generous I yeah he's a gummy gummy you
know in this great voice he's got d down
you know so he I sit down the couch and
he asked me like three questions you
know two of which i can remember which
were how old you are I selves you know
at that time I was 22 he's a UH and he
said something about you cut your hair
or something like that I should put you
know whatever you know whatever you need
you know and he sort of stared at me for
a while it was another question I can't
even remember because it was just real
sore really very surreal and he's okay
and he got up and that was it
I ended up hanging out pretty much we
were a little Musketeers was Patrick
Stewart myself and Everett McGill sort
of be you know we sort of hung out went
to dinners together and things I mean
David would join us from time to time
and I would hang out with David a bit
but he his obligations you know were
quite varied there was always something
going on somewhere normally in the
fellows flat I must say in fact Richie
Fleischer was doing Conan on the next
stage we were sort of back to back and
he came to their parties of course and
one of the boys took some stills and
Richard looked at the developed stills
god I didn't know I was such a porky I
bet you that the people who went to
these parties had nothing to do with
shooting the film
I met David Lynch at at the American
Film Institute and we worked on a film
called Eraserhead for many years so I
had built this relationship with him you
know he went on to do some more work but
then when it came to dune you know we
hired freddie francis it was a wonderful
wonderful cinematographer to do the film
but thought that he could bring me on
doing a second unit doing some extra
footage some special things that David
always had in mind for the movie I
thought it was mad and I still think
he's mad but he's a wonderful guy to
work with and makes up his mind what he
wants I thought he was he was terrific I
thought it this bizarre outlook on life
and he was he's such an ordinary chap
yet he's got all these weird and
wonderful ideas I think perhaps there
was a sense that we were sort of joined
at the hip kind of her tied together in
some way during this process you know I
you know I guess I was you know the hero
of the film obviously and also sort of
the focus but I think I think there were
a number of the were there were a number
of battlefields I guess or not
battlefields let's call him and there
were a number of creative arenas there
were the Atreides the family urug and
myself Francesca Patrick all that you
know sort of the good to good warriors
and then there were the bad guys the
heart Conan's right and that was a world
that David I think secretly really
preferred
david is absolutely brilliant he really
as he is a genius he's a crackpot petit
jean a genius if the producer says no
that's not possible you'll find somehow
three days they each other not only is
it possible it's already been done I'm
terribly fond of him I really am I love
him dearly however the Duke will die
before these eyes and he'll know hello
that is I then Vladimir Harkonnen
encompasses is doomed I think June was a
victim of the expectations people really
wanted you know I commercially they
expected a big blockbuster it was it was
just too strange I think it was too
unconventional I mean there's some very
kinky stuff in it the great thing
against june was that there was no humor
in it I can't remember even smiling once
and it need it needed humor and there
wasn't Eddie at all there was a big
backlash against it you know there was a
lot of it there was a lot of publicity
about the movie before it open how was
going over budget have they're having
all sorts of problems in Mexico while
they were making as potential clashes
between Lynch and Dino De Laurentiis and
the media kind of fed off that so I
think there was a certain amount of you
know people smelled blood you know in
the air and there was a certain ganging
up on the movie and went it open none of
the critics for the exception of David
Ansen and myself of course I was not a
major critic but my stuff got around I
gave it a good review it was almost
universally panned I never read the
reviews of the movies because even the
good one makes you crazy you know it's
just like you spent so much time on a
movie and you're in
tensions are such that you know it's so
easy to sit down and tear at four years
of your life so I just don't read them
anymore critics think nothing will ever
make good film except a good film and
you know it's a terrible thing to say
but I ignore Christians completely my
review was one of the only positive
reviews that came out which I do not
apologize for and I would write the same
review today I think but I do feel that
a lot of my colleagues kind of jumped on
the bandwagon with undue viciousness you
know i love the film I'm surprised
people didn't enjoy it more i really was
i I thought it would it would find a
bigger audience than it did I'm afraid
it wasn't perhaps promoted as well as it
could have been I don't know that the
studio really supported it it's that's
an unfortunate things I think it's a
very it's a very beautiful movie I'll
miss the sea
but a person needs new experiences they
John something deep inside allowing him
to grow most of what Universal did in my
view in my view is indefensible they had
no faith in the film they had no hutzpah
they had no balls they had no no courage
you know a lot of people blame Universal
the way they released it for the movie
not being as successful as it should
have been I think the movie was
challenging you know it was maybe too
intellectual and too difficult it men
ESP was not your obvious popcorn movie
but I think the book was that way and I
think that you know being faithful to
the book which is what we tried to do
turned out a movie that was difficult
but the people that love it love it the
choice of director for a film is always
a it's an unusual process I don't know
that there's any any Best Director for a
film I mean I think David was a
wonderful choice for this one I think
sometimes when the studio is looking for
the broadest possible audience they
choose the safest possible director and
to their credit they supported David in
going out on a limb and and choosing
someone who may not have been the first
choice for this kind of film but but the
vision he brought to it is so
spectacular you think that the Lynch
would have at least gotten the benefit
of the doubt for trying something a
little bit different and more original
and very personal not a total success
obviously but you know these are the
same critics you're always complaining
about how formulaic Hollywood movies are
and then when something not formulate
comes along they jump on the bandwagon
sort of kick it was down I think dune
turned him off making big budget movies
because in a way you give up your
freedom you know for creative freedom
when there's so much pressure on you
because of the budget the time and he
hasn't Hayden he said to me when he
finished that he never wanted to do
another big movie again and he never has
he's always done smaller movie that he
can control and I think he's been really
happy doing that he's found you know his
niche to think he loves doing this I
think is one of the is one of the
linchpins of dunes importance that it
ever actually got made it was a book
that shouldn't have been shot it was a
script that couldn't have been written
it was a directorial job that was beyond
anyone's doing it was a production that
would beggar the imagination and
bankrupt three studios it was a
production that could not possibly be
marketed in any way that anyone could
understand or that they would go to it
didn't hit its audience it looked like
it insulted its audience it looked like
it defamed its its its originator and
yet the film was made
and yet the film remains after all these
you know we're talking decades here this
film still holds up and when you go back
and you look at it you are drawn into it
as far as I'm aware dune has never
really come in for a major reassessment
it always had a couple of fans strong
fans along the way and Harlan Ellison
and the science fiction world I know
defended it at the time but it's kind of
I think overdue for for a rediscovery
and maybe maybe some years down on the
way they'll realize that it's a much
stranger and more interesting movie than
I thought at the time
follow the sleeper has awakened
you