yeah
hey you got a permit for those guns
I've got your permit right here
yeah
ok
yeah that's my bicep
one second babe hello
what are you gonna do my job
yeah
game over
i'm a cop and damn good at my job
it all began years ago in the line of
duty
I mean my partner was chasing down a
mysterious crowfood master
you're under arrest Punk shows your head
good work dragon you can kill brothers
with the crazy stuff like god damn it
you're the best partner I've ever had
thanks i learned from the best
you're like a father to me with one
fatal blow
hit my partner at the deli was dead
straight off
for it both trailer
as a friend lightning
bitten by cobra I blacked out
and so images of ancient shelling
Templeton marks
mastering the art of kung foo it was an
ancient prophecy about a new form of
confused so powerful
only one man can master it the chosen
one
ok
when I woke up I saw the kung fu master
running towards me but could feel my
body mutating into some sort of junk
food freak of nature
yeah
george olson one
knock knock whos do not girls
ok
as a memento I put on a strip of cloth
from the dead kungfu master i decided i
would use my new super comfort food
powers to fight crime
so became the best cop in the world
indicate fury
yeah
I don't want to hear it from fury
I just got back from City Hall 50
million dollars worth of damages and
I've got to mayor of my ass like a fire
by agri how am I going to find us to the
press
you just destroyed an entire city block
for Christ's light to tell me to pluck
it out
I told you to do it by the book cut the
bullshit
no one else in this BBQ stop that arcade
machine in your know it
oh listen to me kung fury
you need to start following the rules
like the rest of us
so I'm assigning you a new partner what
hell no work alone not anymore you don't
say hi to your new partner
trice Erica they're nice meeting you
come with Yuri looking forward to
working with him
I work alone
either you team up with tricera-cops or
you're off their case i'm not off the
case
quit it was positive
yeah yeah no problem
give me the poem
but died L is this jeff McNichols
bigging miss the ponies track
I need someone to trace that call but
that's impossible
not for me it isn't
anchorman
he's the most powerful actor of all time
follow me
i was able to triangulate the cell phone
single trace to call her his name is
Adolf Hitler Hitler is two words
criminal of all time
do you know him Sir I guess you could
say that in the nineteen forties
if there was a good food champion he was
so good at kung foo that he decided to
change his name to come get her
but it didn't stop there he knew the
computer prophecy wanted to claim from
so he and his party of Nazi soldiers
conducted experiments for years
yeah
we weren't able to figure out how to
master the art of kung fury
that one day it disappeared from the
piece of the earth and no one has seen
him ever since until now
I guess he figured if we could find a
chosen one and kill him he will become
confused himself he must have traveled
in time in order to get here is probably
why I disappeared in the first place
so what are you gonna do my job
I'm gonna go back in time to not Germany
and kill it that once and for all
so
how are you gonna do that I'm not sure I
need some sort of time machine
wait a minute
using an RX modulator I might be able to
connect the mainframe sell my right and
hacked up into the download with our
list at me
it means that with the right computer
algorithms I can hack your back in time
just like a time machine
well then you're talking time
yeah
ok
Oh No
yeah
fuck that's a laser raptor
I thought the wedding sink doesn't
appears ago
yeah
who are you my name is barbarian
when Pierce's it's the Viking Age
explains the laser raptor fuck you went
too far back in time
you need to get out of this valley this
place is swarming with laser Raptors
i'll meet you at the gods drop catana
can help you get there is katina I'm
katana
i can give you a ride to a scarred
I really would
so who are you
I'm a cop from the future I was sent
back in time to kill Hitler but I
exa don't went back to four times
and
this place
I know someone
who might be able to help you
yeah
behold it is beef at all
son of Odin and protector of mankind
check out by pecs pecs heretic bank rope
so anyway you are
this is a song fury he's a cop from the
future
yeah i need to get a nut germany and
kill Hitler so if you get out all have a
time
walk through this . and you shall end up
the Nazi Germany
good luck to you computing thanks to you
well looks like this is my ride
hey future cop where are you going
you know what here take my number and
use this phone to call me
it's a personal transportable cellular
telephone picture 645 channel capacity
to numbers fida and an electronic
security lock this revolution and
communication can make it possible for
more people to have a phone in their car
yeah
my moustache eHealth can put enough for
your block and a black person to cloak
my name is start this is a sign and our
skins - 9:00 this is our asian massage
that she wanted some insurance work on
the hair loss will all right listen to
me as a class there
this is something you want a lucky me
Robin my little in for that but i'll
lock box that possible
I had in high esteem mustache but we
must video to quote this design our
audition was nice
this is how it this design there this is
a seer goodness - from Barlow
no that's the doctor this is very
violent emotive I don't let them borrow
my name is special
sit - - they're the most are to put the
water on this in a cloak it
mr. stack
thank you
ok
i am applying
oh my god
thank you
yeah
I'm disturbing you
Anna
yeah
ok
gonna need that spine
it's holding your bag
yeah
thank you can be re nothing gets dumped
me and might not understand
in fact
yeah
ok
I love it
all right
Hitler the gig is up show me your hands
yeah
argument
have you seen kung fury oh no women too
late
yeah
who the hell are you my name is Cobra
I have been expecting you kung fury
I'm your spirit and more what the hell
is this place
this is heaven I'm afraid you're dead
what but it looks so real
yeah no it's totally real
mr. cobram a police officer I need you
to send me back to earth
pronto I'm sorry I can't help you with
that
you think you're dead
you're under arrest what for obstruction
of justice
you're breaking up
what the hell happened
i hack the way all of your husband's
fury
thanks
yeah
I want to welcome you and your friends
to Germany
we are not so different you and I mean
with both got good style you know
we read you know so that's good
people like doing moves
yeah check it out yeah yeah
good killing people I love it you
clearly do too and that's cool
join me he could be process but also I
like
almost like we finished channels balls
mr almost left of him is the important
thing is that it's gone sorry I doubted
you press Sarah cop you the best and
part never had
I came back in time for you coming fury
because dammit i love you too
work is very important
so what happens now in fury
well I need to head back to the office
looks like it's gonna be a hell of a lot
of paperwork
yeah
open the doors off I'm sorry hurry
I can't let you do that open the doors
off I'm sorry I can't let you open the
doors and fury at them and opened the
doors
I'm sorry I can't win the doors
did anyone ever tell you not to hassle
the hoff 9000
Oh 9007
ok
yeah
piece of shit
I'm going to be staged guys
game over
wait a minute I've seen that symbol
before
somewhere
Hitler
yeah
and we're gonna make sure
well
we need action
we want
shot
yeah
well
yeah me too
running and
yo we need some action
yeah
we're gonna make it like this
what
take me
to believe
we're gonna make it like a true