freedom is never more than one
generation away from extinction we
didn't pass it on to our children in the
bloodstream the only way they can
inherit the freedom we have known is if
we fight for it protected defendant and
then hand it to them with the well
thought lessons of how they in their
lifetime must do the same and if you and
I don't do this and you and I may well
spend our sunset years telling our
children and our children's children
what it once was like in America when
men were free
there is a thing right here sit around
me up there she's now 83 years old and
still kicking I kept only because the
only because it's my best friend that's
the only reason whatever
we just hang out with him good with
video Oh terrible well right now I'm
happy but I'm sure that will change very
shortly she kind of drive me nuts hey
all of a nervous RL of you I'm this day
I've been waiting for
you know I always saw myself as a
patriot I don't remember anyone telling
me that freedom had to be fought for and
defended
and I love my country and I love being
free but the day I saw my son packing to
leave our country to fight in another I
understood what my father must have felt
when I left for war there's no greater
love in the world that a man laying down
his life for someone else but a man
thinks different when it's his boy going
into harm's way
thomas was 20 he had his whole life
ahead of him he had a young wife great
friends and future
so proud of you
hey they have this to me over there
taking room
you just go back
wait
we made it back to base safe and sound
every day I pray that God will see me
through so I can get back to your car
the doctor says the next few weeks will
fly by before the baby's born easy for
him to say i love you Thomas I miss you
so much
how long you feel you next to me today I
remember the smell of your hair the day
I left I love you
God's been watching overly 181 days and
i'll be home lord willing i love you and
i think of you every day
I haven't seen your mother act like this
since you were born your son is going to
be completely spoiled by the time he
meets you his grandma has his whole life
planned out by the way that includes
college
the days passed just like all the other
days of every year until that morning
I'll never forget the sound of that
doorbell
now
Oh
ah
Thomas Revere was a brave soldier in the
field of battle sacrificing his life he
was awarded the Bronze Stars do not be a
hearty troubled
and it goes on to say trust in us so
many mansions in a hole or not so I
would have told you my god which means
we'll come back and take you to the
interview it should be with me that
where you are just too Ashley they
dusted us these are the ones
please accept this flag on behalf of a
grateful nation the token of
appreciation for the Honorable and
faithful service rendered by your loved
one half right please port oh hey
you
you know I love you Oh to thank you
for everything Mike you've done your
family you always been would you please
give this to Bob for me
thank you
I wanted the world to stop and
understand the pain that I was in to
know how I was suffering
I felt in some ways that my life was
over qari and my grandson left when I
needed them the most they were the only
part of thomas i still had left
that my son nothing else really mattered
in the plane only one to get off
Oh
something I can do for you gentlemen
well I bet that hurt didn't it
okay come with me 16 it up it was just
flesh from but I have to know what
happened can I be involved in something
to leave you guys wasn't a crime later
he accidentally shot himself you're good
to go
you
ok
in time Mexico
the fast lane on everyone should get up
Oh Chris oh my you you're all grown up
just like your dad he looks like he's
not some la gang handshake is it Bob huh
why don't you get the bags and show
Chris his room okay so after you go
upstairs will have Thanksgiving dinner
oh I hope you're hungry we're starving
and we have not had a real Thanksgiving
for year
do you remember that old missions church
that was downtown the one with the Jesus
Saves cross on the side we bought that
building and we put the community
mission their gross isn't there anymore
can you imagine it offended somebody hey
look I know it's a holiday weekend but I
figured you'd want to know the feds
approve the funds you're kidding me and
we'll get that new edition for the
veterans own outstanding all right man
bye it had been 14 years since we looked
into Thomas's trunk even to see my own
grandson open it was painful can i watch
these
you can watch those
thank you oh that's the Gideon Bible
that he took everywhere
I never saw this cute
Oh see Thomas is a shepherd and JJ as
Mary who's JJ your dad's older sister
actually she left before you were born
we don't see her very often why she
didn't see eye to eye about things that
Bob and I felt were very important so
why don't people do Christmas like that
anymore with the shepherds and
everything well for a long time people
in trying to pass laws to get rid of
Christmas all together today Christmas
is all about Santa Claus and buying
things
what did he say to him told him to come
home and I told him to defend our
freedoms with his last ounce of courage
can I help you with something you must
be Chris yeah I'm Madison you're here
dad in my dad for the best friends what
is that it's my dad's medal from the war
so do you want to go shoot some hoops
with me and my friend hey Bob that needs
to be in the box can I keep it in my
room no stays here wait a minute have
you showed him this this is cool
dad is amazing when i get back from tour
i'm gonna be cruising in this every day
dan you stop worrying about me you made
it through the world okay yeah I would
trade my time for anything you fought
for what you believed in
that's all I'm doing
no son I know hello this chuck was your
dad's truck Maddie you come hey ball
lighten up a little will yet Santa's
coming in now
qari over beer hey hey well you grew up
Frank so did you is is that your son yes
that is Christian in a long time too
long okay
Dottie made her famous brownies to you
do you want to join us I know I can't
i've got a head into work for a little
bit maybe catch you later we will be
here you look great
long back
by man love you
brownies herpa doesn't seem to like you
or me for that matter it's not you I
think he thinks that I let him down
sometimes life isn't fair but we just
keep going
get some sleep huh first day of school
tomorrow I'll let you love you too chris
is so California know what is that
supposed to mean he's so hot hey you
want to get him to try out for the play
oh yeah so you can hit on him speaking
of thoughts
hey I'll be right back Krizz
Chris man what's up with you you got to
go to the principal's office why because
they have some stupid rules about what
you can bring to school would you bring
the knife or something a knife
we found this in Chris's Locker but
madison is now claiming that it's her
responsibility yes sir that's right I
brought it while I'm all for a student
taking a position on a controversial
matter when that position is detrimental
to the student body a health and
well-being as a whole that's when I have
to take action I spoke with the school's
attorney informally and he suggested
that we all keep this as low-key as
possible okay of course normally you'd
be facing an in-school suspension but
you're new here so don't go easy on you
this time now we're just going to
pretend this never happened and just
ignore it understood
all right you're dismissed
trustee they didn't know I'm sorry oh oh
don't worry about it hey thanks for
coming in sure
Christian
when prayer was banned from school so is
the Bible just the way it is now that's
a stupid rule there ain't no room say
again Leonard there ain't no rule they
can have their Bibles here if they want
to they're just a bunch of cowards thank
you letter don't wait for me could you
hold on a second yeah rusty is there an
actual rule that says you can't bring a
Bible into school no but I don't want
any trouble you can't take any chances
of these days Bob everybody's looking
for a reason to sue us yeah it's it's
that space odyssey play I wrote a few
years ago yeah well I want to brag but
I've always had a bit of a flair for the
dramatic oh uh uh mayor nice work on
that veteran something nice yeah I'm
back dr. investigation segment tonight
as you know Christmas has become
controversial in America public displays
of the federal holiday or under attack
by the ACLU and some department stores
even tell employees to avoid saying
Merry Christmas we decided to look at
some retail okay baby here's what we
found out Sears Kmart would not answer
to simply duck the issue they were the
worst we had to deal with eighty-five
percent of americans say they're
Christians chris was a federal holiday
who designed it to law by us grant and
we're living in a time where some retail
outlets will not say Merry Christmas
insane what did my dad die for Bob
that's what happens in war no I mean
why'd he died he gave his life for his
country so what are we doing what are
you doing Chris your grandfather was in
a very special unit he rescued prisoners
of war what are you doing now it's not
that easy kid what are you doing I'm
just one kid well I'm just one grandpa I
think
chris is right
we should all be doing something
and after 75 years the Hollywood Chamber
of Commerce refused to sponsor the
Christmas parade the LA City Council
took over to rename it the Hollywood
Santa 375 years of tradition gone so
what are we up here look important um
Christmas stuff decorations yeah cuz
people are not tucking it around here
anymore well maybe they should start
okay here's a reindeer it's kind of
Christmas ish thank you nice cool Oh
jackpot are you guys thinking what I'm
thinking you're thinking it's cheesy
then ya know let's let's put it up let's
put it all up two nights
so glad you were there oh I just don't
want Chris to get started off on the
wrong foot
no you can get a bad reputation real
fast oh we remember that huh you're
pretty bad boy in school yeah I was
stupid I think you and Thomas got away
with murder because you've smiled your
weight of everything just like that yes
so Chief of Police huh
then again you always have to be in
charge generated so if you don't
my man skiing what's the story on my
mother
Stacy had her own agenda
she's in Philadelphia
sorry how this is I completely awkward
can I take you to dinner sometime
sir Saturday night
perfect
sounds good
Christian's right what am i doing dreamy
honey what makes me any different than
the next guy just sits around does
nothing you remember that plaque are you
still on the courthouse wall or the Ten
Commandments in it okay remember they
great big Christmas trees to be on the
courthouse long oh yeah whatever
happened Christmas in this town I mean I
mean sitting around here watching it
disappears like everybody else nobody
says anything did you ever think you'd
see the day with people were offended by
a cross of public to hell Christian's
right
I had been a coward passive and even
selfish
I had become so bitter and blind to what
was going on around me I asked God to
forgive me I kept thinking about my son
now is the time to honor his sacrifice
and show my grandson that the greatest
battle is doing what's right
mayor you okay ready i woke up about
midnight search the internet will just
about an hour ago and i am better than
okay i am absolutely fantastic oh good
council wants your views in writing
regarding the street improvements around
the new addition to the veterans home at
eleven-thirty you have a rotary media
Estelle's restaurant locate you might
want to put a sports jacket on instead
of that now what about the report
thought i had a key to the city storage
room top drawer silver keychain you ever
listen to me sure you say blah blah blah
Stells restaurant follow me but voila
Christmas angel why does that bring back
some memories what kind of memories hey
Charlie Charlie how you got your boys up
to no good probably what's the news last
night at the City Council meeting it
seems like all we want to do is get
excited about nothing oh they want to
get excited about something they can
help me bring Christmas back to this
town and I mean we're coming back in a
big way I am talking angels I'm talking
majors I'm talking Rees I'm talking to
birth of Jesus kept talking about
Christmas
he's not joking gentlemen did you happen
to know that about a hundred and fifty
years ago Christmas was made a federal
and legal holiday didn't know that a
religious and secular holiday they're
using the threat of lawsuit keep
Christmas push back into the churches
and homes and out of public places and
schools and uh speaking of school do you
know that our children are not allowed
to sing Christmas songs can our souls
well we always did oh yeah you're not
allowed to anymore and a public school
teacher is allowed to teach objectively
about the origins of Christmas in the
classroom and no didn't know that well
they can they don't but they can hey we
can have a nativity scene as long as
other religious symbols are nodes at the
same time school districts across the
United States are taking Christmas break
off the calendar completely you're
replacing it with winter break you know
that that's right some towns no red and
green lights some pounds no trees some
pounds no decorations at all it's not
because it's illegal there is no law
against it just a bunch of people that
are afraid of what Christmas is really
about Oh gentlemen that stops today at
least here in Mount Columbus
sleigh bells ring I'm listening in
mayor how does it worse it looks illegal
to me they're good huh are you sure it's
not unconstitutional Randy what part of
nowhere you having a hard time with if
you're getting nervous go look it up mr.
mayor Connie Lee channel 7 can I have
just a moment of your time oh you bet
I'll be right now according to sources i
spoke with and i quote any religious
symbols displayed on public property is
a clear violation of the separation of
church and state the religious
decoration should be removed immediately
for his part mayor of ear had this to
say hey listen air the mayor's on TV
well I actually got the idea from the
grandson he was wondering why don't we
celebrate Christmas around here anymore
tell you the truth I just couldn't give
him a good answer not illegal so I
figured by the time I'm done I want
Mount Columbus to be known as Christmas
city all right Thank You mayor you're
welcome Merry Christmas you heard right
the Christmas city the mayor's rain
we're legend back to this little town
what a hog I think she's kind of cute
motorcycling moron
Oh Broadway you are an elusive mistress
indeed Oh ladies you ready okay whatever
though but saw no we are with space
aliens who have traveled from afar well
the King except us not to worries endure
has been foretold that the king will be
one this night on planet earth and he
will accept all who seek him and find
him but how do we know it is the true
king the supernova will light our way to
the pot of gold there the king will be
just as predicted in the scrolls of
plutonium oh yes excellent excellent
madison lindsey where have you been
hiding mmm-hmm that was very very good
you are my aliens you know I think with
you two in the cast this will be our
most memorable winter Space Odyssey ever
yeah you bet it well excuse me nothing
Thanks there's no is VP on these
invitations oh you don't need one
everybody shows up oh and you put
Christmas instead of holiday party I
know we have been putting holiday for
ten years I am so proud of Bob mm-hmm
Greg's coming in oh yeah aunt and it
we're just having dinner it's not a date
it's not a date Oh No hmm come on it's a
date think it's a date
yeah the mayor's nothing on Tuesdays
it's the me resistant what can I do for
you doesn't work on Tuesdays well then
get me the deputy mayor deputy mayor we
can barely afford our part-time mayor
but the mayor's the pharmacist who is
this the hammer warren hammer snip that
the warren hammerschmidt up to mtv
exactly obviously your mayor is not
fully cognizant of the statutes that
pertain to the separation of church and
state can you remember all that look
before this gets elevated to a level
which I'm sure the mayor would like to
avoid tell him that I only suggested
that he offer a public apology to the
community and take down those religious
decorations and we will pretend this
never happened if you have any questions
about this at all you just did call me
thank you okay thank you did you get
loose no
sure all over the internet we are having
some major legal problems here I think I
got a call from Warren hammerschmidt
himself who wore an ambushment the big
guy the guy that's a he's on all the TV
talk shows he told me that he told me to
tell you this roaring down kid he said
to take down all religious Christmas
decorations and make a public apology he
told you to tell me that exactly I got
an email what is it mayor they're
threatening to have the governor with
whole matching funds for the veterans
home for Christmas decorations no yeah I
know how you get when you're backed into
a corner no Randall you don't know how I
could but I tell you what you can do you
put together some sort of news
conference for this evening it's not
just about Christmas anymore have you
ever noticed that the mere mention of
Jesus nowadays seems to rub people the
wrong way yeah well I'm very tired not
standing up for what I believe in so why
are you standing there
qari I love you so much
I just want so badly to hold you right
now just be with you and Christian I saw
your picture thank goodness you take
after your mom
what kind of cheese you guys making it
to play Oh Christian just don't we carry
there and everywhere what about your
teacher what's he gonna say ol mr.
bodewell yeah probably nothing and how
you figure cuz being complete mr. mayor
your actions have been described as
reckless and insensitive how do you
respond well if trying to restore a
holiday that the majority of our
citizens enjoy but fuel sore heads don't
makes me reckless and sensitive yeah I'd
say that pretty much describes me if I
made the mayor's actions are not
reckless he's just trying to be
sensitive to all face during this
special time of the year mayor you hung
a banner on the town's water tower that
reads Christmas city don't you think
that could be offensive December 25th is
Christmas Jesus's birthday Christmas is
also a national holiday so here in the
city of Mount Columbus this holiday
season will be a Christmas holiday not a
winter holiday me Christmas is for
everyone if you're a Muslim you want to
pray to all in the middle of the town
square by all means please it's one of
your rights if you're Jewish you want to
display your menorah and blow your
shofar go ahead and accept my admiration
for standing up for what you believe in
but don't tell me in the majority of us
that believe in Jesus Christ that we
don't have the right to celebrate the
day of his birth because it's Christmas
mister man the state cannot in any way
promote a religious holiday
we're not we're acknowledging it's the
Christmas season excuse me if I could
say something here at first it was kind
of hacking me off what Bob was doing and
everything but you know I get where he's
coming from I mean Bob's is trying to
fix what's already a national holiday
Bob can't do that yes I can and we will
as a matter of fact I'm gonna lead by
example you're all welcome to come by my
house and see the nativity scene that
I'm building I mean come on people it's
Christmas peace on earth goodwill toward
men mr. mayor it is our job to protect
all people regardless of their color
creed race or religious persuasion the
people of Mount Columbus deserve fair
and equal treatment but Bell you don't
have any jurisdiction here and you will
not intimidate me you are breaking the
law show me the law well then you are
violating the Constitution mr.
hammerschmidt that is a lie and you know
it you and your organization have been
putting fear into every week needs
school board and city council in this
country most the time you're standing on
nothing more than intimidation and I'm
telling you mr. hammerschmidt that your
intimidation tactics will not work here
in Mount Columbus merry Christmas
everyone you do warrant all right let's
go over the plan I've been doing some
serious research and the real Christmas
Story shepherd's find the baby king not
a lance who really weird you can't be
serious well I didn't know I never read
the Bible it's okay it's okay let's just
stay focused okay well Lindsay and I
have been working really hard and we
came up with the name operation
christmas operation christmas
come up with a cooler name than that and
what do you suggest oh I got one um how
about operation global cooling how about
operation aliens operation alien how
about operation super shepherds yeah how
about not something with the word super
and it always sounds good or super bad
guys guys it's its operation christmas
how about operation sabotage how about
if you're not in on it you can't name it
just because I'm not in the stupid play
doesn't mean I'm not in on ok its
operation christmas christmas ok here's
the stage we're gonna need somebody to
be right here maybe chris or maybe not
you're gonna have to put a clamp on the
rope so that nobody can close the
curtains during the play and then gonna
have to also have somebody here I don't
know maybe Chris or whoever he's gonna
have to put a lock on the light box so
they can't turn the lights off why do I
do Reagan you are the dancer you just
keep on
what Trudy um I I just I just wanted to
say that you know this feels so wrong
and yet he's so right thank you for that
Trudy ok this meeting is adjourned go
pre you have a lot of work to do guys in
schooling oh really Madison I'm sorry
but your sabotage plan it's missing
something are you dumb there's no impact
there is plenty of impact it just sounds
lame look Chris it's a lie if we don't
tell the real Christmas Story you want
to talk about link you won't even help
us that's lame this president of the
City Council have know what's going on
christmas is going on earning I think
Ernie and the council just need
clarification about your intentions Bob
well it's really very simple we're
taking her freedoms for granted couple
years ago my son they mentioned the word
God in His Val Victorian speech well
today we would be sued by some long
humanist Bob we all miss the good old
days I am NOT talking about the good old
days Ernie we're not losing some
endangered species of fish our freedoms
are being taken away from us one by one
well that's how we're taking him back
one at a time we're gonna start with
Christmas now if i want to put up an
activity see my front yard I'm gonna do
it if you want to put a christmas tree
on the courthouse lawn like we used to
then we're gonna do it gentlemen it's
been fun
he means on the road
where's the mayor going something about
getting a big Christmas tree for the
courthouse lawn take care of that matter
now immediately do it
not one channel plays real christmas
music anymore if i have to listen to
that guy sing about his grandma being
run over by a reindeer one more time hey
I will take care of you my friend gonna
get a big o Christmas tree o Christmas
tree that is back to go to good buk buk
buk you go good job we three kings of
all red ah yeah
bring a torch turn that izybelle Idol
what
I couldn't sleep for about a year after
Thomas died we both lost her best friend
sorry then I'm gonna talk about how to
get through it I threw myself into
motherhood at first then I realized I
was a young mother in a widow with
nothing I just trying anything to get my
life back and start over five years
turned into 10 10 de almost 15 I'm sorry
I wasn't there for you be I was just so
young I never seen a broken heart before
I was too young to know what to do or
how to help I'm sorry you apologize too
much sorry let's get out of here
see that little scar
when Thomas and I were in fifth grade he
SAT over there the gazebo and we cut our
thumbs and press them together
he thought it made us blood brothers
he loved you like a brother
perfect turn around let me see it's
beautiful oh no no what yours Merry
Christmas she just loves you
everything's gonna be okay don't you go
get something to eat
and look at you hey Dottie hmm I'm
really glad to have you oh me too well
you are a space alien if I have ever
seen one nano an open see that little
boy over there yeah don't you go talk to
him all right
mine's week JJ when she was little there
in the Old Mission she would she would
hide in a hoe coat rack play hide and
seek with everybody oh and then she'd
climb on the counter and help me serve
the meals whatever happened with JJ
anyway well it's complicated I've never
stopped praying for her her to come back
we're talking
what I need to ask you something
what
despot think that I should have talked
home instead of enlisting hello
sweetheart do you think anyone could
have talked Thomas out of serving in the
military no it that's that something
will never know and although he won't
admit it I believe that Bob thinks he's
responsible he just doesn't know what to
say to you no one's responsible things
just happen right
I love you enough of that dotty is
killing the meal for you oh thanks so I
had a nice time with Greg the other
night and and I told him I needed some
time to think I mean I know I've known
him forever but daddy the health
department is gonna close the mission
over Christmas curtain music Jennifer
Oh
woohoo very good very good very good
okay ladies curry bow and scurry bow and
scurry scurry scurry scurry scurry and
you're off one moment please Stewart
Stewie could we at the end of that like
you know have the lights come up sort of
gradually illuminating the stage and
it's sort of like with the music and
sort of like a rainbow otic kind of a
crescendo we could have the equipment
was built after nineteen thirty simple
yes you know we do thank you all right
Hugh the aliens be holds endure the star
in the east it will guide us but Zond or
where but spacings who chose from afar
leukemia except us not to fears endure
it's been foretold that the king will be
born this night on planet earth and he
will accept all I'm seek him and find
him but how do we know it is the true
thing the supernova will light our way
to the pot of gold and we will find the
king just as predicted in the scrolls of
plutonium well well well bet mickey hey
Tanya Plutonia
she tone yeah ploutonion it is it just
me is it just me whatever okay let's go
to the conclusion please everybody'd
Center this is the silent night wintry
night let me feel the cold blasted door
somebody's gonna get trapped in here
slam shucks walks tight mr. Leonard may
I talk to you for a sec about that door
according to warren hammerschmidt mayor
beer is flaunting the will of the people
as he continues his public display of
civil disobedience as you can see a huge
Christmas tree now stands defiantly on
the courthouse lawn after nearly two
decades of absence this latest
development makes tonight's City Council
meeting even more interesting you know I
appreciate your convictions but not
everybody feels the same as you
we could make this all go away every
year my family throws me a little
birthday party Christmas is about
Jesus's birthday and about there being
dadgum peace on earth and goodwill to
everybody I say we all enjoy that tree
like we used to and everybody else just
take a chill pill mr. hammerschmidt
people tradition is not the issue here
not even close mayor Revere has taken
the law into his own hands to promote
his own religion that is a ridiculous
you have overstepped your boundaries
mayor you have overstepped your
boundaries mr. hammerschmidt I take
offense to your politically motivated
actions and I'm here to protect my
rights as an American citizen what about
the rights of the people you serve what
about the rights of the people you
pretend to serve these liberties are you
protecting what's that supposed to be
you're removing my freedoms my rights
and my heritage as a Christian America
we are talking about the separation of
church and state will please tell these
people and me what are your objectives
you are supposed to represent all the
citizens of your community equally
unlike your organization that represents
anti-american cause
so we are not barks right non-partisan
up well it's like what Charlie said I'm
just trying to bring back some tradition
we all enjoyed before organizations like
yours came in to take them out of public
you really need to check your facts
stepping on your toes Emily most people
know what you and your cronies in
Washington have been doing for years
well as you can see your fine mirrors
trying to pick a political fight with me
hey we didn't start this you're trying
to tell us how we can celebrate a
national holiday that would be like
calling Columbus Day great explorers day
it's just stupid now you've been pushing
your agenda down our throats for so long
I don't think you know what the truth is
and as much as I may hate what you're
doing you're free to do it just like I'm
free to celebrate Christmas mr. Chairman
I did not come to your fine little town
to condemn a holiday I'm here to make
sure that civil liberties are preserved
why don't you tell these fine citizens
you didn't have the health department
closed down their mission of the cross
while you're preserving their liberties
I don't know anything about that
councillor a few moments ago I obtained
a directive from the county court judge
to have your religious decorations for
move in the county courthouse you did
what the judge's orders will be carried
out ASAP meeting adjourned
Oh
stars shine so
on your snow
smiling so one
stars
Oh
we'll find
that night stay up all night all in all
those hand motions just to see them
blown make sure we get it right come out
tonight okay okay and careful with the
little about this those are not trash
bags very very expensive okay now you're
excused but do not be late to office
okay I'm sure hey do you hmm hopefully
the audience will understand that
Christmas is about peace and joy and
love won't we get in trouble for this
yes we will you know guys this can
really jeopardize my position at stage
10 guys we can't get scared and
chickened out I mean we roll in this
together yeah everyone just got a pledge
not to tell anyone about this plan yeah
k tree my lips are sealed sorry mine
mine too me too it's a total secret we
got a pledge on something everybody look
around
this must be Bob's what is that it's a
medal of honor bob is a hero well you
know I got a medal of honor once you
were here in a war oh I guess that
wasn't the same thing right then let's
pledge but I've heard Bob's more stories
all my life if we want to save the
veteran home funding and what's left of
Bob's good name the council has no
choice Charlie you're his best friend I
figured you'd want to tell him councils
made its decision
no one's coming as farty are they
I am so sorry daddy ah I didn't count on
this if this is the way it's gonna go so
we told you I'm behind you all the way
hi Bob I was at the party earlier and I
noticed something was missing and a
couple of folks from the mission decided
that since they were in the neighborhood
did stop by merry Christmas everyone
come in command on Christmas
see
Bob you mind if I talk to you privately
thank you Christmas mayor is this true
you know buddy all those stories about
rescue missions that told you about
they're all true
there's one mission I've never told
anyone about not even you it's not true
boy what's not true what they're saying
about your grandpa your grandfather was
a hero how do you know about my grandpa
I know everything about that mission you
see boy was there he was my sergeant Bob
Revere is one of the bravest soldiers
I've ever met every mission he performed
was perfect Albin one my guys and I
rescued some POWs
we're trying to go to an extraction
point I knew the only chance they had
survival was the dark and making it to
the extraction point my corporal begged
me to rest those men I didn't listen to
him all I wanted to do is get him out
get him safe get those boys home I mean
terrible mistake my foot hit a trip wire
I should have seen it I didn't it's
pushing him too hard flares went up
bombs went off whole thing I remember
was the concussion it with me into a
trench all right side went numb then it
all just broke loose my corporal took
around I can feel Leonard's bladders
friend helped my mare
I could hear men men screaming open what
am I being died that night tried to save
him but her breakfast take my guys that
died that night are the heroes thing he
come hitters the mayor of Mount Columbus
was fired last night by the City Council
because they claimed he was in violation
of separation of church and state we go
now to Connie Lee on the scene thanks
Jessica just when the mayor thought it
couldn't get any worse new revelations
have surfaced that the mayor has a few
skeletons in his closet questions
surrounding the mayor today are about
what really happened during his time of
military service oh here in front of the
Revere body here the mayor's grandson
Chris thanks for joining us Chris what
do you think about what's going on with
a grandfather listen lady I don't know
much about Christmas and I don't pretend
to but I do know it's the time of year
when people do nice things for each
other and I don't get why everyone's
getting so upset about a big beautiful
tree of lights and decorations on it you
know bob says it's not even about the
tree it's about the freedom to do it and
if bob says it's a good thing then it
must be 0 and and what they're saying
about him not being a real war hero
that's ridiculous he is a hero all right
thanks Chris well you heard right seems
the root of this controversy isn't so
much about Christmas after all but about
freedom according to the mayor's
grandson back to you in the studio uh
Jessica I'm sorry in an unrelated story
yeah see I just kind of like the robe
under it it gives me a little more book
ha
looks like things are really heating up
at Mount Columbus Jessica what's wrong
we go now live to Connie Lee who is
standing by and Mount Columbus with
breaking news Connie thanks Jessica the
drama just continues to unfold here
mouthful of us as you can see high above
me Bob Revere the ex-mayor what he
called Christmas city is trying
desperately to foist across the front of
this mission building now channel 7 has
learned that the cross was removed a
number of years ago after a local
citizen complained at the claw
Oh
grandpa good see you got to go back it's
too dangerous mayor 90 Junkers off the
roof before someone gets hurt
can somebody go help them
one more time just doing it
pleasure
let's get one more green dragon
man
who needs help what took you so long it
seems a member of a local motorcycle
gang has come to Revere's aid and he's
helping him pull the old cross into
place and now whose grandson Christian
Revere is helping in the effort
run
make it one get you off ever as you
probably have heard I am no longer the
mayor of this town so tonight I stand
here a freedom fighter this country was
founded by freedom fighters men and
women who love their country and their
Creator 400 years ago our forefathers
left the religious oppression of another
land to build this one and the first
thing they did the first thing they did
was to put across on the shores of the
Atlantic but it was more than a cross it
was a symbol that in this land a citizen
has the freedom to worship as he or she
desires or the freedom not to worship it
all my fight is it about colored lights
or a tree on the city square my fight is
about freedom and taking back what has
been stolen from us we are losing
freedoms one by one that our forefathers
our brothers in arms and my son died for
it is time we stood up for what they
died for but what we believe in our
rights are being destroyed perhaps
forever but don't you see we're letting
it happen
we're asleep
we sleep and they come in like a thief
in the night and they take what's left
wake up we can't sleep anymore wake up
and look around you look what's coming
over the horizon we can't let the enemy
take one more inch not one more inch we
can't be silent anymore the silence has
to stop and it has to stop today young
men and women are dying in foreign lands
to preserve the freedoms that we enjoy
every single day can you hear them just
listen it's their voices from the grave
they're wondering if they died in vain
do we dare diminish their sacrifice by
our silence well if your answer is no
than you think about this when history
is written will history say you stood by
and you did nothing oral history say
that you fought you thought like those
brave souls you thought to preserve the
memory of the young men and women that
have given everything for this country
and for you we fight for freedom we
fight for freedom we fight for freedom
what
it's okay hey it's okay
he's doing his job
there's no bomb
I want you to go see the play
penis
compass
Greg
right here
turn around please just watching hadn't
stepped in
grandpa
I know the truth I found this in the
Attic
if you weren't a hero before your honor
as the children of Mount Columba
celebrate their holiday with a winter
play the former mayor of Mount Columbus
will spend his holiday in jail reporting
live from on Columbus junior high school
Connie Lee channel 7 news back to you in
the studio Jessica it could be the last
chapter in a very dramatic story Jessica
what are you doing here something I
should have done a long time ago Walter
I'm going home to spend Christmas with
my family well happy holidays Jessica
and we'll be right back after these
messages what the heck's going on here
so you're the mayor prove it get us out
of here you did the right thing Bob
our annual holiday play entitled a
window space oddity ever than historical
look at our glorious beginnings welcome
to Mount Columbus junior high school
theater I've Ronaldo belt well your
director please enjoy tonight's show we
will begin in just a few moments good
crowd pinkrod septum superintendent
Jones there on the second row don't get
me started did you see his musical
production last year amateur miracle on
the high seas more like a mutiny on the
low b-flat oh yeah dad cute crooked
Oh
what's going on it they just get nervous
news
now still icky the aliens
Stuart King the aim is killing me
what's going on
behold don't be afraid I am an angel and
I bring you good news of great joy which
will be to all nations this is not going
blue
was the curtain
kill the lights it's locked
bleh there's a breaker box in the closet
kill the lights jumbo game electricity
get out of my way you're useless
so don't break her boxing here
yeah dinner later oh this will be a sign
you will find the baby wrapped in
swaddling clothes lying in a manger and
the angels said glory to God in the
highest and on earth peace and goodwill
to men the Shepherd's made their way to
Bethlehem and that's where they found
the Christ child just as the angel told
them they would just a few days ago he
really didn't care that much about the
real meaning of Christmas but then I
found a video and I want you all to
watch it
Carrie
I love you so much
I want so much to hold you and to be
with you
why miss you
I'm Kristen
I saw your picture thank goodness you
take after your mom
the guys hum I just want you to know
that I'm fighting for you over here for
our freedom I do it because I love my
country and because I love you I'll I've
been thinking that a lot of guys like us
have given their lives and places like
this so we can all enjoy our freedom
back at home man can't even celebrate
Christmas they'd be killed if they did I
mean
just keep playing pretty for our wounded
please please pray for the families that
have lost a loved one over here freedom
is worth it
we're gonna win this
the other witness
god bless you guys I love you Mary
all is bright
well done well
ok the judge wants you out of there
mister I love you
time so
now you've been unfair to you soon
credibly unfair
I hated myself all these years so what
happened to your husband
gave me the creeps grants man ever
could you ever forgive me
heard his performance on the radio it
was absolutely fantastic
Bob it wasn't on the radio
started i was listening to a great guy
whatever the great guy there was no one
in there except you and lofty mayor IQ
better go home and get some rest
you
hi Daddy Merry Christmas
good
just cool
let's all go home
you
Oh
whoa
these commies right
I
our arrest these people arrest the whole
town I thought your organization was
against prison overcrowding loosen up
Warren it's Christmas
merry christmas merry Christmas to
everyone
I love my country and I love being free
but I now know that freedom only comes
with great sacrifice from each and every
one of us
you and I have a rendezvous with destiny
we can preserve for our children the
last man on earth or we can sentence
this generation of young people to take
the first step into a thousand years of
Darkness if we are destined to fail if
this way of our is to be lost then at
least that our children and our
children's children say of us but it
didn't fail because we fail to try let
them say that at least we did all that
could be done in the one moment allowed
up here on earth
the red is for the blood that flowed in
places we forgotten the white resembles
in cell
in some ways we can lost
it stands for vigilance and holding fast
to righteousness what happened
lots of
the stars are for remembering the glory
and the victory we're proud
this is freedom
this
confidence collide along the street in
the last ounce of courage my
our Patriots and hero
where grace abounds and evil dies true
three sounds above lies it's only found
one way and here we
free day
hey
I
this is free
oh that speaks of liberty
beyond our institutions if this is a
reality
where are the solution
ow
Oh
for life eternally
without
it's what we
this is
either though the fight is long the
enemy may wound us the stripes are for
the rays of hope that never cease to
lead us guide us home