you're my see Claire off either
undeclared items will be confiscated job
declare the ginseng to customs why park
they may act pay 50 bucks in duty I know
what am I just hiding my pants they
never know brilliant bahon better yet
why don't have the master hold on to it
they'll never searched him because he's
too respectable anything haha very good
idea of homeless both of you better idea
I'll not hear any more of your nonsense
I just don't understand where we have to
pay duties and everything we buy yeah I
don't care what you say just listen to
me avoid trouble pay the duties that's
it I know best
wait
now watch it's the ambassador and he
deserves respect he's treated like
royalty he doesn't have to pay any do
this how about Wow oh all right let's go
okay okay okay who shot someone push it
Lisa oh I apologize is it a hung for how
much you can watch insane super do i do
a task once we get the tribe I look for
the box hey what a terrific idea what's
that quick throw me down again and I'll
hide some more your ago Eric you must
have tit would you you're so clumsy come
on get up violin
wow what a crowd why do you go get us in
and I'll get attached all right i'll see
you on board nothing to declare
huh great easy easy he kept rushing me
that's good hey where you going stop
come back hey huh let me remind you the
hero lives but a few seconds Master
holds on to his life but he stole your
wallet and I took it back that's not the
issue the point is the stronger man
knows more important to forgive that it
is to fight that's right was I thinking
your turn how about this hey you know
better than that but there's no I
try it again I'm driving it Hey look at
the White cred Wow ever you eres even
like that it's to your plane come on can
we start over you still have a chance
where I can see it ready
are you okay oh my bad death her I'm
sorry sir is this yours I'm afraid so be
real careful yes sir ready ready
hey uh what's this we caught a cheating
hurry up
oh is it I'm fine yeah good idea father
Oh Gail about this let me go find
something you really gonna like I don't
take a ready to eat but I think how
about a nice roasted chicken we can find
a one how about a hug yeah no packets
you to want to look around a bit it's
okay I'll be fine here come on stay out
of trouble you hit again and make sure
you come right back
sorry sorry this place I think I'm gonna
be sick hey this way
vegetations yes I see making me hungry
maybe we could grab a roll hey what are
you doing here nothing you think you
have reservation hell with you go on
back check inside I've had enough go on
one more time then you're off the train
what do we do now I get an idea
sorry sir what
wait
next time I gotta throw you hey listen
I'm not a traitor you hear me you and
what are we fighting about don't play
games you hit me
back again why don't you give up oh no
oh man apologize what did you say how
dare you call me a traitor look II sorry
fine but let's do what we want here who
hey show respect stairs to respect to
you you must be kidding me let's make
this fair yeah ready
Wow drunken boxing hmm that's right I'm
the master you think so again come on
let's go you come you know I can like
you isn't worth my time I show me good
hi good wash & beer quick what do you
call that one it's a call turtle holding
Y bouquet don't play the flute da dee da
and this one nursing a hangover okay
stand up
your kung fu is pretty good young man
you're not too bad yourself that drunken
boxing was a
impressed basically it's slow and you
have no power it's pathetic what I can't
defeat eneko pou I show you power that's
nice but you're at a time hi I'm young
and strong I've got lots of time but
your trains leaving over there nice clay
oh man but now he's gonna get it alright
come back here between
do your hand
hey best luck get what you're after
the teasing
ginseng alright everyone here get up
gather your luggage for inspection
everyone now come on you wake up hmm
mine what are you doing something has
been stolen we're gonna find it guard
search them all right what is all that
you take it out hurry up Joe open these
appear humph let me see they're gone
what else come on green toad fixed do
your phone gincy what's that the one you
dropped open that you mean this one
what's that tried yak okay next shit now
the other box come on let me see the
other box they're gone not that that let
me see that one not that one the one
over there which one on the seat that
one between you this no no no yeah well
that one meets the ginseng he wasn't
hiding it will then open it up what are
you waiting for it's over that box right
now excuse me sir these gentlemen are
clearly physicians from you not why
don't you give him a break huh I don't
give breaks I give orders show me your
papers come on let's see him here
sir my apologies Shh sir
he's counterintelligence he's with the
central government better not challenges
all right next car search up there next
guy I'm amazed they would think we were
stealing it is such an insolent put that
away
do you all realize what this means they
certainly won't buy the rest of the
shipment without it you know I'm truly
astounded at the inn competence of all
of you you severely damaged my
reputation with a British Museum of Art
they've asked me to deliver the Jade
seal of the Emperor and I have every
intention of fulfilling that request I
don't care you do it I want it back yes
sir we think we know who the thief is
Sir get him yes John we're having a bit
of trouble with the workers of the steel
factory I trust your deal with it of
course sir I know just what to do in the
situation I promise you'll have no more
trouble let's make sure yes sir
it's Grand Slam let's go let's go no
Dean Boise okay good mommy hahaha for
now you're good ki with every time
domestic is back yeah yeah the masa
hello what took you so long I was in the
kitchen stand back ya miss me what are
y'all doing it's you I'm so glad you're
home how was your trip is everything all
right all right Oh
mah mah jongg I how many times have I
asked you not to see patients while I'm
away you know it's illegal oh now I know
I'm not supposed to and I tried to wait
but I had no idea when you would return
so and besides if you were me I know you
would have done the same thing wow I bet
you won a lot perhaps I should examine
them uh-oh it's a female problem I can
handle it fey-hong would you prepare my
altar for me all right you should wash
your hands will need the auto ladder
over here please did you remember to
water the plants oh yes x man thank you
hey mom whose money son huh what was
that I do hear anything the altar hey
show a little respect he'll remember
your treatment next Friday ladies very
money hello mrs. Wong yeah how are you
has mr. Wang material she's inside any
news about my ginseng did he get it
let's ask him coming thank you Mr Tan
has come for his ginseng come on yeah
follow you so soon they're half that
isn't bad oh let me get that one it's
beautiful I brought you a whole route
where do you see it it's just in back
some tea ah yuck I please have a seat
I'll be right back thank you oh you're
gonna help me out when the master finds
out he'll kill me here or not um huh are
you doing step mark of you I don't know
what to do we're in such trouble I lost
it easy on the train what did you do now
oh yeah okay okay okay Shh please you
gonna help us out okay huh yes yeah you
just wanted 70 I think of something
gimme I leave up to you to come in madam
which we do about this you see that door
behind me you mean in the cabinet sure
there's a black box look inside another
jinxing account eyelets strychnine what
fool for you oh no matter please don't
tease me this way how are you team mr.
chain thank you very much son enjoy
you must be very hot let me help you mr.
jet
wow it's real now mr. chan I know you
have never seen a specimen as beautiful
as this at you oh and let me tell you
wait you see what happens to you when
you take it why women won't believe the
difference in your moments and you will
owe it all to the master what are you
doing with that rutabaga rutabaga this
is a rutabaga you mean it isn't ginseng
no silly of me of course it isn't
ginseng what I meant to tell you was
that you should stay away from rutabagas
sleepy like this one while you're taking
ginseng it causes gas and neutralizes
the effect or something like that mr.
chan I'm glad you remember to tell you
about that you know most people don't
realize that when you use Djinn see you
should avoid the use of rutabaga because
they're not a good makes know what good
luck now you think this looks like Jesse
oh yeah looks just like it where did you
find it fathers bonsai tree that's a
great idea just blame it on Cho okay how
hard to keep your father distracted this
boy that looks great great I'll juniors
the team excuse me may I have a word ah
just a second of course I can wait what
is it dear what come on just one minute
at this link and busy right now
sorry I couldn't wait any longer to tell
you hey hyung is all grown up now sunday
he will leave her house what oh you know
but why is it wet let me tell you I'm
glad you asked because was just picked
this morning you're really going to
enjoy the potency of this one is it
really powerful it's just me a little
bit a little brother around here could
take his know about this later don't be
rude please oh I will never forgive you
you shouldn't talk that way to me well
you never let me talk honey not now mr.
challenge you turn your back on me ok
roll that up tight to keep my eyes at
fresh make you a close to your heart
remember when I told you I said have
nice day right I really do think we need
to talk about us never yes thanks for
that ginseng ah everything is alright
that's fine ah keep it delay let miss
you out let's see what this is one I
assure you please this way mr. chunky I
don't know what to try to tell you my
love about me HS gone oh what's this all
about look if you don't want to talk
about this right now I understand you've
had a really long trip and you should
get some risk come on let's sit down
this valley please do the rest is good
idea right I better start taking better
care of myself I need to realize I'm not
getting any younger well why do you make
that look cuz i'm free he'll find the
tree don't be silly throw the pot away
that's not all what what happens if i
meet the change i steal me from those
roots oh I wish I could say the same
for sang she's calling down can you give
me some more fire just give me one
minute
10a
that was great thanks for the light
Wallace bedtime
it's at all hey
get them back to work for what go I'm
with you fool here now ring the bell go
on yes full thing what the hell you
doing now yeah what are you out of your
mind sorry I which is tolling we have a
new farming here new-fallen well
we seem to have fallen behind this month
so everybody works the night shift for
one month hold on so let's say we work
all those overtime hours for you then we
need overtime pay why you give us their
choice you either work the every time or
we close the steel mill town and you'll
all be without drops now you can take it
or leave it mr. Smith you can't
blackmail us anymore we work hard for
you and now we've had enough hold it
nobody's to leave you'll stay and work
do you understand that you can take my
job but you can't run my life you think
you can make us who you think you are
let's go
you're in our way
all of you right
get back to work
free
everyone up back to work great you see
it's very persuasive they're gonna get
right back to work yeah yeah yeah yeahs
latekka still hot yup yeah ok now it's
bloody impossible to sleep with all this
noise why don't we just buy a phonetic
bull they know that we've been through
this before Mr Wong refuses to sell its
ruining my life so why don't you go do
something about it yes
hey Vaughn you're working too hard you
need husband to run that snakes then huh
perfect tough for me huh yeah I bet
you'd be running away from these snakes
all day come on now why would I want to
pay some lazy man when I can do better
huh you know you make good porn but
seriously now for you know you don't
have man around so I worry about your
safety hey fuck I've been thinking let
me get you comfort how about drunken
boxing well you get that idea no one
does that if you really want to fight I
teach you the sci li foo boxing style oh
wise man speak what you looking at oh
you better work we've got customers
waiting they need to help now okay does
she know anyway hey Trisha huh wat vir
on a fillet of salmon and a power of a
fisherman ok hey where are you going
things ok what's getting late oh one
person and two others were gone that's
what have been my chest yeah thank you
you want this or not a customer waiting
oh yeah I'll be right there oh I hear
drunken boxing is the bed would he be
able to teach me haha course Andy hey
how about I born it for you huh oh no
that's all right how about later with
that we're discussing drunken boxing
when do you think you could teach me
anything would be fine you just let me
know fun you need real instructor to
learn how to fight may be chasing can
give you a lesson he doesn't teach a
style online it's for fighting drunken
master just for show you cannot win
fight that way forget him he's jealous I
like your son Bay hung time to admit it
your drunken boxing is no match for sci
li foo isn't that right you agree all
right that's right faster much better he
knows he has on who's fighting watch you
say to a challenge then out of my way I
sci li foo your drunken boxing and if I
lose you can have your fish at anything
else you want no charge on me listen you
can learn from Fei hung I don't need
your help
I appreciate the offer so there's too
many people here and somebody could get
hurt no way fey-hong you're going to
fight this time attention everybody
listen i'm jang song and this is one
fei-hung it's your lucky day I have
challenged him to a fight come on I'll
hold this remember it's an exhibition
match so come on haha drunken boxing
Oh
no really it was that all I think chinks
anyway I agree fell over yet yeah I'm
coming it's my stepmom Jack thank you
fine come on see you tomorrow yes thank
you what do I owe you for this you could
have it this a lot thank you thank you
everyone saw it was a draw right okay
okay show / tell me you're fighting
movie away we know your father would
kill your forgiving how can i replace
the gzip pawn my diamond necklace that's
how but why we'll be in big trouble mr
chan decides to root at treatment you
would do that just remember you owe me
one
hey that's the guy we're looking for
stay close to him while I go and get the
boss okay yes sir stop yeah uh okay
here's them I'm sure they're high
quality she got me from her husband look
I'm late already oh let's go okay so
what's the drug very serious in that
properties rice and grain was guests
before there was a drought with no
rainfall there will be no harvest and
that is hideous we must act now it's so
bad they so poor that some families have
to share a single pair pants Wow who
gets the random if you have job you wear
the pants oh hello sorry I'm late it's
all right how are you good and Claude
visit you great we should be going
aren't you meeting my wife 40 oh no not
mahjong again how can you say that it's
a fundraising meeting and you were
supposed to remind me oh I almost forgot
we've better be going then you don't
want to keep them waiting you should go
by not stuck again come on no mahjong
it's been called to our attention that
master Wong needs us to lend him some
money oh no no that's not me I'm sure I
speak for everyone will just take up a
collection I hear what I said I don't
personally need any of your money it's
for the Dropkick but your wife look it's
nothing to be ashamed of this could
happen to you I say if Mr Wong needs
money nothing right now you sure you
better not have said into the youngest
and say well I won't tell a soul besides
she's the one who talks in LA like you
don't how dare you say that I only told
my sister Zhu doesn't even know I came
here Oh ladies somebody's been talking
you always liked me look at that face
now that's enough take a look
hey Kissel's don't hit like that and I'm
only borrowing the money you're going to
have to give it back to me I know I know
I understand halls yeah come on short
wall oh so did you get it no I haven't
actually seen it but I'm sure they have
it well we can't waste any more time
grab the seal and we'll meet you out
front okay grab it and I'll see you
outside hey wait where's you've got to
learn to speak up
Oh leave it
you better run away what's this you
bumped me oh I'm sorry about that well
that's not good enough did I miss
something get on your knees and bow
right now what there must be other
tonight you are in on it I saw the whole
thing why don't you mind your own
business bitch hey who you calling bitch
I can't let him get away with that and
who the hell do you think you are
strutting around here like a peacock and
a bad english suit of yours I think I
should kick your ass oh yeah mum I go
right no way I wonder sky texture hey
you okay oh she wants to find will take
the two of you what huh you go to
Stuckey's again yeah Justin hey hey hey
you want me to go case yeah all right
Sheila oh maybe he'll give us an
exhibition time for dragon buck see what
about 5 i'll take care of him besides it
will be great publicity for the school
your dad will be happy to Kim's birthday
alright what are you scared of for if
you guys can't beat one
yeah what is that fucking boxing come on
now what do you do Kenny do more of
course you come down hey yo my gosh
please come take as much as you can
carry ok hey who's gonna pay for that
out all right then hey where'd they go
over there a thing let's go oh I'm going
Papa please oh but father will kill me
you can owe me you gonna lose that you
don't so just go ahead do you think it
gives him power
are you all right hmm one more helpful
what how's that what does it mean when
there's a picture of us car oh good
stuff
the last one really hit the spot monkey
drinks masters wine there was the crazy
cross you over the white powder like a
boss is erased what's gone you have a
hangover like dunken monkey
ego carries Wi-Fi oh yeah I shall here's
a Peter Piper playing the flute
go drinking may friending with the
master snake eyes and this one Jessie
right Scott gypsy 10 anos thirst apparel
come back against the wall hey you been
drinking yeah who's stopping right now
down the hatch Oh what are you doing
father you have a cute nose how will
they get along how are you dare fucking
again fighting okay you should huh what
was this all about fight it lynx-o to me
what what Disney every second why didn't
you tell us that ho Chi Lam needed more
money we would have helped you you know
we're all friends here oh the school
does indeed money what here you can take
charge of the funds we boys stop that no
matter want I should come you're not a
bad
go on doc follow up you didn't do any
better and what were you trying to do
you've ruined the school's reputation
they think we'll broke and you you idiot
what have I told you about drunken
boxing and fighting in the streets now
tell me is everything here so bad you
have to sell your diamond come on do you
really think I would have sold something
that's as precious to us I would never
don't lie to me how much money did you
lose playing mahjong well how much I
always win at mahjong you don't know
what you're talking about besides who
you going to believe me or friends
stemma I believe you anymore that's gave
you and I told you shut up you disobeyed
me I said absolutely no fighting and no
drinking and above all no drunken boxing
you even fun with me your own father you
just face your family name wait wait
hold on would you stop hitting him he
was just defending me I'm trying to
break my jaw I guess it's something you
don't care about can you woman it was
forbidden they could have killed him
don't you care about that oh sure like
it matters you're beating him listen
those guys ever did you're driving me
insane can't believe this
oh my god what's this what has happened
to my 300 year old bonsai yeah mr. Joe
Malone what went wrong you know this
garden is your responsibility and I
expect an answer well just hold on you
shouldn't blame everything on him that
way because I was actually the one who
did it I was practicing my kungfu and
then I tripped over that statue that's
right over there luckily the tree was
there to grab god only knows I could
have gotten killed but I see now you
don't care oh you know that that's not
it link I am so sick and tired of your
deception if you're going to hit me just
go on you know that's not a bad idea
it's time you show me respect that's not
gonna work this time you're driving me
out of my place your obedient kill me
kill me and another one inside me baby
so here I am
okay leave me alone like that you'll
have to stop this I don't it will you
all right are you doing no this is all
my fault please who ought to be careful
get bottom a chair quickly what are you
waiting for I'm begging you Lee sit over
there you'll be all right sorry ah yeah
you oh it was an accident me let me help
you no of course I didn't he's the baby
all right stop it he oh good are you
comfortable that's the walking I keep
mrs. Chan is here she says she has a bit
of a problem you stay right here I'll be
right back miss Chan congratulations but
I really proud of me thank you ah mrs.
Chan it's a pleasure dr. Wong huh this
really isn't ginseng huh I showed it to
another doctor and he says it's
poisonous now I not sure where you got
it but but you've surely been misled it
has made my husband deadly you thank God
you only brought half of it you owe me
and you're going to have to take the
blame for this mess now
mm-hmm forgive me uncle oh yes get the
snake extract I can assure you do a
recover if you give him this ah dr. one
oh this is wonderful I promise I won't
tell anyone it must have been a mistake
good demon take
well
get over your toe what's this how could
you do such a thing are you out of your
mind huh you are destroying my
reputation here you go Father you drop
your bonsai tree that's it I'm gonna
kill you ruin me oh it was stolen off
the train and he'd get it back oh shit
what am I saying see he was trying to
save you some tax how would he have
known that the ginseng would be stolen
the ginseng was stolen even so he still
lied to me no not acceptable you
shouldn't defend him he set the thief in
a drunk just stay out of it I'm sir yeah
you like some wine just stay right there
I'll give me some light come on open
you're going to fight me down i disown
you you are not my son now you better do
as I say get out of here oh no you back
after him choke don't let him go
ja that way yes
I've never seen you drink so much you
know your father's going to be very
angry with you Faye Hong let's not talk
about this bring me another drink keep
it coming oh no way that's it for
tonight excuse me miss I want us up here
something i should say the oceans crying
but I see you play for me now okay
I am so sad I was so happy and I'm alone
with no home what can I do even uh
father why I be hurting all the time if
only I could go home by the listen to me
know what can I could you grab to make
you proud
why did you there he is right over there
he doesn't look so bad oh yes he is he's
real tough fighter well let's just see
that no matter what cute party's over
suggest your go oh you'll stop that you
shut up listen to me the rest of you go
on home come on get out of here yeah you
gotta leave God moolah what happened do
the music are you the drunken boxer sure
I'm pretty drunk but I don't know how
about dog seems just faking
it's matter you can't even fight me
now out of my weight what are you doing
some on your goddamn business no is this
some kind of joke no one no you should
have seen it he couldn't be stopped ask
anyone stop let you kill me oh look at
you get up and fight me come on get this
drunk out of my sight go go on kill him
wait not yet don't kill him teach him a
lesson
hey hon
up that way
hey hon don't be ashamed when we were
kids we used to go naked all the time
sure found your sooner you'll be okay
just give it some time by the way I have
some good news too just listen to me
guess what every woman in town wants to
be your wife it's the truth hey all
right MA dry your eyes other I know I
have a good reason to put a drunken
boxing those who practice you frequently
wind up as alcoholics not the phone
users restraint and self-discipline but
that's more difficult than you might
think it's true that out mahoe can make
the body loose in its pain threshold
higher but it's difficult to drink the
proper amount many drunken box has
become nothing more than drunken fools
the odds are bringing shame and disgrace
upon oneself and one's family is just
too great it also reminds me there's an
ancient proverb that equates a drinking
of alcohol with water boats can float on
water or so it says but they can sink in
it too now that's a profound lesson I
have only one question what whose boat
are we talking about
I drink again
hey there Fei hung I'm glad to see that
you're okay now come on let's get up and
thank all your friends here for helping
you come on hug your kick thank you
you should you'll be better now everyone
asleep how's the baby oh he's just fine
let him be oh all right
sorry excuse me is he here he might be
it's private I know who sent you keep
your distance you know you're not just
pretending hey ho who's that hold it hey
whenever you surrounded okay huh I'm
talking to you oh yeah would you stop
Lisa I hope you can forgive us I have
one key I apologize you are very famous
meeting you is an honor I am foo in chi
foo and G are most decorated Manchu
officer i think is it true yesterday
it's on honor welcome thank you right
this way good evening
I guess that man is someone important
trust me if he was important he wouldn't
be hitting women what he Oh think about
it what keep setting we have to find it
Hey look in the parlor when you're done
yes ma'am you'll have no idea where you
left him no i don't where could it be Oh
might know tonight okay steady she's
quite a handful Oh toe what's the day
box I had where did you put it I don't
know what is that ground garlic I mean
dating your hand we found it hey hyung
are you going I'm not finished with that
mine when you surprise me the baggage
car I was trying to get back the Jade
seal that capacitor morally headstone I
wound up with your ginseng instead tell
me something there must be a hundred JCS
in our Museum as this one so special hey
hun they all are special think about
this today they plunder a seal it seems
small tomorrow they take another and the
next thing you know the great wall is
gone and what's next our children must
travel abroad just to see their history
so don't you see that you and I are the
only possible defense from governments
trying to strip us of our culture so I
hope you can help me do this if
the future generations of our people all
right I'll be honored to help Thank You
fei-hung it's awfully quiet all of a
sudden where is everyone yeah that's no
one here I'll go take a look what
what do we do follow me
oh they started yeah I see the funds
begun sounds great when you have the axe
gang you're sure to get the job done
that's what we're paying for
oh my god
hi
sure take it off okay
I
Oh
you
what's this what's going on don't get
involved you don't out of here no go on
huh that's
you'll be all right this oil seal yes I
know you're going to get the worry I'll
find it the embassy go quickly what do
we do tonight coolermaster my father
would take care of you I promise
what you thinking nothing
may I give you light oh this please
pick it up what's wrong with you oh come
on you're almost kill me dude what are
you doing here me what are you doing it
come on so where's the seal how should I
know let's go fish and lets you see you
don't
looking for dumping is this what brought
you here I hope you don't mind we've
taken the liberty to document your stay
at our magnificent embassy please do
enjoy our hospitality you can go
straight to hell
Oh that'll be all gentlemen we'll
continue the plan as scheduled yes
officer thank you things have worked out
rather well now that we have the Jade
seal back and a way to acquire perché
lamp that's right I've already sent the
embassy photographs of Fei hung in his
friend to master Wong he'll sell just
like I told you he has no choice make
sure he understands John we expect him
to vacate the PO Chi Lam immediately Oh
we'll plan to execute Fei huh damn those
boys thought the understand there's
nothing we can do as an embassy they are
exempt from the loss of China well maybe
we can reason with him how goes sit up
you know what they want a right to PO
Chi Lam they just wanted to return the
scene they aren't the criminals yo yo
shit with him this is all your fault
you're impossible and you're his father
we're running out of time we've got to
do something you're right I refuse how
can I you know that this land has been
in our family for centuries there has
always been a school here what would you
do just give it up I'll never do it oh
really what were his mother have done I
bet I know just
we need your wisdom what I never why can
we do for hey hon can you help
release them you may let them go
you okay just go on
great why you hurt ok step mom just look
at you I'm gonna be all right are you
okay master some bruises but he'll be
fine so what will we do now what do you
mean Master Wong has saw the school to
the embassy he did what how would it be
don't you see they made him sell it he
had to it they would kill you both
you're just lucky to be alive say huh
this fight is over we can't do this
anymore I hope you know your father has
sacrificed everything I wished it cute
with you now fair hung that is enough
life's changes are like a moving River
what's here today is gone tomorrow and
tomorrow brings a whole new journey
let's move forward and live so when will
the ship believing it's Tuesday and
everything's ready yes ready in wedding
sir good good I want to close down the
factory lay off the workers and
transport the shipment to Hong Kong pick
it up yes yes sir
first we work overtime we refuse Thank
they beat up and now they think they can
just fire all of us just like that so
are you guys going to let him get away
with that what'd you say Kings up what's
going on they closed the milk and you
know what it was english ambassador who
is in charge of doing it sounds like
trouble anything I can help you oh sure
you didn't lose your job but I'm not
going to let them push us around yeah as
soon as they finish the last shipment
they fired all the men and you think
they have something they do with her I
don't know but I'm going to find out for
sure you think what it could be we
should check the office hey ho could
that be it well we know they're up to
something find a way that fetcher okay
then we find a way to stop it let's go
what what's this my God look what
they're doing well we've got to stop
them I'll tell fei-hung hurry for saying
you know hurry
I'll get help
up
Rick van Gogh now
very
madam they're coming out all right keep
it down so we can organize the good idea
yeah goodbye good to have a safe trip
now take care of the baby hey huh yes
Father don't get up keep working are you
almost through with that almost finished
they'd start another one to make sure he
does it's my responsibility listen he's
not allowed to leave you understand me
perfectly all right good you know yeah
I've been thinking about names for the
baby if we were to have a boy he could
be worn kpop if it's a girl won't pick
nice both names are fine but do we
really need to pick one now well my
teeth on earth that shouldn't be a
problem if you take it easy till I get
back okay hung yes what are the plans oh
I will master wok okay hold on oh I've
got to go remember cannot suppress wheel
and come on don't worry they hung and I
will be just fine go we don't have any
time to spare cubby we've got to get
Ching out of there I hope he's still
alive what can we do I'm good to stop
them I'm gonna do what I can I gave
promised tofu and she what do you think
let's go hey wait where are you going
I'm going to battle but way Madame you
can't go in your condition okay this
chain come on I'm only pregnant Oh madam
please think about the baby what if
something were to happen all right go
ahead without me then I'll go get my
students meet me at the mill right I
can't her up the men hmm oh thanks for
help you with us right yeah okay
will you be all right madam I'll be fine
good but what if father face off oh go
on who cares now what's your father
thinks only make me proud I will okay oh
damn huh yeah some c4 good luck I can
use it
zombicide now demand justice we know
what you have in their back God those
antiques are not yours and we won't let
them out of China you have no right to
them is that right
you've got your up good Jake now
Oh
one time
good
you
Oh
desk no wait you gotta fight King let's
go yeah let's go off boss boss boss boss
what happened oh hey nantucket guys here
we got to do something
walk this be fun
wait do you realize what you're doing
you're helping them still our history
our culture you mean these they're of no
use to anyone if they want to buy them
I'll gladly send I won't let you do it
and what are you gonna do about it
listen to you nothing's gonna stand in
my way so why don't you just go home to
Daddy I've heard enough oh well that
makes two of us Henry don't waste time
just get it over with do it you hear me
fine
Oh
do something
ha
ok
what are you gonna do now
drunken boxing well what do you say
haha
you okay
nah
ah
now it's over give me another rod what's
this about can float in water but also
sink in it ah
p
just perfect
how about it
the governor I want to take play hung
for his role in returning the stolen
antiquities and on the arrest of the
imagination could have happened without
the support of his loving father ah well
we need more fathers who treat their
phones like that you should be very
proud of him so worthy fei-hung is still
feeling some of the after-effects of all
that he's been through we hope he will
soon be on his feet I am sure that he
will come to you as soon as he any
better I've got a job with that boy oh
hi I'm certain he will be mostly hahaha
you