'What happened to this city?
Pollution and smoke on either sides.'
'Why does not anybody speak up?
Why should we tolerate it silently?'
'Put an end to this
negligent attitude.'
'Do not ignore any cigarette
or beedi that is lit.'
'Smoking is prohibited
at public places.'
''Violation incurs fine.'
'Do not smoke and let others smoke.'
'Pay heavily if you smoke.'
'Smoking causes cancer.'
'Smoking kills.'
Smoking causes cancer.
Smoking kills.
'Drinking alcohol
is injurious to health.'
I joined police services in
this area station five years back.
Many sub-inspectors have
come and gone in this period.
But you are the first S.I...
Who has voluntarily enquired about
this case. That too on your first day.
It is a good work, sir.
But I am telling out of concern.
It is better not to interfere
in this case.
This is a dangerous area.
And the case you are talking about..
..it is not even registered.
That murder is just a rumour, sir.
Just came to my ear, through
the grapevine. This is true, sir.
It is okay. I like rumours
better than the truth.
Tell me.
They say it happened
eight years back.
A lot of pigeon racing
happens in this area.
There is talk that this murder..
..was a result of
one of those fights.
Pigeon racing? What is that?
Sir, you never heard about it?
It is very common in Vizag, sir.
But no one seems to know about it.
There are two types
of pigeon racing, sir.
One. Homing pigeon.
Each participant enters..
..about five to ten pigeons, sir.
The day before the race, participants
bring their pigeons to the club.
Each of the pigeons are given tags.
A secret numbered ring
is fixed to the pigeon's leg.
Then all pigeons are transported
through a lorry or train.
Depending on the race distance,
they select a town.
Like Nellore, Bhopal, Delhi.
All the cages are lined up there.
And all the pigeons
are released at once!
No matter how far
away you take it..
It flies right back
to its owner's place!
The pigeon that reaches
first wins the race.
Pigeon fanciers have
a lot of respect for it.
They are running these
competitions since long time.
They do not allow gambling
in these tournaments.
But there is a lot
of competition and rivalry.
There is talk that the murder
you are asking about..
..happened during one such issue.
Who did it?
There is a notorious smuggler
called Velu in this area.
You might have heard.
He is very famous. This entire
area is under his control, sir.
He exports red sanders
illegally, sir.
Even he is been a pigeon
fancier for years.
The killer was from his gang.
A twenty two year old boy!
He was not even
a gangster back then.
Just a boy who raised pigeons.
He used to look after
Velu's racing pigeons.
One night,
a guy from the opponent gang..
..came in the night and slit
his favourite pigeon's throat.
This boy went and stabbed
him to death in blind rage..
..who was feared until then.
Die! You!
Hey! Who are you? Stop!
He was just a boy who
raised pigeons until then.
That was eight years back.
He is the big-gun
in the hood these days.
We can not even lay
a finger on him, sir.
What did you say his name was?
Maari.
Velu Anna has many
areas under his control.
He handed one of
those areas to Maari.
His cut reaches him
promptly every month.
Velu Anna's main business
is smuggling red sanders.
It is the top illegal business
in Chennai and Andhra these days.
A tone of red sanders..
..can fetch upto a million
at the foreign market.
Velu Anna has too many
cases filed against him.
And even more enemies.
So he does not get out much.
He handles all deals through Maari.
There is another man
under Velu called Bird Ravi.
He wants to be a
part of Velu's business.
But Velu's support is for Maari.
Velu does not interfere
in matters of Maari's area.
Nothing happens here
without his consent.
Want to pay up nicely?
Or should I smash your shop up?
They are robbing us under broad daylight!
Is there no one to fight them?
By standing in the
sun since long time..
..they are requesting you.
I will thrash you.. - Brother!
Brother! - You are all rowdies?
Why do you request him?
Can not beat him up and get it?
- He is a ruffian. When he gets angry..
..everyone around him flees.
But when he is with his pigeon's..
You can see his other side.
He immediately becomes kind!
This bad guy appears to
be a good guy when he see pigeons.
For ages,
Velu was hosting these tournaments.
Then he left Maari in charge.
Despite a lot of illegal businesses, he is
very honest when it comes to pigeons.
He conducts these tournaments
supervised by senior fanciers.
If someone cheats,
he gets very angry.
He stops being kind.
Hard to deal with him then!
He does not even spare
the people who are with them.
There is a guy called Robert in his
gang. His pet name is 'Sannasi.'
Whenever Maari gets angry,
he calls Sannasi from wherever he is..
..he will beat him badly
and only then his anger is lost.
Beer rates are hiked!
Why did they do it?
There is another loafer
roaming with Maari.
His name is Shanivaram.
Shanivaram? What is this name?
Saturday means..
..drinking day.
So you do not drink on other days?
I will drink. - So you do not
drink on other days for sure?
Oh dirty fellow!
I drink on other days for sure.
So why did you get
the name Shanivaram?
I drink on saturdays at any cost.
He is scratching his head.
I think he got confused.
It happens this way
but we cannot do anything.
He frightened everyone
to such extent.
There was a tournament
in that area yesterday too.
As usual Maari won the cup.
Sir, we cannot tolerate
the antics they do today.
"His name- Prominent!
This guy.- He is different!"
"He paves new routes.
With his steel heart he rules."
"His soul knows no guilt."
"He is seen all maladies.
And misery."
"Maari!"
"He is the good one. - He is Maari!
The dashing one. - Maari!"
"Rub him and he is gold,. Snub
him and he is a beast, this Maari!"
"He is the good one. - He is Maari!
The dashing one. - Maari!"
"Rub him and he is gold,
Snub him and he is a beast, this Maari!"
"Does not know the world.
Does not heed law and order."
"Does not like to change his ways."
"Does not have time for love.
Do not try threatening him."
"He is a solo contestant.
Do not you dare pick on him."
"Rub him and he is gold.
Snub him and he is a beast, this Maari!"
Today is Boss' birthday. We have
to laugh a lot. We are hired for work.
You both will get thrashed.
- I have got a special item here for Boss!
Ugh!
Feels light weight.
What is that?
- Your favourite item.
Hey, come out.
Who is he?
- Product name: Anirudh.
Ani.. - Rudh! Rudh!
- Rudh?
What does he do?
- He plays! - What?
He plays music and sings well.
Perform for us.
- I need some instruments, man.
Get him those instruments.
Why? Cool. Cool! - Not necessary.
Just sing and dance.
Okay, I will do it.
- Careful.
Ugh! What is his dress? Look at his
cap and glasses! Get him changed.
Come, dear.
- Hey! Hey! Bro..
Come.
Sir, it is better for us..
..to remain silent by letting his
do his work. - Greetings, sir.
Sir, where are we going?
- Take the vehicle to Maari's area.
We have got information that..
..betting is taking place
at the pigeon tournament today.
We will go there and
catch him red handed.
But without asking them..
We should not enter their area.
Are we the police or is he?
Start the jeep.
Hey, you are banned
this year, right?
What are you doing here?
Just leave.
I just came to watch.
Can not I watch? - Just leave.
Sir, he tumbled once!
Bro, was that okay?
- That was okay.
Why is it descending already?
Looks like he will not make it!
Who is that aunt?
You are pretending to flail your
cloth and making the bird fly away!
I do not even know that woman.
Must be a neighbour.
Do not you see that tournament
is held here? Go inside.
He is lying.
- Yes. - She is his wife.
You have set her up? - No, brother.
- Why would you set-up your own wife?
Is she your wife or a set-up?
- Did we come for her?
Note that down! That his
bird has lost. - No, brother.
Do not play your tricks
in Maari's tournament.
You!
How come I hear a jeep in here?
Where is Maari?
- Look at that!
Firstly, you should not have
walked in without our permission.
And you have the
guts to ask for Maari?
I have got information
that betting happens here.
Betting? - The jeep must
be heading towards Poorna market.
Must have lost its
way and ended up here.
We are just letting the pigeons
fly and looking at the skies..
..but you are using
big words like betting.
You can not organise such tournaments
without police permission.
Stop everything.
I need to see Maari.
Clear the crowd!
- What is the noise?
Did you ask for protection?
- No, Maari.
Then what is the officer doing here?
A cop's job is where
the rowdies are.
Rowdies?
We are flying the symbol
of peace and you call us rowdies?
Big shots participate in this,
there is nothing wrong.
Some enemy of mine
has told you lies about me.
Only a man who does
wrong will have enemies.
You should leave, sir.
Will not be nice if we force you out.
Your threats will not scare me.
I have got evidence.
Just stop everything and co-operate
to the investigation. - Evidence?
Evidence.. Evidence..
Hey! Come here, boy.
He will not hit you!
- Come.
Come!
You got into a mess
when you cheated last year.
I banned you this year because
you can not pay up the entry fees.
But you should not go to the
officer and tell him lies about me!
Tell me.
Does anything illegal happen?
- Hello! Leave him.
Talk to me.
- One minute. I am asking.
Tell me.
Anything illegal happening? Ask.
Leave him! - Tell! - Anything
illegal happening. I am asking.
Hey!
- Hey!
Let is leave, sir.
Did not he say nothing
illegal happens here?
Leave!
Come, sir!
Who is he? - The new sub-inspector
in the area, Maari.
If you do stupid things again..
..I will rip you apart.
Maari!
Will not be nice if we forced you out.
Hey!
- Hey!
Sir, do not think
about it all the time.
What can we do?
Big shots are behind him.
We have to ignore it.
Not just you, all the policemen.
I am not like all the policemen,
Hanumanth.
He is known to have
committed a murder.
What is the use of being policemen
when we can not lock him up?
How can we act upon rumours?
It is still a rumour because
everyone let it be that way.
Someone told you this rumour.
Someone else told him.
If we follow the trail..
..it will not be hearsay.
We will find the origin.
We will start tomorrow.
We will start with
you and connect till Maari.
Mom!
- What?
You said you will
buy me a new bag, mom!
I am struggling to make ends meet.
You want a new bag?
Use the one you already have.
- It is torn, mom!
Everyone in school makes fun.
I will stitch it tomorrow.
Use it for now.
Do not irritate me.
I will not go to school..
..if you do not get me a new bag.
- Do not go, then.
What do I care?
Bugging me in the mornings!
Mom, please buy a new one. Please!
- Hey!
Loudspeaker Kavitha! - I am pissed
off already. Do not interfere.
Please, mom. - Your yelling woke
me up in the morning.
And now you are pissed?
You do not even have a sweet voice.
You are shouting like a sheep.
Look, mom!
He is always making fun of me.
You know he is pulling your leg.
Why are you still standing here?
You are getting late, go to school.
This has become a routine!
Why are you teasing her?
What were you doing, then?
Are you not shouting?
She asked for the bag, right?
Why do not you buy it?
- Where do I get the money?
If your husband does not drink for
two days, you will get the money.
You talk so much,
why can not you buy her one?
I would have bought
it if you had married me.
You missed your chance.
Look at that face!
Maari, Did someone tell you they
are moving into house number 8?
No. No one told me. Why?
Then someone has moved
in without our permission.
What are you doing here?
Stop! Stop!
Painting without permission.
Stop it, I say!
No respect for a gangster!
Move aside.
Oh, sorry. It is a mannequin.
- Why are you just standing there?
Here, hang this.
- Okay, ma'am.
What?
She asked me to hang this against
the wall. - Why not her face?
Taking orders from a woman!
We are gangsters?
What is this?
- What?
If you move in here and shift
your belongings without informing..
Should we keep quiet?
- Who are you? Why should I tell you?
Whatever happens in the area,
happens only with Maari's permission.
Got it, white bro?
- What?
Are you doing rowdyism?
- I was doing comedy till now.
Now I am doing rowdyism.
Here, this is rowdyism.
- Please! Please!
That house broker never
told us anything about this.
He said he told you.
No, sir! When did you tell us?
- Not to you, sir. - Then?
I told her, sir.
Slap you!
- Hey Maari, control yourself!
It is morning time.
- Think you can touch me?
Had you not been a woman,
I would have ruined you. - No.
Do not do anything to my daughter.
Poor thing, she made a mistake.
- She keeps talking..
..what did we do wrong?
We only did our duty, right?
- Yes, yes.
Did the broker tell
you anything? - Yes.
Why did not you tell us anything?
- Mother..
Why should we pay them up?
It seems I need to pay
them extra to open a boutique.
So mother and daughter are
planning to open a petty shop here?
No. Not a petty shop.
Boutique.
- Mother..
Why are you explaining
all this to them?
Look.
- Hey!
Break your finger! Drop it.
This is my house.
I will do as I wish. Okay?
Look girl..
Keep your petty shop.
Keep him if you want.
- Yes!
But who will give you
protection for all that?
Give us our cut,
and keep whatever you want.
Protection? For what?
What will happen here?
-Anything could happen.
This glass could fall and shatter.
That cupboard could topple
and break. -Do not do that, sir.
Maari, something lighter, please!
Okay. Someone might break the TV.
Do not break the T.V.
Just give them the money.
- Take.
This covers the house,
who will pay for the petty shop?
Boutique!
- What do you say?
You will have to pay double for
English names.
I do not have cash in hand.
Give us some time. I will pay later.
One week.
I will file police complaint.
We are going to the police
station for the next collection.
No, Maari.
Her eyes are too big.
The way you were staring at her,
I was happy.
I thought you were in love!
- What?
Love? For the first time,
I felt like slapping a girl.
I have a principle against
hitting women. So I let it go.
Maari, we have seen
in so many Telugu movies.
The heroine swears in slow motion.
The hero takes it
with a smile on his face.
And they fall in love.
How can you fall in love when
a woman is yelling at your face?
I would rather catch
chikungunya than fall in love.
Then my route is clear.
- What?
No, I meant this is the route to go.
That girl talks too much,
keep her under control.
Hi Gajuwaka!
Felt shock?
I will go in my route.
Maari Boys are hosting
11th Annual Tumbler Pigeon and..
..High Flyer Pigeon Competition.
We are having a prize distribution.
When we call out your name,
come and collect your prizes.
One important thing..
Some people fly their pigeons every year
just for the consolation prizes.
We have got some vessels for you.
You can collect them and go.
Medals, bro.
- Whatever, give it to them.
Maari is here. Applause!
Maari and the oldies
will greet each other.
The first prize goes
to Maari's pigeon as usual.
As we are hosting it,
we will be magnanimous.
But the counsellor still want..
..to give prize to Maari.
Clap! Louder! - After
all those foreign medicines..
..all we get is
the consolation prize?
This Maari does something special.
Our birds have no
value in the market.
Even people from
Delhi and Calcutta..
..want Maari's birds.
We will change everything tomorrow.
Next prize.
Consolation Prize.
Come on stage, Bird Ravi.
You go get it. - Hey, you are Bird
Ravi, right? You should come up.
I am coming.
Put it on his head.
Put it.
Enough, enough.
Enough.
Bird Ravi wishes to organise a
Tumbler-High Flyer tournament tomorrow.
Nothing happens
outside your control.
It only works if
one person does it.
If there is some problem..
Maari's name is at stake
for granting permission.
You are the host, you are the winner.
Why will there be any fight?
- What are you trying to say?
That we win because we host?
I am not saying.
Anyways, you will win.
At least we will have
the pride of hosting it.
It will boost our
pigeon's market value.
Earlier, a Bird Ravi's
pigeon had some value.
Now everyone comes
after only your pigeons.
We are asking this as a favour.
We have got the money
and the manpower to host it.
We will give you your
share of the entry fees.
You can participate,
you do not have to pay an entry fee.
Wow! What an offer.
- Very generous.
I said it like it is.
Hosting or paying
is not the matter here.
You should maintain the sanctity of
the tournament. That is important.
We will handle all that, Maari.
You should give us a chance once.
Okay. Let is give it a shot.
Thanks, Maari.
- But we are not flying our birds.
Why, Maari?
- You said we always win it.
Why piss you off? - No, Maari.
We will be very proud if
your pigeon wins in our tournament.
When did I tell you about
the murder? Stop babbling.
You told me right here,
the other night.
Are you out of your mind?
- You are enquiring about him here?
Sir, I just blurted
some nonsense, sir.
Tea shop owner Satyam told me.
Officer, I do not know anything.
I might have believed you
if you had not spilt the tea.
Tell me the truth.
Some say it happened..
..some say it did not happen.
- Who are these people?
This guy called Murthy,
in the 2nd street. - Murthy?
That drunkard?
The murder happened for real
during a gang war eight years back.
That is all I know. - Everything
we heard since morning is a waste.
There is one person called Apparao.
Father and son pick pockets.
Dad is old school, does a neat job.
But the son is a rookie.
He was caught while stealing
chain in the market last week.
The guy got away,
but everyone saw his face.
His case is registered,
we can use that to threaten him.
Eight years back,
Maari committed a murder.
What do you know about it?
About murder?
I do not know anything.
Someone has given
you false information.
So, shall we lock your son up?
Sir. - Yeah, there is
a case registered against him.
Answer them, dad.
- What do you want to know about Maari?
Keep quiet!
- Why are you scared?
What can he do to us?
Ask me, sir.
- Answer bravely.
No one will know about this.
Speak up!
Back then,
Velu's gang was not in power.
There was a man called Pandu.
He was the top gun.
Those two gangs
never got along, sir.
One day, because of some issue..
They say Maari went
and stabbed Pandu.
Then it turned into a gang war..
..and Pandu's entire
gang was wiped out.
Since then..
..Velu Anna's hold over
the area became stronger.
Do you know anyone
who witnessed the killing?
No sir.
I have not heard of anyone who
witnessed Maari committing the murder.
The case was not registered.
Then when Velu came to power..
..he wiped it clean.
- How is that?
They have killed
a man who was in power.
Maari became a gangster
only after that.
The whole area is scared of him.
But no one knows who
finished him, or how.
How would we know?
If something like that
happens then only we will know.
You only tell the truth.
For any rowdy..
..a murder like this..
..is a matter of pride.
Then why is it still a rumour?
Because it never happened, sir.
It is just building up, sir.
Do not believe any of it.
What is this? Hi dear.
What brings you here?
For whom you came? Came to see Maari?
Why did you bring Maari?
Maari, petty shop
is here with mummy.
Greetings, sir.
We did not know who you were.
We started on the wrong
foot when we moved in.
We will pay you your fees.
Just give us some time.
We were wealthy back in Delhi.
Incurred a huge loss in business.
So we are a little broke now.
We go broke too,
spending on booze every night.
We just need some time.
I think sir is still angry.
We came to apologize.
Your daughter does not look like it.
She seems to have come to sell sari.
Say sorry.
Sorry.
I did not know who you were.
That day I misbehaved.
Now you know who he is.
How did you behave?
Angrily.
You were cheeky.
Yes. Cheeky. - Insolent.
Yes. I was insolent.
- Like you were..
..some big shot.
Yes. I acted like I was a big shot.
Do not roll your eyes.
They might pop out and fall down.
What bro?
- Look there.
It looks freaky.
Sorry.
I forgive you. Go.
Maari forgives you. Go.
So, can we pay..
..the rest later?
No need to pay up. - Have you seen?
- Thanks a lot, sir.
See, if you are
nice to the bosses..
..they will be helpful.
Instead, take me as a partner
in your shop. - Unexpected!
Take me as a partner in your shop.
I will..
..collect my remaining
money that way.
Move.
What is he saying? Partner?
It is all for our good.
Henceforth it is not
your shop anymore. Our shop.
Congratulations!
I checked the calendar.
Today is an auspicious day.
We are partners henceforth.
Shake hand.
It is okay?
- Little small.
Brother, this one?
- This..
Okay.
Want to watch adult movie?
Maari, customers are here,
please you..
Hey, guests are all here,
bring coffee.
Get coffee!
Go!
Go I say! What is this?
She is wearing a lungi!
Why are they sitting separately?
Customer? This is also same.
It is loose, take it.
Hey!
Let is go.
Do not feel bad.
Modern Chilakaraju!
Who is the referee for our loft?
Who else for Maari's loft?
I will be coming.
Take care.
- Okay, Maari.
Is the boy ready?
Want me to tell him about the
missing birds? - You know about it?
Is this Maari's loft?
Maari? Say Maari Anna.
Mister, who are you?
Your usual referee
has gone to another loft.
So they sent me here.
How can they do that? It is wrong.
Wait, I will call Bird Ravi.
Is a tournament happening here?
Yes, Ravi his organizing it.
Who? Bird Ravi?
Has Maari lost his clout?
Look at that flip! That is
my training. - Your training?
What is he scribbling?
It was a foul.
What? A foul?
He is making such solid flips.
Calling it a foul?
He tumbled correctly.
Are you kidding me? Look closely.
I am warning you once.
If he does it wrong again,
you are out.
You will disqualify our pigeon?
Shani..
Come on. Did you see that?
No, no, no.
His movements are erratic.
There is no form.
This one is disqualified.
This one has won contests
in the last three years.
He did it wrong this year.
Disqualified.
I can not cheat for you guys.
Who is cheating?
You or we? Be careful!
Stop. No fighting
in the tournament.
Tell him like that.
Do not know to raise pigeons!
They just threaten us.
Oh, is that so?
One minute. Let those pigeons out.
Which is the Tumbler,
and which is the High Flyer here?
Why?
Just tell me.
Here, this is the Tumbler.
With the way you
looked up at the sky..
..I could tell you were a fraud.
None of these are Tumblers.
I knew something was fishy
when they sent a new guy.
You will disqualify our pigeon.
And when we protest, you call Maari's
men cheats. Was that your plan?
See our product?
Thirty years of experience.
He caught you red handed.
It is not that.
You said something a while back.
What?
Something about raising pigeons.
No, I did not say anything.
I heard you. Say it again.
If the pigeon had tumbled right,
we would not have had this problem.
Is that what he said?
- I think so.
Am I deaf? He said something else.
Tell him.
You said something a while back.
Say that.
I said you did not know to raise pigeons
but threatened without knowing..
How can you say without knowing?
So you are saying
my pigeon cannot tumble.
How should one tumble? You tell me.
It needs to fly up and turn like that,
and this way..
I do not know how to explain it.
If you can not explain,
then demonstrate.
Maari!
Was not that a perfect somersault?
- Yes, it was.
You do not have enough courage
to face me but trying to make plan.
I will finish him off!
Maari!
This a petty issue,
why should you waste time on this?
What is a petty issue? Would you
be quiet if someone hits your guy?
I would not have let
anyone to hit my guy.
What Ravi did was wrong.
Even if there was a shortage..
..you should not have sent
an amateur to referee.
That was not the genuine reason.
Their plan was to disqualify our pigeon.
Just shut up. You tell us, Anna.
No matter what,
you should not have beat him.
Should have either talked it out or
come straight to me. - What should I talk?
Hey, tell Anna what you told me.
What did you say?
I said they did not know to
raise pigeons but they threaten.
I was raise between pigeons.
Would I keep mum when he says that?
Would you have kept quiet
if someone said it to you?
I would have slaughtered him.
If you still think it is my fault,
tell me what to do.
Anna, Maari should not
organize tournaments anymore.
I am here to decide it.
Both of you are at fault.
All this started because you
organized the tournament.
Let Maari organize it as always.
Shake hands and mind
your own jobs. Go.
I..
- Do as I say. Get up.
Hey!
Spit on it.
You have changed these days, Anna.
Anna, I have been asking
you for a while now. - What?
See your hand.
Anna.
- What?
I have been asking
since many days about it.
What? - I told you.
I have found a link.
The demand over red sanders
is increasing by the day.
If you could let me do it too..
You can not even organize
a tournament without hassles.
And you want to do this? Just mind
your job, I will take care of it.
Hello.
- Hi- Hi. Come.
I saw your designs
on your Facebook page.
Your designs have a personal touch.
We do not find that in big stores.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Shall we shop for both the
Reception and Mehendi here itself?
Okay, dear. Whatever you say.
I am buying all my
friends identical sarees.
You need to design that too.
Definitely! We will do that.
Very good fabric.
- What? Customer?
Yes.
I am Maari.
- Hi.
One of this shop's
business partners.
Hello sir, myself Satyamurthy.
Let it be.
- I am also..
..a partner in my dad's business.
Jewellery shop.
- Very good.
Really? - Yeah, sir.
- Okay, okay.
I found the ad on Facebook.
You have come to the right place.
- Marriage is on 23rd...
Mehendi is planned on 22nd.
Your would-be is next to you and
talking of another girl Mehendi?
I will beat you.
Sir, it is not like that.
I meant the henna function.
Say sorry to him.
Sorry.
He is got a separate henna function.
Some of us can not even
afford our weddings.
Sri..
What is that laugh? Just like that..
I was talking to her!
Devi.. Discussed the rates yet?
No, I am checking designs.
Go ahead.
But I will fix the rates, okay?
So, here..
- Wait, wait!
I told you I will fix the rates!
Taking decisions without
your partner's consent?
Here is the bill.
This is too much, sir!
Our shop is special, madam.
You have to pay its worth.
Mr. Maari, this is unfair.
Hey!
- What?
You have a separate
function to apply henna.
This seems more unfair to you?
Okay, sir. We will think
about it and call you.
Yes, we will call you.
Sit.
Will you sit if you
wife tells you to sit?
Sit down.
You have to buy from us.
These are the rates.
Pay fifty percent upfront and
fifty percent upon delivery. Okay?
Look, your partner is
acting like a rowdy! - Maari!
Whom are you calling rowdy?
I am a rowdy! Give money!
Sir, I will give.
- Do not give. - Give.
Saw that?
This is how you do business.
How do I trust you
with such a huge company?
Send my cut across
in the evening. Okay?
He is crying bitterly
just for this? Your training?
Who hit you, sweetie?
You look like Mr. Bean!
Hey!
- Coming.
So sorry! I did not expect
them to behave like this.
Sorry.
I have nightmares about death...
..for looking at death
certificates all day.
No suspicious death have
occurred in the area, sir.
If it were to happen then it will
match with a registered police case.
I checked thoroughly.
Nothing is connected to Maari.
This murder never happened.
Please drop this matter, sir.
Stop! Stop!
Sree baby.
Come here. Look who is here!
What are you doing?
- What?
Partner,
I have not received my cut yet.
They cancelled the order.
Cancelled the order?
Whom he asked before doing it?
I will finish him today.
- Hey! Stop! - Come!
Why are you stopping?
They place their order here and
bought elsewhere. How can we let it go?
They did not go elsewhere.
- Then?
The wedding has been called off.
Why?
When you threatened
them and the guy cried..
..the girl fell out of love,
it seems.
She called off the wedding.
Good for him, or he would
have cried all his life.
Girls do not care for love at all.
You never know why or
for what they would ditch you.
Maari, you are
spurting philosophies!
Do not laugh.
I borrowed a huge
sum to get the materials.
I wanted to pay off my
debt with this money. - Hey!
Pay back your debt with
the advance money I got you.
I returned the money to them.
Why?
I only want to earn the right way.
Look, if you run the company
this way, you will not make any money.
I have a lot of other businesses,
you take care of your debt. Bye!
Brother..
- What?
She is crying.
- I swear on my mother that..
..I did not do anything.
- What brother?
Should not have let that money go.
Who did you borrow from?
Through a friend of dad's..
I think his name is Ravi.
It is Bird Ravi.
Very bad.
So we cannot do anything. Let is go.
Your family, your problems.
Start the vehicle.
Who are you?
- We have come to buy clothes.
Buzz off.
Remove!
Hi!
Take it out.
Stop it, please.
Leave.
Sir, my parents have gone out.
It is okay. They are not needed.
Sir, what are they doing?
Vacating your store
and opening ours.
Sir, we are trying to pay off your
debt. Business is not doing well.
Keep quiet,
and we would only touch the shop.
Work faster, guys.
Sir, please sir.
I set it up with great difficulty.
My dream, sir.
Please.
What is the noise outside?
- Make it fast!
Stop it!
I am telling you. Stop it! Stop!
Hey!
Maari!
Maari, you know what
Velu Anna would say?
Hey Ravi. We are following
Velu Anna's orders.
You touched our property,
and we touched yours.
Same to same!
Okay? This shop is ours.
Have not you told Bird
about our partnership?
Bird. "Bird Ravi" right?
Look, we have lent her money.
This is none of your business.
You should not lend money
to people in our area.
Do we keep quiet if you come and create
ruckus without brother's permission?
We wll finish you off.
- Do not remove your t-shirt!
We do not know, this is your shop.
Do not create a scene unnecessarily.
Velu Anna has asked
us not to fight.
But if you keep showing up in our
area and Anna will know what to do.
Hey!
- Breathe out. Breathe out.
Bloody bugger.
Maari, should we fight for some
chick? You are extorting her too.
That girl is from my area.
I will extort her or threaten her,
or do anything.
First you leave this
place with your men.
Maari, this is not done yet.
If it is not done
then buzz off, man.
What?
Go, go. Do not create a scene here.
Just leave.
Maari, thanks a lot.
See what I told you about?
This is called protection.
Maari!
Why did you pair them together?
Idiot! - Sir, they are new..
Nothing, Maari.
- You are a pigeon pimp now?
Hello.
What do you want?
- After you warned them yesterday..
..they said they do not want
the money. I could not believe it.
I came to thank you.
- Okay, go.
I mistook you to only cause
trouble to the area people.
Now I understand that outsiders
do not mess with us, thanks to you.
You are not as bad as I thought.
You are right.
I am much worse than you thought.
It is.. - Stop flashing
your teeth at me. Get off my back.
Maari. Poor girl,
she is only trying to thank you.
Feeling bad for the lady now?
She hoodwinked that guy with his money.
She is trying to do the same to us.
I will even work for you
till I can afford to pay you back.
Are you mad? Offering to
work for money at a goon's locale?
Wear your scarf properly.
Do not know how to wear scarf
but you are a fashion designer.
I heard that you do not
misbehave with ladies.
Or I would not have
come to talk to you.
This will not work out.
- It will!
We are all parched.
Not just us, even the pigeons.
They must be tired of our faces.
They will be all excited if she comes.
Ugh! - She is a nice girl.
Let her work here.
At least to make up for our sins.
I will kill you!
How have we sinned?
We are so parched, Maari!
What is with the sudden interest?
You were fine till now.
Not suddenly, after coming here
and seeing you fly pigeons..
..I too got interested.
When you win, would hold the
pigeon and stand mighty, and high.
I really liked seeing
you like that. So..
I will come from tomorrow.
Bye.
Hear that?
She likes seeing, it seems.
She meant the pigeons, you rascal.
"I am your don, don, don.
And I am your Golden fish."
"I am your fan.
- Your looks are attractive."
"Gone! I am lost if I see you."
"Do not you pierce me with those sharp
eyes? I want all of you, and more."
"Your rosy skin sweeps me off my
feet. I am no match for you, baby."
"Your masculinity melts me down."
"The bird in me has lost it is flight.
While I yearn to cross the line."
"This coyness holds me back."
"I melt away.."
"Yet, this coyness holds me back."
"I am a loyal husband,
giving you royal treatment."
"And your daily shopping
is guaranteed."
"I am your spouse and am naughty.
Giving you a lifetime service warranty."
"I am a loyal husband,
giving you royal treatment."
"And your daily shopping
is guaranteed."
"I am your spouse and am naughty.
Giving you a lifetime service warranty."
"My dear twinkle!"
What?
You are my partner.
I will only pay you.
"I feel trapped, I feel the heat,
I am ready for a one on one, baby."
"I melt away..
I fade away..I shiver."
"You be with me, become my
life partner and keep me happy."
"I melt away..I fade away.."
"Naughty.."
"I am gone!
- Your masculinity melts me down."
"The bird in me
has lost it is flight."
"While I yearn to cross the line."
"I am your don, don, don.
And I am your Golden fish."
"I am your fan.
- Your looks are attractive. - Gone!"
How is it? I stitched it.
Thanks.
- Brother.
Hey, why are you calling me as brother?
Why do not you call Maari too.
Calling him brother does not
come naturally to me.
"And your daily shopping
is guaranteed."
"I am your spouse and am naughty.."
"Giving you a lifetime service warranty."
"I am a loyal husband,
giving you royal treatment.."
"And your daily shopping is guaranteed.
- I am your spouse and am naughty.."
"Giving you a lifetime
service warranty."
Two omelette here!
Maari..
- Yes..
This is love for sure.
She is in love with you.
Hey, she looks like film heroine.
How can she love me? - Brother..
You do not know your power.
I understand but we gave her lot
of trouble. How will she love me?
Maari, how come
you are so innocent?
Nowadays to trap a girl,
first step is to torture them.
Somehow you did the right thing.
Nowadays girls like
bad boys like you and me.
They do not like me at first glance.
Are you likeable at second glance?
How can someone like after second glance
when they do not like at first glance?
Say the girl likes me.
I should like her too, right? She is
a show off. It will not work out.
Do not say that. She is a nice girl.
She and you are made In China.
Boss, you mean made
for each other? - Hey!
Sleepy face!
You know what I am
going through now? - Hey!
Only I get to hit him.
That is you fate. I think she is
a fine chick. She is gorgeous.
She would get rosy
if you pinch her!
When I see her, I just melt
and can not control myself, Maari.
What? - Yes,
I mean will Maari evert get..
..such a girl in life.
- Yes, Anna.
The whole area is
ogling at that girl.
But she has eyes only for you.
You are lucky. Give it a try!
Am I right for the girl?
Of course you are not..
We know that. But that powder-faced
girl does not seem to realise it!
Someone is going to
get beaten up now. - Hey!
So many girls fall for
the wrong men and suffer.
Add your name to the
list of wrong men. - Hey..
No, Maari..
A handsome groom like you.
Maari, she should be lucky
to find a handsome groom like you.
Correct, Anna.
You are sitting me down and
using this chance to pull my leg?
No, Maari.
- Okay.
How do I explain this?
There is no problem
as long as we are single.
You can just be free and happy.
When women enter the picture,
it gets messy.
I do not think this will work.
Will not work out.
It will work, Maari.
Maari-Sri. Sri-Maari.
It is a good combination.
- Shut up!
Just meet her in person
and say I love you.
If there is a problem?
- He is the one who gets in trouble.
You too go.
Maari, there is no one except us.
It is me.
- I told you to leave. Leave!
Why did he bring
us along then? - Yes.
Hey, it is the shirt I gave you.
Felt like wearing it?
Fits you so well.
You look smart, you know?
It seems you like me.
So I have decided to love you.
First time I saw you,
I wanted to slap you.
But then I saw the way
you were with the pigeons..
So I love you.
What?
I did not say it right? I will
say it differently. I love you.
I love you. I love you.
I am so sorry.
I think you have misunderstood me.
I had no such intentions with you.
I am sorry if I gave you that idea.
Oh, you do not? Okay, we will
drop the matter. I told them so!
But the fools got me excited
and confused.
Okay, let is mind our work. Bye!
Stop! Stop! - What? Do not mistake me.
It is not that I do not like you.
So you like me?
I do. - Then I love you
so let is love each other.
No, I like you. As a person.
This has to be personal.
Can not do this in public!
But I do not even know
anything about you.
What do you do?
What are you like?
What do I do? What am I like?
I wake up in the morning
and hang out with the pigeons.
Then I go to meet Velu Anna.
If he gives me some work, I do it.
Then the boys come over.
I just have fun with them.
I get drunk at nights and fall asleep.
Then I wake up in the morning,
and hang out with the pigeons.
Then I go to meet Velu Anna.
If he gives me some work, I do it.
Then the boys come over..
..I have fun, get drunk and sleep.
That is all I do.
Not that..
How do I explain..
Even if you are a good person,
you are a rowdy.
Oh.. - I would be scared, right?
How will my parents ever accept?
We will finish them off?
What?
No! I do not know you well enough.
How can I trust you?
You do not need to trust me. Let this go.
Do not let it confuse you. Bye!
"The Prince who rules the world.
That is me."
"You are the Princess
who stole my heart."
Maari!
Something wrong.
What happened?
- Not there, Maari.
Why does not that girl like you?
- Do not know.
Did you tell her properly?
I told her I love you in every possible
way! - Do not say like that, Maari.
I.. - I.. - Love..
- Love.. - You.. - You..
Say like this. - Why do
you split it in three like that?
Because it is three words!
What? Is not'I love you'
a single word.
No. - No? - No. - So why did not
you tell me this before?
Shanivaram!
Your girl? - Why have
you brought this girl here?
She wanted to talk to you,
brother.
You have come to develop
our friendship? Come.
Sit. Sit. - Go. You too go.
Come in the morning. You sit.
Want a drink?
- No. - She must be drunk already.
You only drink in star hotels.
- I need to talk to you. - Talk.
I did not tell you
that I do not like you.
I just wanted to
know more about you.
But you had left by then. - What
do you want to know? - Who are you?
How did you turn out this way?
Turn out what way?
- No, everyone fears you.
Including me.
Do I look like a rapist?
Only gutless men rape.
I am a real man.
Real men do not rape.
- No, no..
I know about you.
But everyone is so scared of you.
There must be some reason.
Violence.
Murders..
Murder?
Nothing of that sort.
Murder..
Can not really call it a murder.
Something like murder.
Pretty much murder.
There was this guy
called Pandu in my town.
Real big shot. Not any one
could have laid a finger on him.
One day I just went
and casually stabbed him.
Who are you? Anna!
But he did not die.
So it does not count as murder.
Someone else finished him off
two days later. But I got all the credit.
It will not work out.
Go home and think all night.
If it is okay then okay.
Or else leave it.
Stop bothering me.
Okay? Get out. Get out.
She came in style..
Why is the police here
without permission? - Do not yell.
He is come with a warrant.
Maari's asleep. Come back later.
- Do not yell!
Do not make a sound or
I will kill you. - Heard that?
We have got a warrant against you.
Officer asked me to bring you in.
- Who is the officer?
I said to wake me up early morning,
I am getting bad dreams.
Get up. We have come to arrest you.
- Arrest? Why?
Murder?
Murder? Something like murder.
There was this guy called
Pandu in our town.
Real big shot. Not anyone
could have laid a finger on him.
One day I just went
and casually stabbed him.
Give money!
This is how you run a business.
I can not take this anymore.
I am going to the police.
- Listen to me, madam.
It is an unnecessary trouble.
- I do not care.
I want to meet the sub-inspector.
Nothing, sir.
It is just a petty case. - Sir..
Sir, I want to file a complaint
against Maari.
Nuisance case. File the complaint.
I am ready to testify anywhere.
- I appreciate your bravery.
But if I charge him with this small
case then he will come out easily.
After that he will cause
more trouble for you and me.
We need to catch
him in a bigger case.
I will be glad to
help however I can.
After a lot of searching..
I have found the
file of a closed case.
The murder attempt
of a man named Pandu.
The suspicion's
age and description..
..fits with Maari.
But that is not enough.
We need stronger evidence
connecting Maari to the case.
What can I do for this?
What would you do?
- I will help you.
Calling him brother does not
come naturally to me.
What happened, Maari?
Be careful!
- Hey!
Just hangover from last
night's booze. Give that.
You are disturbing
me early morning.
Good job, man. Good job.
I have done lot of hooliganism.
I broke hands and legs, I did
many things. Nothing happened then.
For the first time ever..
I fell in love.
And they are going to lock me up.
That is the fate.
Fall in love, Maari..
Fall in love, Maari!
Screwed us, right?
What are you looking at?
Come, take me away.
He suggested it but
the girl has accepted it.
Everyone seems to have developed,
just not us.
Wait.
Is it okay? - Little bit
to the right. - Which side?
Left side. - Okay?
- Perfect.
Why are they bursting crackers?
Is it a festival day?
Not a festival, Maari.
The news of your arrest has spread.
Rascals!
They do not even burst
crackers for holidays.
But look at them
celebrating my arrest!
They have torn it already?
You guys do not stay here.
Go away.
They will keep prodding you.
If a girl comes and says
she loves you, just chase her away.
We do not have anyone
but you, Maari.
No one in the area will
respect us now. Tell him.
Who do we have but you?
Did not work out. Do not overact.
You uncle lives in Kakinada, right?
Go.
You have won. You used a woman,
but you still won.
When you waltzed into
my area without permission..
..I should have bumped you off.
Sparing you was a mistake.
Where is that girl?
She must be feasting her eyes.
What an actor you are!
With all that talking and smiling,
you have finished me, right?
See her.
- She is ripped me apart, right?
She trapped you very well.
Get into the vehicle.
Will not be nice if we force you in.
Oh, my dialogue from the other day?
Good! It was a good counter,
let is go.
Bye.
No AC?
Maari!
Here comes Maari! Let is go.
How are you? How are you, Anna?
- I am fine, Maari.
Thought you would have lost
weight but you are all fat.
How are you?
- What Maari?
You have lost so much weight.
When have I ever been fat?
- Beat like that, brother.
One tea for Anna!
- Okay, brother.
So, what is going on, old man?
With me gone, everyone in
the area must have been at peace?
No, Maari.
The situation in the area..
..has become very bad.
What happened? - They have arrested
Velu Anna and kept him under remand.
What? - You said it was not safe for
us to be here when you are in jail.
We went out of town
for a little while.
When we returned,
the area was unrecognisable.
That cop did not just
target us for no reason.
He had his own agenda.
- What?
They have arrested Maari
and you are just telling me!
When he was being arrested..
Start the vehicle.
I want him released today!
Sir! Sir!
Sir! Sir..
Sir.. Please, sir.
We have got information that
you are smuggling red sanders.
The Revenue Department
is here with a search warrant.
Do you know whose place this is?
Fool, there are cameras.
How did the media get
here even before searching?
I do not know, sir.
Someone must have
leaked information.
Sir, start the search.
When Velu Anna got
arrested and put in jail..
..all the MLA's
supported him backed out.
There was no one to bail him out.
Arjun has a solid reputation..
..at the Department for
busting rowdyism in the area.
Everyone in the
area was very happy!
They celebrated that fellow Arjun.
He came to our area one night.
He entered with a plan.
You might have heard about the red
sanders smuggling arrest from last week.
The Forest Department
has decided to..
..export the wood legally.
This job requires immediate labour.
Thought this would be a good opportunity
for the unemployed in the area.
If you are interested,
you may sign up for the job.
Officer Arjun has come
up with this. We can trust him.
Let is sign up. - You have received
an invitation to get a job!
Go sign up.
You too come, we will
go and sign up. - Sir, sir..
This will not suit me at all.
Both red sanders and ordinary
wooden logs are stacked here.
One load of each needs to be..
..loaded in the
lorries That is the job.
The people asked no questions
and continued to work this way.
This went on for two, three days.
One day, Arjun..
..did not turn up at the yard.
There was a raid that night.
Seize the goods and make a report.
Stop the labourers.
No one shall escape. - Yes, sir.
Sir, this is taking place with
government's permission. - Yes.
A government job taking place
all hushed up in a closed mill?
Sir, something is wrong.
You may call Officer Arjun.
He is the one who got us these jobs.
We went straight to him
after finding this place.
He asked us to make the arrests.
Just get in the jeep!
- Sir! Sir!
Sir! Sir! Leave!
Just get in the jeep!
Why is he running like this?
The people who had signed
up for transporting the wood..
They have been arrested and
taken in with charges of smuggling.
What are you saying?
Officer Arjun had taken them for
the job. Did you tell him about it?
I went to the station. They
said he has taken two days off.
The next day,
strange things began to happen.
Listen up, everybody!
All the shops in the market place
are under Ravi Anna's control now.
You had better pay up on time..
..if you want to your
shops to remain. - Hey!
Even Maari is gone now. Who are
you to collect from us? - Exactly!
Want to see what would happen
if Officer Arjun finds out?
You were right! I had to see what
would happen if Arjun finds out.
Anyone else has something to say?
I shall never hear
Maari's name again.
Whatever I say will be the law.
That is when we found
out the real matter.
This cop and "Bird" Ravi
were in it together the whole time!
Sir, we sent our men to
work only because of your word.
Now they are saying
something about smuggling!
Yes. I did take them
for a smuggling job.
Ravi and I did all this together.
If I had told you smuggling
then would not have come to work.
We were just trying it for the first time.
There was a small goof up.
And there was a raid, too!
Sir, testify that they did not know what
the job was. And get them released, sir.
Are you stupid?
Then I wll get caught.
No way. Just leave.
- Sir. - Sir..
Sir, I helped you because
I thought you were a good guy.
How could you listen to
them and do such terrible things?
Listen to them?
This was all my idea. Do you know
why we got Maari arrested?
To take their places.
This is why I re-opened
Maari's old case.
You stopped being of
use after Maari's arrest.
Do not ask unnecessary questions.
Mind your business.
No. I will not let this go.
What will you do, woman?
Sir, this is wrong.
Hanumanth, chase them away.
- Sir..
What are you staring at?
- Poor people.
Let is get them out somehow!
- Listen, just do as I say.
Everybody, leave.
Their plan was to arrest you and
Velu Anna and smuggle red sanders.
Leave! Move!
"Bird" Ravi's controls..
..Pigeon race and tournaments.
There is no ethics.
It is terrible. They just
do everything to their convenience.
Most of the pro fanciers
have stopped racing.
Cheers!
I got word from Velu
Anna after your release.
He said to leave the area.
That it will be better to vacate.
Let is leave.
- Why did you say like that, Maari?
What else should I say?
Velu Anna has said so himself.
Who do we stay back for?
Bring the pigeons and everything.
Let is leave.
Sannasi, you heard him.
Pack our stuff and
bring the vehicle.
We will not visit that area again.
Why are they loading things?
- I do not know!
You useless,
bring it carefully. - What?
Where are you going?
Has Maari been released?
Is he here, too?
- Tell me! - Are you blind?
We are just leaving.
We wll never come by here.
You can be happy. - Hold it.
It is so hard to
leave our birthplace!
Look, it is hard for us, too.
You deserve it!
You played the fiddle to that cop.
We wll do our jobs elsewhere.
People will spit on you later.
Look who else is here
They are leaving with
their belongings. - Sannasi!
Is notyour Anna Maari here?
- How will he come?
How could he ever
face anyone in the area?
Look, do not show off
after doing stupid things.
You are not fit to compete
with Anna. Leave! Leave!
What qualification do we need?
Do not do it I say!
Go ahead and do it. He can
take a beating. - Yes, he can.
Maari hits you everyday.
Let us hit you today.
Hit him!
I will hit you
and you will take it.
He was leaving anyway.
Old man! - What is this?
- Hey, let him go!
Hey! You!
Maari!
Come.
- You will go to him?
Maari!
Do not do it, Maari! Do not!
Hey, dummy!
Looks like your face is poached.
Cheekiness is bad.
"Maari is back!"
"Maari is a fireball."
"Bigger and better."
"Take to your heels."
"Your face will get mangled, eyes
removed, shape beyond recognition."
"Maari is back! Maari is a fireball!
He will cross all his limits."
"That is Maari."
Go. Go and tell the cop.
I will be here.
He may have the area
under his control.
But Maari is always out of control.
Only I get to beat him up.
Think you get to
show off in my area?
I wll finish you off!
Stop! What are you doing here?
Maari does not want
to see your faces.
Go away. - Get out of my way!
We want to talk to our man Maari.
Your man Maari? - Do not
you understand when we tell?
Maari, things got really
rough in your absence.
That cop tricked us and..
..got us in trouble.
- Not just that..
..he is hiked the bribe threefold.
None of us can live!
- Drop dead, then. - Yes, Maari.
We were really scared and helpless.
We wll be brave
now that you are here.
Hey, you..
You are the ones who
burst crackers and..
..celebrated my arrest!
This wash-basin face was
the one who fired a flower-pot.
You people chose to
be allied to that cop.
Suffer, now.
Go away!
Maari! - Leave! Leave!
Maari Anna told you. - Leave!
Are you stupid?
He would have left on his own.
Now you picked a fight
with him and made him stay back.
What could he do here, anyway?
We shall corner him..
..at the right time and place.
Check if all the pigeons
are in the right condition.
I wll come and check on
the young birds in the morning.
We wll start the training
tomorrow morning.
Okay, Maari. - Okay?
- How dare you come back again?
I came to say sorry.
I am sorry.
I know you must
be very angry with me.
But I did have my reasons.
I thought I was
doing the right thing.
I did not realise I was helping..
..the bad guy.
Anyhow, it is wrong to betray..
..someone's trust in any situation.
So, I am really sorry.
I have come all the way to apologise!
Will not you at least respond to me?
I forgive you. Leave.
Go, go.
Maari asked you to leave! Leave.
Do you know why Maari
committed that murder?
Because they killed
his loved pigeon.
Tell me honestly.
If you had been in his place, would not you
be furious? Would not you do anything?
Why do you trouble the area people?
Why can not you show
the affection on people..
..that you bestow upon pigeons?
- Why should we?
To these people?
Did they do that for Maari?
Who helped him when he was a kid?
When he was alone and hungry?
Who helped him then?
Not one person came.
He only had one thing then.
His pigeons.
It was the pigeons that fed him.
Maari always says..
..you can trust a pigeon..
..but not a human.
Now you have proved him right.
What I did seemed right that day.
Do not you talk about
right and wrong!
Have you ever struggled in life?
Have you ever struggled
for a daily meal?
If you just waltz
in here and apologise..
..think he wll grin and accept?
Look, he does not ever want to set
eyes on you after what you have done.
If you keep coming back here..
..it will get rough.
Stop talking to her. Let is leave.
What is your problem?
Tell me, or buzz off!
A few days after you went to
the jail, my school fees was due.
But it was not paid at all.
After that my school staff said..
..you were paying my fees.
I was not paying.
I know you are paying
without anybody's knowledge.
It is okay, I will not tell anybody.
Did not I say that I have not paid?
What do I care if
you go to school? Leave.
Did that cop trick you and
jail you?
Did they hit you in the jail?
Did you suffer?
Poor thing.
It was not that bad. Go, now!
I was not talking about you.
I meant the cop.
You wll get him, one fine day!
Loudmouth, go to sleep.
Rogue!
We can enter our birds
to the race next week.
All the pigeons are ready.
Our next target is Arjun.
Do not know why, but my hands
feel all jittery since morning.
What?
- No!
Need to do something about
this Arjun and "Bird Ravi".
He is a cop.
You can not do him on urgent basis.
Must keep calm.
I am idle nowadays.
Feeling a little lazy.
I am so bored. I want to some job.
- Job?
Oh Jesus! Save this Child.
What?
Did you have a job before all this?
We were breaking a few bones,
causing trouble!
Collecting racketeering money
and we even raced pigeons.
Is that a job, Anna?
You have been acting cocky ever
since I returned from the jail.
Not for me. What job can you do?
- I wll do any job! - Any job?
I wll do any job!
So we wll get you a
painting job with Murali?
But painting is an artist's job.
I can not do that!
You paint the place red
when you hit people.
But that is not the same, idiot!
There is a mechanic in our area.
Mani.
You can chase him
out and do his job.
Chasing out part, I can do..
but mechanic's work..
But I do not know about unscrewing,
screwing and all that.
You said you wll do any job!
You are only naming
jobs that I can not do.
Remember sister Rani? We
seized an auto from her husband..
..when he failed to pay up.
That auto is still with us.
That is correct! - We wll dismantle
and sell the parts? - No!
We wll drive the auto!
Just talking about it will not do!
You need to know how to ride one.
Come here.
You never game me so much respect.
- I will tell. Come and sit.
Tell me. -Sit down!
What is the matter?
- The auto..
You are mocking me?
Auto.. you can drive.
Say something.
- Shall we? - You can drive.
So are driving auto drive tomorrow.
Super, Maari! You go. Be careful.
- Sit in the auto. - It is okay. - Get in!
Get in!
- You too come.
Get in! Get in!
This is strange!
Want to take the auto?
No, Anna. - Where are you headed?
- Dhaba Gardens.
Will not take the auto to Dhaba Gardens?
- I will take the bus. - Get in.
No, Anna. - Get in. - There
is a graveyard nearby. - Get in.
Get in! - Anna! - Right!
Stop it!
Give us the amount.
How much, Anna?
- Just give me that! - Anna.
Anna! Anna! - Leave!
Please be generous.
- Okay, carry on.
Anna! - Stop!
Get in... go sit inside.
Get in.
Auto, huh?
- Of course it is an auto.
Get in.
Sir, I have come on my bike.
- I said get in. - Maari.
Get in I say! - Sir, sir..
Get in I say! Will not you listen!
Squeeze in! Push in!
Stop! He wants to ride
in some other auto!
What are you doing?
- Anna! - Get down!
Get in! - Anna.. - Get in I say!
Keep going, do not stop!
Maari, they are refusing
to accept our entry.
Have a word with them.
The entry time is up, Maari. They have
said not to accept any more entries.
That is not a big deal at all. Call
Murthy Anna. We wll talk to him.
He is not the current president.
If you want to register after
the last date, talk to the new president.
Here he comes. Talk to him.
Greetings.
- Greetings. - Greetings.
Hello, Maari.
You have come to register?
The last date is over.
You should have come sooner.
Oh, I am sorry!
You were in the jail, right?
Okay, okay.
What do we do?
- I do not know, sir.
I said there is a chance if
they request you. - That is true.
Ask them to request, then.
- Request?
This dirty face? - Hey!
- Maari, we wll see next year.
Shani, do not play up.
- I am saying it openly.
It is our turn in this area now.
Are you flying your birds
this year, "Bird" Ravi? - Yes.
Okay, that is nice.
- What are you grinning for?
That is nothing. Forget about it.
I asked you why you were grinning!
Look at that board.
You must wish to see
your name there, sometime.
That is not possible if I compete.
So go ahead.
You think I can not
compete with your birds?
The whole world knows that.
Raising your voice will not change it.
We wll let you win this time.
Hey!
Take his entry.
We wll see who wins.
No, I wll let you have it this time.
- You are competing.
Come.
Why is he requesting
so much? - Yes.
You heard the President.
Take our entry!
We prevented him from participating
so that you could win.
He knew you would fall for it..
..if he teased you.
And you fell for it!
You only gave him entry.
Let it be.
His pigeons are three
months behind ours in training.
He does not have any money to feed
them special food and medicines.
We have readied our pigeons
with imported medicines and tonics.
We have been training
them for four months!
This year is ours.
You have been doing
all this for years now.
Why have you never won?
You can not win unless you
admit the opponent's strengths.
Even if he starts
training them late..
..even if he trains them with
just water. His pigeons will win.
That is Maari. That is why
I told you not to let him enter.
What do you even
know about pigeons?
Wait and watch.
As the race day draws closer..
..you wll get nervous
and ask me for help.
It will happen.
Do not stare at the pigeon after
feeding it. He can not digest his food.
Anna, you told them to train them.
Pigeons are ready.
Anna.. - Hey..
Why are you hitting him?
He asked me not to come.
But I came anyway.
You do good to others
secretly, right?
You have been paying
Kavitha's school fees..
..without anybody's knowledge.
Who? Our Loudspeaker Kavitha?
You never told us!
Why do you refuse to reveal..
..the good in you?
It is fine if you
do not want to accept.
I knew there is a good guy in there,
somewhere.
Now I have seen that.
And that is enough.
Even if you keep chasing me away..
..I wll keep coming back to help.
You have helped me enough, already.
What are you trying to get from me,
by fawning this way?
Why do you like it
so much to be a bad guy?
I had rather be a pure bad guy..
..than an adulterated good guy.
Ask the street vendors to pay up.
Do not leave out anyone.
Pay up! Quickly!
Pay.
- Here.
Greetings, Anna. - Take it out.
What are you staring at?
What a measly amount!
Have all the auto drivers paid up?
- Yes, all of them but he did not pay.
Since when does
Maari drive an auto?
Why has not he paid?
He refuses to join the union.
He refused and you accepted?
Pay up, man.
Pay up nicely or we wll make you.
Hey..
Go.
Go!
"Maari is back!"
"Maari is a fireball."
"Now he is back.
Bigger and better."
"Better take to your heels."
You wll take it?
Will you take it and
reach home in a piece?
"Your face will get mangled, eyes
removed, shape beyond recognition."
Bloody bugger!
"He will cross all his limits."
Hello!
- That is Maari.
How much?
- No, it is fine.
"That is Maari."
"Maari is back!"
"Maari is a fireball."
"He is back!"
"Take to your heels."
Maari..
Still scared of him?
You should have beat him
up and collected the money.
Easy for you to say.
We are the one who got beat up.
It is nothing, sir.
Let it go. Does not matter
if one guy does not pay.
Why do you think we collect?
Is it a major source of income?
Even they are struggling to pay us.
We are collecting to..
..keep them under control.
Even if one person refuses to pay..
..that fear will subside.
Can not let that happen.
Need to fix it tomorrow!
The chains were a lot heavier
before I went to prison.
Now it is all light.
He was roaming around with them!
- Roaming? - I had it in my house, man.
Maari is the most bejewelled
auto driver in this area.
Anna, look who is here.
Maari drives an auto?
I was expecting complaints that he is
doing rowdyism and causing trouble.
But he is just driving an auto?
What is it, Maari?
Heard you refused to pay the fee?
Caught up in the past, were you?
You are a nobody now.
Get that in your head first.
If I am a nobody..
..what drove you to come here?
I meant, your jeep.
Looks like a bit of the old Maari
is left in the auto-guy somewhere.
Should not be. Drop your cigarette.
Drop it!
Sir, why are you hitting him?
Careful, Maari!
Maari, listen. He is a cop.
Let is not cause trouble. Sir, sir.
Sir, we will not cause trouble.
-Trying to slither away?
Sir, do not hit him.
Please listen to us.
Do not hit him.
Sir..
No, sir. Do not hit him!
Please listen, sir.
Sir, please tell them to stop.
Stop hitting!
- Okay, that is enough. Stop!
I am the boss here from now. Okay?
Either run away with your pigeons.
Or lie low with your
tail between your legs.
I wll come hit you
whenever I am bored.
You are my Punching Bag now.
Hey, give me a cigarette.
So..
When a mosquito bites a sleeping
man, it does not make it a hero.
One fine day, if it bites him when
he is awake, it will die in one shot.
One fine day..
Maari
He comes in his cop uniform,
owing we can not hit him then.
If only he dared
to come without it!
We should not keep
quiet anymore, Maari.
Just say the word and..
..we will deal with
him in other ways.
We need to get Velu
Anna released first.
How will that cop let that happen?
Leave! Why are you
taking me away? - Come.
Leave!
- Come, come.
Maari, I do not know anything.
I did not help him intentionally.
I thought he was a nice guy.
I am not on his side. - Hey..
I need some information
to lock him.
You know all about
the frauds he is committed?
Tell me.
I had lose my job if he found out.
If you do not tell him, you wll lose
your life. Is that okay? - Tell!
I do not know his
lorry routes, Maari.
But I do know one thing. To avoid the
checking that happens in all the tolls...
He uses travels vehicles
to carry small loads.
I know some of these routes, Maari.
Looks like the customs guys.
We are caught!
You!
Yes, we got it, sir.
- Means?
Thieves are caught!
- Open the door!
Bloody hell. - What?
Bullshit!
Hello? - Sir, the press and
media have come to the station.
Did you call them?
- What, the press?
We will give the entire
details of it very soon.
Inquiry is underway. - Sir, how
did you receive the information?
Officer Arjun is here! Catch him!
Click photo!
He is done so much,
but acts like he is done nothing.
Thank you, officer Arjun.
You have made our jobs easier.
How much you have contributed!
-He does that a lot, sir.
Keep up the good work.
- Thank you, sir.
Come here.
What is going on?
Sir, this is your doing, right?
You are so great!
- What?
When I came in the morning, the
smuggled wood and the smugglers..
..were outside the station.
I thought you caught them as usual
and called the Revenue Department.
Are you out of your mind?
- Not so loud, sir! - Sir, look here.
I did not do it.
Who else? How do you
get it right every time, sir?
You are a smart one, sir.
Right? - Maari..
He is so right every time..
..almost like he is
the one transporting it! - No!
He is a very nice guy!
Wondering why your own
goods are in your station?
You are not in control,
as you think, officer!
I stand to lose nothing with this.
Red sanders is transported
to Tamil Nadu from Andhra.
It is all happening..
Somebody has given..
It is not just the goods that were caught.
Your men were caught with it.
Upon enquiry, he is willing to talk.
He could talk to the Revenue Officers, too.
Think about what would happen to
you then. The Press is here, too.
This was the mosquito that bit me
when I was asleep the other day, right?
What did I tell you?
I told you, if I wake up one day and
hit you once, you will die immediately.
Did I say or not?
- Yes, Maari. - Right?
What do you want?
Release Velu Anna.
How is that possible?
We have got evidence.
Like you need lessons in deceit,
officer!
Get one of your own men to surrender
and get Velu Anna out or else..
Sannasi!
Present, sir!
Just checking!
How did you do it, sir?
It was superb. The area
has been better since you came.
Ask him one by one,
he wll answer patiently.
May I leave, officer?
Move, move. Careful,
do not share it on WhatsApp!
"That is Maari."
Maari!
"Maari."
- Release Velu?
Do not do it, man.
You have been an enemy all along.
But I was an insider
who betrayed their trust.
He would be very
pissed off with me.
Not just that, Maari's position will
get even stronger if Velu is out.
What can I do?
Want me to get arrested, instead?
Your man has been
caught red-handed.
This was the one thing you had to do.
And you have screwed that up, too.
Do not take tension unnecessarily.
We wll all get locked in if we are caught.
- That is why I am telling you,
Velu has to be released.
Velu has lost his political
support after he went to jail.
Even if he is released now..
He can not touch a
policeman without support.
You are police.. okay..
What if he targets us?
That is your problem. - Sir,
you are disassociating yourself?
Look, it is your
man who is been caught.
I can still get you
in trouble and escape.
Be happy that I have not done that.
Try to transport the
goods safely from now.
What is happening, Anna?
He is saying such things.
And there is no respect these days.
We need to be careful with him.
Move aside!
- Greetings. - Velu Anna has come!
Come, Maari. Put the garland.
Greetings, Anna.
Father.
- Hey.. Son..
I told you not to go there!
You did not listen to me.
Are you okay? - I am okay, dad.
- How did you get released?
They released Velu Annan first.
Then they said it was the
same case and released all of us.
Maari is the cause for our release.
- Okay.
When I heard that you had been released..
..I knew you had get me out somehow.
But why did you use this evidence?
It is gone waste! - You are out
of prison. What more do we need?
If we had gone to Revenue Department,
we could have gotten back at him.
Or even finished him completely.
Think I wll let the guy
who got you locked up get away?
I wll take special care of him.
You forget about it, Anna.
Tomorrow is the festival of lights.
And you are out of prison!
You just watch our
atrocity in our area today!
So, I am going to the barber..
- Barber..
You do not have any hair.
Why do you need a hair cut?
Go! Go!
- I am happy, Maari.
Because of you everyone
got released. - What?
What a pity!
- Who got your men out?
I only got Velu Annan out.
You were just free add ons.
Get out!
Hi, dude!
- Hi!
Look at all the reverence.
- Salute, Maari.
How is it going, man? - Fine, man.
- Give me a hi-5, man. - Cool!
You fool.
They are here?
It is the festival of lights indeed.
Start collecting in all the shops.
Go to the street vendor.
What, they are back?
Pay up the money.
- It is festival time.
So what if it is festival time?
Pay up!
Pay up, man.
Anna, pay up. I want to go home!
It is not unusual to collect,
right, Maari?
Poor fellow.
There!
Anna, at least you pay up, please?
"Maari is different now."
"Maari is more stronger."
You are wearing make up?
Oldie, walk away or I wll
light up this cracker on you.
Hey! You!
Come, I am going.
That is Maari for you!
Poor girl.
This is the usual amount.
Return this back to them.
Festival wishes to you!
- Same to you.
Bye!
- Bye!
"I know it looks crooked, my path.
All you straight-forward guys, get out!"
"It might feel a bit wrong but
it is right. This is Maari's style."
"This light of our lives Is Maari the
Great! Even the police salute him!"
"Stay if you want to.
Or walk away. Good times are here!"
"Bend over and people
stab you in the back."
"So stand tall.
That is the only life hack."
"When finding a partner
is like finding trouble."
"Being a loner
makes so much sense."
"Do not you say such things, son.
We are one, now and forever."
"Do what feels right."
"The doors to my home are open,
for you."
"I was born alone, I wll die alone.
I do not need any family."
"Her words oozed honey,
she came into my life."
"I know it looks crooked, my path.
All you straight-forward guys, get out!"
"It might feel a bit wrong but
it is right. This is Maari's style."
"This light of our lives Is Maari the
Great! Even the police salute him!"
"Stay if you want to.
Or walk away. Good times are here!"
Have the birds
returned from training?
We flew fifty,
only twenty have returned.
What about Maari's?
He flew thirty.
All thirty have returned.
What is funny?
I told you the other day.
That you had come to me for
help as the race draws closer.
What can you do for me?
He can not participate without his birds.
- No, do not do that. Be quiet.
You do not understand the seriousness
of pigeon fancying business.
Make sure he does not do anything.
Officer Arjun,
you have done so much for us.
Let us handle this.
- Who says I am doing this for you?
He should feel pain.
We need to hit him where it hurts.
Do not do anything without
Ravi Anna's consent.
It is already done.
Hey!
Maari..
Ten of our pigeons are dead.
They have set it on fire
when we were not around.
It was that girl Sridevi, who opened
the cages and saved the pigeons.
If it was not for her,
all the birds would be dead.
She burnt hands while
trying to save the birds.
She was here when
they burnt the cage.
If she had not been there,
all the birds would be dead.
They say pigeons never
return to a burnt cage.
They would have gotten scared. Our
pigeons will never return, Anna.
Maari, do not mistake
me for saying this.
Let is leave this place.
There is nothing here for us.
Why should we suffer here?
Velu Anna is back now.
Let him deal with the police.
What do we gain in these fights?
If pigeons were furious
then they could have attacked us.
What did the poor birds do to them?
I know you wll refuse to leave.
But, it hurts to see
you like this. Maari.
Let is get out of here.
Sannasi, pack our things
and get the vehicle ready.
Go!
Shani, see there.
You said pigeons do not
return to a burnt cage.
How did they return?
The birds know this is their home.
But you do not realise it.
This has to end today.
I told you not to do anything!
Everyone found out that
we set fire to his loft.
I have been banned from
pigeon racing altogether!
What about it?
My dignity is lost!
I can not race pigeons anymore.
Stop yelling!
Following my word got you this far.
So what if you can not race?
Playing with pigeons.
You will not understand that.
It is an ancestral sport.
You are following
his instructions now?
Anna, do not just hit me!
You are just a label.
Who plots the action?
It is our Officer Arjun.
So you are supporting him? Fools..
Do you know what you have done?
Do you know what Maari would do
if you lay a finger on his pigeons?
What is happening? - He was
just waiting for the right moment.
You have taunted him. He will come!
Fire!
Maari!
Maari, listen to me!
Do not do this, Maari.
I only kept quiet this
long as you were a cop.
But you have touched my pigeons.
I wll kill you and
go to prison again.
Coward!
I am sorry, Maari.
Maari, wait! Listen to me.
Wait, Maari.
Listen to me, Maari. Listen to me.
I forbade that policeman,
but he threatened us to do it.
I had nothing to do
with your loft burning.
I know all about the frauds
he is committed.
I am willing to testify anywhere,
anytime.
I do not even trust a good man.
Why would I trust filth like you?
You were saying?
You wll kill me and go to prison?
I wll say you killed
him for revenge and..
..get you locked up forever.
You crook!
I told you not to trust him.
Round up everyone.
No one should escape.
Sir, hope you are fine.
What was that? You always say..
"I wll finish you off!"
See what I have done?
Now I have finished you.
You wll spend the rest
of your life in prison.
Drag him away.
- Come!
What are you doing?
That is not our man.
That is the man.
Get him. - Okay, sir.
Let me go. Sir.
Sir, why are you arresting me?
Let me go.
- Stop.
They have told us what you do.
I have got a guy in
the Revenue Department.
I wll be restored to my old power.
All I need is an eye-witness
to everything that Arjun has committed.
Sir, I am not afraid,
with Maari and you by my side.
I am willing to talk openly.
Maari!
What did you say? You wll finish me?
That was nice.
You said it real nice.
And do not come out, okay?
Just stay inside.
You wll be safer there.
Maari!
Sub-Inspector Arjun
has been arrested by..
..Revenue Department
for smuggling red sanders.
I can not decide whether..
..you are a good guy or a bad guy.
Why do you doubt it?
Of course I am a bad guy!
Good guys can not be trusted.
They can turn bad at any point.
Men who appear to be good
but do bad, are even worse.
But a guy,
who openly claims to be bad..
..but does some good,
can be trusted.
I trust you.
So what?
I feel like a lie..
..from a long time back...
..has become the truth now.
I am serious. I really..
..do like you now.
Oh dear. No, madam.
This love thing will not suit
my character. I have got my pigeons..
..my boys and I have got the area people
to trouble whenever I am bored.
I would be free and happy
like this all the time.
You think about it, we could
just be friends if you want.
Okay? Bye.