Sudan...Africa...
A strange place to me,
Unknown language...unknown people...
Having been a fisherman all my life,
it's not easy to learn new job.
I found a good friend there.
His name is Swamy.
Like my Chinna!
I hated this job but still I did.
I separated fish from sea,
may be that was a sin,
life too me away from sea.
Oh no! Why do you always talk
about water, sea and fishes?
What's so great about your place!
Pani!
People back in my village
too work in fields.
This is different Pani.
You can't understand.
Buddy, the best thing I learnt
from you is smoking cigars.
Very good.
Isn't it great?
That's special from my place.
My only comfort is talking
to Pani once in week.
I'm happy all that day.
I'll sleep peacefully.
Slowly I got used to the place
and the people there.
All were like me, right?
2 years!
Somehow went by!
I'm going back home.
I'm going to meet my Pani.
I'll sleep in the lap of Mother Sea.
How are you, Pani?
How about you?
Now I feel good!
Just one more week to go, Maria!
Two years went past somehow.
But now a week appears much longer.
You said it and I didn't, that's all.
I'm coming Pani!
Back to sea breeze,
salt water,
and you in my arms.
First thing, I want to have is delicious
spicy gravy and rice prepared by you.
Sure.
Did you get my last letter?
Got your 53rd letter...
and...got that also!
Hey, don't send me anymore!
Rest in person.
Is it?
Yesupadam has announced to every person
in the village about our wedding.
The only thing left is
to stitch your suit.
Tell Yesupadam my size has changed
in the last two years.
Let's get it done when I am back.
I hope you are in the
size I can hug, right?
What?
I am running out of change.
I need to get back to work.
Shall I go?
Shall I?
Listen Maria, come back safely!
Okay, see you.
What is he saying?
- He thinks this is Dubai.
Hey! This is not Dubai!
This is Africa!
We have shed our blood
for two years.
He has just arrived.
He will know as days go by.
Hey Bald man, play some Telugu song.
Hey uncle, play Hindi song,
What Hindi song?
You made Ravan with Shahrukh
competing with us,
it flopped, right?
Why do you still insist on Hindi songs?
A heart is sprouting inside iron...
It is seeking kiss in love...
Madrasi in Dharavi...I see you in Africa...
find them everywhere.
Shut up, you nasty!
You're with us unable to find
job anywhere, why still separate us?
Sridevi is from South,
Hema Malini is from South,
Silk Smitha is from South.
A.R.Rahman is from South.
So is Sachin Tendulkar.
Sorry! Tongue slip.
Maria, isn't our place
foreign city to this place?
Will you keep shut?
Keeping shut always has
made it useless.
Your life is set,
you'll get married soon.
You're feeling so much
for 2 years seeing a photo.
But see, I'm feeling so much
for 4 girls in on photo.
But still unable to trap even one!
No use if you have the feeling,
it must come from that side too.
My name is Maria.
Maria means
the man who never dies!
As my name suggests…
I was arrogant and full of pride.
Instead of salty air,
I got dust storm.
Instead of dry fish,
I got tasteless meal.
All my arrogance disappeared.
There I was the king...
King of the sea.
By catching the Tiger shark
Maria has brought pride to place.
What his late father could not
20 years ago he did it now.
You are the King of the sea.
You've kept your father's pride!
Youth is swinging...
Swinging amidst lashing waves...
It's a garland of flowers...
It has come seeking you...
Oh my golden girl...
Come my, dear...
The golden girl gave her
beauty to me...
She hid more beauty under her wings...
She gives kiss for kiss...
When you're with me smiling
time flies away...
My cuckoo...my melody...
my golden girl...
My moon...my jasmine...
My golden girl fills my life...
Looks like you've stolen everything, Maria!
Leave something for us too!
Didn't find anyone else to pick up fight?
Mind your work.
He's the only guy refusing
to come to my way!
In cool eyes...
Under cool moonlight...
One the wings of romance...
Heart is having hiccups...
Kiss me passionately on my cheeks...
Make a bed of honey and love for me...
Okay, come abroad.
You're the lone man who rocks with the
spear fishing technique learnt over years.
Buddy risks life to catch fish and
we enjoy eating food and drinking!
I'm hungry, open the lunch box.
Take this, buddy.
He gives only cooked rice.
This is mixed with love and wish.
Is Maria yearning for it?
Look, he always tells about you to Pani.
He's delivering dialogue
about love and wish here.
If he likes, he won't leave
without having it.
If Maria doesn't like,
he'll never go after it.
I too know that.
Like NTR and Savithri...
like ANR and Jamuna...
She's the perfect match for him like them.
Buddy, shall I tell you a thing?
- Why not two?
Buddy, I'm serious.
- Go ahead.
What you don’t expect may never happen,
but what you expect will surely happen.
Are you giving counter punch to mine?
I'll kick on your pot belly.
If you kick on my belly...
Nothing happened till now and
it'll not happen in future too.
Got it? Shut up and mind your work.
I promised her to bring him
to church tomorrow.
If I don't take him, she'll kill me.
If you become a hurdle,
she'll poison your food too.
If he comes to know about this,
he'll kill us.
What is that murmur?
- Nothing, he keeps on blabbering.
Why did you insist I must come here
as if it is very important?
Church...God...
- To wash off the sins committed by us.
The only sin I've committed
is meeting you.
Nothing else.
Where's Das?
Where is Das?
He would've got drunk and
playing cards somewhere.
We must reform him!
What's this Chinna?
Strange to see you in church.
Why not ask him directly?
Will you keep shut?
You came here to see me, right?
Did you feel like that?
He brought me here.
Then, why did keep on staring at me?
Staring at you?
I was watching the girls with you.
Had you seen other girls,
I would've cut you to pieces.
You know that, right?
Why are you hitting him?
Look at me!
What you don’t expect may never happen!
What you expect will surely happen!
May be he got it!
Why do you hide your feelings?
Look dear...
Don't play with me about
inner and outer feelings.
Before it is dark, go home carefully.
Go.
How long will you escape from me?
Hey...look at me!
I saw it in your eyes now...
Some day you will be mine!
Bye.
Looks like she'll trap you, buddy.
How is it possible?
If she thinks so, is it okay?
Nobody can trap you so easily, buddy.
Who Maria is!
Why is he looking angrily at me?
Hi Pani! How do you do?
Long time no see.
Are you returning from church?
I don't feel like talking
to any girl in this village.
But I don't know why with you...
I'm going on talking to you
but you're not responding at all.
You must talk to me next time
as I talked to you now.
Brother, if you like any girl,
either you take her as concubine,
or else devastate,
but why are you hesitating about Pani?
All other women are like losing hair.
But Pani is my life.
I must touch only after
making her my wife.
That's why I'm patient.
I'll tell how to trap him.
If mach remains inside box,
can it light fire?
It won't light fire.
Fire is lighted only when stick
is rubbed with the box.
,Got it now?
How much we owe to Dosa Punnamma's?
Rs.100.
Let's clear it today.
Who is Joseph? Never seen him here.
He's new to this area, buddy.
He took loan and refusing to repay.
Where did you get money to give loans?
I can't believe it.
Why did you back off?
- Nothing, buddy.
How far still?
- Near by...next street.
I don't know to which street
I must take him now.
He's killing me with questions.
Buddy, next street.
Just now you said this street.
I'm telling the same thing again, buddy.
I'll tell that again, buddy.
Come.
What?
Dreaming about me hugging her!
If you act like a pimp again,
I'll kill you.
Got it?
You talked about match box and stick,
he's dumb like a mud doll.
I'll puncture your back.
Buddy!
Come here.
Coming, buddy.
The slap I got morning
is still hurting me.
Don't know what he's up to now?
- Come.
Why did you call me, buddy?
Buddy...that is...
- Tell me, what's it, buddy?
Nothing...
Buddy, my button!
That is...
Tell me now.
That's it.
That is...
It came..
What has come?
That thing...
It has come...on her...
Buddy! I knew!
You will get it.
Hold your head high.
I feel shy.
Buddy...will you do me a favour?
Tell me, buddy.
I want to meet her.
- Who?
Tell me.
I must see her...
That's all?
I'll get her right now.
Buddy, not now.
She makes fantastic gravy and rice,
will you ask her to come here with it?
Look, how he's blushing!
Sister! It has worked!
My son never asked till now,
he asked me to get food for him.
I don't see him here.
He'll come.
I'll leave it here.
He'll come and have it.
He told me to come here, right?
Yes.
Would he come here?
- Why did she come here?
Where else would he go?
She too has brought food.
- Buddy!
Buddy!
He asked me to come here, right?
Why hasn't he turned up yet?
Let him come at anytime,
please sit here.
How was he today morning?
Have you started it again?
It's 50th time now.
Tell me, this is that last time.
When he came out,
the way he was feeling shy...
Never seen him like that, trust me.
Infact I too felt embarrassed,
think about it yourself.
Then?
He hung his head feeling shy
thinking about you.
Why hasn't he come yet?
He'll come...wait.
He must come from home, right?
That old woman is there, right?
She'll not even sleep.
She keeps vigil on him like a ghost
fearing some girl may kidnap him.
I must gouge out her eyes with ladle.
She thinks the food counter
is some big star hotel.
Only I know the pain of people
eating in her food counter.
I'll take you to task.
Be patient.
This will carry on few more days only.
As soon as I go to that home,
I'll shut down the food counter immediately.
Do that first, at least for this
I'll unite you with him.
Keep watching the scene, the old woman must
come wagging like dog for food after me.
I'll hit you with slippers.
How dare you talk like that!
Bloody girl!
My son knows about you,
that's why he told me to bring food for him.
Come...come...
- Stop...stop...
Stop, you girl.
Stop...stop...
How dare you try to trap my son!
If you look at my son,
I'll gouge out your eyes!
Get lost!
Buddy..it seems he'll cheat me
into going to church,
and take me around the streets
for collecting a never given loan,
and imagine Pani as his sister
like in the film 'Raktha Sambandham'.
Hey buffalo! You won't anything
silly like this again, right?
Nephew! Can I ask you a question?
Why not ask 5 or 6?
I'm serious, why are you doing comedy?
Don't get angry.
Come on, ask me.
That girl is yearning to be
yours since childhood.
Why are you rejecting her?
You've grown old but not wise.
Ever since my father went to sea
with Yesupadam and died,
Seal has been accusing them of it,
6how can she accept this girl?
Even if I go against her and marry her,
can she live happily there?
Let's allow them be happy like that.
Sea is there for all my life.
If you want to share drinks
happily, do join me.
If you want to talk about this,
then go to bed silently.
Got it?
I'm scared you may hit me!
Will you hit me?
Go to sleep.
Special news bulletin about weather…
Fishermen are advised not to venture
into sea for 48 hours...
It seems your man has gone to sea.
Does he have sense?
Are you up?
What brings you here in so heavy rain?
Heavy winds and rains, yet he ventured
into sea with his friends.
What are you saying?
Inform Yesupadam about it.
Sir...
Where you my King?
Dusk has fallen...
The food has gone cold...
My heart is sinking...
If you're with me...
The sky will be bright...
Today you're not with me...
My heart is broken...
heart is broken...
What am I to do, my King?
I'm aimless...
Why are you sitting distraught here?
Missing fishermen have returned safely.
Boat got damaged, that's all.
Lost honour, buddy.
Damaged Yesupadam's boat.
Entire village saw this, buddy.
Buddy...buddy...
Lost honour, right?
Don't you dare come with me again!
Go alone.
Lost honour...
Maria is shameless man, right?
I don't have any honour, right?
You went away as you like...
I almost died waiting for your return.
You know there's cyclone,
why did you enter sea?
Go away silently.
What do you think of yourself?
I don't think of anything.
What?
Love?
Empty ground!
Mind your work.
You're alive, right?
I've seen you, right?
Get lost.
Go away.
Get lost!
Got match stick?
- No.
What?
Got match stick?
Got it.
Take match box.
He'll never reform.
You carry on.
Found him for free.
Sea and love...it's always new
any number of times you see.
What do you say?
Hey old man!
Looks like you're in mood for it.
I'm telling you with my experience.
Experience?
If you've experience,
how is that you're a bachelor?
Love is heart must always hit
the coast like waves.
That will give you strength.
For a man who wishes to succeed,
a woman must be there in his life.
That's okay,
who is the woman in your life?
Buddy! Did you hear the old man?
It seems a woman must be
there in a man's life.
Stop it.
My dear new couple...in the presence
of Lord and friends...
Pani! Girls of your age are getting married,
when are you getting married?
Just say okay, let's marry immediately.
Don't you know whose bike that is?
Move.
If you're feeling so itchy,
rub yourself into some thorny bush.
Why are you rubbing ladies' slippers?
If say loudly what I said now,
people would laugh at you,
so, what you will do in future is,
if you come to church,
don't misbehave with girls,
behave properly!
What bothers you if he
touches Pani's slippers?
You like her so much,
why do you hide it?
You love Pani, buddy.
You'll get the sick instead of him.
This is what you get for telling truth.
Stop Pani.
Please listen to me.
Wait a minute, Pani.
- What's it?
Maria...
- Why? Forget it.
Stop.
I don't want this trouble anymore.
Please listen to me.
What?
Listen to me,
I'm happy with choir singing,
going to church and offering prayers.
He told there's nothing
in him for me, right?
Why again?
No, only I know how much he loves you.
Yes...would anyone hit the girl he loves?
Listen to me.
He grew up like that.
He loves you, that's why he had a fight
with dark man for touching your slippers.
Do you know that?
What did you say?
Go, ask him.
I saw you, right?
You're alive, right?
You like her so much,
why do you hide it?
You love Pani.
For a man who wishes to succeed,
a woman must be there in his life.
Some day you will be mine.
Why so late?
I had to prepare food.
Though I warn my heart refuses to listen...
Even in dream I think about you only...
What?
Annagaru's romance is rocking,
he's sensational.
There's power in first love...
And you know that well...
Dreams are murmuring...
My heart is swinging...
Isn't it sensational, buddy?
Buddy...buddy...
Take it.
The time girl has come seeking me...
When she stands away from me...
Without your order
I can't even take breathe...
Hey Yesupadam! Come out!
My son is NTR but
your daughter is not Savithri.
If you've shame and shy, come out.
Hey little devil!
Didn't you find any other man in town?
Did you find my only my son?
Come out I say!
What? Why are you going overboard?
If I come to know if you're
after my son or talk to him,
I'll throw you into sea, mind it.
Why are you staring at me?
Why are you all watching fun?
Fight between daughter-in-law
and mother-in-law is common.
Isn't it?
I'll cut your tongue.
Who is your mother-in-law?
Why are you asking as if you don't know?
You!
Have you gone that far?
If you enter my home as daughter-in-law,
I'll cut your legs.
Go now, let's think about that
after marriage.
Are you planning marriage also?
Let me see, how you'll marry him!
I know who is responsible for this,
let Maria come.
Is any record dance going
here to watch? Go away.
Get lost.
Go...have come to watch...go away.
Today, he's dead in my hands.
Love story between a famous
film star and...
What are you doing here?
If there's not a woman in house,
did you see how shabby the home is?
Don't you wash clothes?
If Seal sees you, you're gone.
Go.
Your name is Maria,
you're afraid of Seal.
She'll wake up entire village.
What am I to do now?
She has already done it.
Announcement is also over.
What do you want?
Will you give whatever I ask?
It depends on what you ask...
What if you ask more...
Would I ask for a child?
You may ask that also.
Go.
Shall I go?
You said empty ground.
You own it now, right?
Go.
Why don't you be with me
for some more time?
Why are you leaving urgently?
Before our talk drop like rain
and hearts sprout out...
Please don't go away from me...
If you vanish like lightning,
I'll remain in darkness...
With an unseen net,
you trapped my heart...
Blowing unheard whistle,
you made my heart to tremble...
Come to me like a wave...
Shall I become a bangle on your hand?
Late is nectar...
learn to be patient...
Nectar is bitter and
your word is sweet...
You've to wait for some more time...
What's so urgent for you?
Why are you wearing these
clothes for fishing?
Are you not coming for fishing?
I told you to go alone, right?
Go.
That's it, why would you need us now?
Carry on.
I'll wait for you like the
ever lasting sea water...
The anger on my face is
unknown hurdle for you...
Even in salty winds,
I can taste sweetness...
Let's cover ourselves with
the warmth of hot wind...
The fish smell on your body is
fragrance of flowers to me in my arms...
Talk all the night and
hunt me with your words...
You're the eyelid of my eyes…
You're the father of my kids...
Our kids must sing and
dance like waves...
Your words will come true...
you and me would we...
Let's drown ourselves
in the sea of love...
Why are you surprized?
If we've come to your house
seeking girl, you must be very lucky.
My elder brother
who refused to marry till now,
today he wants to marry
only Pani no one else.
How long will you ponder, Yesupadam?
You took loan from me years ago.
I didn't care about it.
4Keep it as gift and give your
daughter in marriage to me.
Marriage for money!
Sister insisted, so I came
seeking hand traditionally.
If not I would've kidnapped her.
What's wrong with him?
Okay...just because Chinna went away...
You always hit only me.
I can hit only you.
Who else can I hit?
Okay, don't get angry.
I should've killed and
thrown your body in sea.
Just because I left you,
are you acting like a hero here?
Hey dark man! I don't have anyone.
The people I have one of them died.
I can't lose her.
Why are you still talking to him, Maria?
I expected you'd hit him.
You calm down.
Sir, please don't.
A girl's life would get ruined.
Pay my money or give me your daughter.
Go...go away...
This is my family problem,
don't interfere.
Go away!
Come...come...
Yesupadam, my loan with interest must
reach my home by tomorrow evening.
If not you'll not live.
Threatened Yesupadam...
He warned him to pay up.
Don't know what Yesupadam would do?
Hello...please, come in.
Two years contract.
First year salary will be
adjusted with advance.
You'll get only the second year's salary.
If you're not happy with job,
you can't quit midway.
You're going to Sudan.
You know that, right?
Sign the agreement.
Seal was telling you all these years,
good sense prevailed on you now.
Settle the dark man's loan.
Don't take it as for him, it was Pani.
Take care of her.
You were born in sea...
you grew up in sea...
How can you leave this place? How?
Just 2 years only!
No problem, bye.
You were living happily with sea
and your friends.
Because of me...because of me...
Not because of you...it was for you.
Don't cry.
Will you send me off with tears?
Just 2 years only.
It'll fly away.
I'll be back at the wink of an eye.
I didn't have the courage that day
to turn back and see her face.
2 years have passed.
I'll go home and see my Pani
in person not in a photo.
Are you sad, buddy?
His lover is waiting for him back home.
My good friend has left her there.
Will you please stop it?
Do you've lover back home?
Wife?
You'd have escaped from her.
It seems he's married.
He's not a happy bachelor like us.
From Andhra!
This is Lord Venkateswara's dollar.
Where are we now?
What?
Nothing...he said sizes have changed.
Will it fit him?
Forget it, if he eats your cooking,
he'll get back to shape.
Sister!
- Come in.
- I'm here.
Got two calls from Africa, sister.
Don't know what it is, come quickly.
When?
I'm Williams here, Maria's colleague.
Where is he?
I called you to tell something.
Go ahead.
Few workers in my company have
been kidnapped by terrorists.
We don't have any information
about them till now.
We suspect Maria is also among them.
What are you saying?
You don't worry, Sudan government
is trying to rescue them.
Nothing will happen to them.
You...
Give it to me...
Tell him to give me...I'm hungry.
Tell him to give.
Yesterday...she was there...
I was also there with her...
I...
I was there...
Millions of stars in the sky showered
light when you were with me...
She filled my heart with honey
and happiness..
She entwined me like a plant...
My heart...my thoughts are
filled with you...
Till yesterday sorrow wasn't
a part of my life...
It was your breathe I felt in
the jingle of my bangles...
O time, go back and get her for me...
Waves of tears are rolling for you...
It's waiting eagerly for arrival...
Sir, we sent him trusting you, right?
We can find a job for a man.
Can we guard his entire life?
Forget about your guarding duty,
you sent him there, right?
Answer me.
Look, I sent him on his mother's request.
Ask his mother or
the company where he works.
I don't have anything do with it.
Bloody...
Bloody mad men!
What do you want?
Money?
We don't have.
Neither you have nor do I!
Can't you see it?
All we've is just life.
Take that also, bloody!
What?
Fire!
Come.
They'll not kill me.
They need money, right?
If you cut my legs and
ask me to dance...
If you strangle my neck
and ask me to sing...
If you cut my wings and
ask me to fly...
Sorrow in my heart is turning
into erupting lava...
I'm a hunter who hunts in sea...
I'm the king of sea...
I spill blood to fish out pearls...
Maria is the king of sea...
If they make prawn gravy,
I'm on moon...
Salted fish curry is mouth watering...
The intoxication will last for a day...
I've put lid on the volcano
of anger for you...
I'm singing alone before
people with stone hearts...
I'm struggling between
these heartless people...
I came alone to a strange country,
I was living like a corpse here...
I lost my sense living with the
hope of uniting with you...
Sir, I'm AOC worker Maria here.
Yes, I'm Maria.
Where are you, Maria?
Sir...want money.
They're shooting people here, sir.
I don't get what you say!
Yes Pani, it's me.
I'm alive.
I don't know how long I will be alive!
What? What did you say now?
Yes sir...help sir...
I don't get what you're saying, Maria.
Yes, it's me...tell me...
I don't know if I can see you again or not.
Please don't say like that.
I don't get what you say!
Where are you? Please tell me that.
Where are you?
No sir...I don't know, sir.
It's all over, Pani.
Why are you talking like this?
You...don't wait for me.
Listen to me carefully.
Nothing will happen to you.
Yes sir...
Speaking...speaking...
You're my husband.
Nobody can separate us.
I'll wait for your return.
Can you hear me, Maria?
Hello brother! Kill me right now!
If not you'll regret for it later.
I've informed Pani, it's over.
Over!
What happened?
What did they do with you?
I was scared without you.
How, buddy?
Let's go from here.
Yes, let's go from here.
Let's go.
Where is he?
It's all over, Pani.
Don't wait for me.
Don't cry...don't cry...
Don't cry, Maria...
Come...come...
Come.
I don't know if this mother's
love can bring him,
but I'm confident your love will
surely bring him back.
You're coming...you're coming...
Yesupadam...Yesupadam...
Maria is coming....he's coming...
Yesupadam, he's coming!
He's coming!
Maria is coming...Maria is coming...
Who told you?
I'm telling!
I made inquiry.
He'll never come.
He'll come.
I'll come.
You humiliated me here, right?
I'm like fire, what will you do now?
Are you laughing?
Laugh...hasn't your pride come down yet?
I should've taken you to task
that day itself.
You can't do anything, you dog.
Are you calling me a dog?
Can't I do anything?
If Maria can't get me,
nobody else can get me.
I'll kill you.
Will you kill me?
Okay, take it...kill me.
Kill me I say!
Yesupadam...Maria is coming.
Maria is coming....he's coming.
When cyclones of fire hits...
When the snow clad mountains of mercy melts...
When injustice touches the sky...
When humans lose humanity....
When life is strained by tyranny...
Your love will not stop...
My heart get going...
my heart get going...
You get up and run...
Love will never end...
Though our skies are different...
Though our hopes are shattered...
Though youth has changed...
Though you've forgotten me...
Even if world loses status...
Your love won't stop....
Don't get afraid or scared...
Your sorrows are yesterday's tales...
We're new born...
Your words are cool like moonbeam...
Your love will stand test of time...
In a fraction of second it vanished...
My Maria promised to come
at the wink of an eye.
I'm living for you only.
Come back...I must bear your child.
It must play with waves.
We must watch it.
Come back quickly....come...
Come!
Come.
Mother!
It's sea!
Where you my King?
Dusk has fallen...
The food has gone cold...
My heart is sinking...
If you're with me...
The sky will be bright...
Today you're not with me...
My heart is broken...
heart is broken...
Eyes are searching for eyelids...
Sea of tears rolling down...
Body won over life...
Moment stood still like eon...
Where you my King?
What am I to do, my king?
I'm living for you only...
For 21 days I was held
captive by the Sudan militia.
For 9 days I ran over 300 kilometres
without food and water.
I lost my friend Chinna in sea.
Lost Swamy in desert.
I overcame every hurdle
to come back alive.
For my Pani!
Now only I'm breathing.
You're my breathe.