prior to the Second World War the
Japanese military's had occupied
northeast China and established the
puppet state of manchu quo in order to
expand their Greater East Asia Empire
the Japanese did much preparatory work
some of their least known activities
were the experiments on bacterial
weapons by the manchurian 731 squadron
this squadron had many subsections they
were Helia
Sunwoo
Lynn cow
mutans yang and the and our rural
experimental station
the headquarters of the 731 was situated
in the ping Fang district of Harbin it
covered a large area of land and the
existence of the headquarters was highly
classified surrounded by high tension
electric fences inside there were
extensive facilities and animal breeding
units a crematorium a pathology
laboratory of jail an electrical
generating plant the Commandant office
and other facilities for various
experimental projects infirmary in 1945
the Japanese forces were suffering heavy
losses on all fronts in an effort to win
the war using biological warfare the
military headquarters reinstated a
leftenant general oshiro a medical
doctor to be the 731 squadron commander
yet the same person had previously been
relieved of this post on charges of
corruption at the same time a group of
young soldiers were sent to Harbin as
new recruits to the squadron
I wonder when they'll come and pick us
up I'm freezing captain takahara is
going to buy hollow he said to collect
on You sergeant he's been gone almost an
hour where is he why aren't will have to
go to buy wally ow this place is
freezing cold it's as bad as chiba
prefecture i think this is much colder
than chiba right is she karwa it really
makes no difference to me we're not
going home anyway we're stuck here huh
look it in it's only been a few days and
it should cover already misses home
ishika was just a mama's boy he even
broke down and cried when she said
goodbye to him you cried as well didn't
you know I didn't only my mother and my
sister did yeah my mom cried too
although I didn't cry but I never i
still felt very bad it's because my
father died here in action so did my
father so did my father and brother they
were both killed here fighting in China
here try this go on
huh
this kind of rice cakes hard to get even
in Japan hmm don't you know that teach
you to waste food eat it I don't know
he's so strange
excuse me sir dr. a she's just arrived
at headquarters would you please it's
okay I'm coming yes sir
isshikawa yeah catch dr. Ishi general
kikuchi general
easy old friend you still look the same
you haven't changed at all since I saw
you last same old 731 Ichi dr. Ishi is
back let's welcome him in another way
dr. ish's return to the core yeah that's
right he just arrived today I'm
surprised they set him back here catch
yo Eddie now listen up I'm your new
section head my name is sergeant
kawasaki now you're in the Kwantung army
you're all members of the 731 squadron
youth corp do you understand heads now
if you get a chance to go to Harbin
whether you're on leave or a day off you
must change into your civilian clothes
when you return you must remember to put
your uniforms back on it by while y'all
if you meet other Japanese or get
stopped you mustn't reveal your
attachment to this squadron is that
clear nah nah Nona see Allah equally not
see da yo
bye-bye well it's almost three years now
since nineteen forty-two I'm glad you're
back with us to her brother's reunion
thank you sir Thank You general
gentlemen although I've been away from
the squadron for the last couple of
years I followed the research that's
been done so I'm up to date now with
reference to the research that mr.
Katona has been doing I believe that
he's focused too much on the theory I
think that what we need most is to
increase the quantity and quality of the
bacteria we have to use them in this war
to speed the victory of the Japanese
Empire so gentlemen let's drink a toast
victory and gentlemen I would like to
propose a toast to dr. Ishi to welcome
him back here to the 731 squadron to
victory hey excuse me sir Lieutenant
General Sir lieutenant owner military
police reporting for duty from the
Kwantung army command office that's
right I'm just lieutenant general I
could have been a full general a long
time ago if it wasn't for those fools of
military headquarters who say army
doctors can't go higher than lieutenant
general they're ridiculous not one of
them recognizes our worth well now
lieutenant gone why don't you go and
report me to the military command I've
just voiced a criticism of the General
Staff hmm go on
hold it do you have no respect for your
seniors
oshino let's forget about this if they
find us we'll be in trouble no I'm not
gonna forget it my brother gave me that
bull when I left your pan I must get it
back
get on your feet is she covered you see
no I don't know sir I don't know whether
sir you don't know where are they I
don't know
Oh
give me that huh kushina don't run oh
that showed a total lack of discipline
nothing like this must ever happen again
the training of the youth corps is
important not only because we're short
of staff it's mainly because what we
require here are people of the highest
integrity and loyalty headquarters only
recognizes the importance of bacterial
weapons in this war they fail to realize
that biological and chemical weapons are
also very important they'll affect the
outcome of this war in the future of
japan i believe they'll play a crucial
role so we have to speed up these
experiments Sarah that incident with
hoshino was really unexpected security
and discipline must be stepped up it's
late I'd better leave you to thank you
sir right let's go good night sir
brother please sit down so zero what's
happening back in Chiba hmm there's a
shortage of everything people have
suffered a lot in the last couple of
years but the families managing I see
well brother I think we can only do our
best under the circumstances now that
how's everything here for instance what
about the men's morale it's all right
the men oh really complain oh yes we
managed to find out about that incident
which got too relieved it was due to an
informer you were right it's Colonel na
kotomi the idiot he even ridiculed the
effectiveness of your water purifier he
did did he damn Nakatomi
lieutenant colonel nekkid told me if you
hear anything present
generally she would like you to
please forgive me sir oh
kawasaki any absent tease unfortunately
so her she'd have had an accident last
night hmm
kawasaki i want you to treat these
youngsters well the youth corps is
important thank you sir machinae was
electrocuted by his own hand and now all
of you are behaving like a bunch of
schoolgirls idiot what kind of soldiers
are you still acting like kids you want
to get another for Chiba then you must
start acting like real men close-up
tanger down prone position crawl come on
move it move it
gah boom-boom it meet up come on oh and
you hurry come on go hurry up all right
go on hurry up hurry up quickly oh come
on you yeah oh yeah come on all right
everyone up come on on your feet I said
everyone up come on me do too
hey you know I just heard there's a
rumor going around that the Fighting's
very heavy on the southern front a whole
army could be wiped out sounds very
serious there's no other way we got to
speed up these experiments more logical
weapons are the only way we win the war
hey what did he say that sounds like
Japan will be finished
hasten the doctor said we should
conserve the marula this one can be
stuffed and mounted it won't be wasted
hey this is real tough but fortunately
the money's quite good and also we can
study is that right and she called you
sent money home no so does that mean
that you spend it all here I don't mom
said we must save it up for the war
effort this is a nice place it's similar
to my home in Chiba kamaraj she must had
this cold this place is just like a
hospital no I don't think so a hospital
to their patients but we only have dead
bodies this place is more like a medical
school no I don't think so medical
schools don't have soldiers everywhere
and they're not heavily guarded like
this I don't care what you think it's
okay by me I well and they pay me a lot
of money the only problem is that fat
sergeant Kawasaki he's too much he's
always looking for trouble look is that
her she knows ball let's get it back
come on
she knows ball wasn't like this hmm how
are you what are you doing here he must
be a mute
hey
are you okay sir what's wrong with ya
he's been here for over a month but he
still hasn't managed to adjust sir he
found us every time he comes and works
on these experiments when he gets like
this we have no alternative but to let
him take a break I think sir it'll take
him a while to get used to it don't
worry about it i'm sure you'll soon get
used to it this job is very important we
rely on the colors to determine the
results of these experiments as you know
we can't just depend on black and white
pictures so take care of him and getting
back to work sir excuse me sir Sir I'm
sorry sir I've been transferred to the
southern front by direct order of the
Kwantung army commander congratulations
the situation in the south is very
serious I think that a patriotic soldier
like yourself should be able to achieve
great things especially as you have such
a close relationship with the general HQ
that's good you should sacrifice
yourself sir I suppose that this was all
your doing sir this maruta has been
injected with bubonic plague three times
but still no symptoms have appeared so
we've decided to conduct a live
dissection on him that's good to collect
accurate data we're dependent on
continuous experimentation so all the
maruta that we use not only do they have
to be alive but they have to be fit than
in good general condition experimenting
on live subjects is a rare chance sir
oh alright so what is that that is a man
sir you tell me what that is he's a
Chinese man huh you tell me what that is
sir here's a very bad Chinese man take
it out now remember that is called I'm a
Rooter it's a log for the fire or for
making coffins its material for
experiments it is called a maroto now
tell me what it is maruja sir I can't
hear what you're saying Naruto tell me
what it is
oh all right what is this
we must do all we can to collect
evidence and then get it out of here the
outside will must know what's going on
in here this is the only thing we can do
listen why go for all that trouble we
have no chance of getting out of here
alive you damned rotted you have no
backbone and you to stand up like a man
don't copy this chicken he's a disgrace
to the Chinese at ease now the lessons
on experiments will start tomorrow to
work hard and learn while is that clear
come on let's go please sir please
please let her take it with her she
thinks that is her child
general please
quickly now hurry up and get changed now
hurry up come on let's go
all right then let's go
let go
this is the culture medium production
room
this is where the bacteria are killed at
high temperature this way please here
they're transferring the bacteria you
must learn all this as soon as possible
here we're doing a cold injuries test
the maruta has been at minus 35 degrees
for 10 hours
it's 15 degrees now
alright
what you see now is a quick freezing
experiment that minus 196 degrees
dinner's chewing your Apple and then I
want you to spit it out just like I have
remember this don't swallow it this way
you can eliminate germs from your oral
Kevin you understand all right then I
want you to go tell your sergeant that
I'd like you to be my guest this sunday
we can all have a drink together thank
you sir uh-oh marita you're invited to
you want to join us sure it's all just a
question of humanitarianism don't you
understand no this concerns the rise and
fall of our great Empire listen nashik
our they're human beings just like us
they have parents too don't you
understand what I'm saying that's all
nonsense they're prisoners how can you
say that Oh Jade gonna come on this is
Sunday let's not discuss business here
come on let's eat okay everybody this
fruit was brought over specially from
Japan please help yourselves Oh madam
you mustn't carry heavy things let me
help you thank you maybe you can tell me
the difference between the child that
mrs. tanemura is going to have an
emeritus child what's that oh you should
not have said that how can you compare
we Japanese people to a marui de we
don't speak the same language I have
nothing more to say to you I'm sorry sir
please excuse me
isshikawa
kawasaki pushed him and he fell down the
stairs he hurt his leg we're gonna do
something to get back at that pig
kawasaki and we want you to do something
to help us as members of the 731 youth
course we should obey our officers just
forget it we have to abide by
regulations here you're just a damn
coward chicken you got no guts
those goddamn murderers what the hell
are they up to now hey specs what do you
think they're gonna be doing to us now
what was that injection this morning
I've had no reaction at all I don't know
what it was why didn't these people get
it
a careful of contamination the last
accident caused sakagami oh no honey
their lives so I'll be careful everyone
inject those people first yes sir let's
go eat sir according to the previous
test results it'll be quite difficult to
produce a strain of bubonic plague that
is more than 60 times as infectious as
the standard type now we're doing the
seventh experiment and here here are the
results of the last few tests mm-hmm sir
I heard that the Germans are performing
similar kinds of tests using the Jews as
subjects and they've achieved good
results so can't we approach them before
the war dr. Ishi collected data on this
project in Europe for two years
according to him the german research and
experiments in this area are far behind
our own compared to them our equipment
and facilities are more sophisticated
what they've achieved so far may not be
of any use to us at all come on now and
don't feel discouraged you keep up the
good work and report to me at once when
the experiments are completed yes sir
sir I heard that lieutenant colonel na
kotomi died in action on the southern
front is that right hmm it's true dr.
Ishi really shouldn't have gone so far
as he did hmm I suggest we keep out of
that it's nothing to do with us you just
concentrate on your own career you know
the medical department is awaiting your
return the future of Medicine in Japan
is in the hands of people like you
so in other words the success of the 731
decides the survival of the Empire so
today we really should Harbor no more
illusions about the Kwantung army the
Kwantung army other than relying on our
bacterial warfare has no other way of
winning the war I've always believed
that chemical and biological weapons are
a far more effective way of waging war
than bombs and guns and right now we
must regroup and mobilize our forces so
gentlemen I must entreat you to work
doubly hard in order that we can win
final victory we have to get ourselves
well prepared for the coming bacterial
war offensive gentlemen please speak up
if you have any questions ah please go
ahead we have managed to successfully
produce a mutated plague bacteria which
is 60 times more lethal than the norm
the amount we have cultivated according
to our calculations sir is Varens enough
to wipe out all of mankind at the same
time we have increased the number of
mutated plague infected rats to three
million we've also produced 300
kilograms of fleas this is equivalent to
about 1 billion fleas if 1 billion of
these plague infected fleas were all
released simultaneously it's not how to
imagine the situation on the war front
will be drastically changed we'd be
assured that the Empire would win the
war our bacterial weapons are crucial
the fate of the Japanese Empire lies in
our hands it's up to us one thing it's
been proved that the metal casing
holding the fleas gets very hot during
the firing and the majority of the flea
since I get killed consequently these
bacterial bombs have failed to produce
the results that we expected it's proved
to be quite a difficult problem weapons
Department
does anyone have any other questions sir
there's being a strong reaction to
Kawasaki abuses of the youth corps it's
getting quite serious there's a lot of
tension and unrest among members of the
Corps transfer Kawasaki immediately out
of the youth corps oh no I want you to
replace him sir excuse me please enjoy
the food huh
huh general seems you so it's not rested
yet out you too yes
hey
all right all those who've been hit or
touched by the fragments put your hands
up
yeah yeah gentlemen this thing is my
latest invention and i've called it the
low-temperature porcelaine bacterial bum
to the Empire buzzer
be careful don't break them
gah
take off your clothes
ah
by 10 hey there Kawasaki hmm I want you
to find me a healthy young fella do you
think you can do that healthy young
fellow what do you need that for we know
that's not much use to you but it's very
important for us you know come on now
you can find us a healthy man kawasaki
if you can help us find a healthy young
guy for this experiment then I'll buy
you a few drinks oh yeah we're all about
your drink how about that don't worry
about it call us up he's good at that
I'm sorry I can't help you with this you
left a fun one oh he means he's only
good at finding young women hey Carlos
aki really help us out on this you can
do it come on give us a hand ok I'll see
what I can do please let my daughter go
I'll do it but I'll do whatever you want
that doesn't matter about me but let my
daughter go please please let my
daughter go she's so young please let
her go she said she didn't do anything
I'll do anything you wanted anything at
all anything but let my daughter go my
daughter please let her go here would
write you can do whatever you want with
you let her go please let her go thank
you I thank you
huh
you've been here a while are you used to
it yes I am sir oh good army life is
like that you know how things are my boy
live are you still seeing that Chinese
mute no sir not often why do you ask oh
I just wondered if you could find it
sir here's the mute that you asked me to
bring the other day thank you well done
now come on hmm I go with Impala k don't
worry come with me come on Eddie bring
him in now sorry hey hey come on come
here come come come now you go in there
understand isshikawa you wait here you
can take him back again only when a
surgery is finished what surgery be
quiet no more questions it's not your
business keep out of it sir come here go
on
hey Segawa where are you going the
surgery's finished you can take him away
yes sir are you all satisfied well then
you have now got the heart and you've
got the liver and you've got the brain
that you needed her all these organs
from a living boy in puberty are
difficult to come by that was very
successful and thanks to color saga my
pleasure so buy you a drink this evening
isshikawa what's wrong now take the card
away sir
is order to ya
give me that
hey draw the curtains okay oh that fat
ice is a bastard is a real animal yeah
hey that mute wasn't a marotta so why do
you kill him I really despise it yeah I
can't stand him either right let's think
of a way to fix him is she I want to
kill him hmm if there's any problem i'll
take the responsibility no we're in this
together yeah
come on hurry up now get ready for
disinfection
hey
what do you think you're doing get back
Oh
a small rat can beat a cat please and
Jerome's can defeat bombers and guns
this is the basic theory behind 731 and
it's also my philosophy so big tree we
must take the strongest and groom them
and the same philosophy should apply to
the 731 squadron youth corps to
understand that sergeant start
I
Stoli wait
listen you must get out of here alive no
matter what happens we must get the
evidence out
stoney quick Let Go you bastard your
head is still in the sand Stoney you'll
never get out your way you only get
killed if he goes out your weight doors
open
dhoni know
fine
ah
you idiot many marui sir are dead this
is a serious matter you know that your
job is to keep them healthy so they can
survive longer but you've neglected your
duty with serious consequences this is
intolerable do you understand that it's
unforgivable all our maruta a precious
experimental material today they mean
more than ever before you had no right
to kill any of them the Russell Japanese
war will soon be upon us but still some
of our tests are not yet conclusive 731
squadron is our last hope we have the
power to turn the war in our favor and
save the Empire all right get up I hope
you won't forget all of you were brought
here by me from Chiba you are the core
of 731 squadron Tamara the and our rural
station is preparing for the final
puzzle in bomb test soon they'll need
Maruta so have you sent them off yet yes
sir they look very early this morning
its back said that what you did was very
stupid you can't get out anyway the
motor is this the quicker we'll get
killed he said we must try to get the
evidence out of here that's all he can
do but we must let the world know about
this hellhole that's the only way we
have of getting back at these bastards
dr. Ishi I'm told we're running out of
time the situation on the battlefront is
very bad looks like the final battles
coming this trip to fen qián is
extremely important so you mustn't worry
about things here thank you
good luck
general kikuchi I rely on you to look
after things sir coeliac or they can go
the target site is ready all right I'm
sorry sir but we haven't go through them
yet oh I see all right keep trying go
sir oh yes go ahead and find a signal do
it now yes sir
we need the Maruta urgently all right I
just want to know from you whether
they're on their way on that excuse me
sir Sir urgent telegram thank you
okis knife nagasaki was bombed the
Russians have declared war man shoe 731
squadron retreat independently we must
get dr. Ishi back here at once yes sir
hello cancel amiruddin airfield come in
airfield hayfield airfield coming
airfield come in give me that airfield
come in come in airfield yeah God sorry
the marooders are trying to escape their
what
good night for them we got let any of
them get away get in the car after quick
you
split up run out run quickly
come on we must give the evidence out of
here let's go
hey
Oh
go that way quick crime
little stone
ah
Oh
got him up to
scallion no no no equinox etoile oh boy
I owner ooh knock on door oh boy
excuse me sir I'm sorry to disturb you
sir Sir an urgent telegram from the high
command the Russians have declared war
nagasaki was bomb now the High Command
has ordered all troops to retreat
independently what do you think sir we
feel you should come back the Russians
have declared war on us all troops to
organize retreat sir what do we do
gentlemen we have received a telegram
saying that the Americans have bombed
Hiroshima and Nagasaki it seems that
both cities have been completely
destroyed and also the Russians have
declared war I'm afraid to say that our
fate is sealed we received orders from
High Command to retreat but I personally
think that the work of 731 squadron
involves highly classified information
so now I'm requesting the following from
you firstly we must exterminate all
remaining maruta every facility in his
compound must be destroyed nothing is to
remain the engineers will be in charge
of this job second all buildings must be
razed to the ground I want nothing left
third collect all data and documents I
want them all destroyed at once nothing
is to remain at all fourth the youth
core retreat stat Anwar fifth all units
commit suicide also families and
dependents will commit suicide as well
in other words everything must be
destroyed no evidence must be left
behind dr. the squadron consists of some
very highly qualified people it seems
such a waste to order them to die really
there's no need for such meaningless
sacrifices I'm fully aware of that
general but we have got to ensure the
secrecy of this facility excuse me
doctor if you commit suicide then we'll
join you dr. Ishi these soldiers and
their families to have followed you all
the way from Japan to Manchuria so it's
your duty to at least try and get them
home that's reasonable as head of the
731 you're responsible for them you
should be concerned for their welfare
you can't just simply order your
subordinates to commit suicide I hope
dr. Ishi you'll see just where your
responsibility is the general is right
we should all return to our homeland and
bring our data with us
it may be possible but still we must be
prepared in case we're captured no
matter what happens the results of our
experiments must not fall into the
enemy's hands in that case we each carry
a bottle of cyanide then if we're
captured all right we die
all right then that's what we'll do go
ahead and arrange it I will personally
direct the retreat and I'll arrange for
the transport i'm very happy i think
you've made the right decision I'm sure
everybody will be grateful to you
what are you doing why are you throwing
out our children's clothes the daughter
is more important please keep this with
you at all times it is a come on dance
order if you're captured you must
swallow it well it was prepared by your
husband it's so late where are you going
at this hour I'm going to get more data
oh come on my dear the war is over we're
going home we don't understand why you
want to take this be quiet what do you
know all right it's true I may not know
much about anything but at least I know
that now we're going home you're a woman
and you know nothing at all I agree oh
well we doesn't know anything and she
certainly doesn't know how to make
poison enough how dare you speak to me
like that don't go don't go yet please
huh stop that what do you think you're
doing this is important Donna you can't
burn it damn it stop right now or I'll
shoot it stop it don't shoot we're going
home now nothing else backed out of here
I just wanted to go home I just Monica
oh stop it you burn anymore and I'll
shoot you down I'm not making idle
threats burn it all sir listen this is
an order you must burn it all nothing
must be left behind sir we can't destroy
this this is our whole reason for being
here it represents years of hard work to
amass this data we've all had to
sacrifice a great deal and sir Japan
will need it one day if you wish to
destroy it then kill me first
thank you very much sir releasing a
pleasant gastonia
I think I'll Mickey come here hey mickey
let's go
it's platinum it's worth money take some
more look at that rider hurry up hey get
up we're gonna blow it
let's go
all right get out of there get out
quick hurry up come on hi let's go go
that way
me
hey where do you think you're going go
back I'm sorry dawn
you
excuse me sir I love the laser clear
according to schedule
ah mrs. tanemura can you hold off just
animal are you all right mrs. tanemura
is going into labor can she write in the
car is that possible hey because cool
enough the needs of things no she can't
dr. well the train is leaving in another
five minutes would you like to address
the man
yes I would
well gentlemen I can tell you this is
not the end the Japanese Empire has not
yet been defeated our base may have been
destroyed but our work will continue I
know we're now going home I trust all of
you will realize the secret nature of
this base has got to be safe guarded at
all times no contact between squadron
members is allowed furthermore under no
circumstances will you reveal the nature
of your work here and also you are
disbarred from taking up government
posts if any one of you contravenes any
of these conditions you will be severely
punished I hope that's clear Marita
who's that who is he he's not one of us
who is he I I don't know who he is hey
that's a maroon
man behind the Sun a chilling movie
which lays bare the most inhumane and
horrifying scandal in the history of
mankind the true story of the use of
live prisoners in grizzly medical
experiments conducted by Japanese
scientists in search of biological
weapons during World War 2 this film is
based on information kept a closely
guarded secret for more than one
generation