way down in deep 13 dr. Forrester and
TVs Frank we're hatching evil scheme
they hired a temp by the name of Mike
regular Joe they like their experiment
needed a good test case so they come to
mama
control and breathes and other science
back he do yourself it's just a show I
should be just relax for Mystery Science
Theater 3000
root cops check police cards check fresh
guest halls in both the men's and ladies
rooms Chuck okay Tom got the sparkling
pink futaba juice and the champagne
glasses check hi everyone welcome to the
satellite of love dr. Forrester and TVs
Frank are some sort of a major
announcement so we're supposed to
celebrate and Tom here is head of the
party committee that's right Chet Mike
you're not gonna wear that it's my
jumper door okay that is a good thing
but I see a question on the pouty lips
neglect citizens of Maratha dr.
Forrester they say clay what's next well
I shatter the known laws of physics hmm
i symbolically rub my sweat socks into
the pimply makers of those with Donna me
how about a 270 miles Heather to an
orbiting satellite oh you'd like that
wouldn't you Frank prepare to receive
the umbilicus hey just what are you
black science cool you see you're in a
geosynchronous orbit negative radical
feminist and right now even if Lisa P it
physically is being deployed from
satellite of love to us here on earth Oh
fly my keys by physical link yeah but
give me rocket number nine
what in the heck Ramsay is that that my
little crawls is fixed world is genius
undefinable or is it as Homer once said
the stop okay crow lock off gotcha
clusion let me quote great man once said
excuse me while I kiss the sky Frank
umbilicus oh no problem but Frank these
are both male connectors and you just a
minute folks that history will be made
go down to hardware Hank and get a 38 c
brass adapter alright yeah hey yeah
while you're waiting for history to be
made please enjoy girls town and history
I don't want you to link to the man
poopies I know gypsy one okay
she's okay wow she's smart a shadowy
figure tonight on Viper Oh Jaguar
dealers just become class what a Jag you
are boy primitive nuclear power huh yeah
looks like John Deere is really wreak
cooled to combine he's dating a kabuki
dancer that's one of my fans you better
get hey was just a fake rubber snake
come back on the shores of gitche gumee
Heidi and the most dangerous game you
know that kind of put me in the mood
come here elma Flintstone
haha boy that Kennedy compound gia was
easier in From Here to Eternity what's
nice will feel I'm harder yeah man look
if you wanna wear my dress just tell me
a weasel ripped my dress relationship is
suffocating me why you ought ah carrot
right now the guys replaying the date in
his mind where did I go wrong Mort
aureus for its shallow roots the common
cliff shrub gives way easily too gentle
pressure mommy he's breakdancer hi well
that finally got Mel's attention
catch up with the von trapps whatever
scuba noodle what's going on suit jacket
e chip hey Freddie where are you going
Scarborough Fair wait a minute uncle
bitch hey chip where are you chip but
down here I got a crick in my neck quit
hiding chip we know your hair missing a
great view chip chip say something will
ya wha Chuba Gouda what howdy hey think
the dates going pretty well well later
on them chips and daddy plummeted to
attend to me go a watch your P's and Q's
oh you will have the girls down just a
camper this dam is dead he's done mr.
James danggg is ever the dead again from
girls town boys club welcomes you to
girls town some of them seem bad I don't
know either shoes okay cuz when they
leave their they are with me
bet they're all in the same cycling
girls where God family and Industry come
together from girl know how do you do
mr. Rankin she plays all the girls
teaching and Billy Chapin
you know there hasn't been a cast like
this since judgment at Nuremberg Oh with
Jim Mitchum you can even skip a day hey
dick Contino boy fuck with Fatty
Arbuckle jr. Larry find junior and Sammy
Davis junior junior you know hrabowski
was the big prop comic of his time no
grabowski and their kids did you do
listen to me girls yeah why does it hurt
when I p and q this guy's just flaunting
his bad driving now well I was fine you
come out with these survived from girls
down girl can dan rostenkowski goes for
a drive congressman be careful
congressman Stanley congressman Cooper
Costa I've laughs ow ow
girls you'll always find you'll come out
with peace of mind from girls town girls
town yeah but how's the food leave your
drops oh I get it haha
fashioned hamburgers what do you know
stay here hey crack a window for her oh
come on it's Mel Torme open up Mel's
greater was smaller back then Bob Marley
what do you want where's silver she's
not home where is she I don't know oh
come on baby don't lie to me wear it Mel
always looked 50 yep tell you if I did
know oh you Salvador Dali ever see this
before switchblade lipstick give me that
Oh dice little bit no dice Mel's built
like a min framed sober pretty jazzy do
give me that that's my sister's you the
the baby chick aren't you all right come
on we're silver she had a date with chip
Gardner tonight didn't she know Nellie
Lee your telephone go home right now
I'll call the police how would you look
at her somebody picks your Apple who is
she with she went to Lake Malabo with
the Dragons stay bright ruin I'll be
there in a sec would what dragon to the
one we stand joys and take your paw for
me hit him he'll cry hello baby chick I
think you're lying what were the Dragons
be doing a lake Malibu they're having a
party doesn't just do laugh merrily I've
got boiling oil well why aren't you
there with they think I'm too young Oh
sexy move yeah and she's not bad
lipstick the colors being dissipated by
the chance all right I'm coming like a
youthful job of the hot get on to you
later little one he's dreamy I stayed
here just like you told me what do I get
what do I guess nobody responded until
you shut up hmm i'll be settling wow
that is one fast funeral of room rooms
coming whoo well it's a tie thomas gang
is tell you how old chap 4 i'd split a
livable and quiet bill clinton dick
continos world ' your dick we brought
you a bra we're looking for silver
Morgan you found it Oh a chip tonight so
what you drove out to the cove with him
guess again flee brain pull the plug
actually why I got tired of you cats
with the fast cars slow heads you give
me a pain in the air that's telling him
chick is your lipstick baby where did
you get chips dead his lipstick was
found lodging in skull dad yeah how did
I die I always told him II drove that
jag real crazy wait a minute how'd it
happen you went over a cliff but not in
his jag silver here must have pushed him
hmm you're in Claire's nail gonna dress
yeah yeah I saw you run away over an
hour ago you're nuts at chicks been here
all the time crazy weenie roast began so
why don't you guys just get your little
cars and blow look out he's gonna scab
huh yeah sure come on baby you're
blowing with us hahaha ho ho ho love
tralala it's Owens crush and I'm a
diabetic it's on
don't worry how did the state troopers
won't tell anybody yes it's teenage on
with Les Brown that is band of renown
due up zubin could you do oh you make
Sun go away you are powerful fight
choreography by Jimmy finlayson thank
you doctor shrunk also bridge on the
river Wow and Down Goes blaze I never do
with the road Scholar come on baby it's
the Battle of the Laura Petra's there
can be only one whoa girl fight when did
this director look into my dreams my
saber the heart of living and it's all
lights out cage baptism
this is why there's no alcohol at Euro
Disney hey Hillary whoo baby well now
she's Stacy Koons nobody called us about
the party ever nick mancuso is Edsel
girls do who are you gonna call you grab
the Eucharist I'll wait here wait if you
hear any shootin just pull around the
corner and get ready duck done it what
she's got a mother superiority complex
hmmmmm well she pulled out her uvula oh
oh look mother Veronica come in come in
it's certainly nice to see you did fine
won't you uh like a scotch as usually
sit down please yeah I'm uh I'm sorry
got a little problem black girls now we
can't expect operate girls town without
occasional difficulties they have
problems at Vassar even with girls who
have parents a normal home life uh
mother this is one of my girls Jimmy
Paolo you heard his name we hear the
radio even in girls down how do you do I
thank you what he wants to intern is
enough cool though that's the club where
he sings at a quarter after two you know
muser I did his hotel at two-thirty he
called the night clerk no more than a
couple of minutes after he went up in
the elevator and asked that the police
be called hmm I didn't want to make
trouble for anybody mother but a thing
like this could ruin me I had to do
something I understand can I see
Sarafina it sold out bring in Sarafina
Garcia please you know mother I'm not
completely square but you're hot coming
into my room and seeing this young girl
in a lace nightie I did it my way I beg
your pardon no go on the church is aware
of the existence of nightgowns mr.
Farlow all the priests wear them Oh
Jimmy Jimmy done please please it's the
50s hey you're lucky my chicks you
never saw you before last night how can
you say that over there it's major
Barbara I love you You Love Me two you
wrote it across the picture what picture
I don't know what she's talking about
honest mother she has this autographed
picture of you hanging in her room wait
this is a picture of Jesus to my darling
Serafina with a million million kisses
Forever Yours Jimmy I guess I do love
her this isn't my handwriting mother
it's Clifford Irving's I know Jimmy
Sarafina you're the devil spawn Jimmy
you don't want to get him into trouble
contributing to the delinquency of a
minor is a very serious offense I don't
get it what's your idea I love you Jimmy
I love you Sarafina let's get you back
to Letterman's house many of our girls
are orphans mr. parla would you like one
sometimes they need love so desperately
they invented a few hold patty why me
mother they hear your voice on the radio
or listen to phonograph records you sing
love songs mr. parlo you'll roast in
hell for that sometimes they think the
songs are meant for them tell the truth
Sarafina Jimmy didn't ask you to come up
to his room did he ok it was Snoop Doggy
Dogg you don't want him to go to jail
now do you make him promise not to sing
she's having my baby and you don't want
to go to reform school yourself at least
I'd get some action sent her to reform
school she's just a kid she didn't
really do anything wrong hey if you
won't press charges against a mr. pollow
I can take her back to girls town isn't
that a kind of reform school no it's a
home for girls who have had problems
with the law who the court fears can be
rehabilitated if they're placed under
the proper in some reform school they
used it girls that have no parents so we
tried to help they're all white and
Catholic by the way you do want to go
back to girls town don't you Serafina
it's meatloaf night tonight don't know I
don't know this was the Golden Age of
stalking now yeah I don't love you Nana
Nana Nana suppose I cannot visit you
once in a while okay mother you know
we'd be very pleased maybe I could do a
song or two for you and the girls oh
they're being punished enough would you
really sure why not you just be a real
good kid and do it mother Veronica
you too okay oh yes yes I will we're
married now all right or the custody of
girls town then you think of the name of
your favorite song when I come out I'll
sing it just for you do you know white
light/white Heat Jimmy alright Sarafina
another successful sexual intervention
courtesy of the Roman Catholic Church
okay I can still stalk you right well
tell the other girls we haven't been
friends all the time we've been friends
for years oh this is really healthy
you're ready Seraphia yes yes I'm gonna
kill Eisenhower to prove my love for him
oh boy you are not coming to say what
you said I mean it would be cruel to
build up her hopes sure amended mother
I'm at the club at nights but how about
a week from Saturday afternoon you're a
fine young man Stephen look at just a
minute mr. gosh just a minute nothing my
son's dead I wonder if your thermos do
she had a date with Chet they found her
lipstick in his she's gonna get this
rumor to judge mr. Garland she has a
dozen witnesses who swear that she was
at Lake Malibu all evening this is
probably a bad wild animals young
gangsters who swear to anything to
protect one of their own I water tried
for murder um excuse me mr. Clive out
here let me get rid of my not on my teen
idol let's get out you two
now guys this movie what would that mel
torme it all reminds me that golly i
just really love the scat hey you want
me to ask after you guys well you could
scat to or sick of it I suppose yeah
okay it's gonna be doo doo ba ba dum
study go but I can do it oh we're sick
of it Bobby no good entertaining allows
get out of Dubai hurry we got commercial
sign we gotta go cut him out of there
she's mean everybody good app do that
because it does okay sit down Silva if
you can this is chip God his father drop
him in charge Hills my son I'm sorry for
you mr. Gardner but you're dialing the
wrong number no smoking please I'm not
instr yet you're not helping yourself
silver I'll never understand what my son
saw in you know do these explain
anything Silva Morgan senior James Polk
high school father in the State
Penitentiary his third conviction on bad
check charge the entire his whereabouts
unknown active including with father's
sister who's on relief picked up three
times twice for after-hours once for
solving a teacher she hit me first
today's bail on probation alright if
she's on probation revoked put her in
jail where I can always find whoa what
do you want to find me for pops I'm not
your type
young woman you I'm gonna convict you
killing my son if I have to hire every
detective in the state of California and
I want to know where you are when they
found the proof no I always thought ship
was a sick kid now I know why hmm you
gonna throw me that jug because you
found my lipstick and chips car can I go
home now we have very little a holder on
look Clyde I want to keep this girl in
jail if I have to go to the governor and
JJ all right mr. garden I'll tell you
what I'll do yes she has no parents if
mother Veronica taken I'll commit her
two girls town you do what it's not a
prison silver it's just the Catholic
Church it's my crime dad we're not
having as much as this jerk well first
start lady wasn't in the Social Register
here's another reason your crime was
knocking down a high school teacher
probation isn't a right it's a privilege
like stretch you don't want to go to
girls no I could send you to reform
school what for knowing this characters
kid oh man shit what you think your
grease that was gonna keep me cooped up
your tune in on the wrong channel yeah
let me show you the brochure for girls
town it's very much meanwhile at
Monticello wait no field hockey wait a
minute hey you feel like a girl I
temperature stately girls town hey you
want to wheel this hot run a drag races
yeah well it does have a six-pack might
just this girl's ville girls town or is
the prison walls there i'll be looking
right now how do you we conduct girls
town on the honor system brother we have
no brothers here only sisters too bad
come on let's go you and me mano a mano
hey those kids are hip I mean they
really send me dude it 30th doing Mel
Torme nothing wrong tink
knock it off I'll mess you up a bad look
your wig I got your signal where is this
cell block we have no cell blocks here
good nuisance it's a nice clean room
with three other girls well isn't that
just dandy o chão supper bell rings at
six o'clock I'll have prime ribs baked
potatoes and fresh asparagus you'll take
hash now come along Gigantor Hayley
Mills hayley mills hayley mills and
hayley mills with hayley mills in really
know hey you of m apples that you and
your work our girls proceed from room to
room in an orderly manner this pad
spruce me this is the new girl mother
Veronica welcome to girls time you'll
have to check those at the desk I hope
you'll be very happy here it's real gan
ma I'm customarily addressed his mother
okay if I call you something else that's
a dirty word to me many of the girls are
bitter when they first get here we break
I'll get over it in due time dude no I'm
get it where do I park the light come
with me and I'll show you to your room
Gigantor yes it's a tribute to British
bombshell Diana Dors blessed be peter
o'toole home is that some guy supposed
to be good for you thank Jude the patron
saint of hopeless cause he was with the
Mariners if there's something you want
that seems impossible perhaps he can
intercede for you I stopped believing in
Santa Claus a long time no Lupita prayer
I don't hate doctor but you do believe
we can hear human voices thousands of
miles away you mean on TV or on the
radio so why couldn't God hear your
voice if you prayed to st. Jude what's
he got to do with it Oh think of him as
a microphone or radar let him send your
voice to the Lord's here Jude's wearing
a wire he's never tuning am i what
yeah keep trying sarafina's yes this is
your new roommate silver Morgan would
you take her in and introduce it to the
other girls Yes Mother thank you hi I
love you are we married now hmm what's
all not jazz for it's holy water what's
holy water it's plain ordinary water
what the hell boiled out of it and with
only half the calories runes right here
she's dressed like many mouths only many
times hotter really isn't so bad we have
volleyball courts sewing room in a
gymnasium oh great oh that's your bed on
the top those are the lockers in the
second drawer from the bottom is empty
so this is the cat oh heavens we called
it the crib yeah studs around here hmm
can you what daddy o's females eggs only
the gardener's and father father know
what do you do for kicks we go to movies
on Saturday night Oh the end when Benny
Hill comes over and chases is around now
and there are you in for what do you
mean what was the rap shoplifting
stealing cars and sorting with shorts
singing an orphan my mother and father
died you don't know what kid what's your
way ahead hmm 00 Romulans lose it all
silvers I new roomie so for this is Vita
and flow flows a big hard throwing
southpaw hi silver you uh got any nails
could be what are you in for wish I knew
I'll take charge of these get it back
smoking's against the rules we got a
good school here and that's where we're
gonna keep it you'll make the beds and
fina will do the washing you raunchy
slob get my safe back why don't you slob
you just described my dream girl maybe
you don't bleed when your cut hath not a
chick eyes I'm gonna have to learn the
hard way the door flow love you and
grapes of wrath you want your cigarettes
could come and get him mmm she's gonna
christen her hmm
I wish I lived off campus yeah walk we
got a new champion and girls dumb how do
you like it kill her rouse can drink
wants to see you all out front what's
going on in here oh we were just
rearranging our lockers money we're
gonna take our showers with four of us
in this little place yes it's an heard
such a load of crap no you have any more
trouble with your locker just come to me
i'll be there anytime you want to return
match you just say so first I want Joe
Frazier well you should have them over
more often your flower vase sorry I love
you cigarette Dina why yes it is that
you never smoked I am pregnant with Paul
Anka's child you're not Paul's the Polka
do you know said two girls guilt she
break somebody's neck her father taught
her all that Judah he's a bouncer in a
saloon there's a law against judo when
you use it to roll a drunk mhm mark
Eden's greatest try are you and girls
down for I mean really well Paul Anka
and I pulled off the Brinks job together
I bought some clothes you bought some
clothes and I killed a guy lost track of
my charge account or something mm-hmm
honor system seems to be working quite
well don't you think I have as much
right to nice clothes as other girls
sure you do careful Greg Morris is in
there how'd you like to be my henchman
what's a henchman you know buddy buddies
pals doorman I think that'd be wonderful
out wonderful crazy cool fantabulous not
for the moon done tabulous we gotta do
Mimi contemplates away over the picket
fence maybe she could tunnel out hmm
stupid recessed filter no taste van
doren meets Van Dam in death warrant
dodges hmm hi how about some
fresh-sliced me I'm really white and
really straight new around here aren't
you fresh out of the box daddy-o hmm
what are you doing in girls ville I all
the goodies that's my chariot you speak
slang got he seeks I'm tapped out are
you beautiful anything thought they were
nails thanks buddy boy I'll remember you
in my prayers my name is dick kildane
I'm silver you know you're the first
chick around here to doesn't give me the
creeps you're the first stutter I've
seen around here period stop what are
you doing like Saturday night going to
bed at ten that's lights out of this pad
oh I mean like oh and getting up again a
quarter after where do i meet you uneasy
street where i am right now what was the
best shower ever right yes the tub is
mine all mine she kinda looks like robes
Pierre whip the robe at all Jesus sees
you child maybe sabotage is the sisters
Seder by planting multiple afikoman
obsessive compulsive cleaning ritual you
know mmm terrible yes excite your
husband by hiding your lingerie
throughout the house really snap the
curve over the corner then oh I had our
darling a shower like I'm five minutes
you know so many rules how come you made
it to this prison camp some dizzy
blondes right my boyfriend and I forgot
the one about turning the other cheek I
mean she's really clobbered her you
don't look so tough to me you do
everything two sisters tell you to do I
give them a fair shake they give me a
fair shake
I'll bet you do Randy brewer all right
so she looks use a lot of soap but don't
use too much it'll dry your skin oh and
be sure to use some nice moisturizer and
have to get back one the back of my hand
I call dibs I've no doubt you could
sister I've seen your work but remember
muley Ryan what an ass but this one
reminds me of her I have a feeling
you'll get further with patients lots of
patience maybe so but when the patience
runs out what then pray earnestly sister
Oh before your poker in the kisser ah
Rock'em Sock'em I'm meanwhile at father
O'Rourke's house modeling the latest in
Terry fashions Mamie Van huh didn't the
rich brothers stay at this house I
chased by a big a person yeah what's the
address of a 9009 club I guess this is
back when deliveryman made 40k a year so
I have a table for you all run your dl
be a subtle evening gown that screams
look at this would you care for the
four-pound steak with a two-pound petite
steak and how many martinis will serve
it downing this evening hey Tom Skerritt
why does that not surprise me lonely and
I'm all alone a Greek night at June's
I've just had the only talent in town
tell you just don't see rhythmic
gum-chewing like that anymore someone
yes someone to love George Winston unbe
r did someone to hold well this is so
graphic place is just packed with bakery
drivers I like to hear somebody clap
somebody say i'll give you my love each
night he's just making this up as he
goes all marine band but somebody
somebody somebody somebody please shoot
him do end but just waiters anchor
burger table 3 pick up red sofa I think
it got a big book do the heavens above
he looks like a young share that I might
find my first baseman's gloves
oh yeah yeah was I thinking I'm all
alone why check that out while it's
smooth you wax that often I've got
everything except a career you could
think of what all i want is someone to
is longer than in a gadda da vida teen
song for bangladesh and so yet another
season comes to an end for the texaco
Metropolitan Opera mr. tinkles cooking
grease
hey this is from RT Johnson's point of
view he's just a lonely boy say leontyne
price this is kind of good yeah the
platters love them
my salad up soon I get my calamari
please and sing with you your warm
tumbler of jagermeister ma'am and your
martini sir I tell you that sourdough is
my idea boys to men to women
hit-girl pretty big Oh what another 30
that he got something against betting
cheeky bird I'm invoking Landers law how
do they support all these bands with
just ten customers
see there's a smooth they're almost not
singing
no oh here comes the big move you know
when they appeared on Sullivan they had
to be shot above the eyebrows with the
camera dooms as good as the statler
brothers yesh of the gavel these hands
over a great come on lunch I heard it
what you talking about Willis
oh yes she Kevin oh yes she put them
over X you have some of the dead girls
town aren't exactly your pals silver
baby
they say you took the mother Veronica
route to keep out of the hotel with
barred windows I'm OD'ing on slang here
so scared so you ever read any Balzac
this dragon every one of them strictly
US mint well Zhu Li for them Zhu Li now
they're just improvising not what do you
mean true or not well truth is a
subjective phenomenon it ah who is it
worth of me
hey now out the back wait they made up
fast hmm you know even if you did show
that jerk off the cliff they couldn't
been anything unusual he did drive him
there in your car I didn't go there in
his car either you heard with the dragon
said you smell like ride the Dragons
lied for you you an eclair that parks on
a lonely road and practically attacks
you he had a right to defend yourself
yes but I didn't say what are you a cop
are you trying to trap me into something
nothing like that I'm a simple bakery
driver ma'am no I remember ships father
said he was gonna convict me if he had a
higher every detective in the state of
California pretty smart I'm done to fall
for a phony deliberately since you're 38
private i did Gardner hire you take it
easy we don't have to get mad at each
other just cuz I have a job to do mm-hmm
why did you level with me maybe I can
generate a clear you something
say Mike girls town is run by an honor
system what's that oh it's just some
kind of Catholic thing you know it's all
about guilt original sin rotting in hell
for all eternity something along those
lines yeah Tom it is not it's about
accountability it's about taking
responsibility for your own actions you
know as a matter of fact I think the
honor system might just be the thing we
need right here on the good old
satellite of love oh the candy stash she
Mike you usually keep it locked up and
only let us have one delicious candy bar
a day yeah well from now on it'll be on
the honor system you still get to have
one a day but you have to police
yourself oh gee Mike can honor really
build character I can torture can't grow
I mean ever since demosthenes went
walking the streets ain't you really
looking for one honorable man by
lamplight an honor has been one of the
most noticed rates that we have like
history is filled with stories of men
and women who are not let hardship stand
in the way of their own deep personal
sense of on it right now George
Washington cutting down the cherry tree
is a parable perhaps but it's still it
reduced rates how honor contributes to
the dignity and the stature of our
nation's leaders you ask if honor can
build character me well I say to you my
friend without honor would we even have
character to bill without honor we are
nothing more than wild animals Oh Mike
what was that you were saying about the
honor system thought I got kind of
distracted good one oh I got a little
out hey we got movie
why that guy can really put the
groceries away no no self-control oh
excuse me crow Burton oh hey oh sorry
about the foot rub off oh jeez help me
lift up in the know kind of folk this is
hell week for nuns top of six weeks of
your life but then you're a nun I'm the
outcast here dirty Skaggs maybe someone
else to tell you how we operated girls
town we have a regular court with
regular pay off it's tough for the rest
of us the court he has the charges and
decides what to do what's that got to do
with me getting the witness here and
find out I think you're a Zoo full of
weird but nobody's gonna drag me yeah
well you're a cookie full of arsenic and
I'd like to take a bite out of you sit
there and sing shock the monkey courts
in session I'm full we've got charges
against silver Morgan what are they this
new chick think she's a smartest thing I
ever walked through the door well if
she's so smart how come she's in girls
town we got a pretty good thing going
here there's no walls around us we're
not caged up like a bunch of monkeys and
the sisters treat us real human so what
is this flea brain do she sasses the
sisters smoking room in last night Oh
goes night clubbing she wiped it out her
chin how long you think they're gonna
let us stay here we'll all be locked up
in some stinking concentration camp with
bars on the doors and grease in the
house just cuz it's one fungus Amongus
thinks she can get away with anything
well this is Schindler's List now do you
deny any of this deny it I didn't come
to this jailhouse to be heard around by
the keepers it came for the food you
chicks are gonna need guts we can take
over this place we got guys yes we do we
had that's how about you go
your bunk Oh crinkle your Chronicle Oh
Finkel your fool call go Pinkel your
pongal guilty verdicts say i ah pose no
yes or no prisoner is found guilty she
is to be hung by her bond girl until
bingo you want to suggest a punishment I
have an idea grabbing a death Saturday
night and somebody's gotta scrub up this
whole dance floor mr. be the florist
scrub hey maybe you missed a spot there
yeah come on lay into it there well
scrub elbow grease please oh I'll help
you so your dream bow can step on a nice
clean floor why are you laughing the
audit need something hmm you promised me
we'd be henchmen so what so that means i
can help you if i want to the two of us
against the world i love you man okay
okay don't make it a big deal look at
this spill what is a creamed corn set
flow in here for beauty parlours hmm
what do you mean beauty parlours she's
always getting permanent ways and
special hairdos and fancy cosmetics
Jessa steal to pay for them uh-huh
beautiful she's been a million bucks in
a beauty parlor I know it but she has to
try top helala vine we not hear the
sentence was that you scrub up this
floor alone hey Gloria honor this creeps
got junior helping your scrub up how
about that uh-uh that's strictly against
the rules come away from there Sarafina
but I want to help why aren't you gravy
pusses get lost before I do understand
grapples oh yeah we were rolling down
that front turn him off in the slaw
girls girls what's the meaning of this
disturbance she had a fair trial mother
the court sentenced her to scrub the
floor for the party friday then we came
in and found Serafina helping her I want
you all to leave immediately you too
Sarafina hmm oh but silver the Word of
God into her
it's okay Paul doesn't want me to work
outside the home anymore ding what
what's that I said I must think yeah I
wanted to help her mother I'm sure you
did Sarafina now run along well we have
to meet with the realtor's anyway Paul's
a pirate you know and you risk Dickies
looking good sister been working out say
your prayers blondie I don't need any
help we all need help we're all bozos on
this phone I don't know what gets into
you young people it's more than
rebellion yoooo conjoined such a great
world force too bad we don't appreciate
it it's not a perfect world silver but
some of us try to make it better don't
bother you remind me of a story my
grandmother used to take a rabbi and a
priest washed all animal in Norway
called the lemming hmm it has a very
peculiar instinct and odor one little
lemming is a perfectly sensible creature
in all this one but you get a bunch of
lemmings together and they they start to
run then they run straight to the edge
of the cliff illegal they killed
themselves oh why are you driving I'm
saying there's no such thing as a bad
girl not really bad just a bad lemming
but sometimes when a group of you get
together you act just like the lemming
reckless and suicidal for no reason are
you trying to say I pushed that creep
off the cliff because I didn't I wasn't
there for all I know he jumped off at
like a lemming maybe didn't need his
gang to jump with maybe in this country
they jump off themselves you're just a
reckless lemming so you want to scrub
scrub but don't you see lemmings at then
they open i'll forget it
pitch catch the game last night I sure
did I lost 50 bucks would you have the
point spread Aikman slips out of the
pocket and he's a cupcake Eggman can go
to blazes that's the time to cry you
know if they were Baptist they could
have got the platters you know you're
lonely he'll only would you find a new
theme please the one and only attached
at the loft ready for today cheese
sandwich Tater Tot and fruit cup and
please congratulate your cross country
team for getting fit the district that
is all let's see Sarafina Anka you know
Paula anchor mmm I like the sound of
that he'd never touch you Terry your
dirt the music that rocked America
gently to sleep hi sir could you please
close that you can be sure i'm going off
my shift could you close your tab please
if you could sign it with a card or bees
or something you guys what sign you
autographed your picture to me remember
oh yeah security security
short women only dance with short women
that's the way it is well I'm taking the
children and going back to your mother's
I heard of a Sadie Hawkins dance it's
kind of a KD Lang dances though Mel
insisted on doing his own stunts the
first of many burgers today from el it's
John Waters velvet hog warm fire rumor
true good afternoon sir what would you
like a cheese sandwich on a root beer
mmm mmm two fumbles good force do
they're having way too much fun cedar
and the Pope stops by for a snap
inspection are you kid I'll dance this
is one of those dances with the girls
went up in one side of the room and the
girls line up on the other small Tom's
please yeah baby change your mind and
riding the drag race with me today huh
no dice loverboy I'm a working woman
well in one more time through the menu
Tony Randall meets Harry all relieved
it's Matt Joyce it was early how early
four o'clock five six I don't know hmm
it didn't finish the cheese sandwich
oh man I should have had the clown
burger almost 3pm and still going strong
how could you dance with another woman
on our honeymoon benedictus qui peut you
know minute dominance googly apt pupil
Pam she's trying to steal my Jimmy we're
going steady Jimmy don't say you don't
love me anymore I never told her I loved
her mother I know it could be surfing
you've got to stop imagining me sleep
all like us beefy security nun skeptic
veena sister go after Jimmy I'm sorry
our party for you had to end this way
excuse me it's all right mother i'm only
bleeding was a partisan what time to
chip come after seven o'clock eight it
was after dinner well what a chip say
when you told me she was gone you said
don't push me off a cliff I don't
remember lying again I don't recall less
of a straight Kidder you know what's
gonna happen you'll wind up in jail
yourself what the chips say will you
give me a dime what for I'm gonna call
someone who cares supper Thomas doesn't
know where I am stop giving me that
princess look when did she turn into
poly holiday hey what's going on here
what's the scam it's Sarafina she's
taking sleeping pills better not be my
sleeping pills oh wow look how cheap
frankfurters were but Larry Hagman what
what do you what
yoooo you want to milk a cow with me Oh
milk
Sarafina wake up we have to keep her
awake silver until the doctor gets
better on our feet and get sharing here
you shouldn't sell Class C narcotics in
here huh mm-hmm to BHS no that's rust
that's what I'm looking for chestnuts
yeah judy judy judy can't believe how
many girls towns are there l girls down
girl sound furniture you crazy little
goon come on stay on your feet
knucklehead up bean brain known your dog
calm your dog big bro please give me
whoa girl Dale mall girls vil gerne just
reach out and touch someone baby dragon
your axle I don't work work Sarafina
whoa she blew out a knee out for the
season over walking on Earl's town hey
ah my necks not getting any skinnier hey
and what about check for 56 did that
clear he's it's a tugboat crazy crazy
let the face no waterworks come on I be
careful we now baptize you a swirly
girls problem please hold oh yeah I say
is you taking an awfully long time you
wake up baby up wake up run atv none
around opened her eyes Sarafina watch
his uppercut you gotta cut me Mick
cookie you're wanted on the telephone
sister Grace is it's urgent take over
but I don't know any slam Eleanor we
must keep her walking come on Sarafina
Sarafina open your eyes all of our
thoughts are currently busy the last
call will be answered first and those
who call first shall do let's go if
you're using a girl's got product please
hold the line someone will call Erica
back it up boo boo David a father
just follow the trail of scat dump dump
data okay ready hell I know who you are
I saw what you didn't I know what you're
wearing oh hello oh you have to use the
st. Jude stature oh god child we're
grateful to you for keeping her awake
but she's dead I had this phone call
there was nobody on the other end sister
gray said it was a girls voice it could
have been my sister liar you're really
not as hard as you pretend to be are you
that's what you see okay if I use the
Alexander Graham the what the telephone
I want to call my sister certainly well
you do stop with the slang and it's
better than scatting operator
information give me Jesus on the line
what's that he plays well he's
everywhere so what's the matter sure I
guess mary lee there well then is Geddy
Lee there she even ordered own she's
ugly it's the Jay Leno game with Malcolm
for
go greased lightning you're burning up
the quarter mile
ah the banks of the beautiful LA River
huh Cena greetings captain ready for the
big drag race sure anytime the Jags are
ready dick Contino looks like dances
melt our main is jazz Nazi swinging
action yeah koala 90 to meet ask you
about the dirac to maybe sir Nazis yeah
I can come with you for this i was just
getting away from that top look it takes
24 this chicken race baby you can't make
me if I don't want it maybe you prefer
that I Drive over to the jail till the
cops when I don't know why me what did I
do well for one thing you shouldn't have
won that scarf today it's not a pussy
won your war the naija push chip over
the cliff no I think Lou salty you said
you saw my sister I saw her scarf found
her lipstick but middle I saw your face
out of that scarf today I knew that the
Dragons weren't a lion silver was at
their beer bust and little sister
borrowed her scarf scarf or lipstick and
her boyfriend you said you were sure
could you just keep doing what I say
baby face and I took them a Smasher cool
Anika hmm Joe Jackson hey you ready to
go man and it son freak cantinho looks
like he's ready for harness trail rules
Joey's Boing a girl in each car rolling
started to get the flag hands off the
wheel before you cross the starting line
let this black then first one across
under the florence avenue bridge wins
dick Contino if our friend or chicken Oh
get her well if either member of the
team touches the steering wheel before
the car crosses out of the bridge that's
bad thank our losses yeah
I'm driving with their areas or
something here then her I'm him I rides
here that we came out that we surrender
it's funny
not now honey battle of the Las Vegas
crooners oh now what they're not brought
you with
well it's a nice day for it whoa Union
it's just good to be out ironically they
have their seat belts on and Nell is the
driver side airbag kind of a dirty Larry
and crazy Murray here
kiss my pinky ring Torme care lot women
drivers
can we just stop and ask for directions
only dummy brunch Beth I whipped your
but can t know I can contain Oh can't
eat oh oh oh you're all dead and stop
he's even when he's dead he still gets
fresh
oh you guys forfeit my exchange slang
here so who's gonna make Danny Oh
this'll want to talk to the cops come on
it's either Jerry Van Dyke or a trained
chimp haha it must do Christina's world
yeah bus that jay walker chimera lassie
but I'm princess tell it to the judge
now what we're prepared to offer you
singing silver sedan or slide down yeah
I'm afraid your sisters in trouble what
kind of trouble girl trouble yesterday
afternoon she was in some wild
automobile race one of the drivers was
injured you've gotta let me out of here
there's nobody to take care of her but
an Scrooge and she's cracked would you
like me to go to the authorities and see
if I can bring it to girls tongue Wow
aggressive retreating listen if you
don't let me go out break out anyhow if
you appear in juvenile hall silver
you'll be arrested it wouldn't do any of
us any good mother mr. pollow is here
bring my leather heaven that's a good
well then I'm very sorry to barge in on
you like this but they told me Serafina
trying to kill herself after I left
yesterday congratulations i feel very
bad about it is there anything i can do
yeah quit showing up very nice if you
could speak with her mr. Pardo she's
really not a bad girl it's just that she
needs to be loved I can do that you tell
me what the same I'll do the best I can
thank you oh that's probably God I have
to take this hello hello sister see this
father Dolan say it's David darling the
doctors at the infirmary now I'll see if
Sarafina can have visitors perhaps your
visit will push her over the edge wait
for me here silver there goes one hell
of a nun they don't come any Leonard you
know I know a lovely way to say how much
you love me oh did you enjoy the party
yesterday yeah except for that
interminable song Kingu becomes the
dungeons ville to make with a song so
Poli Lola's hmm what do you want me to
do kiss your foot that's pretty tough
talk isn't it well yes no you got a nice
face why do you want to spoil it by
hating people it's fun what are you here
for to throw that porn and chick
breadcrumbs what is a cat like you with
all that gold know about a kid without a
buck in the world no old lady no old man
who are you too big shot over her a kid
that didn't have a fuck in the world hmm
no lady no old man
what are you handed me an act you know I
don't have an act you should see the
neighborhood I was raised in you know
when I was 14 a couple of us broken or
pool halls stole 40 bucks let me TP the
players are you doing this place paid
back the 40 bucks I guess that's one way
looking at it you see I've got a lot of
the street you know I'd you like to read
me back my kids hitches in trouble to
juvenile hall how'd you like to go down
there and get her a lawyer maybe Alan
Dershowitz mary lee mary lee morgan she
doesn't 16 yet she's just a baby I'll
see what I can do you mean it yeah I'll
go there this afternoon you doing
whoever keeps the books he'll share mark
that 40 bucks paid in full the big
comptroller in the sky will forgive you
better get out get out honey I'm home
yeah the baby's just fine honey teasing
you you're mental certina no I'm so glad
to finally have Paul Anka out of my mind
and I'll never happened you look after
cheap have you bought it for me remember
but I want to talk to you I'm never ever
going to love you there's no way you
could ever attract a man they're better
when I was a little kid I was always
alone I'm just a lonely ball I had one
secret wish baby and that wasn't I have
a younger sister make her try to commit
suicide ever come true I'd like one just
like you said not so spooky with pretty
black hair and big brown eyes and a gut
full of pills
keep little smile she's dead oh you know
Sarafina if I was your big brother and
you were my little sister it's nickerson
agony we couldn't be sweethearts but you
know a brother and sister make off with
good friends we are knee-deep in a
Freudian quagmire here yes Jimmy looks
there for you I'll make a deal with you
since day one hundred yards away from
you behave yourself and do everything
mother Veronica tells you to and i'll
send you a record Blair for your room
with no further obligation on your part
I'll do better than that I'll have the
refugees send you some new LPS and some
swinging platters everyone oh great
she's getting Paul Anka the home game
that cools Frankie's look sis don't get
to concentrate of anyone seen understand
cuz in cuckoo Ville there's no hit
parade understand yes I'm mental not
stupid it's to shake up come on shake
okay I'm your husband now shake shake
by the way the wedding pictures are in
you close up he's really a putz next
she bought it come on let's scram yeah I
do a lot of good stuff basically I'm st.
Paul of Anka I thought you said you were
going to help first step bottle rockets
please God just one more hit record
please ant ant ant ant ant ant ant she's
good
if you sing I'll become a personal
representative of Satan so help me what
are you doing why are you looking at me
but what should i do i don't i'm so
nervous i owe everybody
you coo coo maria Libous special lyrics
by Sammy Cahn
wow I'm epiphany in like crazy here I
gotta sit down oh I'm a bad guy cancer
this is driving all hope from her soul
oh I remember why I left the church is
the speaking of leaving what's a good
time pad mini disc
Mike how come women don't look like
Mamie Van Doren anymore they do it's
just the styles of change so you don't
hear about huh so women who look the
most like the news style are considered
the clothes it's stupid but yeah so say
it's 1953 and I happen to look like
Twiggy I'd have to keep my job at the
cleaners until I became stylish in this
60 yeah I guess so you know it's all up
to the media they go and change styles
without consulting us they think it's
funny so in the future it might be
stylish for women to have wings oh hey
Wow hey start sketching my aggregate
folk ok let's women in the future women
in the future a basic woman ok uh huge
ferocious wings good a fire rainn yeah
no I think of the future women will
adorn themselves with Mexican tiles
they're stylish yet easy to maintain
that's too far in the future sure okay
Nelson add-on huge island yeah Nick
enough to roll up in and hide out oh
yeah and power takeoff I she's got have
power takeoff and an air-conditioned cab
a lotion dispenser complete swing sets
Cadillacs passing to the north star
system at every dealer commercial sign
in 15 seconds oh man we gotta go what do
you got there pal well you guys I have a
feeling that in the future women all
pretty much look like me
yeah you make a good point my friend now
throw some wings on are you sly boots
and power takeoff I can't tell you how
much I believe in that power taker and
in response to media pressure women will
dress like pencils right back in time oh
I love them Paul Anka mass are usually
single uses pomade from Lourdes I'll do
the head tilt second verse same as the
first
all right that was Ave Maria going out
to our lady of perpetual grooving
meanwhile at the hotel New Hampshire mmm
poison ivy follow the fin hmm what
happened I went straight to juvenile
hall from here and Clyde told me a
lawyer been in the bail her out you know
I thought everything was just fine but
my cancer this morning to say tried to
reach her sister at home she didn't go
look there's nothing to worry about he's
checking with the Laura now to sue the
bail money came from I've gotta get out
of here I've gotta find him look silver
easy Pat I think gotta play cool can't
expect Clyde to tell you anything
especially if you left this place
without permission Paul Anka p promise
to call me as soon as he finds her when
he does I'll let you know right away
that's a promise yeah he didn't count on
me in fact i'm bringing sarafina's
record player over tonight I'll give you
a report there I'll bury Maria huh come
on I'll be
Tom Stewart killed me happy on Pepe own
hey you didn't finish your beats
princess no dice you can't keep me here
rather go to jails real huh look you
know I didn't mean to hurt you he was
trying to you know what he was trying to
do to me nah look the guys are out
raising a couple hundred bucks not when
they get it will take it out south get
you a job with the headhunter hostess or
sup go on get up those stairs go on dad
a dumb don't doubt it i don't dog
operator I've dial orchard for 2 12 to
10 times I can't get anyone to answer oh
you want me to go to the house and
answer the phone Nazi scat non scared
hmm so where's the Go button oh you
there's clown burger wrappers everywhere
french fries on the floor Mel is not
very good at holding people hostage is
it you know hey remember the double
clutch or your grandeur cares it's not
synchromesh and then as oil bath
carburetors wells your junior clean amok
crap stupid dirt Smith Smith moody bland
and gray may help you here's the file on
Thelma George's my office Monsignor is
waiting mother you may use my office as
long as you like silver hey I'm already
here where have you been ho silver it's
ok to tell mom all about I didn't want
to ride with him in that drag race but
he made me who made you God made me Fred
it's one of the jag game but how could
he make you go line a line he knew about
me and chip chip Douglas you and chip
tried to tell you before but I was
scared sit down and shut up maybe it's
time you level with me you know how
we're both hot
we remember the night just to chip up he
died well he was real sore when he
didn't find you and then he died so then
he asked me to go in your place I'm
gonna killed him and he died what's kept
saying I was too young to go anyplace of
my way up and they killed him and he got
all dead great I was fun at first when
he only kissed me he wasn't dad them
Jenny died started you killed by me at
your fresh and I ran away really chip
caught me and tried to throw me down and
lick her out right before we got that no
you don't walk slipped out from under
his feet if he became killed he fell he
died so that's how they find my lipstick
in his car toward his friend come in
he's not dead it's not happen good
thought it was you at first you barely
saw me again my fuel did all the time
you but letting me sit here in jails
Tommy's over i gotta tell you the first
on my team we're gonna doesn't hurt
thank you yeah it's all over the ship
just can't believe you went out with
chip are you laughing at something in
gilbert never mind another damn it's
over the cliff funny huh well forget it
I'm scared Fred's trying to send me to
Tijuana and trade me for a chicken t1
maybe I could push herb alpert over her
quest fine he's afraid his dad will take
the car away from him if he finds out
about the drag race you mean that rat
with chip a 15 year old kid to Mexico to
save his hot rod man who's gonna give me
two hundred dollars big to you they're
onto our sister let's be cheeks
I never haven't you want to talk to nip
he says where'd you don't come here you
go out the same way you came in you dig
me here the door I'll meet you the
highway okay hey wait are those my
dungarees where's your rod hmm yeah my
rod probably still around here someplace
agent double o heaven where do you think
you go out no you're not you're staying
right here bear yourself back to the pad
Tiger cheated my way day one of these
anywhere silver the council had a
meeting who cares about you and your
phony console we care we decided
nobody's going to bus stop listen I've
got my sister she's in trouble your
sister my mother my sister my mother my
sister no but I beautiful did it drive
away I see a guy with a dewlap and a
triumph that's all hmm hmm I don't see a
thing but that was this thing and now it
are you saying there was no thing was it
that was a there's no thing suppose
she's telling the truth hey thanks for
coming down tonight has supporting live
liturgy say what can I tell you about
myself well I'm a saint I'd like a
bigger medallion I'm kidding of course
it
listen say two of you you're supposed to
help people who haven't got a chance
that's me I haven't got a chance in
God's world never once did you ask me to
your house for coffee no silver Morgan
praying oh no one more of her phony
baloneys Mortimer Snerd chance any
chance at all I believe her I'll tell my
fellow Mounties what statue doesn't work
anymore are you were unleveled oh you
know I you she's 15 years old and
they're shipping her to Tijuana
kidnapped your sister they've been
keeping your prisoner the Jag speechpad
with a kid fell off the cliff they're
afraid she'll testify against them huh
Santa Claus silver Jimmy's outside he
just drove up he's back from fighting
Nazis on the moon we got transportation
maybe we can still catch them I haven't
seen him praying with my own eyes let's
give her a chance girls yeah you and
flow go with silver I'll wait here to
mother Veronica gets back good luck
girls suddenly there an elite
crime-fighting unit and then go and find
Jimmy and tell him that they haven't
stolen his car just borrowed it Chuck so
anyway I wasn't very popular so as a
freshman I had to work extra hard to get
on the wrestling cheerleading squad
here we are they're here Park see you
block the road angels I need you to go
undercover his high school girl st. Jude
is coming and he's packing heat Scottish
the high cuz it's Lincoln you bring a
bag we can't know this house is on the
National Register of Historic hideouts a
Nancy Drew mystery damn cape cods hmm
nobody expects the Spanish Inquisition I
came for my sister you came to the wrong
place not the winner when you pushed her
in that t-bird you're out of your little
scope blow the only way I blow is to
blow the whistle on you Wow yeah sure
baby you just do that little thing call
the cops go on galand right back in the
clink maybe so but I'm not leaving here
without Mary Lee not without my daughter
she's gone you lousy bug head if you
sent that little kid on Mexico wait a
minute wait a minute you say you saw us
push her on a t-bird right how do you
see any t-birds out there now you know
my sister isn't 16 yet you know what
they do to you for contributing to the
delinquency of a minor your ambition
know what they do to you for murder
revoke you do laughs here please hurry
mother Veronica will be on time Jimmy
you must have faith we'll get you to the
köppen time for your gig here Jimmy
this will strengthen your faith you got
a weird theology mother right
right on woman oh wow we're Team let me
just sneak by you here thanks Sam
Peckinpah six degrees of separation care
you just won yourself a one-way ticket
sauce let me guess mexico ville wait
creep early yeah yes go I'm seating find
some rope you just wait till there's
nuns and croquet mallets well I'll just
back through the door here nothing to
see anyway 20 bingo oh it what happen in
there oh I found the dark dumb jerk
sankyu skulls chips old man's got a
private eye on this case now if i can
find out that Mary they pushed chip over
the clip the detective can't to unless
we get her out of the country look you
know I didn't mean to hurt him he was
trying to attack me you saw I run after
me nobody else did baby chick you just
remember me check if I say he was
attacking you he was attacking if I say
you pushed him you pushed him I'm Mel
can we go talk about this by the cliff
we ought to be friends you know what I
mean real good friends and if I say you
kidnapped mary lee i can make more
trouble for you than you can for us so
gain weight well that's the way you want
it uh-huh uh-huh oh my mmm well I'm glad
you decided to be friends you know
you're not a bad look a little Damon to
turn those teeth the rock in Betty Lou's
pantyhose can always had eyes for ya
Rock you know there are awkward moments
like this at every house parties just
like that now say that almost looks fun
oh these guys are confusing romance with
football that's the problem
we do smile all right all right let's
start again you get your potato and
pantyhose and that you're going to get
her show me lover boy oh that move with
pure Emma Peel Oh evening and Jake
LaMotta house now there's going to be
some real ass kicking no I'm gonna split
your head open oh now it's greco roman
catholic wrestler who the age-old
struggle between hop and jazz you want
to finish him off sister what's with
this guy he's the only one that knows
mary lee didn't push chip over the cliff
then he can solve a rubiks cure nobody's
gonna believe this babe look Holly
you're gonna be a witness so you're
gonna be tried for kidnapping you know
what they could do to you for kidnapping
which way would you rather have it which
way okay please that's why by velvet fog
emanates from so run out of the cabin
Jim Jim was chasing her and she must
have been defending yourself huh yeah
well he's not really high season was
buddy gets the job done you heard him
whether Monica we already hmm and if you
don't know what to do with that baseball
bat I could give you an idea Oh sister
you're gonna rot in hell but I love you
I was incredible hmm hmm is this the
place i have an appointment for a facial
in a pedicure where's the warden there
isn't any good by Silva goodbye sister
Grace Oh who's in charge mother Veronica
is in charge other than 30
word to me you'll learn I've already
learned too much cat that's why I'm here
love lifts us up where we belong contd
flaws oh we've come to say goodbye
silver Oh Serafina got the lead in the
Thanksgiving pageant look at the baby
chick now I'm happy now silver really
happy found somebody who loves you huh
I'm happy now really I'm glad it'll be a
wonderful thing for it she'll have two
years in the novitiate to make sure
goodbye baby sober you're still my hinge
I'm happy I'm really happy to be and
you've become my henchman too soon ha
goodbye it's a mother actually the names
Phyllis good lucks sisters silver
wouldn't have sounded that regnum change
of habit listen to me girls yes watch
your P's and Q's uh-huh oh you're gonna
have a girl so long suckers good to have
you back finish you got it
is Brandon
poukisa vine from girls done what she
sees in men i'll never know many girls
need love Oh many girls he can't they do
and if they're not attend the to
discover well let's go savage a new girl
I owe a lot of hands hey have you be
walking now is fine I got idea what the
time damn those girls down girls town
once again I just like to say how
monumental this history-making event
will be the link the linking of the
whole umbilicus doctor and the oh I
brought you to give me that Frank a
little crush and in conclusion I give
the world the first Earth tethered
satellite ha dr. shall I send up the
envelope odd in the envelope or be that
frank i impart this vessel unto the
heavens and I think I hear something
coming inside supposed to smell like
banana cream tell Frank I dr. Clayton
Forrester bid you welcome what news of
you from the far reaches of space doh
push the button Frank hmm Frank I'll
give you three seconds to stop licking
my face counts low
you'll tell that boy to go home right
now I'll call the police