so
you
I have a little balloon a happy to and
dreams enough to last me all through the
afternoon I have the New York Times and
14 knives and explanations all the most
profound
Nursery Rhyme
we fall forever
run dry before the
I said
let us be gone
we can try
uh
so don't just throw your ever bath it's
not too late to
before the Sun
and as all
ha
oh the hourglass
you
so don't just throw your
it's not too late to find out before the
side
and as all run
all of the hourglass
do they died it now it's all around us
now
I want to go beside me now
this still is time but all my points to
let me
Oh
before the
the last sagar
let us be gone
if you are
we can
I
so don't just lawyer
love about you
let's find out before the sound
and as all wrong
oh the hourglass
hi Carl hi Jeremy any minute i'll get
you racing the phone for you hey are you
been ok well handicapper what do you
like today I don't know oh this is horse
in a big race yeah yeah my love has been
spared no no here you guys it's for
summer melody stepping way down in class
not a romp own thank you I'm going to
put something off 1 no thanks you know I
don't bet
forget it
I've seen take character some crazy kid
comes in every day always buys amazing
for me always pick someone never bet
I
Jeremy let me ask you something I'm a
little puzzled how far do you want to
get with this I mean how good do you
really want to get I want to be able to
play pretty good you know you'll never
be concert quality you do know that
don't you
why not your energies are two divided
great musicians saved all their energies
for their work
hmm I were carted my music you know that
look I'm not finding fault with you I
just think you're at a point in your
studies where you ought to know where I
think you now stand look there's nothing
wrong with being a good musician you
don't have to be great not everybody can
be great
I'd like to be
well look perhaps I was a little harsh
with you just now but music is harsh far
these harsh standards are high and my
standards for you and all my students
are high so if I have to sacrifice a
little warm from the way I talk to you
he wasn't think that that's a lack of
affection sure I understand do you
I think so oh I hope so
sometimes I think it's a lot easier to
be a friend than a teacher
God
each other
yeah you know Sonny can't go to his left
you got a plane way over to his right
you know so he can't pull my fade away
jump shot shitty no score that way he's
just having a good day that song should
have beat those guys hey could now let
me see you that came to go for a soda
Jeremy Jeremy oh hi there what are you
doing son homework how could you
possibly work with that thing blaring in
your ears it's easy what do you mean
easy you can't do two things at the same
time and do them both well dad music
helps me to concentrate ridiculous
what do you think would happen if
everyone in this world tried to do two
things at the same time probably get a
lot more things done that's not funny
Jeremy sudden be serious we've been
through this so many times but everybody
works everybody has a job my job is
advertising your job is school look at
me when I'm talking to you Jeremy I got
where I am on my job by working hard by
concentrating and you have to do the
same you have to concentrate too but Dad
I get straight a's except for one be
that's beside the point
what are you eating history well music
just don't mix
how about music in English how about
English in English ok then I'll explain
it to you again the orange blossom in
the Caribbean orange both sell for
fifteen cents a tile including
installation the other cell for ten
cents a style by the installation is
extra on the other hand Marty said this
room cries for avocado who's Marty his
roots friend the decorator I didn't know
where we're using a decorator since when
are we paying for a decorator then I
can't get these ties without a decorator
now pick the one you like best and then
i'll tell you the one I like why don't
you pick the Orangemen don't be a
smartass
but dad won't the same to me well I
prefer the Caribbean orange it's happier
happy excuse me happier than what oh
there's a pie in the ice box will open
the ice box and you'll find out and hey
watch out for my plants it's this one
been boys right damn things all look
alike well to you I suppose they do
you
hey Jeremy up what's my number
Thanks I always get it mixed up with my
gym locker yeah
right thing down it's 3012
bar in class morning uh I could have
your attention up a few minutes the
concert has definitely been scheduled to
take place in two weeks uh-huh two weeks
not much time will be all right now
Diane and Shari are scheduled to begin
the program so if we could have
something from them to begin class with
good you've been twerk it was good a
second first half the second half we're
gonna have to work on a little we've got
plenty of time to take care of that very
good thank you all right now let's have
Jeremy why are we ready Jeremy take
that's very nice german engineer that
class now that cello piece is usually
played as part of a quartet with the
slow passage is count appointed by
staccato sixteenth notes in the violas
here let me show you on the blackboard
okay there's no chalk Jeremy would you
please get me some chalk sure thank you
okay now what we'll do instead while
we're waiting for the chalk is carry on
with our ensemble work okay what page
would that be are an excuse me in the
continos uh let's all move to any drop
page seven and on your page that's what
you
Oh
oh gee I'm sorry you really scared me
I'm sorry what are you doing
I don't know uh oh I was walking by this
door and I saw you dancing uh hey that
thing you were doing that was a plie
right what makes you think that wasn't
plie I don't know it's the only dance
would I know oh it wasn't Oh what do you
want um um is there any chalk in here
you have some over there oh yeah you
have to excuse me I gotta get this thing
together I'm being tested in a few
minutes oh yeah she'll go ahead
it's nice meeting you Rafi she's
beautiful oh this is new girls school
dance if I can't believe me I was gone
past this room to get a piece of chalk
when I was this conscious dancing oh wow
she's a real so what's your name eating
in her name
let's reverse we ask alani escamilla
islands Ibelin you swap up to suck on
six food I have to get it out with you
listen to the poem hmm she was a phantom
of delight when one we she was a phantom
of delight when first she gleamed upon
my sight a lovely apparition sent to be
a moment's on verizon star as a twilight
fair like Twilight's too her dusky hair
but all things else about her drawn from
a time very cheerful dawn
an image gate to heart to startle that's
it for today tomorrow I'm conceiving a
haiku poem obedience which may or may
not pertain to some of you come on let's
go
was a nice surprise you picking me up
from school today hmm Billy was Justin
selfish of me I didn't have a very good
day Bianca bill is doing his best to
help but I'm not making any headway here
New York's a tough town are you sorry we
left Detroit dead no I don't think so
especially after the raw deal i got
there things are gonna get better I hope
so they probably know just saying you
after a tough day makes me feel a lot
better that's for sure
how was your day okay I got tested for
dance mmm I got a good teacher how are
you making I friends yeah anybody in
particular that you like
hmm it's hard making friends something
just have to work out like everything
else in like you know
and
ridiculous man good father days why
don't you just go up there Nance crown I
can't do that you mean it can't do that
I don't know just not ready hey look
this okay I just like being there you
like being here then why we think I
cared she sitting way up there I don't
get it she'll never go out with me how
do you know if you don't ask friends
probably laugh at her if she went out
with a sophomore tell you got left back
no I get and you think I'm stupid hey
luck thanks previous lunch I'll talk to
him
I can't you don't walk there I'm going
up here I mean it well you better not if
you don't go up there by the time I
count to 10 I'm going up there I'll
speak to please Robbie ten nine cut it
out seven six five four three I'm on
there too we going 18
remember me roughly and soon whoa that's
my best friend leaves name is Jeremy
Jones shit my thigh and what did you put
any 45 figure easy she wants you to call
get out of here I read it I don't know
why but she wants you to call her really
yeah wow she know I'm a sophomore you
know she doesn't know your self oh great
I told me you were seeing you you told
her I was a senior fellow leak a vision
I just thought it said you were the best
musician in school and I heard that she
was the best answer how do you know
she's the best dancer hey Muffy you
don't know nothing I don't know nothing
I was the one who went in there to rap
to her not you you see what you needed
all along was me oh wow there's only one
thing well she's wearing this shirt with
this guy's neighbor at nine all right
hey Scott this guy's name written on
right over the pocket you know like
those shirts you see in a gas station
Lily what does it say well I don't know
I didn't want her to think I was staring
into tits for anything but guys
up
I
what do you think hmm that's very nice I
don't know why you're so nervous about
playing it at your school recital the
problem is any interpretation not in the
technique at fingering you showed me
before they really helped me a lot yes I
know but my value is your teacher is not
just to make you a good technician the
emotion is equally important more
important in fact that I know I some of
the things you doing in here what do you
think about when you play this piece
what do you mean I mean what kind of
thoughts go through your mind and a
plane
mmm it's a sad piece it's kind of lonely
sadness is just part of it he wrote this
piece before he was 20 he wrote it for a
beautiful peasant girl he had seen just
once in passing just once so the music
expresses love and parting
simultaneously music expresses life play
it that way
ah
I'm sorry I don't know what it is it's
just that sometimes my hand gets sweaty
I can't keep my fingers on the strings
that's just nervousness look the only
way I know to keep from getting nervous
is to stare the audience down before you
start to play before you even pick up
your bow look out at the audience don't
play a note until there's not a sound in
that room not a sound you'd be surprised
how fast the nervousness will go away
when you're in command hmm i'll try to
know if it's gonna work though
Oh
you
well done
very well done John I'll see you next
week
thank you very much
Oh
hi Chelsea to me Oh
anything
but it was encouraged on encouraging
things I loved your plane gee thanks I'm
since evolved yeah I know
really good thanks
want to call of it I don't know what to
say well how about a loafer story yeah I
know he should say hello the problem is
what comes after hello I mean girls like
Susan her probably used to talking to
guys on the phone if she probably
expects me to be interesting no I mean
it's easy man really easy we'll give me
something to say you don't know what to
say
okay ask what you do today what'd you do
today yeah I think that's pretty good
what else I don't know ask if she thinks
he should pay to tell or a different
color come on my obesity what do you say
to girls when you talk to them on the
phone well I don't usually say much I
usually listen for instance my girl Lori
hast gluttonous him yeah honest to god
we used to stand over ours man was I had
to say was mm-hmm really no kidding man
she's a Babylon 4 hours know what I
gotta think I should save him hey what
if I made a list yeah make a list oh
yeah write down everything have to say
when you finish with the list hang up hi
Susan
listen and that you didn't think I had
calls our bears huh God sits up to
well Susan this is jeremy jones
no um hose Susan this is jeremy jones
I'm sorry call so early but like I'm on
my way out it's for you hello oh hello
Susan yeah um this is jeremy jones Oh
Jeremy how are you okay okay i guess i
call a little too early huh wow that's
okay oh how are you Oh what did you do
it um but I i woke up timed some orange
juice Jeff Jeremy it's only it's only
nine o'clock uh listen I know this is a
little short notice uh-hum uh but um
would you like to go out tonight okay if
you don't want to go out tonight that's
all right no no no it's okay tonight's
fine oh oh great well the movie goes on
at six and eight oh I didn't know we
were going to the movies oh good net all
right sure what movie my little
chickadee with WC Fields is that okay
yeah yeah sure
if we go to the six o'clock show will
avoid the lines gee I'm sorry it
somethin
I never expected this you know we could
be waiting here all night I don't mind
lady I heard that the usher said they're
only available seats the twisty roads
do you like pizza uh-huh hello why don't
we go get so instead of waiting in line
okay okay what kind of plane Elijah
please sure you might ever seen
yeah yeah Susan let me ask you something
what if I hadn't been sent out to get a
piece of chalk that they probably would
have never met you you believe in things
like that like what I don't know like
fate oh I don't know if I too I think
I'm too practical I believe in those
kind of things mmm that was good how's a
coke please oh when you get a chance
could you bring me some cokes sure
thanks okay
Jeremy what are you hmm sophomore no i
know that i meant what nationality he
knew that i was a sophomore yeah to
think i wouldn't go out with you if I
knew
things like that don't bother me yeah
they don't bother me either thank you
so what are you I meant nationality
Jewish really yeah he's challenged your
real name ya wanna hear how it happened
yeah my grandfather's name was Jonas
Rahman and then you came to this country
from Austria they were asking for names
anyway he thought he was supposed to say
his last name first in his first name
last so he said Rahman Jonas see
somewhere along the lines jones became
Jones that's it hey you're making this
up no really so I guess I'm really
Jeremy Rahman rahman I guess I'll call
you rock oh no don't call me back I
always wanted to call someone rock yeah
i want i'm only kidding
what are you oh I'm half half french
canadian half Scottish English Welsh and
Irish wow wow I like that you know what
I like what when I heard you're playing
the cello I couldn't believe it you were
so good yeah well i guess i really feel
things when I play music yeah I know
you gonna be a dancer uh-huh I hope so I
like to go to Juilliard have you ever
heard of that oh sure
well what are you doing in New York my
dad had to come because of a job
Wow what's been your heart you leave are
your friends oh no i didn't have that
many i'm the same way I don't have many
as either
so anyway my mother diagnose 5 and I
lived with my father and different
relatives who came over to help you know
wow that must have been rough no not
really later on it was really a problem
I'm not used to talking about myself
this much well
I'd like to hear about it unless you
just don't want to talk about it you
know no it's okay it's just about it
though I guess that's why I find it hard
to make friends I'm sort of unsure of
myself I think I I don't know who I am
it's like it's like I'm half a person
you don't remember your mother at all no
not really only from pictures someday
I'll find out who I am do you know who
you are
sometimes what I don't know I know who
I'd like to be I'd like to be a great
musician music is the only time when I
feel like I'm me you know not like my
pants little boy some kid going to
school I mean I feel like a whole person
I understand sure I mean it like brings
the the me you know it's like the me
inside of me coming out doesn't make too
much sense i don't know you're funny why
when I first met you I'll forget it no
no tell me what well you're kind of
goofy
and I usually like serious people
why'd you go out with me
well after your concert I just knew that
anybody who could play like that must be
someone special
I guess that's fate hey
I thought you didn't believe in fate did
I say that yeah I couldn't have said
that come on it's getting cold
I'll be eight fun oh yeah thank you
don't say things come on okay I mean I
didn't do anything
yes you did what did I do made me happy
tonight
tonight was beautiful
you know it's beautiful you're beautiful
welfie I couldn't believe I said I swear
it was like someone else was in my head
saying those words wait wait tell me
again you said what I told her she was
beautiful oh my god if you just popped
out I just can't believe I said she
probably fixture anyone or something not
on my mind in love I knew this was gonna
happen I know my head's like spinning
around Justin love hey answer me one
thing it's get anything hey come on
forget it I can't talk to you you got no
feelings got no feelings I was inside
watching the colts and vikings play you
called me up here he told me you told
some girl she was beautiful what am I
supposed to say forget hey Jeremy listen
I really think it's wonderful that you
and Susan I found such blissful
happiness together god bless his boat
Jeremy Oh what are you doing here what
am I doing here
I was just on my way to pick up some
music supplies there's a very good music
store right here oh really where I
didn't know that uh just up the block
somewhere I didn't know there were any
music stores around here sure there are
between the delicatessen and the
drugstore oh wait a minute there aren't
any delicatessens around here you sure
there are riots hey Ryan's I'm not very
good at this but I didn't go to any
music some iced tea
to walk you to school so I came by early
waiting for you how long have you been
waiting since seven
really yeah I guess that's kind of dumb
huh no it isn't
that it's a good morning kiss
I never kissed then you were a good
morning before
really weird since seven yeah
she know what I like best about it's the
little things my voice she says hello
what boy and she says a lot it's so
beautiful I don't like what's happening
to you at all man rafi it's so beautiful
I've heard to say hello before plenty of
times ever hit me is anything special
what depends are not she says it how
does she say it's not important it's
important I wonder how she says it all
right looking this isn't exactly a lady
looks something like this wavin carry
you ain't listening yeah ok now it's
special the way she says it it it's like
voice is all alone why me
hello hello that's it yeah that's it I
swear they're gonna take you away I know
they're gonna take you away you know
what is called what it's called love you
know what that's called come
i'll pick you up early saturday morning
how early six am-6 a.m. yep six o'clock
in the morning
yeah I suppose so good for it's a
surprise
well okay we call me before you ready to
eat and make sure I'm yeah I'll call but
you gotta be ready at six six o'clock in
the morning I can't believe won't you
tell me where we're going nope come on
just a little hint no just one all right
one hit that's it all right okay okay
you ready
you
look at it Wow look at that stride he's
beautiful yeah Wow now you know why they
call it breezy yeah actually they run so
smooth they just sort of breeze behind
yeah it's kind of like the easy do they
train like this every morning yeah they
start out hearing about dawn we can't go
Jeremy when you said we were going
someplace special I never thought I'd
wind up here don't you like it oh I love
it hey it's just sort of weird seeing
you in a race track oh is it okay
oh hey you know I used to spend every
summer there everybody know about 23
years ago the three years in a row yeah
I used to be like a hot walker for my
uncle I you said yeah I speed the horses
and welcome it was a hot walking this
okay have to eat breathing and walking
off Oh
you know it's funny my dad used to be
the same as we when he was a kid he
loved horses he did the same job I used
to do here yeah now no he doesn't have
time for that kind of stuff it's too
busy come on I show you go Wingate's
part you should be a really good friend
of my dads oh there's a horse I really
want to show you he's a great gal he's
one of mr. Odom horses were dancing oh
no nothing oh here he is this is Simba
yeah his sire has never been that of an
ambry ex-mayor know what that means no
oh well a sire means the father and the
mayor is the mother when a feed a piece
of sugar yeah yeah usually horses with
Nashville the blood or mean but know
what we're looking what do your hand out
flat half lat that's it see these horses
are inbred they're really jumpy but he's
okay
yeah chase mother horses do you ever bet
on the races no I handicapping for fun
but I don't think why not I guess I'd
rather spend my money on records and
music stuff like that what can you give
me a good tip yeah sure Billy blue in
the fourth are you sure to live
absolutely that's triple van still early
June it and flavor City in a close
second and third with beasts for falling
far by as they come into the stress
that's triple barrel tunic that's true
riverbed and tunics to nibble baiting
tunics as they cross the water it's
triple man does anyone else know you do
this nope it's a secret
I wouldn't tell him if I were you okay
you know what else I do what promise you
all that it's kind of stupid promise
well sometimes when I'm walking down the
street I see some guy head of me you
know just any guy I want to raise him
you know just me and him I create
imaginary finish line I call the race in
my head I don't believe it and there are
the man in the blue suit has a two-lane
cleat as they come out of the starting
gate and Jeremy Jones is it
disappointing thick on the outside
Jeremy makes his move at 16 Poland's
Jones and the Madame blue suit neck and
neck as they coming out on strikes
that's head and head Nana boo suit and
your meeting with the man in the wolf
suit and Jeremy Joe is it
and it's Jimmy Joe
you
sure you want to yeah sure
ok
this is you can see something you've
been going out together for a while now
we'll have you been having fun yeah
haven't you oh yeah yeah of course
that's not what I meant what I mean is
well I'm kind of serious you know I mean
basically I'm kind of a serious person
what get some kind of quiet I was just
wondering if you having a good time
Jeremy sometimes I don't understand you
I mean do you really feel you have to
ask me that I mean like I I really like
spending the afternoon here with you
talking looking out at the rain play
chess
I noticed that too exciting look if
you'd rather go someplace else we could
go Jeremy you don't have to take me
places I mean that's not what a
relationship is all about you really
feel that way yes I feel that way of
course I feel that way I mean just
spending day together talking it's great
in glare
let me ask you something else remember
that guy you used to go out with Danny
yeah well I don't need to start nothing
you but uh I thought you said you were
gonna see many more I am seeing him
since I started going up with you you
well if he said that he saw you with him
yesterday after school oh that I'm so to
speak to her did you tell me you were
gonna see him anymore I told him so much
better than what I told him that I loved
you
did you really tell him that I really
don't do you really love me yeah
so okay i don't okay good yeah i mean
that I feel the same way about you it
she just that I can't say you don't have
to say just so long as I know what type
you so I feel
I have a little balloon a happy to and
dreams enough to last me all through the
afternoon I have the New York Times and
14 knives and explanations over moms
profound
Nursery Rhyme
if all the rivers run dry before the
last
I said goodbye
let us become
another
and your eye
so don't just throw your
it's not too late
to find out before the side
and as all run aah
oh the hourglass
do they died it now it's all around us
now
I want to go beside me down while there
still is time that all my points to ride
let me love you
we can creep the world good
before the rivers
I'd be father
i sag god
we can
Oh God
oh yeah
about
hey Leland my god
all the side
and as all
Oh
is anything wrong
I'm just
wispy it's that
I don't know
happy kind
why
very happy
yeah kind of
wispy
don't make fun
my 20s I wonder if anyone will ever land
on me success Carolina happy you own it
yes i'll probably laugh about see i
towed it's always been the other way
hate baltika climate give you a run and
you can all you I need some time no
outside yes I do I need some dad I need
some help I'm sorry Eunice I'm tied up
but I'm Susan hi come on in you need
what I thought what do you need you know
I have the gun crime Susan darling got
my ground what is not my parents this is
my niece Susan from Detroit doesn't she
look and this is roy and Tina hello you
do and this is Fred how are you and Oh
forgive me I don't seem to be able to
remember guys sherry sherry Spencer hi
Spencer thanks date or is she yours
darling I can't seem to remember you're
my date humming hmm that's reassuring
you do weapon what we play I was wrong
how was your day good day specialty well
right I guess it just takes some people
a little longer than others to realize
their mistakes I don't understand why
Wellington Brian himself called me today
and asked me to come back to Detroit of
course to Detroit well you're not going
are you not going home I mean five-year
contract twenty percent increase stock
options an apology the whole works
when do we leave right away right away I
thought I'd try for the day after
tomorrow it's all the time I need to
wrap up my affairs here and you know I'm
only with parkinson on a consulting
basis anyway what about my school I
forgot to tell you mr. brian is on the
board and he assured me that you could
go back to Jefferson as a junior and not
lose any time or any credits for the two
months you've missed we're leaving New
York in two days sure anything wrong
well dad I have friends you honey
friends you've got hundreds of friends
in Detroit I know dad it's not what I
mean oh well I know it's it's hard
breaking off relationships but Susan
it's only been a couple of months hardly
enough time to have anything serious dad
there's a boy I don't understand oh you
have your one I can't talk in here come
please she'll add let's go over here sit
down and talk okay
now what about this boy there's a boy
I'm see you must become serious you mean
that young man from this summer uh does
named Denny Oh Danny you met Jeremy
Jeremy Susan you've only seen him once
or twice three weeks and four days
exactly honey I know this can seem very
serious to you at the time but there'll
be a hundred other boys in your life
before you're married the boys at
Jefferson have probably lined up to wait
for you right now yeah honey I know I
drop this in your lap a lot to swallow
it once I think you'll see that
everything's gonna be fine in the
meantime I've got a lot of work to catch
up on no dad I'm happy for you yeah it's
just that it's so sudden you know it's
kind of you
so close
you
phone
Oh
blow
I swim
she
news
ooh
No
hey
sure
we've come to
Oh
I must fall
Susan what's wrong Jeremy Susan damn it
Susan listen man it's so awful what's so
awful please tell me Susan
last night so beautiful after you he
kissed I stood there for a long time I
could still feel your lips on mine I
could still feel you all over my body
and I thought to myself I'm a woman and
he loves me then I went inside I just
wanted to be alone just wanted to think
about you the whole rest of the night do
you know what I mean no no and it's I
were a bunch of people and my dad was
there and he told me you were moving
back to Detroit huh in two days we're
leaving Detroit my dad got this new job
we have tickets I gotta pack will you be
back Jeremy I'm not coming back don't
you understand oh my god Jeremy what are
we gonna do I always been so long I've
always felt so outside of things I never
had any friends I never had anybody I
could be really close to oh jeez look
you can stay in New York you stay with
your hair and maybe my dad will get your
dad a job you don't have to go
Jeremy I'm not coming back don't you
understand
you
coming but
I've never had anyone I can really be
close to I've always felt outside of
things
Jeremy what are we going into
what we do coffee no thanks at me well
we're all ready for you hey why don't we
run through our first tape sure let's
take it from the top okay stand by we
reviewed your position we're in good
shape fine Jeremy Jeremy oh I did and
yeah ah how do you know what it loves me
alright so stay there I'll be I'll be
right up
how do you know I was here cut you off
no I'm not here son but now i can't look
I'll talk to you home
I tried Rafi I wanted to see my father
just wasn't any use he can't help what
am I gonna do keep talking like that let
it take you away Oh what's the gate
number please gate number three directly
down this aisle and then she's right
Susan honey it's gate number 43 why
don't you kids meet us down there but
hurry okay we don't have much time sir
do you have any luggage yeah check the
den downstairs
are you still my point don't worry
she'll get over
it's a nice boy just say you'll never
forget me what can you say that so that
I love you all the other passengers have
bought it sir so please hurry right
through that door
three passengers only safe flight 127
should have you on board this is your
final before the river
mini car
we can
true
in
it's not too
two
before the side
of the hourglass