I
they're freaky they're fun they're the
mad balls wild and weird these oddball
toys have now bounced their way onto the
video screen follow the bouncing balls
on their animated premiere as they rock
and roll their way across the galaxy in
madballs escape from all go crazy go
totally mad let the good times roll with
madballs escape from order oh good you
came at just the right time aren't folks
the most wonderful things well they can
take you to places you may never have a
chance to see you want to go to one of
my favorite story places you do great
because it's right here Hayley Mills
story book contains the practical
princess Beauty and the Beast the
furious fly cycle and hard lucky these
stories are from wonderful books some
are classics which parents will remember
like Tom Thumb other stories are brand
new with exciting plots but all the
stories feature characters who come to
life on the screen friends you want to
meet again and again even the sad
friends woe is me what am I gonna do how
very sad these stories will take you to
faraway places and wondrous adventures
with new friends who brighten your TV
screen you shouldn't miss hayley mills
storybook I couldn't have said it better
myself the toy that Australian children
already love is now a chart-busting us
video sensation my pet months
these statues possess the power the
transform anyone who stands before them
into monsters this is crazy it's a joke
right my theories are correct I am
vindicated monster lives in that TP mark
late again max yes mrs. huggly I don't
want to be a monster that is thick
starving haven't eaten all day it is
hunger that's what changed backs into a
monster you can't get away right there's
the monster somebody stop the monster
well yes actually that sounds my pet
monster go definitely it's disgusting
come on not so that's my dear what's
down that check
Mac Smith is my pet monster new from
Oxford
family home entertainment my pet monster
a perfect movie for the whole family and
for a change of pace sing and dance
along with the award-winning baby songs
a merry medley of upbeat and happy tunes
for babies toddlers and young
school-goers this music video for
children combines live-action puppet
characters and animation to bring a
distinctly different look to each song
the Los Angeles Times called this an
absolutely top-notch video for tots baby
songs also took center stage at the
first annual American Video Awards
winning the award for best children's
entertained baby songs has also received
the golden eagle Lord and the
prestigious Parent's Choice Award from
the respected non-profit guide to
children's media in the United States so
clear your throat get your feet ready
for some serious tapping and join in the
fun as these children laugh and sing
their way through the magical music of
baby songs
the medals are rolling your way again
hey listen to this they're back they're
bad and be luckier than ever in gross
jokes a spaced-out joke book journey the
mad balls have been bounced around in an
interplanetary pinball machine and now
the joke's on us because they're headed
for planet Earth to save the world from
bad jokes
get me the mad balls for the same eous
madcap gags in the universe from the
people who brought you strawberry
shortcake and the Care Bears mad bought
escape from oven roast jokes both on the
one crazy cassatt let the singing
continue with more baby songs on the st.
cossetta's baby songs family home
entertainment brings you another ten top
toddler tunes more baby songs won rave
reviews from the LA Times and the United
States Gazette for the songs that
include stories about green hair which
ear is crazy monsters wild and woolly
fun tickly Tuttle's horses hammers and
high chairs so maestro let the music
roll
family home entertainment putting your
family first in entertainment
let's see now one ounce any dried fruit
Parmesan cheese Romano will do 14 egg
and protein in color
breakfast no time for breakfast Julie
I'm late oh oh that one well you'll be
missing out on what could become Julie
special recipe number 52 uh I've got a
city planners meeting at nine well do
home early it's a nutritionally
fortified prune shake my loss I'm sure
your readers will love it breakfast ah
beautiful morning run morning mom dad
where are Max and Melanie hmm hello max
Melanie you're gonna miss the bus come
on you guys will not believe who I have
a date with tonight Oh Stephanie summers
poodle that's her oh no what where's max
who knows mmm breakfast I'm dating
Stephanie summers not her dog you were
eavesdropping gagging the whole time
butts trying to raise those way
Stephanie's heart by taking your dog for
a run after school yep it's working like
a charm why fine chip off the old block
morning max hi dad your max let me help
you if you're some kottdeer thanks for
waking me up now I did he must have
fallen back to sleep come on we're gonna
be late you go what's for breakfast hmm
tell you on the way to the museum I'm
starving we're gonna have to take the
shortcut um no I hate this shortcut
Chuck Lee barn and Melanie late again
max yes mrs. Hockley better hurry
you mean breakaway and why can't we walk
to school like everyone else save me a
seat
whoa this section of the museum features
ceramics that's Padres youth and it
dates back to 2,000 BC it is March keep
Oh dr. Lewis dr. Lewis must I continue
this idiocy I have more important things
to do but they take a bunch of children
on a tour of the museum like boring your
colleagues were those ridiculous legends
from primitive hieroglyphs you are so
covered every century from the Stone Age
to the Roman Empire no matter how many
more centuries till lunch hungry no
Snyder what can be more important than
these children they're the future of our
civilization to me now made us lunches
oh good old mom oh man go there is to be
no eating in the museum is that clear
you
is that clear next well hey good one
ah children more years ago I dr. Eugene
Schneider excavated these Babylonian
treasures on the banks of the Euphrates
River and single-handedly completed the
arduous task of restoring them to their
ancient splendor here quietly let's have
a little more civilized behavior shall
we get back from a barrier the
inscriptions on these tribal artifacts
reveal that these statues possess the
power to transform anyone who stands
before their
into monsters hey let's say you embrace
mark this is no bedtime story this is
fact i have spent half my life
translating these hieroglyphs years of
research and documentation and for what
for my colleagues can call me crazy so
insignificant bunches of little brats
like you can laugh at my theories i am a
man of science not a tour guide one day
i film it something I said good one
Bernie come on we better find Mr Blair
what a crackpot that doctor needs a
doctor you need a muzzle good one exit
you're a monster yes what is it dr.
Schneider sir my brother has a bit of a
problem the wash room is down the hall
excuse me sir your statues turned me
into a monster my parents aren't gonna
like this it works tell me how it
happened tell me everything well one
minute I was normal yes Schneider I was
sprouting fuck in September fifteenth
speak hi I'm max wish for her boy that's
my simple-minded colleagues was the
voice of the monster living proof that
my theories are correct I'll be able to
prove this before the entire world
listen I just assumed keep the world out
of this if you don't mind you on my
ticket to fame and fortune oh great John
stop now wait a minute i told you i
don't like that John Blair Mr Blair ah
it's about back Smith and desist it is
anything wrong oh no no no no no no
nothing serious do something Mel calm
down mr. Blair will notice we're missing
and come looking for us you're right
buzz the bus still there yep there it is
they're not feeling very well yes we'll
see that they get home safely did you
hear that you're what Schneider he's
lying I can hear him bye-bye oh great
now what do we do sliders gonna come
back here and put me in a zoo where
people poke me with sticks and feed me
do bread why baby oops and you've got
monster powers you heard started from
all the way up here didn't you how this
come on
open the door what am I Hulk Hogan it's
la hi okay oops my hero hey I could get
to like this Wow let's get out of here
why wouldn't you stop hmm right there
right there dr. Schneider be careful
blue Richard oh I know where did he go I
don't try the animal exhibit
Oh
Schneider what is going on what is the
meaning of this have you wigged right
out hardly my theories are correct I am
vindicated the monster lives in that TP
see for yourself but he was a monster I
saw it you have waited one more display
like this Snyder and you're through i'll
cut your research grants so fast it will
make your head spin yeah boy I'm max
with your heart boy I'm max fish
max Smith park suite school party time
that monster will appear again and when
it does I'll be waiting
what just because I'm back to normal
doesn't mean Snyder won't come looking
for me maybe should go to mom and dad
what do you think huh and they've always
said I could come in with a problem Oh
what am I crazy they probably locked me
in my room forever the best thing to do
is handle it ourselves besides I'm that
cool and there's nothing's gonna change
that thanks maltsters can talk to me
like this what you thinking about think
you have the way to change you back more
think of all the good you could do with
those monster powers but I like being
human I like you being human too but it
wasn't that bad was it well called okay
i guess but how would you like to be
covered with it blue fur and fangs oh
hey so there's a small cosmetic problem
but it's worth thinking about right Wow
what's up you sick starving I haven't
eaten all day
a sandwich pimp order a mango you got it
max you okay she's strange very strange
I think it's happening again we should
watch city more often huh did you like
they're tipping just think after the dog
show don't wanna you can walk her every
day haha hi Stephanie come in um excuse
me I've got some homework to do hmm cute
kid like that geez don't work in no
plane well uh shall we yeah get
comfortable no kidding so tell me Steph
what are your feelings about knocked
enough on the first date huh just
kidding oh look another article on Timmy
they say she's the favorite to win
tomorrow's dog show that would be four
times in a row else really it must be
for you to be such a wonderful dog with
the wonderful mistress I mean master
owner
I don't think you're taking this very
seriously male what was that it's tippy
get rid of
go away to be shoe
tippy well maybe she's just practicing
her bark for tomorrow well could you go
get her please tippy shouldn't get so
excited before a competition here to be
your girl garad got a nice bone to pick
with you well that fur balls gonna bring
the whole house up here thanks a lot
life is on a roll
you see we were at the Museum hyphema
light shot out of the statue and hit
that's right on the face and it turned
him into a monster this is crazy it's a
joke right no way rod max it's a
real-life monster with monster powers
rod where are you hmm Stephanie hi
rosman what did you jump my baby hi you
scared tippy half to death she's
downstairs looking like a wet mop her
perm is ruined I can explain Stephanie
what's that oh well that's my sister
Melanie you saw her downstairs no that
thing Oh
I mean this actually thats adds my pet
monster Scott that goodness it's
disgusting I think it's cute Stephanie
that's what gave to be such a scare what
bad things give my tippy Oh mommy tell
me let's go now my future's of snake
what about my future uh max you stay
there stay thanks for would stay mad I
don't believe this look what you done to
my dog she's wilted I can't show her
like this don't worry about it Stephanie
a fixer a little brush hair little gel
there she'll be dog show calburn no time
right absolutely right don't be
ridiculous tippy can only be groomed by
raul roll Tippy's hairstylist my room
here's his card hmm and I've looking
back to home and happy by nine oh no he
rod will make it all better won't you
rod a problem my treat uh la maison du
shit that's awning Fairfax's me thought
so here I gotta check on max
max
flax oh where are you Zach no dad can we
talk of course son you know you can
always talk to me hand me the
three-quarter box French will you this
isn't gonna be easy dad so I'm just
gonna tell you straight I've turned into
a monster no I'm said son you're just a
little rambunctious that's all no dad
really I really am a monster did I miss
something nothing important but I was a
monster dad on is that don't mind him
dad he hasn't been himself lately come
on max is not a problem for dad anytime
kids anytime I thought we promised to
keep this tour itself ok ok ok but what
are we gonna do right now we have a
bigger problem on our hands what could
be a bigger problem in the brothers that
turns into a monster girlfriend that
turns into a she-wolf we've got to get
tippy prettied up and fast let's go back
and watch the thief button
okay come on let's go maybe you should
have put less money in that movie paint
job and more into the engine oh haha see
sometimes it's better look good max are
you hungry again yeah I think the change
has got something to do with food I
don't want to be a monster
want to be a monster i wanna be a
monster I don't wanna be a more
have located subject in human form at 84
balsam street will follow and capture at
first opportunity
check out these prices
Rose number one in canine care three
hundred and fifty dollars for shampoo
and set what fine number two in
he's not gonna like this she definitely
said values what Stephanie does no one
hurt me still I'm sick of dogs are you
sick of dogs why did we ever go into
this business anyway because horses took
too long wash oh boy more sons time oh
boy look at this mutt I tell you sick
you were sick of dogs I'm sick of dogs
yeah but I'm not sick of money this is
tiffy pedigree dog champion three times
running oh oh how like that could win us
enough dough to do anything we ever
dreamed good like move to Florida and
start and telling Kate a fob oh that is
deliver
this is the place for bandaging Carl
cutting curl nice rod I'm glitz the
glamour just about cheap service come on
but are you guys going in I've gotta
find something to eat so hungry I could
die wait a minute rod if it's the same
feeling you had in the museum yeah just
before it it is hunger that's what
changes max into a monster you think so
sure and the warning signs are stomach
growl you better get off the street
quick one I'll meet you back home right
on man
the only change our season looks wait a
month or is a fury before my very eyes
Oh watch it Schneider I bite come on now
left come back here
you can't get away that emergency hey
there's the monster somebody stop the
monster
cool
oh did you get out of your cage come on
get back in there it's lunchtime yeah we
got Chihuahua ciao doggy delight bologna
sandwiches whatever your pleasure hey
you must be some kind of dog escaped on
this day beautiful No yeah yeah that's a
boy good boy
by any idea what just walked out the
door well you did not this door the
front door Oh tippy which is dog in town
tippy yeah so oh so knucklehead we're
gonna grab a little football it's gonna
be hard ticket out of this dive but
that's her dog napping Oh Stuart why
don't you tell the whole neighborhood
okay grab a cage and get out here why
are you over here what are you doing in
there table break what do you think I
got wheels I can't pick up my dog huh
max will you fetch Emily please I know
low on by name she described him oh he's
about that high big o
oh ya ya puse keep on it just a minute
need a big joke yep Oh Maxie darling Oh
ute thank you very much
what do you think I'm stupid or
something that'll be five bucks bye bye
bye very ugly dog car must have done
that job what Stephanie it's gonna flip
I tell her this maybe we should call the
police and tell them what and our
brother Blue Monster overheard a couple
of guys planning to dognap TP summers
yeah they lock us all up and feed you
the key this is like some sort of very
gross nightmare tell me about it you
should try being a monster now wouldn't
help Stephanie would still kill me I
know it's simple go back to Carl shop
and rescue tippy just like that just
like that just like that sounds
foolproof let's do it hey wait a minute
what if Carl on stour is still there
simple you bash the door down to scare
those guys out of their mind then rescue
tippy okay 18
I can't go anywhere looking like this
what that's good none will ever
recognize you store closes in 10 minutes
okay baby tune up next week I promise
come on Ron not good enough okay it
turned up tomorrow I swear come on right
now what do we do push come on Mac the
woman's milk felt by your fam god we
meet you that will take you a shortcut
and try and keep up this time just watch
me time you got here where's max he's
hiding around the corner the place
closed early it's not going the back way
what are you gonna do I'll sweat it out
here thanks rod and if you're not back
in five minutes I'm coming in after you
good luck nice move Mac thanks I'm get
real good at doors Mel is this against
the law so his dog nappy come on
sure is dark in here four people maybe
not for me hate to be where are you girl
forget it mal she's not here hey now
look at this like entry far to the dog
show not this one I can reveal friend
see says Coquette to walk poodle wait a
minute Collins do are gonna enter tippy
into the dog show under a different name
right come on not so fast my dear you
see max you can't get away as easily as
that let her go you creep only if you do
exactly as I say what do you was better
I thought I made that perfectly clear at
the Museum I want in the cage
you have no idea how long I've waited
possible to actually witness my life's
worth standing there before me it's very
moving I'm touched what are you gonna do
with us first I plan to transport you
back to my lab there I will videotape
your every move for my records and 6
News
haha try these on only if you want
Melanie go of course it's you I want
don't do it max you're slime Schneider
hmm sticks and stones I'll be back in a
jiffy you've got to get out of here
can't you break those things it will
coffee strong not strong enough all
right max 50 stages of pipe
Oh
nice door the rod rod over here where's
tippy what are you guys doing in there
practicing for the zoo just get us out
and we'll fill you in yeah I'm sorry
nominee but there was nothing I could do
yeah Raul said it would take all night
to fix tippy right the roles of pro
right uh-huh yeah no problem hippie now
meet you there in the morning raring to
go do you hear that every spineless word
couldn't tell her the truth it would
have killed her not before she killed
you well we're just gonna have to go to
talk show and take Tippie away from
carlan stoop for Stephanie and her folks
show up Chapel we can't even get into
the dog show we don't have a dog
I
hey wait are you stirring me like that
what ladies and gentlemen welcome to
West annual dog show
we'll all contestants and their owners
please report the ring number one this
bears why did I ever let you guys talk
me into this need your help
I didn't know there were this many dots
in the country will never find to be a
time don't say that Stephanie and her
parents are gonna be here any time so I
let's split up right you guys put this
way okay good
I'm sorry the poles my excuse me
tippy world tippy tippy bark twice if
you can hear me are you trying to kick
you sure it's bad are you kidding I'd
recognize those cheap cologne anywhere
just the same stuff forgot to have lost
christmas where are you tipping new doc
hey Stephanie Mr Summers how are you
where's Timmy wrong tippy yeah her
poodle where is he G oh well your dog
tippy is being weighed in right now wait
in waiting well you know office judges
are picky picky picky I'll tell you what
I'll gonna get to be and I'll be right
back ok ok
you're right ah now you think about
that Tippie Tippie all right let's get
up so nice see you in public and go sire
hey what better place to announce by
discovery turn around everyone gather
round I have something to show who's
that we thought you were Snyder did you
find Tippi Stephanie in her purse again
later read look good I have yours I
wonder why look thank you oh it gives me
great pleasure to present the grand
prize of twenty thousand dollars to the
winner of this year's competition Cole
kept du Bois
not be very proud mr. Dubois I'm so
proud I could smell stove but it's the
owner he's in the audience base bodies
are not the only ones what Dom not check
you dog lovers do nothing Matt not
protected waters tippy summer
we're all free and what about dollar
richer
that is step on it call I am stepping on
a spoon
what is there's a dog hanging on the
back of the truck now
Oh
that's a mama
why
hey guys come because who could be
aren't you remember me
you will yes
Oh
r
the keys car what that truck hadn't
broken down those hoodlums when I gotten
away scot-free I'm telling you Tina is a
little monster thing eat our truck keys
no honest how about that Judge sure was
nice of him toward tippy grand prize
well after all tippy did win wouldn't
you say don't do that hmm um listen
Stephanie about what happened back there
I you don't have to explain I know what
happened you do of course I do and I
think you're just wonderful you do
jumping into the ring and rescuing tippy
from those dangerous man you're a hero
whoa hmm something I felt I had to do
seeing as you put be in my care you're
really great you know that yeah what I'm
still a monster no you're not you're
just a nice kid no monsters body how
I'll be gotta do figure out how you do
that so you can change back and forth
whenever you want I don't want to change
back and forth whenever you want got to
admit that breaking down doors and
stopping bad guys you just want me to be
your pet monster so think of all the
good you can do it'll be fun how we made
fighting injustice scratching fleas
helping the helpless you'd be a
superhero let Batman do it I'm hungry
always why beast or why it was I who
found you I dragged you from muddy
obscurity and restored you to your inch
splint why was the chosen
Oh
to most
they're wild their wacky their the balls
from outer space don't miss the madballs
news from high tops