[Music]
my name is John norful and this is a
story of a girl and her gift against the
world
[Music]
[Applause]
police have reported the disappearance
of a missing three-year-old girl in York
the news came when neighbors to try
carrying two gunshots from next door
police are still searching for the
missing girl's parents who've also
disappeared two months were found in a
lake on the arms of the New York this
morning around ten a.m. to ever need to
be the parents the missing
three-year-old who vanished suddenly
from her home a fortnight ago police are
continuing to search for her whereabouts
today marks the 20th anniversary of the
York angel whose families tragically
murdered in 1992 the world Phillips the
question if she's still alive and is so
where is she now
[Music]
reason health care we understand the
importance to keep your body healthy a
research selfie contains the latest in
medical technology to ensure we provide
the most accurate results our dedicated
staff members work around the clock to
bring in American see tomorrow today our
goal is to drive towards excellence and
provide our clients with the best health
care money can buy our promise is to be
with you every step of the way your
health is in our
[Music]
sir this gentleman 5007 it we're
starting a little bit on material well
work with today's event so you have
every reason to be please take a seat so
tell me why does the wealthy man who
always want the most profitable private
hospitals in the country what was a man
like me I need you to locate someone for
me and I want you to bring her back
unharmed you know what services don't
come cheap I'm quite aware of your
reputation marks and your methods here
are a nasty piece of work max but you're
exactly what I need you can tell me
daughter her name is Kyra she's a
mentally disturbed patient of mine and
she needs special attention due to her
abilities as a child she had incredible
psychic skills she could move small toys
without touching them I experimented on
her mind at Kyra grew she'll didn't look
the piece but you became unstable she
began to fail the psychic test on
purpose so we had to take drastic steps
injecting her with drugs which
suppressed in mind and allow the stick
is a haunted control
of course they were side effects the
drug is affected of mine that you began
to hallucinate she spoke of terrible
visions of death and construction Kyra
believe that the world was coming to an
end her mining was fractured but
needless to say she is the most
dangerous girl on earth she is not my
flesh and blood but she is my property
she could bring though a helicopter in
the matter of seconds as she wished nice
where I wanted a box of food they come
after double my price she was heated by
this man Randall believe you know him no
no my old mental she made a few others
Dutton so I decided to work for myself
solo he scored everything will chyron
the experiments which in the eyes of
others will be clustered illegal and
that crime against humanity she could be
anywhere right now well fortunately
Arundel commonly had one of my vehicles
and they're all fitted with a GPS
trucker our provider will send any
require
I need two vehicles one Jeep in one van
in a group your best man the scarcity
and such a fear she is that we need to
be prepared for weather shit roses I'll
see to it or marks if you see Raul on
your troubles I'll handsomely reward you
for his head Raven I'll gladly do for
free
[Music]
keep running Carmen I'm over here be
clear
[Music]
television flip down to the car park
I'll be there we will be me what if this
runs over here to get you out we came to
get your same time I'm setting you to a
friend called John omelet you'll be able
to help Tyra
[Music]
ah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
excuse me viña Sol knows where oh so no
I will probably be the bedroom
how did you be looking for me who sent
you follow me
apologize for the call tonight what
people say looking for me also
disappeared please take a seat what's
your name just kind of it fine How well
do you know Randall that one I never
seen it for today well tell me sorry
molly is better than aperture Coleman
and we love and would had trouble
Randall helped me escape hospital I
never left before he said I've diets he
did a lot of this makes any sense to me
Raven is taken care of me some owns a
title and now the land after me children
on fire so you stole Kyra whatever
you're not the first person I come
looking from a help Randall used to do
it all the time whenever you thought is
going to be trouble you'd say go flying
John call fine John ll via English
what's your point I'm old
if you walk through my door 10 years ago
I might being able to help the decade to
where don't protect people anymore
sold out some you want beer as explained
everything I'm don't care can't belong
in this shit again but friends might be
able to help I think you too now is gone
with a rambling
[Music]
but I already met Kyra and try to figure
out what I've got you into now well over
the past year I declined to infiltrate a
man called Raven and a secret
organization he portrayed himself as a
private hospital ornament it's just a
smokescreen to hide illegal activities
for nearly 20 years has performed so
many unforgivable tests on Kyra to
enhance her abilities I don't know what
she's fully capable of but I know that
she needs to be protected she cannot
return to Raven if she's captured again
an innocent life would be lost I'll bet
you're wondering why you should he would
care I know he gave up this life a long
time ago and we didn't part of a good
terms but I know else to turn to Kara's
been dealt a cruel hand in her life
she's healthy to start a new one by
doing this I know Len danger myself this
will probably be the last message or
send to anyone I just wanted you to know
John that you are my best student I'm
very proud of you I know you'll make the
right choice goodbye
[Music]
you
eyes of civilian
Oh
[Music]
mom
Oh John Northwood
[Music]
sorry No
John for the night let me deal with you
thomas cook anymore home this one thanks
for your life like a coward Randall
what is it was there now sing about
[Music]
people talk tom and the girl
by John
[Music]
don't you worry your shoes
and
[Music]
well to jog well do
thanks i gave you Elliot
you became a long
talking is John Northwood him and I
trained together same mental suddenly
local Josh intelligent see the hard to
hand combat in the crack shot with a gun
you know who lives on this or Marcus
John Walton to be taken care of and
they're psycho killer and see that you
do totally not your apology
[Music]
I know
so Tony the burglar I could have killed
you so he didn't good to see you man
yeah you too here's a bounteous
initially given you spare time I like
them I really like them just are going
on but not time today just a quick one
what is it just say cheers is what to
tell me what the body's feeling you
doing mr. here Billy ain't tell you
something about Randall he died a few
days ago by my head we need your help
are usually exactly car is being hunted
by a man called revenues mercenary not
quite sure about the intention the car
believes we need to head seminar it's
very important that we find it before
they do John tells me you know the
northwestern anyone I don't know what to
say your boss not Billy the series no no
no you expect to live it cut it I'll
just let you here we go the John do you
want something we didn't need some help
we're being honest feeling Ronald vistas
like to say Skyler ms i doing it you
would have done that for nothing and
both nola they want to use it for her
powers go ahead oh let's prove it fine
she wants annotations I'll give him 10
oh shit are you good I'm still running I
guess i canna do on a hungry sure dude
well just move it may be needed elderly
we need you mean you together side by
side on the old day you know a loophole
by my phony money my daughter Tara in
prison did she leave their guys it's
long I know what the help I've got some
gearing stairs I'm up so good in here
you love them to keglers thanks very
much let's get this stuff in the car the
better hurry and tidy up before your
wife gets back hi develop your nook do
me a better look and I find a pretty
cool rundle given one from me oh well
don't worry Billy Ray I'll go get this
stuff
I have got one question what's so
important about this building in mannar
I don't know why I think my vision to
transform something
[Music]
there looking fun well everywhere it
will be later them
[Music]
is the building close by
siren
Tyra declining
you
this one this was supposed to come you
guys come on
and
[Music]
can you remember anything from your
visions how did cry like I've been here
before
I can see myself it doesn't feel real
kyle is nothing here happy thinking
these images might not be what they seem
no makes sense that quiet get going
[Music]
no what so this could be a lot more
difficult seems the edges finally caught
up with you John and here he is the
great John Northwood and a better
sidekick she is more loyal than you max
you betrayed everything we stood for
Randall trainers to in a bed you
murdered him in cold bored lower Kyra
Raven what will be bringing button off
[Music]
but I don't see the same for him shoes
jump hey we're on the back let's all
just down there
[Music]
I target efficient when this fun easy
our yummy go now go cool
[Music]
you
Oh
[Music]
gay boys so I was kind of girl
he's wiping back
[Music]
[Applause]
so you're the man who's been causing me
all this grief air I must say you don't
look much like a bounty hunter to me
we're Kyra in isolation away from you I
know everything about you John I know
that Ronald took you in as a child when
your family first in a house fire he
trained you to become a bogey on that
just like him I don't know a history
lesson I have a question for you John
why does a man with such skills as you
have blond yourself in a mess like this
this message something you began you're
the one to blame
but I believe that if you think that you
should know before I let our mutual
friend Max they kill you tara has always
been gifted ever since she was young
unfortunately her parents didn't think
the same way so I did what I had to do
we conducted tests on her every single
day and her abilities improved Kyra was
a miracle she was the miracle but over
the past few years candidly Clemont
stable she be gonna disobey orders and
accidents became more frequent the more
enraged she comes the more powerful she
can be Phil as a precaution we used
drugs to regain control of the mind and
it worked for a while so we decided the
best way to keep in mind confusion while
the use of suffocated memories a series
of images repeated on a loop images she
could relate to the kini image was the
structure in a form we knew that if she
ever did escape she would find a way
there we will be ready for extraction
the only thing I didn't count on was you
Tara is a threat to the world and you be
protecting her all this time she was
afraid I did what I have to do to
protect Earth and let me tell you right
now I am their protector and I'll do
anything to make her safe I'm afraid
it's too late for that the time is cold
except everything like what you're going
to do correct my mistake
[Music]
begin the procedure
[Applause]
[Music]
what
hey
[Music]
Oh
don't
the patient job repeat the patient has
gone heads on to the trigger
they will do you any good John you go if
you want it you become miracle look I
need you thank you order just stop Kyra
from killing anyone else
to a follow her path on the GPS she's
heading with the Scottish border rajah
somewhere wishes been before somewhere
with a high population in a city was
levee system a helicopter ready well
gone
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
good morning ladies and gentlemen on
behalf of Carl andalusia I'd like to
welcome you to this their wedding day
here at Angel hole I'm sure you'll join
with me in wishing them every happiness
and success as they begin their married
life together today
to Carl and Alicia I now pronounce you
husband and wife you may kiss the bride
[Applause]
[Music]
hold on there son Carmen Trinity's
monster fill it with me he'll tell
anything they missed Church round open
last laugh the weapon stone
fuckin good luck John
[Music]
[Applause]
fine
[Music]
and
guys the problem x on here we'll see
legs down what gets it down quick gets
my jaan
what's going on the road before anything
gets out that we can't go that way what
look why not we love to
let's go
[Music]
all right clean-up on aisle two
Alan
[Music]
alright
[Applause]
[Music]
you're right yeah yeah can you want to
look on how'd you know both never show
anybody before is the first time for
everything come on let's go good job I'm
on the ground I'm sure Kyra
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
bollocks not many a package
[Music]
Oh
you
[Applause]
[Music]
stop right there Kyra in this what you
wanted well that's you strong too
powerful beyond your control were you
afraid of me
[Music]
ah
when don't get all done
[Music]
[Laughter]
you
every time I was in the army
[Music]
let me help you
you wanna
I
[Music]
Oh
sorry I'm so sorry fine fine a few
pictures no no no John if you truly care
about me you have to let me go
[Music]
will you stay with me I don't want to be
left
[Music]
hey Billy how's it going man I thought
just start check on you I've just been
thinking think of continuing bundles
work these people out there who need to
be protective understand and you league
of bounty lunches I will take
outstretched and listen Billy thank you
for all your help really appreciated I'm
here doing unicom speak to you later man
tricky so much bye for now I
[Music]
hello is this John Harwood yeah he's
calling doctors about her I have a
client who wants to speak to you a bit
busy just now and give you something
else is numbed I insist that you speak
to her what's then in order
[Music]
and
we
in
[Music]
you