you
of all the Christmas tree ornaments
turned out that year very long ago only
one hand of happiness his name was Noel
and at the very moment he was created
old Hermann a glassblower received truly
joyous news alize his only daughter had
just given birth to a baby due he was a
Grandal at last in being quite emotional
for a glassblower furman crime pure joy
it was Noelle's good fortune that that
one Mary tier became part of it
my name is Noel and I am
yes Herman's tear of joy had become
Noelle's a wonder what the world will
hold for me I couldn't care this gosh
you're pretty it's not proper to speak
until we have been introduced oh wow why
you don't know I am miss freezin the ice
maiden if you please very unusual and
precious ornament oh you just know else
but I have a happiness how terribly
middle-class friendly Noel and miss
presento were placed with another
Lawrence into a cardboard box all of
them together with something called a
dozen where are we in the box thing
stupid each in our own little
compartment but we can't see each other
this way I rather enjoy that not me
you're a pissed but what about the
others I couldn't care less hi my name
is Noel and I have a happiness
no rebel please who's making all that
racket
then the Box the health a dozen is
delivered to a truly magical place
the afternoon of Christmas Eve in a
five-and-ten-cent store Saginaw Bay is
that was the only place some folks could
afford to be married
Wow will somebody please shut that
greenhorn up hey what are those big
things walking around don't shout they
are called people thing salmon and my
littler Oh honestly they are children
thing i like the children face it
figures you would look respectable noel
we are a thing called for sale and we
want to be a thing called bought
finally one of the people things Noel
sanda she was a thing called a mother
bought a dozen dropped them home
look at this beauty cost fifty cents
down at Smitty's coal yard oh darling
it's worth every penny and look at these
hey there swell ah Merry Christmas dear
this reason de don't ask we are in a
thing called a home what's a home thing
a playful things box
I love you I want to go on the terrain
what that's not a good idea honey now
come on all of you it's time for dinner
wash wash wash again watch yeah
everything counts with Santa she loves
me
Noel looked up in the stately evergreen
mighty branches were like great strong
on
hi my name is Noel and I am happy
wonderful my name is Brutus glad to know
you
kindly Brutus became Noelle's first
friend it was very patient he didn't
mind answering any Noelle's thousand one
questions what's happening now Brutus
it's become a thing called Christmas Eve
the reason you were made and I was born
it feels like magic when the children
things were tucked into a thing called
bet the people things came back
downstairs and went to work here's a
good spot for you little fella I get it
what a neat idea Hey look at me after
the duskman along with several other
dozens were hung onto Brutus's strong
arms all right dear plug him in Noel met
the mazda sisters a delightful if
slightly world-weary by my name's Noel
and I am a happiness I know well sweetie
he wasted me then of course there was
the tinsel plan mighty groups but very
necessary
then under Buddhist lower arms replace
many colorful boxes type right fancy
ribbons and around old is the father
thing placed a toy electric train named
Micajah frequencies the frickin freezin
think Jesus treatment hi guys my name is
Noel and I have a happiness why can't
you talk
what's oh my god so busy about he's
trying to catch us please why don't know
but it seemed very important for toy
electric trains to cats lately darling
and then
special place was made for one final
thing lovingly placed under this
what's that down there a Buddhist I
can't see inside justin is a toy stable
but why would they have a choice stable
well Noel somehow that little stable is
the thing that tonight is all
I
then finally with it we're a one-day
only parent things can go on Christmas
Eve and they realize the job was
finished as they done every year as
their parents had done before them they
had taken holiday trinkets and made
Christmas magic what this I feel now
it's so lovely it's a thing called peace
and goodwill you're quite remarkable to
be able to feel it usually it's reserved
for the people things and animals and
sometimes us trees figures maybe it's
because I have happiness I guess maybe
it is hours past but it seemed only an
instant suddenly suddenly
Christmas morning
it was a wonderful time with toys and
there was laughter and presents were
exchanged there was laughter and loved
ones visited right there was locked
the more trailers were opened it and
there was even more laughter the guys
ran around his right season freaky freak
freak the fair was clapping and good
things worry man there was life and good
kisses were kissed and then to top
everything off there was more laughed
was a wonderful time which went on for
seven whole day and night things
but then it became a terrible thing
called January 2nd back to normal huh
they're gonna put us in that old dog box
again Brutus why because
it's old oh he's not gonna get me I
won't go
goodbye little fellow goodbye keep that
happiness of yours never
no L ever saw Brutus again
Noel the rest of the dust were put into
a high dusty dark thing called an attic
where they became a thing called
forgotten
but as it always does the thing called
time relentlessly from season to season
and it became a thing called spring and
thing called summer eventually it was a
thing called autumn a time for pumpkins
turkey
then came a truly glorious day when the
first snow the year fell and then
finally hey thing
hi like the little electric train and
chased its tail around the universe
arrived at Christmas once more there was
a new free Harold but almost everything
else was the same as the year before
family the friends as disasters the
tinsel plan the brightly wrapped
packages mysterious little stable and of
course this is frickin seizure frequency
the frequency
hi guys careful Noel hey Harold what's
inside that little stable down there
Brutus that it's the thing that
Christmas is all about it well I guess
Brutus was right but it seemed that
almost before it started Christmas was
over again Noel said goodbye the herald
the Attic things prison once more and in
this way year followed ye this is sweet
blend joy and attics after Harold there
was Bernard after Bernard there was
absent and Gregory Irving Sean but as
the years passed Noel sensed that a
subtle change seemed to come over
everything hey the children things are
getting bigger oh no
must you always be so dramatic they're
getting to look almost like the people
things I couldn't care less indeed the
children things have become people
things then came of things that changed
all things things such as graduations
and engagements and weddings
then one day years later Noel heard
somethin terrible from down below
Oh what's the use kins scattered all
over the country with families of their
own let's not bother with a tree this
year all right dear oh no no Christmas
no more Christmas good a vacation at
last
and as the long lonely attic years
continued to pass Noel finally fell into
a deep and seemingly endless sleep it
was lucky that he slept three miss the
thing called heartbreak which visited
the house he missed the things called
wills and auctions he never heard the
words I just leave that junk in the
Attic it's in no use Noel never heard
the terrible final sound the lock babe
is it shut off life and warmth and joy
from the old empty house leaving it with
the ghosts of long ago Christmases which
everyone did forgot
and as the years crept slowly by the
Dozen slept on like the house their
bright colors faded and chipped
indeed everything seemed over I say
seemed over because when you have a
happiness nothing is ever completely
gone and perhaps it was the happiness
working its magic who knows
24 hours got it down at the mall it's
worth every penny
look I found these all ornaments in the
Attic maybe you'll look pretty with all
the new plastic ones Merry Christmas
honey Merry Christmas what's Mary about
going back to work
Christmas is Matthew tomorrow now come
on all of you it's time for dinner
no these are just two chipped and old to
use shift an old Oh what does he mean by
that not pretty i guess put me on that
tree I insist upon me on that train no
he you they don't want us here come wait
we could use this little fellow to
balance out that branch in the back
goodbye miss risen de goodbye she didn't
even say goodbye seems she to worry
about being chipped and old oh hi my
name is Noel and I ever happiness call
me Abraham yes there was a new tree but
all the old friends were back including
Jesus reconsider greetings hi
long time long time
oh the little old red ornament it's
broken somehow no way was still aware he
was on the floor he knew that and for
the first time he could look into the
tiny stable why there's little toy
beautiful things and allow my children
thing
hey
well now that his old glass body was no
more the happiness really was released
curated happiness if you go anywhere
it's the world thing the thing on the
world
over the brain
Oh
new healthy wish out pour house
nah
how does me know
totally forgot it and way down
better people in children's pain but
some spoke different on different days
of life's often never even heard of
Christmas
Oh
the Wonder one
the pure
Christmas
you