how
the same old ground
same or fees
wish you
builder
it did stem from those first four notes
that popped out of the guitar one day in
Kings Cross
somehow those notes evoked a song about
Sid and his disappearance absence if you
like mean Roger it's my homage to Sid
and my heartfelt expression of my
sadness and and but also made my
admiration for the talent but and my
sadness but the loss of the friend I
think the song is brilliant innit sort
of evocation of what Roger obviously
felt about said and it certainly it
matches mine I think what was so
important was to not try and write him
out of history
ha
there are no generalities really in that
site it's not about all the crazy Talmud
is about SID
when I first saw the floyd i remember i
mean the first thing you noticed was the
lights because nobody was doing at them
in the science and but Sid really
started to shine you know you couldn't
really take your eyes off him even in
the merc and the purple and green blobs
you know the bright eyed Sid and his
singing and his guitar playing kind of
jumped out at you
by the time I was working with the
studio it was clear that the real
creative shape of the group emanated
from syd although you know certainly
wasn't Sid and backing group
suit was a very wonderful chat very very
witty very very sharp you know he was
outgoing charming wonderful friendly you
name it having a wonderful man losing
one of the gang I guess you'd say the
good friend funny follow annoying
because because he was good-looking and
play guitar and could paint he always
had nice girlfriends
no one that you ever really would have
imagined would wind up the way he did
wind up
when you
Oh
shine like the Sun
in this post Dark Side of the Moon pure
we were all having to assess what we
were in in this business for why we were
doing it whether we were artists or
business people
having achieved the sort of success and
money out of how did all that that could
fulfill anyone's wildest teenage dreams
why we would still want to continue to
do it now remember the disappointment of
Top of the Pops or having a the first
hit single or whatever it's it's not as
world's shaking and changing as perhaps
you expect it to be so that that may be
the you know because of the enormous
success of dark side it was still that
sense of Alice hasn't made us feel
enormously different to satisfying roger
i think is sometimes said that he thinks
that we were kind of finished at that
point
and she may have been right
I think we were at a watershed then and
we could easily have split up then and
we didn't because we were frightened of
the great out there beyond the umbrella
of this extraordinary powerful and
valuable trade name big flight
it was the first song they played and it
was like words they've been singing
about syd barrett
the band that was known for their
musicality they weren't doing their
music justice dear recall there was a
business affairs review my neck candy
how could I forget I kind of overreacted
obviously I mean I feel now that I
overreacted but at the same time they
partly deserved it it was a bad gig it
once it was a shambolic am I mean it was
some it lacked enthusiasm and I'd like
to know there's a perfect sense of
purpose now I don't really know why from
my perspective now to look back upon how
I felt then scared as I word was a my
own shadow you know nevermind my
relationship with audiences and the real
concerns about not making any contact
with the audience during much of that
tour of England that we did in 1974 and
we didn't we were but we were very
disconnected
if we weren't giving a hundred percent
we couldn't quite sort out why not you
know there was an element of frustration
which and having someone tell us that I
think we probably knew it then couldn't
quite sort of deal with it that review
would have been one of the things which
would have once we've got over our
initial ire we would have been taken on
board and realized that there was more
than the germ of truth in
I was asked to record the Floyd at
obviously called the Empire pool she's
now at wembley arena and when I saw the
floyd before they went on they said oh
do us a favor when you go and sit with
our sand injury and that's it ok how
long lovely never 30 years and anyhow I
went back in the interval and they said
what do you think and i said it's
rubbish because I've been used to
working with smaller groups on Smalling
mixing vests and there's was messy so a
cop I'm story show actually I knew I was
doing the next night at the Empire pool
no goodies just take me back and then I
ended up doing the rest of the British
to have something better just worked
with this hour and then assailing k wish
you were here though a lot of days where
we didn't do anything while they were
thinking about ideas the reality was
that we were struggling with making the
follow-up to dark side and we rushed
back into the studio to do that you know
we put ourselves under at sort of
ridiculous pressure in the way tried to
make a record from nothing he was
disengagement it was not being willing
to apply yourself sufficiently a lot of
moments where any one of us might have
been much more interested in thinking
about what they were doing that weekend
it became a case of two would be in the
studio and two were running late or as
it was always known there I play squash
and then we had the dartboard with the
air rifle
the concentrated activity was rather
diluted and I'm sure for a a very
pushing driving sort of person like
Roger was more frustrating than it was
for any on earth although considerably
frustrating for all this I suspect when
I'm in the studio I'm there to do
something otherwise I'd rather be
somewhere else frankly and it's on there
to work
well you know there's a bird the
legendary argument that I must have had
with the rest of them about my thought
at the time that would be better to use
the other two tracks as well that we had
been working on I had to fight David for
a bit as he acknowledges completely you
know he we had a completely different
idea about it was and that was a and
that was a fight that I won Dave saw a
record that had those two songs and
shine on and it felt cobbled together to
me it didn't feel like like real and so
at some point in that process yeah I
said yeah I came up with the idea no
this has to be thematic and it and
that's where I expressed it
this will make this a more coherent work
and in because it's more coherent it
will be better than if we just throw all
the songs we've been working on together
and go boom they are that's it there's
one song that's about Syd but rest of it
it's it's a much more Universal
expression of my feelings about absence
because I felt that not that we weren't
really there we were very absent
remember tip common here dimple have a
cigar you're gonna go far come in here
and have a cigar you know and become a
star and and become immortal you're
gonna make it if you try they're gonna
love you you become part of the whole
buying and selling machine it's high I
would need to do a number of vocal
exercises before I attempted that I
think the lyrics so much sum up the
recording business
rock roll Matt
go go
the record companies were they were all
powerful in the way no one worked
without a record deal those days said
they play had a lot of power you're not
longer really an individual anymore you
just your cipher we're playing a part
you're a puppet you're not your own man
by the way which one is pink which one's
pink which one's pink
we're gonna run
it was with felt that since madness had
partly come about through the demands of
the record industry you've had a hit now
I want you to do another head I want you
another head and I want another head
that's not as good as your last head
that's not as good as your last record
you know and I want you to a bigger show
and have more lights and more people I
mean it's how all i want to do is to
play a guitar and write a song and
suddenly I'm in the middle of all this
the star thing doesn't make doesn't make
you happy you know that the star thing
can make you want to withdraw from
society it is solely consider did you
think
and I must obliged you
a kiss
well you could argue that it was burned
by the music business but actually it
was probably burn bothered by us
sidered sort of gone off the idea going
top of the pops of being sort of
commercial
I think it wasn't the record company
putting the pressure on it was us
putting the pressure on because that's
what the way we wanted to go
and I
when you are my love
when I
now
have a cigar you go from with have a
cigar both of them you that night room
could sing it I always thought Dave's
force was not deep enough all right I've
always had a deep respect I mean that
motion city state
I think the Bears fantastic that is
really what I think by the way which
one's pink that's right they wanted the
ferocity which Roger give some other
tracks at the time you just felt that he
hadn't got it come in here dear boy have
a cigar you're gonna go far Roy was
definitely one of the great characters
around for a lot of our early hour early
life really we used to do quite a lot of
shouts why Roy would be on the bill good
guy to have around I was in stereo too
and they were in Syria three I think Roy
was it she's rather lacking in momentum
himself I think we will it didn't only
seem to affect Pink Floyd you know that
that's why I have this vision I guess of
me being in and out all the time in and
out in and out in and out he spent quite
a lot of time in the studio with us very
expensive recording time that you spend
just in our control room chattering and
anyway I digress roger was really
struggling with it and then Dave then
they both tried there was a lot of
arguing about how we were going to do it
and how we were going to make it work
and the one point Roy who was in the
room pipe gun sit I just said I'll do it
if you feel like for a price deep
respect and I mean that most sense silly
I mean Roy really plays hard I mean I
can I can picture it now which was pink
put this on something to her as if his
life depended on it you gotta get an
album at you owe it to the people we're
so happy we can hardly count I mean
lyrics
if I have written those lyrics I'd feel
well pleased and did we tell you the
name of the game boy we call it right in
the gravy train
played millions of times around the
world as a single that was my vocals on
a you know really it kind of a number
one selling single everybody thought it
was Roger okay I was with peed off about
her I think if I'd sang it would be more
vulnerable and less cynical than the way
he did it but but that it but that's not
the way Roy sings he went off and did it
and did a great job and thank you very
much I don't think Roger liked his
version terribly much but i think is his
version is the perfect version he was
singing a sort of parody anyway and wish
I don't like I never liked it the worst
of it is that one sometimes when I'm
doing you know when i'm doing a gig
there's some waggle shout that was a
girl you know I regret it and then
that's not because I've got anything
against Roy I haven't you know and then
I think if I'd persevered with it I
would have done it better
you're not gonna die
I was so unbelievably thrilled to be
this and I was just very young as I was
just about 21 but was actually a rather
nice picture of me that nick mason took
and sort of sums up because i just look
wide-eyed and you know thrilled as the
only words I think Todd Bates and fairy
cakes and I thought had been quite as a
pregnant of the studio there's this
wonderful sequence of of Roger proving
that he did enjoy the cake I think that
that Nick took these pictures because i
can't imagine that i had the courage to
sort of you know take them a bratz I did
Roger is in the driving seat in these
pictures as far as the studio's
concerned and perhaps that position is
is hard but actually it's probably
better if just one person's and driving
seat Roger actually you know kept a
tight hold on the helm and that's what
what he does what he did and you know
you can't gain say that because the
record you know that records were very
good
dog side which is such a sort of see all
the pieces fell into place so as Nick
Mason says drumming did it so I think
that that was quite hard to do with what
do you do makes what do you do to top it
what do you need to be different I
couldn't draw so fantasy pictures were
out I couldn't pain so artsy fartsy
without I wasn't the graphic designer
and also it's not interested in band
pictures because I didn't really I
didn't found them bit dull you know a
group of four musicians to play guitar
drums and bass or keyboards would seem
to me to be four musicians announced it
could be anybody we always felt that
representing the mood the music was the
order of the day I know it sounds
radical even revolutionary so in order
to represent the music one didn't really
want to be limited in the great palette
of art and life to a pitcher for geezers
we mostly in those days left it to storm
to come up with things which we would
give him a diss sultry to miss of our
mixing time to say that one maybe that
one no that no that they were recording
at abbey road and I remember going there
and I remember I was very I was very
nervous in doing a presentation he came
up with these this you know from the
lyrics from this theme of absence and it
just seemed like a very very good idea
all I remember getting a little round of
applause that was a most gratified i can
tell you storm actually is probably one
of the most argumentative people you
could ever meet Roger and storm it has
these intense conversations over fine
wines and so on storm and Roger with two
great intellects and you know there's
there's sparks flying in in in their
brains that is too I got very
preoccupied with four with a number for
the fall words in the title for members
of the band and four elements
life air Fire Water and Earth for the
first thing that was tough as a postcard
the post-grad said wish you were here ho
found his fantastic location called late
mono which is such an amazing location
that you could just about photograph and
plastic duck and you'd like it we always
thought there was an element of storm
loving to find the most expensive
distant location in the world so he
could go offerin and have a little jolly
for a few days as our expense this guy's
doing a yoga position in a yoga chair
locked into the mud poor man with a
breathing apparatus on and he had to
hold his breath shouting in the bubbles
that's all shop for real that's not an
airbrush no cutting or anything and that
was a moment in time on a magical
evening with amazing light did that take
a long time to set up much of a fucking
long time this shot was a pain in the
ass
I came to the notice of Pink Floyd
because I made a film in Los Angeles for
the BBC I thought that I would do a kind
of a visual diary of Americana at that
time so I drew everything I'd like to
think of at the time like black power
playboy magazine Mickey Mouse it's
fantastic Mickey Mouse secret when the
key goes from being the mouse to being a
sort of drug-crazed mouse
Amy yep far out making such a clean
living and there he was on drugs I told
it was absolutely brilliant and I just
thought this we could really be great to
work with someone who produced something
like this and I took it to Roger and
show garage Aaron Rodgers loved it I
wasn't it was a very was very awkward
like all relationships at the beginning
because they wanted one thing from me
and I wasn't coming up with the goods I
felt when I say this to Roger these days
he said oh I don't remember that I just
remember it was an enormous relief after
a lot of the flailing around visually
that we're done with dark side of the
moon I think the Sandman is a
particularly great image
you know the fact that we're all mr. Sam
that can blow away i think it's just an
idea I had really I wanted to do the
impermanence of life who are you know
it's all sounds rather pretentious crap
really
you
the beginning of the record sounds very
melancholy and is very melancholy and
his melancholy music sort of blues and
it's a sort of G minor blues that whole
first six or seven minutes
we obviously found a mood that we wanted
to not exactly jam to but play around
with them and find something within
we were never too afraid of leaving
quite a long period of time instrumental
before locals came in
at the time it was a case of let's see
what works
so then hence the wine grass tape came
out
the wine glasses were recorded for an
album that we're going to make called
household objects which we had on a loop
and then Rick then built up sound with
synthesizers and Morgan
they've wanted a big sound so the guitar
was recorded in a different studio so
hence the creek track he put his
amplifiers and speakers down in studio
one being a classical music studio and
then marked it from a distance I think
it comes across on the album you could
picture it being played out somewhere in
an auditorium
this will be Rick featured on the end of
shine on where he really came into his
element
hammond organ on there you had grand
piano plus the other synthesized
intimacy plays
I remember exactly what synthesizer that
was but this is Richards trademark
he's a great piano player
does highlight is passable training I
think if he had another 20 minutes he
would've heard probably like a required
concerto
at the very end where he does the
tribute to syd barrett i don't remember
if that was just Rick thinking of that
at the spur of them over on a moment
that was a nice nice touching thing
he was kind of a crazy diamond and all
the things it says about him those
brilliant lines are very very accurate
you know you were out your welcome with
random precision was certainly a part of
him
please
go
you
my memory is that we were recording a
radio 1 show at the BBC and Sid didn't
turn up I think it was a Friday and no
one could find him so we've basically
waited and waited and I think we had to
cancel recording or we tried to do some
without him not sure and then the
managers went off trying to find him and
when they found Sid which I think was a
Sunday or Monday they told us that well
if something's happened to sit and
something had happened to total
difference and I remember if he was
being right like this and looking in his
eyes I was just like somebody turned the
lights out it just looked so bad
he was living with a whole sort of
community of people who were very much
believing acid can release him you know
get to the truth and all that stuff and
he took too much and he went up on on
stage and he just stood there for long
stretches and playing the guitar for bed
and then stopped he had done so much
damage because I said that's what it
does to you too much acid would
literally fry your brains
No
honey
ha
we were unable to help sit and probably
I won't say deliberately but had our own
interests at heart and so consequently
probably tried to hold on to him for far
longer than we should have done Sid left
the band in 1968 Sid Sid was only around
for that one record it was a tiny piece
of it was a very important piece it was
the opening piece of the Pink Floyd
story and it may well be that pink floyd
would never have started and would have
never carried on and nothing would have
happened we will never know he was a
real hindrance to to the band in in many
ways having said that we simply wouldn't
have got to where we got to would be no
Dark Side of the Moon if Sid hadn't been
around to to take us on that first major
step
I prize so upsetting working with Sid in
those days we was like trying to seeing
someone so drowning and trying to pull
them out but they were kept on slip you
know the hand slipped away all the time
you were hoping that would be
therapeutic for him and might help him
come back trying it was like trying to
tip to paint that combats
it was never likely to be any way back
and that is quite awful to think about
you reach for the secret too soon
you cry to the blue
yeah it all
and of course they love their room so we
just who the same shadow you crazy that
when you just read the rest of the way
they love doing Colleen and Vanessa
being Americans and soulful was a
wonderful contrast between the such
appreciation assist Pink Floyd I didn't
know them from Aurora soul and I didn't
like their music in the beginning it's
all in a minor key is all very low and
everything was losing us who are these
people I thought Motown was meticulous
but this was the most meticulous for
musicians that I've ever seen work
before and something told me in my head
banana you're here for a reason you have
must enjoy this music you must get on
with this music cuz you're here there's
something for you to learn they manage
to do their job without getting involved
in the band politics so yeah those two
very good at just that you know if we
might be in furious with each other
about something or other and having some
great were our the dinner table or in
the car and the weight of the show
whatever and they'd just be very very
relaxed and just get on with it and they
always sang beautifully one of my
father's fondest memories of being with
Pink Floyd recording shine on you crazy
diamond because that was the only thing
that we got to actually record with them
as opposed to singing performing dark
side of the moon so that was a great
thing about it we actually got on a
record
so welcome to the machine they just
wanted bits of add hot animation bummed
into the show willy-nilly and of course
I had my little team of animators who
are strictly trained to work to a track
and without a track they don't know what
to do I used to go and tell Roger this
doesn't matter about a track just let
them do something I assume he made that
all that spherical stuff having heard
the VCS three throbbing at the beginning
of welcome to the machine all that stuff
when it came to welcome to the machine I
think Roger Rudy getting into his
synthesizers so hence you have all these
different effects
I mean some of these noises to me just
futuristic
I love that machine I used to a lot back
in the day still got one it's still good
for wind and explosions see in the throb
is basically what Roger would have
played on base he adds to it later on
with the real base really realism is
really on there are Dave's acoustics
good
you add a bit more to the aggression of
song the tips and symbols are added
it just sounds like a very angry song to
me always did very angry that somebody
was getting something artists
I do
way
this particular creature I created I
remember showing it to the gang we sort
of went along with everything as I said
at that point they didn't sort of
correct anything Roger it particularly
has this idea that if you hire an artist
you don't try and change what the artist
does you hire an officer for what he
does cherry has a very similar kind of a
bolshie attitude towards all status quo
and all the powers to be the item
d
see you blood that comes to gorgeous and
crashes super to steel towers goodness
what it's about but and so that I
thought it was a very kind of a strong
image a seal blood I did really add
piece by piece the animation so when I
dropped down the sea of blood Roger
probably said we need it a bit longer
so then the sea of blood had to turn
into hands praying grasping hands
hopeless lost kind of hands I suppose
searching for some God or some reason to
it all
you could say that welcome to the
machine is only about my experience in
the music industry it's not it's about
all of our experience in the face of
that monstrous grinding thing that
chooses up and spits us out
in the meetings that stall I had you
know one of the topics were suddenly
getting burnt in the business you know
which was an expression of the time man
have been burned you know so what more
logical magritte concept if you like
would be then two men shaking hands and
one of them is getting burned we both
had yeah mostly cuz it was so outrageous
these are the days before computers
though it meant sitting around on fire
which we did yeah it wasn't very
difficult it's hit issuing orders from
the bunker it's really easy over the top
men anyway that was done for real in a
studio lot in holy what could be more
absinthe than his TV a lot
believe it was the Warner Brothers lot i
betche doing a lot of firework in those
days and i had the special suits and all
this stuff for full enveloped fire but a
partial is basically you know pretty
safe pretty easy one to do and in most
cases he had a team of 20 people rounded
with five distinguishes and ready to and
I deal with any emergency the effects
mantels step out and he's got a wand
about that long with a fire on the end
of it and they go we're ready action and
he just touches the three or four spots
like that steps out everything's burning
and it's a still picture so shake
shaking hands nothing to it and after
I'd shot about I suppose 15 shots I'm 15
times for somebody to catch fires rather
a lot suddenly just a breeze and the Far
whip-round his face there was a funny
thing about fire when it gets in your
face you're going to move it's just
that's just part of the thing and once
it blew it around I turned as fast as I
could he fell to the ground absolutely
smothered with foam and blankets and
everything like that and he got up and
he said that's it no more I'm luckily I
got it McCann from here we see him his
foot leaving frame I mean it's a sort of
rather surreal teammates of absence in
itself you know but that's real absence
out of frame how to say you know and you
just kept shooting I just kept shooting
yeah I mean I had to get this shot and
had to be right so you know like have no
time to be concerned with this
since fuzzy you know if they want
somebody burning and they're going to
pay me I don't care if they have an
artist drawing the fuck
when developing a theme of absence it
seemed therefore appropriate enemy and
the cover to be absent the got it here
DM this is the end piece the end or the
end part of the puzzle anyway the record
companies pet in America went completely
apeshit you mean wrap boucherie and
black opaque the shrink wrap so you
can't see it are you completely fucking
map but you have a sticker that said
what it was otherwise the fact he
wouldn't pack it probably let alone the
fans by it I hear a story that there are
thumb efficient others
who've had I've had wish you were here
for many a year now and have carefully
slit the opaque vinyl shrink wrapper and
extract the record and actually haven't
seen the cover in 35 years brilliant
that's really absolutely
that's the one I can remember my clearly
it's that was me strumming a 12-string
guitar which I'd recently purchased from
a guy I know and coming up with their
unit the opening riff of wish you were
here
and again like like the four notes at
the beginning of shine on you crazy done
other people starts going hey that's
good I've got you got something there
nice it's about what state you're
playing that's really nice any-any
played it and I said that's really good
maybe I should try and do something with
it I think Roger and I then worked on
writing the verses and putting those
courts into the into the whole thing and
Roger did those brilliant words and
there we are did they get you to try
you
coo coo
I'd ashes for trees
cool breeze co-come fuccin and if you
shame walk-on part in the wall
for lead role
that collaboration between David and I i
think is you know really good all bits
of it are really really good very happy
about
so so you think you can tell
Hamilton care
blue skies from pain and you're choking
field
from a cold steel with
smile from away and do you think you can
tell
I think most of the songs that I've ever
written all pose similar questions can
you free yourself enough to be able to
experience the reality of life as it
goes on before you and with you and as
you go on as part of it or not because
if you can you stand on square one until
you die and I know this that it made
that may sound like bullshit but that's
what that's what the song is about
I wish you were here
which is to love so swimming in a fish
bowl year after you running over the
same old ground the same fear
wish you
all the songs are encouraging me I guess
I write them for me and it is to
encourage myself not to accept a lead
role in a cage but to go on demanding of
myself that I keep auditioning for the
walk-on part in the war because that's
where I want to be I want to be in the
trenches I don't want to be at
headquarters or i don't want to be
sitting in a hotel somewhere I want to
be I want to be engaged and
probably i might say in a way that my
father would approve of
it's a very simple sort of country song
it's still because of its resonance and
never the emotional weight it carries it
is one of our best songs
Oh
people do attached to lots of internal
feelings that they may have and they may
not be entirely sure what it's about and
neither am i I mean I'm only telling you
what it's about for me and but there's
no reason why other people shouldn't put
other interpretations on it which which
could be just as valid
although shine on you crazy diamond is
the one that is specifically about
certain wish you were here has a broader
remit I can't sing it without thinking
about it
my memory is that I came into the studio
and there was this guy standing there in
a gabardine raincoat and large large
bloke and I had no idea who it was and
surprisingly no one's saying who's that
person what's he doing wandering around
all our gear in the studio and then then
him coming into the control room
standing around and how remarkable how
long it was before anyone actually woke
up finally I think it was David who said
necting the recognized him and I looked
and I think I either shrug my shoulders
or what at some point Dave so put me out
to my misery and said it said we just
stood there or sat on just a shell shock
basically
and then tow somebody thought of
something to say to them
and then we were all unbelievably
shocked victim his appearance I mean I
didn't recognize and there was him
but it was a pretty pretty affecting
really I mean version Dave cried yeah
this slim elegant if bedraggled and
dazed person that I'd last seen had
turned rather balloon shaped and no
eyebrows not much hair
there is the photograph of him in the
studio at the turret
you if you looked at sitting the early
67 said then it was so different
he was a great loss am and you know the
imagining what he would have gone on to
do is speculating on that if you like is
his he could have become so great
Oh
those years
to the rest of you
do this flag
I'll tell you cuz you see
you
to me it's about the most complete album
in some ways and we all know how
difficult it was to get to that point
and the problems we had
you
it's full of grief but and anger but
also full of love you've got to see
beyond the grief and anger and to the
possibilities of of love
you
Oh
No
you