the sprites are putting on quite the
show tonight I wonder what the occasion
is
you
how about rude oh it's fine
and he thinks so too
Oh Blitzen look come to Papa Rudolph
come on go on Rudolph you can do it sooo
you know Dasher dancer Prancer and vixen
Comet and Cupid Donner Blitzen but do
you recall the most famous
no red-nosed reindeer had a very shiny
nose
and whoever saw it
you would even say it glows
used to laugh
join in any reindeer
Christmas Eve santa came to say Rudolph
with your nose so bright
won't you guide my sleigh tonight
reindeer love
and they got it up quickly
and off the red-nosed reindeer you go
down in history
red-nosed reindeer you roll down in
snow
this is where we live Rudy Santa's
Village
we call this that's right snow Mitzi
he's at it again I don't see what the
problem is noses are not supposed to go
hey blitz we're not no no not now hey
buddy boy hello fellas so where's the
baby buck uh well embarrassed by your
own son hmm come on out resulting
Rudolph these are your uncle's comet
Cupid dash
coochie-coochie-coo hey cuz i need a
spunky one chip off the old buck yes
look at that
no need for alarm it's just an allergy
let's take it
why I'll lock antlers with the next buck
who makes a crack about my son's knows
he's beautiful not odd and perfect the
way he is you're absolutely right look
at my little guy isn't he a cutie this
bouncing baby bug of mine and his name
is Rudy he's quite a strapping ring here
and is very clear
your grace of style that way till he's
old enough to play and bring your games
huh then one day you pulled the sleigh
with Santa I love reigns le Cheyne yeah
it absolutely glows
little guy with his angelic grin so
cuddly a snuggly you shower that up he's
such a special in here there is so
endearing one thing that I'm clearing
when we start to school
perhaps they'll ignore it maybe
rudy's Moses
you grow out of it I think
yes what about
alright break it up show's over
hello moon hello naugle any mail today
for s clause let me check
if we play our cards right we'll be up
for a promotion before you know it you
mean we won't be picking up the mail
anymore that small potatoes or
exceptions elves like us will be
promoted to the factory floor that's
where all the action is um byah byah
byah byah life in crossing storm Ella's
bridge always gives me the creeps
slow down bone you're going don't pass
now no look what we did the Queen storm
Ella's garden maybe we should leave a
note you numbskull then she'll know
we're the ones who did it Doug of my hat
never mind that let's get out of here
Rudolph welcome to Santa's toy factory
make it on for you
for Santa's clientele I'm talking
darling
haha
making time for you
making sure
make it
the train as elves we're ready
hey
right someone's in device
baby what's one of you warm blooded
pipsqueaks that's why I skull
superb a madam
I want names was it you feminine anomia
royal regal there put that else down
starbella what's the meaning of this
your l's vandalize my beautiful ice
garden and I want justice how do you
know our elves are responsible duh
because I found this at the scene of the
crime we'll get to the bottom of this
come on out everyone no need to be
afraid now to whom does this hat belong
be honest
you please don't let it take us boss
would you younger dies it was an
accident cheap honest accident uh oh
yeah yeah yeah I'm gonna show you an
accident step aside Kringle I'm taking
these culprits home to ice castle you're
not taking them anywhere how you
obstruct justice you turn them over or
I'll I'll I'll close my ice bridge to
the public
storm ella your bridge is the only way
across grand chasm if you close it will
be cut off hand them over I can't then
my ice bridge is closed and if anyone
from your village dares to cross it I'll
bury the north pole in my biggest storm
yet I am talking here i am talking sleep
i am talking snow and a windchill factor
that will knock your thermal socks off
baby so be it good day storm ella
I think we'll still get our promotion
take it off really really really now we
wait before what ridley it's only a
matter of time before somebody crosses a
bridge and on that day I will storm
that'll put Santa out of business ever
see a club
I
two
good morning yearlings now let's see
what we've learned about being did
history who can tell me how Santa picks
the flowers for his team Zoey once a
year Santa holds the junior reindeer
games hmm it's every Rangers chance to
shine in front of Santa and if you
really impress out at the games he may
ask you to be a flyer wendy has you know
hearings all flyers wear the coveted
Medal of Valor but who can tell me what
the Medal of Valor stands for courage
character and a heart that's true
correct Rudolph but next time raise your
hopeful my dad Cupid says I was born to
be a flyer just like him you're out of
order arrow I could be fire too why not
with that nose
ready try the Surcouf instead runny the
red-nosed reject they never gonna be a
flyer
we hate being different like an abnormal
loads like everybody else
hey now no one can see I'll stay like
this for my whole life but you know
young buck hello sir lose something son
uh no sir
whoopee you must be Rudolph how'd you
guess you look mighty cold son
so I understand you want to be a flyer
like your Papa you and want me on your
team sir not with this nose but I think
your nose is grass but everyone laughs
at me they call me names and stuff oh
we're all different on the outside son
but what counts young buck what really
counts is what's inside our hearts and
as far as i can tell parts don't come
any bigger than yours
remember Rudolph I come
everyone in my village rid of an
reindeer part of my family so listen up
and I'll fill your cup with everybody's
a some body and Santa's family tree
everyone has a place in my extended
family so glum mother reindeer Chum
everybody cows and small and great
amount
install android on bombs inside
thanks for the muscle T
you gotta wrestle up a bit of courage
pup put your nose to the grindstone
a little faith it takes to make a
reindeer fly and live
to the sky and I no one gave you do it
if you put your mind to it everybody's a
son body and Santa's family tree
everyone has a spot in my extended
family
here's the secret potion it takes
devotion you have it in your heart
you've got a great head start and that
makes you a car
of my extended family tree consider
yourself
inside
see you at the Christmas Eve launch
Rudolph you can count on it sir
buckle up and drive safely dear
roco Dasher dancer Prancer vixen comet
Cupid Donner Blitzen
you all look so handsome in his arms
moon is right tonight and that's enough
Christmastime yeah choir of children
sing their song they practiced all year
long
Oh
one day that's gonna be me ladies and
gentlemen we present the Medal of Valor
to our newest plier Rudolph thank you
thank you very much I'd like to thank my
parents for always believing me oh and
santa too for making everything possible
but most of all I'd like to thank the
dough of my dreams Zoey oh my gosh don't
be embarrassed I didn't know you were
there I liked your acceptance speech you
did want to take a walk
I'd like to be your friend Rudolph
really I mean you don't mind being seen
with me you think I care what the other
end you think but what about my you know
I don't think your nose was funny at all
you don't it's unique just like you gosh
I don't know what was unique look we're
in a missile fell know what that means
you're supposed to kiss me
hey we were just talking narrow look
more like kissin to me there's no reason
to be jealous we're just friends jealous
over it neither red node reject don't
make me laugh he's not a reject whatever
come on let's go ah gotta go Rudolph bye
loser back
she likes me
any practices and trees for the day
member
I'm sure Santa will notice you in the
game's Rudolph oh I'm sure he'll notice
you too Zoe I'm really glad we're
friends me too
but I put what are your what I mean to
say is it's your luck gosh Zoe
once a year we hold these games to honor
the mighty reindeer who draw my sleigh
every Christmas Eve may the Flyers of
tomorrow be discovered today oh let the
games begin and now for the first event
of opening day the sleigh race you
weren't Zoe's pendant she just gave it
to me for look hey she's my dough
understand she's not a trophy and you
shouldn't treat her like one on your
mind
and they're off
Barro's racing dirty we can still feel
my my my
so he's only nice to you because she
feels sorry for you that's not true yes
it is she told me so
the road out where
you just want to find for illegal use of
the glowing red nose but you're banned
from the rest of the games
sorry Rudolph what your fault ogle the
judges rule arrow winner by default
that's just not fair but mama the chug
has the final decision not us
you cheated so what the point is I one
and Santa's gonna notice me you're no
flyer arrow fires are brave and they
have character and true hearts like
Rudolph but he has a red nose oh you're
so shallow but Zoey I don't want to be
your dough friend anymore Oh next event
is the living contest but you can't
throw him out of the games sorry the
decision is final but the nose problem
isn't his fault a was born that way that
nose of his was an accident
one day you'll be proud of me pop
I'm out here on my own face the day
I need you to get me through the night
lost out in the cold I want someone to
hold I feel you're near though you're
out upside to forest I'm
wondering where you are where is the
love surgeon for me too
I'll be on the mat and tough the dream
will never stop give me a sign I'm
running
and of time
ray of sunshine
Oh rain
show me the love
so each owe me
hello hello might as well sleep here
all right put up your dukes this is my
cave yup who's I found it voice I'm not
a moose imma reindeer whoa wise guy huh
well prepare to be evicted
I'm just
come on Sam Sam shit
uncle P will they welcome to the cave
kid thanks you got a name Rudolph they
called me slightly nice to meet you so
what's your running away from kid who
says I'm running away from anything huh
I can we just like a book your family
never understood you your friends they
all turn their backs on you you couldn't
take it anymore so you're sucked in your
slave wow you were good hey he's a
little secret kid when things get bad i
mean real bad just remember it could
always be worse allow me to elaborate if
the glass looks half empty and your
prospects are low adzuna justement the
only way to go things could be why
standards
you could be lost in the desert 200
degrees no water around and lots of
snakes and bees remember it's tough and
it's cold out there life sometimes don't
be unfair so for every step ball with
there's a step in Reverse things could
be better they could always be Weiss yes
things could be better in this big uni
voice but remember it could always be
voice
so far every step but there's a stepping
rejoice things can be better they can
always be worse yes things could be
better in this big uni voice but
remember II could always be wise
remember it could always be worse than a
man remember me
see ya what's with the glow-in-the-dark
snores yo I don't know what you're
talking about let come on kid let's have
a look-see go ahead and laugh everyone
else does like yeah sure make jokes
clever and more my nose can start
traffic I I have a glowing personality
or on Christmas ornament Rudolph Rudy
look you left a note dear Mom and Dad
goodbye forever love
hi can I see Rudolph please he ran away
what is gone
I have to find him
so well what's in the back way just
stuff hey if we're gonna be friends no
secrets but sly late it's private come
on let me see oh now look what you did
Dunkey okay I'm sorry
teddy bear so where who gave you this I
don't want to talk about it say no more
kid love this procedures well let's get
some shut-eye ready
rudolph's out there please Santa you
must help us find him he's never been on
his own before
Oh Santa we can't find Zoe anywhere oh
dear well don't you worry I'll send out
a search party immediately I promise
we'll have both children home for
Christmas
I have an important job for you even
after we let you down the last time
everyone deserves a second chance spoon
I've gotta find Rudolph even if it means
crossing storm Ella's bridge
oh this is what we've been waiting for
Pengy prepare the sleigh
brutal
it's not an Martin you crossed my bridge
thanks to you I get to blow the storm
that'll bury Santa for good nowhere to
run nowhere ha
what have I done wake up
Oh nuts the cave sealed we can't get
back in it could be worse ly ly oh
really how could have been trapped
inside the cave yeah good point men come
on we'll find ourselves an even better
okay
so see anything
just a lot of snow we gotta find them
doggles we can't let Santa down
well this looks like a cozy little spot
come on red
see I told you we'd find a better cave
slyly I think someone already loves you
just let me do the talking red Kim
Putney chosen friend away from the
Bureau of cake safety huh now I am sure
that you were aware that recent shifts
in the young polar ice have made some
caves unsafe for habitation huh now
please step aside whilst we inspect the
premises though as I oh oh oh boy this
cake is collapse any minute you've got
to vacate immediately no no no no no
need to thank us just doing our job
bye-bye now she right if you get work so
easy that wasn't very nice slyly yeah
it's either him Horace bed that is the
law of surviving you trick me
Retreat retreat hi there mr. polar bear
oh my name is Rudolph I'm sorry we tried
to trick you it was wrong we were just
cold and hungry with nowhere to go oh
well why didn't you say so in the first
place I I I am Leonard fun Appetit boys
he lifts kiss how'd you swing it I just
told him the truth hmm do one on me
reject a never gonna be a flyer so is
only nice to you because she feels sorry
for you
that knows of Israel was an accident was
an accident
gosh
hello Rudolph you know my name have we
met before we're the sprites of the
Northern Lights and we've been keeping
an eye on you we're admirers of your
wonderful nose wonderful you see Rudolph
everyone has a light that shines from
within but only a lucky few can make
their lights shine for right enough for
the whole world to see now Rudolph
listen closely your friend Zoe is in
terrible danger what she's in storm
Ella's I Spungen and only you can save
her how your light will save her Rudolph
but first you must learn how to use it
close your eyes Rudolph
think about everyone you love and
everyone who loves
be the light of your heart
now let it flow out as the brightest
night shuttle as the light your elf show
us the light
I did
Oh
slyly oh hey hi you you know it looks
you seriously look and I need your help
well this is as far as I go red I still
say trying to save your friend is a lost
cause yeah there's a secret way into
storm Ella's castles through the ice
catacombs yeah but no one who ever goes
in those catacombs ever comes out alive
I gotta do this guy's I have to save Zoe
oh yeah I am I am coming with you I
click in your bed don't do it as soon as
you cross that bridge storm Ellis snow
wolves are gonna be always sprite said
to lose my lunch follow me better
yeah nuts the father is hey good luck
somebody's crossing my bridge show me
the bridge must be on the fritz
this must be the way in
how about some light little bunny
let's try everyone show me the line
someone to lead and guide me our
footprints oh no we're going in circles
wait listen it's Zoe far voice we're
gonna crash here I'm never getting out
of here I'm here to save you Zoe Oh
Rudolph
pleased to meet you Joey I am letter
here it won't watch you need the key
where is it right here
welcome to the hotel storm Ella my dear
oh you'll be sorry when Santa hears
about this ah Santa's not worried about
you honey he's got his own problems you
see the dough crossed my forbidden
bridge and now I'm throwing the Storm of
the Century it's almost Christmas a
storm will ruin everything hit it Ridley
I get a certain thrill from area falling
snow flake or a nice shift that causes a
catastrophic earthquake I get a happy
chill from the crush of avalanches and
trees with a thousand
because I thought that you could center
for the joyful joyful oh so Mary you
watch me an extraordinary what's with
that ho ho ho and his jolly disposition
kidding toys girls and boys I must ruin
his Mary mission I'm just getting warm
when I
wicked storm and crash Santa Claus oh
because you cross my path you'll feel
storm Ella's right now I shall release
my store me master
in a wizard and it's because I hate
Santa Claus that cheerful Santa Claus
Oh
I hate him oh no no stop thank you where
you're from stop ah you'll never get
away with this just watch me you're an
evil old witch that's what you are
remember my little toe I know you made
the storm possible work that out in
therapy
bye Oh Rudolph had ruined everything
novo e this is all my fault but I
crossed the bridge what I ran away yeah
well maybe you wouldn't have run away
well if I told you Rudolph you mean
everything to me good gosh Zoe hmm what
I need to say is you make my whole heart
glow
frigid weather seton hail snow and sleet
and wind said well I makin me from meet
you at least all mine
this storm came out of nowhere chief
storm Ella someone must have crossed her
bridge
see what happens when you leave a rescue
mission two amateurs slowly you need the
dungeon key to get herself it's a raster
millas neck nuts how do I get myself
into these things
are you doing still in the key to the
dungeon now go back to sleep I Turtles
Leia know this truth thing really wakes
let's get out of here stealing the key
to my dungeon
that one this one mouth Flyleaf
quick let's go back
I do and do and do for you kids and this
is the thanks I get nothin nore
who shall I freeze first about You Zoe
doughy leave her alone you are you about
grab on to my antlers and I'll pull you
up oh joy no
we're just saying my life well I
couldn't let your whole could I well no
you couldn't well you could let me boil
your rice oh well you're free to go
consider us even steven knocked until he
gets his wish Wiz well is he saved your
life now you owe him a wish those are
the rules of the North Pole the Fox is
correct madam oh those are the rules you
mean I get a wish anything I want well
don't stand there like a deer caught in
the headlights I want I would I want you
to be nice I wish is that but Rudolph
you can have anything you want yeah red
come on think bigger are you you know
you only get one wish little buddy you
got it I got it Rudy Rudy Rudy how about
a normal nose huh yeah see that's what
you always wanted right say the word
lists yours ciao I want you to be nice
come on kid picks up an L I want you to
be nice the North Pole's about to get
awfully dull mmm milk to whale autumn
ice you heard me right make me
nice hmm cute little penguin someone
change her back please you don't look
any different but I have changed Rudolph
on the inside okay now call off the
storm well if only I could huh once I
unleash the storm it's got to run its
natural course I'm I'm afraid it's out
of my hands
use my bridge just shortest way home I
want Merry Christmas
it's a white on I can't see a thing
maybe this will help way to go red but
we still will make it holy not in this
weather
I've never seen a storm like this it's
like pea soup out there too dangerous
for flying I have no choice but to
cancel the Christmas Eve launch
Chief look
yes
Oh Zoe well done boondoggle I'm sorry if
I worried
oh you're wonderful glowing nose gives
me an idea so crazy it just might work
what I mean to say is Rudolph with your
nose so bright won't you guide my sleigh
tonight with honor your honor
there's just one thing missing what's
that sir every flyer needs one of them
burrows because you've demonstrated
courage character and a heart that's
true I now pronounce you flyer I mean
gosh congratulations red yeah you be
careful out there you're the best
friends I've ever had good luck redang
men the worst of the storm circles the
north pole for a hundred miles if we can
break through it the rest of our journey
should be smooth sailing but I won't kid
you this is gonna be one bumpy ride but
with Rudolph and his wonderful nose at
the lead I say we stand a fighting
chance if we all work together I think
we can make it sir I think so
I'm proud of you son Dasher dancer
Prancer vixen comet Cupid Donner Blitzen
get up Rudolph with leisure shows
faster hires we can beat this storm I
know we can
even though we have many here
mountains behind
and there's no
much time
if we try
on your dream
we face the storm things in life
as long as you
we can make
we
Oh
we made it
look madam look what Santa brought you
Christmas media a Merry Christmas madam
look under the tree red left is presence
dancer
do
reindeer
see
rude off with your nose so bright won't
you guide my sleigh to knife
history
Oh
Rudolph with your nose so bright won't
you guide my sleigh tonight