the best seller in the world
the Bible but one reason it's the
greatest piece of literature of all
times it's really tremendous isn't it
the shippers and three King flight into
egypt the childhood of Jesus Mary chance
they're very fine cheeses in the temple
where you can see how this would be an
inspiration in the home do you like that
honey what's in it Christine which Jesus
bride she's pretty like a mother huh
Christine you know how my name is yes oh
oh you know whatever kutta me oh okay
you can see how completed it the Bible
runs as little as forty nine ninety five
and we have three plans on cash Zod and
also they have a little Catholic on a
plan which pair plan would be the best
for you the ABS see I'm really not into
see what y'all speak it man yeah yeah
yeah you wouldn't want to give him a
surprise did he have a birthday coming
up you lovely kiss and on the show we
place a tremendous the Bible is still
the best seller in the world so I just
now
I
Oh Rob hey mr. McDevitt from the church
area day what is this the church Sunday
and now I guess you've got me mistaken
what name do you want from dinner and
were snow across the street oh gosh and
this is the ceiling the crowd they claim
I don't know exactly about thirty
thousand or more attend one mass they
buy them something st. Peter's right
right no Vatican I don't know that I
didn't need that are you Italian actor
mr. soprano the gads are not at an inn
their Swiss yeah what I know did you
know why I never know that 26 feet see
their trial of in the cabin the
functional usually I mean see this six
feet now here's something I see a lot of
people they like to be frank the print
it's lad it's a ten-point register
there's nothing can I down with thanks
for the order yeah
how'd you do Joe I do the trip yeah good
did you get for well I got one a quad 25
down where it you think you got me beat
don't you I said I know I just think of
all time how'd it go fall yeah he still
had one a day vitamin huh let me get him
off that man operator I'll call back
later yea yea big impa you sell them
crows huh yeah by Alan do fit court I'm
all class and i'm due for quality help
you do it for that i just got to hold
the density 10 intended but but that we
lost ghouls time getting you know back
that will i get to go to spencer ya know
webster what ellipses years young well
that's the time so now it gets it well
understand of work with if you're not
familiar with the turret I don't go to
me in your wife you're not familiar with
the territory it's difficult you know
permit me to offer my own any man is not
good at selling should be able should be
good at making excuses hahahaha a man is
not good at sounds you'll be good at
find it there yeah machine work online
and he shows up a panel about it where's
your orders oh oh we got a producer Mike
at that minute for you three things yeah
I didn't get another lady o'clock and i
think it is
or pretty good depth 12 10 10 20 yeah
nice tuck yourself very good money is
being made in the Bible business it's a
fabulous business it's a good business
all I can see the people who aren't
making the money it's their fault just
keep that in mind the money's out there
and go out and gather I for one am sick
and tired of haggling with you people
and clean with you to get you to do
what's good for you and what's good for
us instead of friday and saturday
instead of goofing off for playing gin
rummy or poker which i think is all very
important i think somebody decide in
this territory should go on see if this
church is in a good neighborhood or if
it's in a skid row neighborhood meet the
priests and if you're going to have a
problem is it in time to let us know so
we can get another church you would
double your earnings we would double our
volume and we'd all be a lot better off
maybe you see some missing fascia sure
we eliminated a few men not because we
were mad at him not because we didn't
like them not because we didn't need a
few cells that they made but it's a
question of the sour apple spalling the
boro certain guys have a habit of
getting a couple of beers and fly off
the howl and badging people round and
throwing their weight around I want to
go on record and I want to tell you all
the next man it gets off base with me
I'm gonna tag him out the ball games
over you've got a job to do and you go
out and you do it I thank you very much
I thank you for coming for listening
don't you worry about it buster I've had
it I'm sick and tired of being sick and
tired and it's not good for these guys
you know they'll get um discipline to
get disrespectful than Phil alibis
why not EDD then off of his bumper mr.
rich
boy
well mr. rorish man mr. McDonald I'm
father yeah we have a display at the
church mr. McKeown yeah and she gave you
a name that's why I'm DST she came very
yawning that she gave me her name and
I'm here because she gave me an agency
that goes business our families in it
again a name you know at the church see
this is where it with the approval of
the Monsignor know ya see like if you're
at the church and you see the display
you say okay can you give me a name ci
comme tu si si this is no no I don't
know what the hell Roy weekend well yeah
all right I don't ask you I don't know
you're ok right we're done yeah all
right sir
we place a lot of nurses people in the
phone company you know ladies like
yourself and you read educational man
you think that you won't get get the
elephant I'm a photo said I know you
won't want to know I want to say this by
the way I hope it brings you lots and
lots thank you i know i just touched my
get around to reading it okay i'll give
you a flag to its attack god bless you
now see she's making it balanced they're
a lot easier for you alright you bring a
lot of life i don't i keep my big mouth
shut about look online personality yeah
yeah my response often scratch oh my
that's a good comment well you're more
Scots in your iris jamail so thank you
very much for saying that Jimmy outside
of something i'll be very truthful I've
ever run into a moves like this in my
life the biggest point I don't think my
life yeah they always give me about Tali
muches a day like this picture what do
you mean is it a target okay no people
had read a lot and appreciate folks yeah
don't tell me in the hotel was reading
this sheet me she don't wait out the
Wonder Woman I certainly was a raging
laughs uh you'd really love the Bible
you won't run into people like me all
the time you're gonna have to work
harder but you men are doing fine yeah I
like to see me about you know I'm there
when Louise
in the family right get away from
companies get away from the borgata
white compan comes right after would you
play for life just like you yeah we were
swollen you're gonna go no she don't
believe what she's doing children she
hates you supervisor anyone works foot
long cock no she hates it so I've
everything I being out in your own I
don't like being you know under anyone
like food really it gets tricky after a
while now supposing you're kidding us
who do we get in touch with the FBI yo
you have your dog okay a double ganger
as a microphone don't mean a thing my
mother of fact let me ask you that you
always say you don't think he's an
artist me and you're not literal like I
am I mad she is a living sing and I have
an f1 race and I had a daughter in the
convent and I'm a devil
are these people are finding they make a
lamp sometimes the lot of servers
oh damn
there was fears and gentlemen
I'm gonna go don't back out out yeah
I'll Charlie how many more dilutes the
hell
Oh
I'll try to find maybe mrs. Rafi so
wished I was a rich man I wouldn't be
going on this shit Lance oh shut the
window now let's see where I don't act
get another one of these beauties mrs.
Rafferty
rather you be home and i know i'm not
home
we ascertain anything die we're not
selling the Irish fight with English
negotiate down automation or difference
to me
cause the admission of paying me bidders
the Irish should taken away
let's see
today chimpo the entire Mac I went
farming yelling I'm here
we do have the Catholic Encyclopedia
they spent four and one-half years now
we can't carry it but this will give you
an idea this is fantastic this is the
brand over now Catholic Encyclopedia
what this is that this stance is 43
files on the answers in the face now
this is a terrific i'll tell your wife
this has from the reformation carmax all
you religious now you know that you're
over witnesses denied table but they
know more about our religion that they
have good literature to find out that
I've said Carly this on you want to look
it up at then you can blink encyclopedia
would the comparison the Catholicism did
thinking the ideology involvement yet
the Tennessee sir but frankly we can't
carry the set as i mention it's too
heavy but this is gonna make them it's
got a good personality honest to god I
mean that he thinks I'll give my sale
talk I know he has he's got a good
personality but the screen here is vast
and scholars as Muslims were Donna yeah
and they come in red or white some
redneck collision this is may I said I
call an antique gold but advantage in
that but on that and that you have your
choice of colors now what color would
you folks children it mmm have a captain
cream ah what plan would be more
convenient and I know it's like a
railroad station today but what plan
would be more convenient than the cash
yeah all they ever careful about a plan
no no I
I'm saying find them oh I see you on sat
at church you're not gonna lie but is
this how you're related to miss McKenna
yeah by a friendship that's wrong my
best pal is this your best buddy sure
well I'll turn to get a good friend that
I know I I told him what was good what's
your laughing why'd you i miss advisor
as did you hear about the scratch mental
only Irishman a half a dollar he know it
but they're supposedly LA I feel did you
hear about the scratch him in alone I've
heard many of Merit about the one that
don't was gonna get know that Scotsman
and the jewel and the Irishman are going
to get a BD for something yeah but
anyway what about the half at all love
dad did you ever heard about them I
think I had my gosh I an intelligent but
nor you say you say I never have and
I'll say you never will away know what
you want to do well is a pea beach mouth
BAM Bible man I do you want to see over
there may be a rule deposit on it now to
make binding hey thanks a lot wow you're
really know thats why IM once on AI here
and this is obviously not get your house
yeah i just have to go down to the cabin
offering 10 hey i'll just take this out
of my chest
I got no bitches
not one in know what number one that
asks for the Bible yeah he wasn't home
the other one wasn't home at all
well I have to deliver this way to puts
great
there is a left hand right to the head
too strong to the midsection and how
they tie each other how the battle go
well not much of a Babel left up to the
head air pressure
just get to scratch
huh
the kids know England no life for me not
power Kenny and tell me can we the rest
of my lead I hit him with everything but
the Chinese fence how's the time we
couldn't even get in the door couldn't
find the houses i spent about two hours
and the last one boy i broke my ass huh
this is the middleweight champion for
fighting the purpose but I like the
being of myself not bring any market of
these people I actually get in no
pitches because you know soon I can't
afford anything we just don't have the
money and safe kid my wife though and
hazard element and this is continued I'm
not thinking negatively but I tried to
give relatives in the common polyol
Mickey stuff but these are this is the
most Bob licking territory everyone in
since Gallivan Boulevard where they had
duck and behind the door phony name the
phone did the fathers and yi yi they
didn't even ask that they didn't care
about the fam Carol Grady boy the name
hey the Italians and the Irish and
really dead you know no no who do you
feel like evening him I feel like Gigi's
not avoid go but more fucking Italian
fool for me Anthony's in US and flour
Sicilian the Irishman the commode a
banana box nice charity you'd have to
rely still working they say he'll ask is
good territory no that's a fact all the
time we're going to go i'll ask you
remember oh you are we know about eight
years ago you were told me if this
business is on the fringes the fringes
don't
is worse than others know well this is
just business reminds bridges of a sorry
of a one of those you know the little
things in the old days you know the
wagons with the thing on top carousel
you know yeah well a Surrey with the
fringe on the top they got these little
tassels the way I take this business
only the tassels aren't even left yeah
that's a bit red i waked all my news
nails on a five-year plan good did you
don't like Adam so how'd you talk that's
call I go one motherhood and that would
have been a little mad at you got it
what do you mean because it was the one
that you went next two are you know and
they weren't home and you went to this
pudding by mistake are you register with
just a wife with her husband left the
name with me think people know Jesus all
him a little problem with our apathy
Ellen stuff yeah I thought it better
what can I took a long time to it how
potential was her akasia a Bible life
yeah but he said to me so like a
household and nothing on there also was
a little bit tonight hey Wesley was all
right yes he's doing turned out to be
tough enough this was a yes it was the
one yeah she was very bossy no but she
was all right oh yeah poor Sammy says as
a matter of fact I had to sell him a
demonstrate I saw him the one I had yeah
and he says gia $40 enough 14 level when
i said hola when you figure out you're
gonna have it for a lifetime him it's
not a lot on the time what do you think
so is he then she says that she'd go
half with him you know first he tried to
get the daughter to go half of them and
he says he don't happen to him she'd go
half with him in this gentleman well I'm
gonna get some sleep i'm tired out it's
a long day yeah that one phony yeah
Carla's guy you know what he thought if
he says well this wouldn't be the
appropriate
so I said well but next year thank you
since while the couple years bi what do
you say get this one we what the
appropriate time was getting married or
some no he said / go for the tollamune
assalam what yeah you know what i want
you know i'll tell ya I tell you what I
I I would have not appreciated say with
the way this was the last call I got
that say I know that whiskey this big
son just poop on your face that he's
skeptical say so then I said well
frankly if you never took the
encyclopédie you have the Encyclopedia
in the back of the Bible anyway you know
so he says yeah he says but fifty
dollars a lot of money so then I went
into the demonstrators well you know
that lease is forty dollars a lot of
money you know
you get your green pants on the day
cream that time know you're irish the
official i'll be loving to see you if i
was on the fast he gets a pinching so
good job he's a fine working bad pat
what's in a long time but he gets his
reward it is provided on run he retired
he does exceed oven a good piece of
money did you get for about two weeks
just went I he same for trip to all your
official something over there however
forget when I was a kid lived in a
tenement the Coldwater flat you know no
bathroom or anything just a bathroom
that no bath and amazing their last
admission of me and
I was going on a journey of farm and we
got what tuxedo in the family it's my
brother's sexy dough will forget this
the day and JC I had to go to the junior
prom he had to go to some festivity MIT
was like the guy that you know how to
say little one so P shit out of the bed
so I get there quick I'm he didn't had
the soup its taxes and all set and hit
the road you know she's okay hey come
looking for his tax we go to the
festivity they was blue murder I don't
forget that he stood after that boy he
caught up with me one night tuxedo
well I still got my hat trust me a lot
of money to send you had a nice I don't
want to sing negative but I can't see
anything here but the link on the couch
I'll tell you one thing Paul you're
putting me in a very negative frame of
mind for the sales meeting in Chicago
you'll be all right for Chicago
we guys not a success he's got nobody to
blame this stuff what everybody's got to
do is to put making alibis and excuses
and accept the responsibility of success
or failure a lot of one simple my
production for the year 67 I'm real
happy with everything I've just got one
thing in mind Kenny said while ago is
this making half with money for the guys
capable I think he's right I for one I
intend to make this next year something
I my wife just talked me into buying a
big house and she wants to have few more
kids and all this kind of rot so I'm
gonna make thirty five thousand dollars
is coming that's all I believe that me
this is fantastic I haven't what I've
been with the three months read long
damn i wish it was three or four years i
mean it i expect to make 15,000 not 35
over
ciao you say
that one back questions yours is real
good fathers great as usual yeah thanks
man the next speaker of course needs no
introduction to no one like to introduce
the designer and theological consultants
on the books that we sell dr. Melbourne
I Feldman vice president consolidated
book publishers this is a little token
of our appreciation i'll try to read to
you what we've been scribed on it
melbourne I feltman THD the world's
greatest salesman of the world's best
seller with gratitude that America hey
there are many people who know the Bible
there are many people who can quote from
the Bible but you're somewhat different
you know the business and what is that
business isn't it the business that we
hear when the young boy Jesus was lost
for a better of three days or so and
they said to him why didn't you follow
us why didn't you come with us we were
worried we were scared to death where
were you and he said very quietly and
very simply whiskey not that I am about
my father's business now I don't intend
to portray the fact of the father's
business in itself is selling Bibles for
dollars and cents and for the commercial
aspect of it but I do believe the good
that comes from the selling of Bibles
and the getting of Bibles the reading of
Bibles is definitely identified with the
father's business some of you at one
time or another may or may not have had
a higher income but you have never held
a higher position of a steam in the
minds of the world or in your own self
satisfaction than you now hold knowing
what you're doing about your father's
business hold your heads very hot be
very proud of your position stop
thinking in terms of Bible peddling
because I'm confident that once you
realize what you are doing for others
you and your own esteem will rise so
high not with conceit but in humility
knowing that you have the privilege of
the power to be of service to others and
with all my heart for the coming year
and for many years to come god grant you
an abundant harvest thank you
why'd you bring up a ridiculous matter i
just behind your fellow like ourselves
me you like sales me but okay very has 5
6 7 8 75 offer 500 outrage mmm taco
dollars right huh cuz me another heaven
down the hall before well ciao no wild
card now this is what you put into
simple kid Guptill phone I'll Ashley I'm
gonna check them beat the corneas check
I've been to Queens you scared to bed I
can bet I know I get you be up at your
house at six affection for checking us
both away cuz he's our innate yeah yeah
I'm gonna interrupt again for a minute
I'd like to find out everybody's plans
and thinking as far as I felt far when
we can leave and where you want to leave
from it I don't care mammut Gerald esme
gonna die fun whichever way you decide a
matter that's my another maintain going
down yeah all right fine I'll take quite
frankly I look forward to the trip all
right now I know you know I don't my
wife cheater but I would enjoy a basking
in the Sun you always don't report about
ran ahead if the trip is successful then
you know they say maybe ten weeks mmm
you might want to go home in the
meantime but ten weeks all right
tomorrow and large the Florida tonight
we're gonna put tour all right good deal
yeah
LOL or online
welcome to the city of Miami Beach to a
little Lewbert an Irish tudela by
Casablanca i'm free bogey the hell is
that funnel
Oh
fontainebleau there you are am I gonna
VES my money in that I want to see what
it looks like Wow
I said hello hi honey how are you fine
how are you okay that's good where are
you tonight I'm it outside of Miami it's
the Congress in oh really beautiful
swimming for right out the door I think
that you look at Mike Chang yeah I'm
living like a king yeah but yeah it's
really pretty nice yeah wonderful
wonderful yeah mm-hmm what's with snow
up there Oh Robert and Charlie Henry of
course they all kept me out for 20 drive
too fast well I'm not driving fast i
know i mean just excite gently drive
around 45 to 50 no God 78 you take you
guys retires yeah yeah yeah yeah I'll
take care of that so why anything new at
all oh no nothing a lot of money look at
how do you take care of yourself you
take care too all right don't drive too
fast ok ok I'll keep it below 50 yeah
okay alright then bye now oh is it she's
there feeling pretty good chief you
shall keep your low 54 loan I'll tell
how fast they're going no I mean just
scared he doesn't mind it makes you
figures you going 70 miles an hour well
you know I wasn't very solemn I go that
fast
actually I mean it's a question how'd
the hell was a call back there well I go
to the dough slips know everything out
yeah see a doctor you may want to call
operate it you try my call to Boston yes
I'll call again thank you come on let's
go swimmin let's go from how much your
methodology don't go on the pool oh wow
I don't want fickle yeah good run of one
yeah you're going in the water what are
you out of your mind why not what do you
think of Daniel business
golly yeah
all right that water is cold
I come on mr. Baker yes I find Catholic
crest opening catch you two getting on
top of what a second oh thank you very
much okay we're calling all the family
some same rules just have a seat beer at
home trying to end up too much just me
okay the I what's your last name family
again my name is Turner what was this
for all from the church I'm the helmet
sure just how much seat me to the wife
was telling me about that I'd like to
mention first of all of course we're
working on the full of fire to the
church I like to mention this has a
recommendation of his holiness pope paul
i want to mention first of all this is
edited by father john o'connell you may
be familiar with this and is published
by the Catholic press pushing buying
anything Catholic you will up for them
promoted sure assurance of course it's
approved then in addition to the regular
Bible blend right in with the sacred
text you have all the paintings by the
old masters see here's immaculate
conception that here's his story now
this has your infancy childhood in early
life denunciation the wedding did you
ever see some any other the beautiful
painting or how would you like how
something like this well personally you
did it's a nice set I'll be frank but
they saw mr Turner blimey I'm not trying
to the wife no but this may sound odd to
go but she's taken of change and say if
you notice i left my name I'm Catholic
and I believe in raising the children
yet but but I don't want that made kind
of push her us he said other words she's
a different religion and may ask you
this mr. bakery please understand i'm
just a Bible salesman I'm not a
theologian or missionary would it it
would please you if she were to come
into the faith and join a church am I
correct attached wallet I mean I'm gonna
be happy a bit there's a wonderful aroma
understand and say I don't want to
decide this year the man of the house so
this is this is for your own use but did
see what the point I'm trying to bring
up to you what's the effect i'll be
trying to force her because it's my
religion say well one would buying this
have anything to do with this knowledge
that the Catholic gets you may convert
so that's the point well actually that's
her decision and not mine I see your
point let me ask you this do you like I
took a sax lolazo do you think that it's
worth the money but it is what I'm if
the price when you receba did you manage
two and a half a week for like I
certainly could that be honest with oh
actually there's no reason then why you
shouldn't have it is it there's none for
make a fun one you want to pay this ten
amount then uh for couple dollars week
is no reason why well I'd like Sally
honey by the way but I'm his brother why
I think you could ask our songs to cut
down but i'm dani rhodes hurry part of
the bag is your issue you did I was
bothered by taste my problem did you i
was thinking of this but I'd have to ask
my wife you're his brother law he's my
father loved not notice not his father
or no no no you saw it in your just his
brother-in-law yeah yeah do you work for
him haven't had the best buddies on the
world what do you live here or anything
where do you live oh yeah I live right
here soon if you did wasn't us it kind
of hurt me because I think she'd like it
but the other thing I don't think I'll
be pushing up because I think would have
a father for the children that and he
brought up a very good point it's not
anything non self and i didn't i think i
will try it yeah i was just thinking
that statue of it that's that didn't
cost anything like essences well I think
I the people with that yeah just a
minute brother Martin are you trying to
help me if you are I could do without so
much to help I Oh wonderful I thought
you did i'm glad you clarified that very
good no good I'm glad
you don't have charity right thank you
very much and we'll get on with this do
you want aight oh well then quit make an
excuse just sign right now ok uncle I
wanna play some time to figure it quick
they're gonna start writing mr. Baker
hey is this st on it that's the good one
part of random after all you get have
everything brand-new you don't want to
blot on your discussion let go to work I
want to get gone you know I'm taking off
like a bird okay okay sir not be
hospital ready to go tell me where you
got that Irish bro and before you left
to her knee did your mother yes and that
it'll touch your bro denied in our part
of Ali's father phone when he was young
he says mr. Brennan how do you came
right from our nieces oh yeah yeah if
you're smashing oasis you'll join the
fast and catch a pension oh hi DD haha
this is a drawing breath of a man God
god bless him he's over there he's he's
giving read in that 70 you get a big
head of stone oh you in the father said
he'd never seen anything like that
hedstrom a beautiful headstrong I can
see him now and this year and a farm
with the shiny button yeah yeah
then another tournament an inattentive
antena de never defended internal
antenna derivative than an inanimate a
fitness 4320
gold
opelika City Hall
Kara's at boulevard
bad me can you tell me what hundred
eighteen street is you're just instead
of jog to the left Joc to the right yeah
jokes are the right down there yeah okay
so thank you
Jack to the right
but likable of that
do you know 118 street is I think you
get all this in this place little fucker
hey I hope alarcon this is all bellaco
business well yeah I see thank you sir
hunger through all over here ok sir
yeah he shows some dad avex in bed to
sail it that's it so dad
Wiz
opa-locka City Hall
damn it aah
can tell when 18 18 d needy
118 street how does that go into a
terrace 118 terrace that isn't what I
want where the hell is 118 street Jesus
Christ boy this this should be located
so that you'd go to Street after Street
so I'm looking for twentieth Street no
2020 fares 23rd 22nd jagoff down here
reason jagoff Jesus jagoff for that
there's two different straits on one
Street and then I was in a Muslim
district what our Muslim district what
we mean by another muffin well no matter
how can you have over did you catch this
puppy no no I wasn't him I was one
district candid a street and pull Sinbad
and what kind of stuff is this alibaba
applauding things anyone kind of stuff
that he Open Sesame all I could think it
was very tense you don't want to move
cattle deficit he stops fairy tale it's
not the bum territory just a bum in the
territory let me told anybody like that
I mean they'd say you were drinking
again just can't canada i canta hello
Sinbad road if this thing is stupid cuz
every time you go on the street there's
a canal now a railroad on over here put
are their graveyard ok glass over loca
follow Christ the guy too late this city
out
when we forced to go coffee what the
fakirs cow it's a pleasure to meet a
nice guy like Pete and thinks that my
cooking is the best to believe
take that cream away from the rabbit and
paste it down here yep oh do you know
that's a pic yeah I got on my buddy bull
yesterday i want to kiss and make out
with him he pouted at me for about three
minutes if you do that then I'll really
get well I don't want to give nobody
hard time but I just want everybody to
realize the potential is here and we got
a job to do and i dont no more excuses
you know Jesus I we come down here to
work and if you kid yourself and say
well it ain't there it can't be done if
you sell it short that's the main thing
then then you're in trouble but today we
want to hit a murder wrap this up soon
as poppin heading along you out Jen here
ok Bo when you eat like your successor
many are called but few are chosen the
Gipper a rabbit the ball and myself they
all bear the names of different types of
animals the rabbit is a very impulsive
guy he sells he has a lot of energy and
he's young doesn't help there possibly
the class of that the other salesmen
have maybe it's because he hasn't have
the maturity the spray no its revised it
teaches the children get in color yes
they spent a long time to revise it it's
not complex I don't understand Barry
wedding did you know you know I I know
the Ambassador things the principles I
understand you but I miss many things
that's why I fake if you notice Jerry
very slow yes could you say what does it
help the family I mean honestly could
you see what this had helped the
children and Frank and yourself could
you suggest so what I'm trying to
explain the stages could you see what
this would be a value in the home again
true yo could you say well does it help
could you see what the Bible is nice no
I understand you you find your point but
um really I don't seem we can now maybe
later i interested later but right now I
don't know I understand your point
enough no you just pay a night right yes
we do take on us what you heard us
you're gonna be very enclosed wait here
today Matt we do we do take ladders well
then you're gonna be imposed we take the
others what orders well then we take
others on the new missile I'll do you go
for mass yes we have one finally to do
with all the changes do you understand
my point no mr. page' you go to Mass
fight yes sandy yeah what do you think
now that I'm Nestle
right yes you're not a follow the praise
yeah we take on designer but no one
they're released finally mm-hmm good for
you say in other words on the mess hall
you've been an ass yes they're released
um we take a listen you're not for
master missile yes I don't have one yeah
we have done no one with all the changes
yes you know all the echo medical
changes in the minute we don't have them
available finally yeah after all two
years so would you like one no like the
world you can drum and he's a big
powerful man and he's got a lot of
stamina probably hasn't got the
technique that Charlie has but he said
he makes up for that for the salute the
stamina I would love to but I really
don't have the time now and I couldn't
possibly take on anything at the moment
I'm lucky I meeting right now in order
history told the whole library of other
people were impressive on with the Bible
but I couldn't even take on if it was a
dollar a month I couldn't even take it i
have always sorry okay thank you anyway
and this is the Catholic one yes that's
the revised delirious how much is
something like well we have different
bindings of like explaining ah well with
the least expensive big well can I ask
you this do you have a member i could
show you for the whole library if you're
interested without have a whole library
not necessary if you want the filagra
fine if they want just the Bible of
wonderful yeah you want to come in
please
comes back to the old adage it's
ninety-nine percent perspiration and one
percent information you got to get out
there and you gotta push push push push
push once you've lost that push you've
had it the Gipper is a an emotional
straight man he does his sellin is a
cleanly effective extremely effective
because he knows how to take advantage
of everything in any circumstances and
they were honest opinion you ever ever
seen a more beautiful not only something
play know intimately this comes in the
white or red we find most the folks
choose normally how are you gonna do
you're gonna write yes dari with that
point my shorty doll no it's not it to
me Oh it'll be nice month for evening
derivations place sure I make it for two
months pay for it with Tom sure it's up
to yourself so the mail out at your
convenience in other words we can't be
in everyone's going when it would be
more oriented so much how much would we
have to start with just the one payment
or wouldn't you want listen basically to
happen soon it's a nice party because
they have no collectors nobody come see
at home well anytime you want a leopard
80 Sony you can they leave it up to ya
oh you don't want anything promised yeah
just the esc sayin otherwise they have
the a B or C plan yeah see this is
suggested Oh awesome let me ask you this
what part of that can you apply on it I
can't be any cash today yeah how about a
trike now we have checking the only cash
me out of the house has ps4 into a
friday that's 10 high skoo tree I'll
tell you guys that's it alright a lot of
guys welcome into
yes let's say well gee I have the
insurance money the milk man's money eh
I can always see them now everybody's
pain right gonna can I just make one
more suggestion I've had this happened
an awful lot of times no oh uh potato
you haven't she knows what I'm gonna say
that's it what am I gonna say boy you're
so far out for somebody if you know I
mean I should know them you know but if
you've been here long enough you know
usually I tell me the way my neighbors
were shape the way are you talking to me
one of us could repossess their ass lick
slower how do you mind if I say
something Charlie all right ahead so
what they use it i'll say this is what
they suggest no more my office but we
actually meet the people we know the you
know things goodnight sincere legal but
we don't want to ask you axel what part
of the sea could your product fine who's
the bookkeeper could you put down as
little as six yeah wait on the end of
the way well you know now until one said
one of the men from the calc impressive
that you like this fellow mr. Brennan
for our brilliant hmm and that yes he
said you may have read about him in the
Catholic News I'll send Paul by to pick
up the down payment as a matter of fact
it on I've seen him do in one day five
different times he's laid out ten
dollars for five different people 15
hours and while the reason for their
season a third is fanatical but he's
very devout the very devout Catholic me
he feels that every Catholic family
should have this hahaha did I get a kick
out of him he's a character that yeah
she was a wonderful guy he keeps the
ball going wrong what's this one 21st in
one yeah 10 10
I think we got us you feel like
something like this in the home would be
helpful mrs. Gorman you know I mean will
you you seem like a pretty mature woman
you feel something like this would be
actually you know I morel family get
together well I'm all by myself so much
I place this Bible with a woman that had
close to 15 Bibles to know what she said
she received a lot of solace of just
looking at the pictures and she was a
woman had a PhD I had a cum laude myself
come no more from one of the ecology my
brother's little difference magna cum
laude demand would come no more when he
was going to school is classify as a
genius and so I followed him in school
and when they came to me that you
everybody used to say it but where did
you come from far you know so where you
know I get kind of an inferiority
complex and course when I get married
that made it worse but anyway at would
you be kind enough to write out your
address well I don't have any years I
had to read the bar well let me say this
i tol was one woman said she should
believe you me paused he said well I
mean host attend they call me Pauling
mr. Brennan but to me I don't think it
titled it missed it means anything but
what is your first name mrs. going
Christine CH I did you / see you
Cristiano that's a very honest chr is
sta yeah and I spy dollars a mile could
you make that 795 and make it even
alright do now I'm putting the five
dollars that's it I'm gonna cut this
down a three on the civic yeah you've
been very lovely and I know what it is
named joy tire whether you took the
Bible he didn't a kitchen it's very
enjoyable talk to you thank you and this
is not the Irish plan he believes this
comes right from the Hat they had an
arson you did do yeah my mother was a
Protestant denomination I don't know
actually what denomination you I sir but
she belong the High Church of England
yeah and she was the roughest that you
were i mean i SAT email right says
you're supposed to be English I said you
know Jenny they're a little more
complacent a little
acid I said but I said you've got
Spanish blood in you it's nothing but he
had a fiery temper but well I tell you
one thing is this she I'll ever forget I
cause my father never hit me in his life
he never stuck me in his life and my
mother really massacre I guess I I
really needed it and I always thought I
never got enough beatings wow are you
imagine your mother was pretty strict no
no sugar ball she was real how about you
firebomb how'd you get you huh well he
not his girls I might hit the boys but
girls he fished shook up a little kiss
you come but the boy she really beat up
yet when Rama Rama one laddie yeah yeah
would you mind right you're naming your
address right yes you haven't even told
I don't have my glasses that's all right
c which try this try these er see how
those that Anna you just use reading
glasses of it you're a lovely home here
well simple good enough no father
rallying father silo and all over there
by the Sullivan yeah we co some money
nigga the woods you know oh yeah sure
custom jamaica plain most in a min they
say they bought it for a pot of beans
and a jack tonight honey will you come
sometime oh by golly let me shake again
they have the raynham race track down
there and all about and that's you'll
have to have the zip code you have it on
your 20 30 5 4 3 30 54 you can tell who
does all right in round okay now he's
got my signature on I guess I laughter
but yeah all right sure you look like a
cash bread and gun he aware that handout
he should have better prospects cruise
you know what you have you have a sense
of human which most people lack in magic
idea g-man and my job I have to have a
sense of humor he don't you go nuts yeah
how long you'll with with the Sanitation
to 12 and a half here oh and a half here
and as I said before the port and
powders have it
because if it's not bless you will not
get the benefit out of it you know
yeah I can't come over to pick up um I
don't want because he's already mailed
me out on that he did ya see that she
had appreciated I mean I don't want to
sing but he already may only on sound
the district manager and so I've already
put it out arena honestly i'd appreciate
you know it's something that you're
really about yeah i know we and six
months from now lemme face it was good
off it won't be a separation you got a
lovely set because it tends with the
full endorsement other church no I
promised my husband one at all I charge
mr. McDevitt with the audit because i
have to do otherwise the class to the
mailing and the handling and everything
was the book keep and i have to give
them a painter penalty i don't like to
do it but that's the way the castle
that's just the penalty yeah yeah well I
jadon 725 okay I have no control of that
despot else ah you call me tonight and I
won't be here dear see I've got to move
out into another there so I made a
special call over here today well there
any place I can call you around five
after he cums no ma'am I'm gonna be in
Jacksonville you love the books one that
delivered okay all right thank you did
these tires i tell you
oh yeah what i would do is that before I
even dragged that icon jack is an all
the angle oh wow I'm pretty proficient
in all departments
I'll tell you one thing here I do find
that the people are very weak you know
not bad no there's ever very adaptive
blood I got something you know what I
mean I did I am 11 guy wouldn't even
come to the door but you can expect one
of them where were you worried GG with a
lot of courtesy and a lot of respect
what's a lot better than a gallon
Boulevard in Boston they're not gonna
Boston are you that's your oh well I'd
bless me still haha how except to it
believe you me I'll tell you truthfully
I'm three hopes it if I can sick Nance
I've been away quite a while Kenny with
them more days four days I'm along let
me stay is it for days it's lying let's
say when do we leave she's like four
weeks yeah but I made not call us to
know this territory is good hi Jim how'd
you do nice house I won't know how the
rare it done oh that's all bad i got a
couple yeah right got himself I got a
couple it's all on a single I call on
one woman she's our Mickey you know and
don't like your video romance inning
when I came up oh I would get up ahead
of would I try to develop a co do that
you know and go for self and then
getting that 50 80 out of you know
that's nice silver for my pussy yeah
when we stay had ten of them a day
believe you me i tell you this way i say
ten a week it'd be happy i had a flat
tire to begin with you know I don't give
me excuses but I'm glad you clarified it
it's that selective about tomorrow but
I'd like to get a very early stat and
see where I can bang out a good day you
know really push it out in about four
chords and I'll be all set all right
we'll see good morning mr. Brennan from
the church mrs. Gloria for how are you
today
you either interested or not interesting
on to me I'm very sorry with my sister
just gold and she's waiting for me right
now I'm very sorry okay okay good to see
what it should be helpful to your missus
oh it's really boy can afford Oh tis
here tis is she gonna be amazing I tell
you know you see like anything else to
afford something like this as they say
it's not like buying a new cat you know
I get it I place this in Home has it
been 18 and 19 so you know what glass
through his maths the fishermen at sea
places one more month 18 children and
believe in me as they say it wasn't easy
but in this life if you have a desire
for anything you'll get it isn't that
true table where does a willders away
that's what that's what Charlie Gipper
says you know you probably heard of him
Notre Dame zacapa mm-hmm well somebody
new games well let me put it this way
there were a lot of folks in this world
it's been thousands of dollars on
material things but what I mean is this
do you love it hey you love it see I
have one heinous mask was it was about
oh that's all right but I mean do you
think you'd appreciate that mrs. kaushik
I have been seeing we just see that I
don't see us all right now you're the
breadwinner right you're thinking I
never did it yeah we then I mean as they
said before I could ask you one thing is
this you think the dollar they would
really hurt you i wouldn't want to place
it if you couldn't afford is your
william him by then now you can't go on
santa for that darling three more than
the house and I'll yeah yeah yeah well
we're all up to here I'm over here leave
that I don't believe you can wait on me
you're gettin it on say it yeah well the
only thing i can so sorry that you make
big family no no no no where your about
you yeah I bitching nothing like my
business myself I can clean them with it
oh you do you're so friggin cleaners you
scrape them up but yeah yeah that's
there so we score from up to when you
were sale then you'll know
you know I had a vacuum salesman kind of
my wife you know but he's through all
the dirt over the floor and then he
walked out and he didn't scoop it up you
know even need a new bag I don't know
but oh I guess that's the thing and
everything if you don't scoop it up you
don't win it and then that you need
about new bags problem yeah and with
that I will say 400 ooh but because they
have at hand more less more class to
make
hi mrs. O'Connor mr. Brennan from the
church how are you today this is on a
display we have it to church only take a
minute can I ask you this question and I
know what you're going to say what part
of the set do you like the best which
part of this complete glad you do you
like the best what's do I like the best
yeah Oh which would you consider which
would you say is the basic part of the
library or with something which it would
appeal to you all that you drive the
most out of I personally think the Bible
that's right that's the most people shit
oh and of course i have one that i
wouldn't part with for years for nothing
yeah I've had I have more like here's
that uh we liked to my mother-in-law and
I don't know where she got it from I
have to go fan the old family guy bit us
over 200 years old then oh I'd say close
two hundred anyway oh no by no means of
a pad with a Bible I have one myself but
my husband said his mother-in-law his
mother read to me every single day out
of that right now well racially it's
something not shut the metal well your
collage true well I could see where you
would choose the Bible and I tell you
the reason why the Bible that's why the
Bible is the best-selling oh well well
actually I can't see buying another
Bible when I already have one even only
200 years old well you're probably tight
now is that correct oh it's for sure
yeah cause they say it's the only thing
that I know that you secure in a
lifetime that doesn't appreciate I got
after three years is worth noting a
battle like that will Billy something to
look really build up a heritage in the
home it's a girl football isn't
beautiful I know you'll love it
honest-to-goodness mrs. O'Connor I've
been in the Bible vision out the reason
I minute I know that I'm placing
something older people will never be
satisfied the longer they have it the
more they will enjoy it it's like a good
wine with age it improves and don't
worry they don't repossess the Bible is
for months you don't smell in the famil
mail them came in the floor a month
that's uh oh marie you've been on that
phone long enough and if you didn't like
it mrs. O'Connor I wouldn't spend the
time but most of people that I do place
are with the Irish people because
there's a very devout Catholic you know
yeah man that I just well it doesn't
make any difference are you not Irish
descent yeah what the sin how you do
polish polish well the polish of good
people I I know a lot of good polish
people they're very devout Catholics to
it doesn't make any difference but the
Irish I happen to place an awful lot
would because I'm a virus you know
heritage myself but I as they said
before don't don't think I in Worcester
I had quit at all a polish accent
believe you me replace more Bibles and
you can shake a thicket who everything
that's life is a sacrifice that's right
how about six months from now don't know
what's expense is gonna bring well
nobody knows what the next day is going
to come you know that's why I don't tell
and I want to take the chance include my
saloon me too much for chance it
involves 4995 for the Bible Michigan
home and that's not much you know what I
mean Tanner cigarettes a week crash your
three dollars just dad have a birthday
coming up
well I'm sorry not at this particular
time you want to reserve it for any
later day cuz I don't know what's gonna
well nobody knows the only thing we're
sure it was general tactic right no I
also get better cook myself I also can't
see my way clear tour right now how
about in three six nine or twelve months
you're still couldn't see your way clear
oh I also get better take it at this
time
well I don't think that any more I can
add to us mr. O'Connor I imagine make a
lot of decisions it's like I know my oh
yes you have to you have to that's for
sure that's for sure all right like
anything else I think this would be a
wise decision but that you ever you know
the circumstances were different I'd say
yes I wouldn't hesitate because it is a
beautiful piece of it well I mean
actually is it the dollar week this
won't happen huh I mean I don't
understand really honest to god I bazan
Bibles a 10 year I don't understand
about a week no it doesn't sound like a
much but there's other things that I've
got to take care of first before I can
start but not another 45 hours a week a
month a month rather out as to whether
many other ones hmm I've gotta pay up
first okay then
I'll beat your phone on the dolmen
sometimes I undergo thank you for your
time that's all right that's my job hi
mrs. counter mr. Brennan from the church
oh this is my associate mr.
really
yeah I was just wondering why you left
your name you know me thank you get the
time and no money wants you give me a
name after four years of trying to find
where's the advisor throw them in the
river that way this is worse than toy
hey Parker mutt here if I don't say yeah
relax i'm into this arrow here don't
know no well I mean I got haven't
changed around I'm not working anymore
after those very eyes I'm working the
way I want to work I went away I want to
go out for like cuz that this thing is
that I'm I'll i should be yet killed
myself when the thumbs this is
absolutely no good go my palm safe a go
so what
tanda fires and get a pension what do
you think just sit there how I'm Nikki
I'll you Mickey Mickey lead this is
Lynch your private time at each end the
path that gets attention oh this guy
here like him it's one Bible in the cpe
Catholic people's encyclopedia which
plan would be the best view well I have
to get it for six a month and this is
where you put your name right here
that's where I steinlight John Henry we
got a new record here the other day my
love these Beatle songs
tape there's a better
then a fair watching element
Oh longer
you
the correct
when the first
the first
that's just like the money
now four weeks after you receive about
the new nail
with the first
he's just like 20
go to
one in Chicago one in charlotte knocked
down and you'll give her the envelopes
good month deceptive
at the office furniture 2097 will be
drivin that's that and then enjoyed the
visit all right I know you'll enjoy the
Bible and yeah I'm sorry to hold you up
in here I'm gonna make my he's and
husband
I gotta go to work at all the clocks off
I'll take it at work at night so he can
read it while he's do another good night
doing nothing my good looks like what do
you like I do at night oh you're riding
around in that car and a chilly night
like this thanks to getting up
hello Paul what happened you get a
haircut yeah did you get a haircut I get
a shot you look like a shrine hunt I get
a thin one I get a thin one
what happened to your stomach
and break right away
mark how the belt off
yeah I went through the no trouble
finding any of the places how many
pictures i meet all day
we can't get cattle I'm way they get
Collins up there I might be able to
knock out for Chrome whatever no ash I
can't of the action I can't see any
deals here every time I every time I get
in the house all I hear is I mean the
pressure at the door and you know real
rough these make you feel rough really
rough does your fight you know you found
out that probably similar to yourself I
find he and if you analyze it you don't
have that many Catholic see if we don't
have that many Catholic one church
because a hell of a wide area and it's
not that god damn it as they say and how
many times you have to go back on it to
get these people in well I went through
whateleys like is this right to attend
haunted I think of a Bingle to be with a
finger love him
I've analyzed it myself and I think
there are areas the rich air is a tough
they're right but believe me we forget
in there yet the point you have no
trouble with that money and you can
shoot a quitter you know it doesn't
break because what the hell they can
shoot the money up did it got money to
work with I'm not thinking negatively
would I even if I get caught a week
saying at 10 or 11 sales I would be
happy with it Eve yeah it spoken yep all
you're in a bed frame of mind you have
no royal couple of weeks it could be
served of talking these people are often
oh you fight them they can spotted a
mile off
you got a week into a good production
under your belt you'll be okay
wanting to see be four kids hitter with
the backhoe ate too much money yeah
the husband
I never be wrong and I can't say
and
we place the venom all for as little as
forty nine ninety five complete he's not
amazing this will all be changed pretty
soon on it no are you with the nice i
only name no he's not carefully but I
mean he follows me right
I appreciate honesty guys we got your
home when it's a mixed marriage we find
us in many cases the husband is much
more than throws too often times than we
even this cradle Catholic which was
something that children's encyclopedia
instead of this yeah well let me put it
this way now that's none of your
children would ever get a sunburn or
they'd never get it called unless they
were exposed to a draft they did never
get a sunburn let's do exposed to the
Sun the mere fact that they were exposed
to a thing oh you think oh they're gonna
receive somebody benefits from it they
have to you know because if it never
does the money go to load over the hump
kind of fancy bottle for each other man
what a me miss do this for them and well
not any young saying that they'll be
exposed to write in what manner looking
at it all may interject just say one
thing the hand that rocks the cradle
rules the world is that right it's a
woman behind every great man there's a
good woman as she spends the corner of
the Reader's Digest about eighty-five
percent with the children now whatever
she is and what she impacts to them is
how those children are going to grow up
and this is the age when they need it
because of your house doesn't have a
foundation you've got no kind of a house
does that make sense there we are there
we exactly what there we are and we have
them white and red and we give it in any
color that you might like and that's
another thing to the Bible is the
heritage of life and so when you come
right down I know the price is something
that doesn't enter in it off it's the
utility of it and believe you me i think
you both have to agree that you have the
utility there is that true or isn't
that's all we have to say it's the way
anything is designed as to what effect
you we get from it i just feel sorry
and demonstration oh I was outside I was
running a little stale anyway and I had
to wear this is why I'm taking mr.
Bremen are really see if I it's sort of
spark him up a little practice are you
shocked the way down yeah you see here's
to write it if I recall that at one time
fallen you prime you're right 12 a week
but it dropped away darkness pray I said
what he says what's the moment mr.
McDevitt and I said well koala I think
it your room negative negative and I
think this is what you need one spark
and I think someone should take out a
spark you up is it show you how the
people will look like this yeah I'm not
doing this to embarrass you Paul believe
me well sometimes it isn't a spot you
need an explosion they will say gonna do
thank you very much oh thank you very
much
yeah join the flash and get a pension no
siree gloss merely she works for the
telephone get a lot of stocks they're
hard-working ad working people and
working
Sammy's been working in the police fast
now the boy he retires he gets a pension
as i whispered I
go
back buddy