how shall I begin my story that has no
beginning in these averages my great
grandfather raised cattle before the
angles ever came our roots go deep in
this place deeper than the pines deeper
than the mine shafts this is my village
when I was a child it was called San
Marcos the Angeles changed the name to
zinc town zinc town new mexico u.s.a
this is our home
the house is not ours but the flowers
the flowers are ours my name is
Esperanza Esperanza Quintero
I am a miner's wife 18 years my husband
has given to that mine living half his
life with dynamite and darkness
the land where the mine now stands that
was owned by my husband's own
grandfather now it belongs to the
company
who can say when it began my story I do
not know at least they I remember as the
beginning of an end it was my saints day
I was 35 years old a day of celebration
and I was seven months gone with my
third child
and on that day I remember I had a wish
I thought so sin I thought so evil that
I pray to the Virgin to forgive me for
it I wished I wished that my child would
never be born no nothing to this world
is a planet no I balita i said i will
going to church right and fashioned
later when I free me child
fighting again with those Anglo kids oh
they think they're tough but you
promised me you wouldn't Papa sighs if a
neighbor makes funny and to let him have
it never mind what your proper code
steel
does it hurt
I've come the cake never mind a cake go
get your father when he comes off shift
that we could come straight home
he had trouble quintero defective fuse
well you're all in one piece so it's a
beat you know the beef this new rule of
yours that we work alone we're taking it
up with a super super is busy with your
negotiating committee so much the better
now wait a minute supers one made
through he ain't gonna give you no help
he will if he wants us to go on blasting
read your contract I'll get somebody to
read it for you they don't say nothing
about no help there's a mr. Barton
there's blood in that mine the blood of
my friends all because that work alone
that's how you get splattered over the
rocks when there's nobody have to check
to you nobody to wonder other men to
stay clear warnings a ship Foreman's job
Palmer wants to get the ore out minor
wants to get his brothers out in one
piece you work alone savvy you can't
handle the job I'll find someone who can
who was cab an American
man ma not a word about the cake here
Papa is there going to be a strike come
on I don't like to bother you but the
story they say that day we don't make
another payment on their ready this
month they'll come and take it away we
are only one payment behind I argued
with her it isn't right he didn't write
you face was it right that we bought
this this instrument but you had to have
it didn't you it was a nice to listen to
I listen to it every night when you're
out the beer partner no money down easy
turn payment I tell you something this
installment plan it's a curse of the
working man
where are you going gotta talk to the
brothers
this waters cold again I'm sorry the
fire for not forget it forget it I took
with forest oh five times a day every
time I remember I remember that across
the tracks the anglo- hot water in pipes
in bathroom inside do you think I like
living this way for you out of it but if
your Union that you're asking for better
conditions why can't you ask for decent
flaw me too we did got lost in the
shuffle quiet we can't get everything at
once right now we have more important to
match what's more important than
sanitation
safety of the men that's more important
five accidents this week all because of
speed up you're a woman you don't know
what it's like a prayer first we gotta
get equality on the job then we'll work
on these other things give it to the men
I see and then your strike maybe for
your demands I've heard wife want that
sons later always later now don't you
start talking against the Union again is
it but me your Union speranza have you
forgotten what it was like before the
Union came when Estella was a baby and
we couldn't even afford a doctor when
she was sick it was for our families we
met in graveyard to bill that Union all
right heavier strike I'd have my baby
but no hospital will take me because I
just Rikers wife stole cut off our
credit and the kids would go hungry
we'll get behind on the Pens again and
they're coming take away their radio is
that all you care about that radio can't
you think of anything except yourself is
I think of myself it's because you never
think of me he never knew stop it the
children are watching stop it
that's wrong it has to be taken care of
the company will always tell you those
things we know it's not safe for minors
to work alone but they don't work alone
in other mind angles always working
there so why should I risk my life cuz
I'm a Mexican that's in the demands when
evo she ate three months of negotiations
nothing happens even with brother bars
here from the International what have we
got no raise no seniority no safety code
nothing take your true cut my dick I say
we've gotta take action now rest man
feel the way you do you talk for all of
us did you ever stop to think maybe the
waters to strike little one will strike
but with a war boom on and why is the
company hanging tough it's signed
contracts for the other locals find out
this one because most of us you're a
mexican-american he called we want
equality with angle minor the st. bade
thing conditions exactly inequalities
the one thing the boss is can't afford
the biggest club they have over the
angle locals is well at least you get
more than the Mexico okay so
discrimination hurts the angle to me but
it hurts me more and I've had it none of
it but you don't fully strike when the
bosses wanted so they can smash your
Union you wait till you're ready so you
can win the divorces wait no sanitation
so my kids gets a key to the company
doctor wait twenty bucks so we miss one
payment on the radio bought from my wife
the company's 12-8 bail would take it
away why is the bosses store and led to
her find us Kara's that's why to make us
afraid to move to hang on to what we got
it like it well I don't like it and I'm
not scared now fed up to here éremon
Davis gun
what are you doing here I'm being wrong
with mama I thought maybe you forgot
forgot watch its run the saints day but
a kid he can't wait it's my wife same
state I was going to ask you brothers
how bottom will you need uh huh what
time 1mon Anita later the better
why'd you soon I thing ever to light the
candle yeah now we can write account
Tony
I mean I'm into it the game crusher weep
for joy I'm a fool
was it expensive the beer Antonio paid
for it freaking container inside of me I
did forget Louie's told me
all the next week I kept thinking about
my man Anita I have never had some nice
party it was like a song running through
my mind a daydream to lighten the long
day's work 1 2 3 we all forgot our
troubles at the man yanita even Ramon I
couldn't dance that night not in my
condition but I wasn't really jealous
when he danced with the others because
it was a good just a second smile again
and then one morning I was hanging out
my wash
and while we were talking the ladies
came they were a kind of the location it
was about a sanitation they said the
angle miners have bathrooms and hard one
in water why shouldn't we this mini ROK
zangoose toast in an hour contigo en sus
casas por que nosotros no I know I spoke
to Ramona bout it only way click on he
said they dropped it from the genome
demands he is not a siempre we've got to
make him understand make the man's face
up to it Jorah the sign will make a lot
of sense like this then we'll get all
the wife's together and go right up to
the mines to the mine sure where they're
negotiating in the company office will
go up there and pick up the place then
both sides will see we mean business
epica Chinese ladies sure why not you
can count me in booth listen we ought to
be in a war choppers Union chop wood for
breakfast chop wood washes clothes chop
wood epr chop wood scruffers chop wood
Caucus dinner and do you know what he
will say when he comes home what have
you been doing all day reading funny
papers come on les parents how about it
we got no no I can't if Ramon ever found
in a picket line with what pic you know
mr. Polinsky
how did this happen he wanted into a
drift when that felt was blasted I told
you it would happen it's gonna happen
when a man works alone why did you give
the man a warning signal your Foreman
says that's a farmer's job I'll shake
the drift just before he blasted was all
clear and that must've been asleep or
something you weren't even there you
were back at the station Kaminski told
me you're alive poncho no-good dirty
yeah get a hold on yourself man's been
hurt I'm sorry about it as you are savvy
accidents are costly to everyone to the
company most of all I see no reason to
treat the occasion like a paid holiday
suppose we all get back to work
rotten all right now there's the
excitement's over let's get to it I
water trail see why they saying no savvy
Barnes what of honor tell him how to get
back to work they don't work for me I
worked for them Reese
it's up to you brothers z 366 see
that night they men held a union meeting
just to make the workout official it
didn't take them long they voted to
strike 93 25 and Theresa said now was a
time for us to go in I didn't want to I
have never been to a union meeting at
the other said one go elko tenemos
varias a grados hermanos y muchas de
bandas pero todo esto se puede para un
punto basic oh my evil dad the meeting
was nearly over when we came in Charlie
Vidal was making his pitch he said there
was only one issue in this strike
equality but the mine owners would stop
at nothing to keep them from getting
equality dvd-r Ilan loss there may make
an American he said the bosses would try
to split the Anglo and Mexican American
workers and offer rewards to one man if
he would sell out his brother hermanos
solamente una defense a contra de esta
tactica esto es una dad la unidad de
toros hombres trabajadores
yes you ladies have an announcement
announcement ideas only the ladies
wanted me to our control Oh will you
speak from over here
the ladies have been talking about
sanitation and we were thinking is the
issue is equality like you say it is
then maybe we ought to have equality in
plumbing too I mean maybe we could make
it a striking me some of the ladies
thought it might be a good idea to have
a very sexy jury well we'd like to help
out if we can I think I can speak for
all the brothers in saying we appreciate
the ladies offering to help but it's
getting late and I suggest that we
tangle it the chair will entertain a
motion to adjourn I second all those in
favor opposed sorted
national plan why didn't you support her
you're the worst of a lot but there is a
you can't push these things too fast you
were pushing all right put your nose
right back in our place why didn't you
change this thing with me it's
embarrassing at least UD make a fool of
yourself like one swallow it's not a bad
idea to make sanitation one of our men's
honey or why don't you just put a sign
outside no dogs no women allowed
and so I again much like any other
strike there would be no settlement the
company said till them and return to
their jobs at the back to work movement
didn't work and so the company recruited
a few strikebreakers from out of town
but they usually lost their nerve and
they saw the size of the picket line a
shirtless men were always there they
stood around showing off their weapons
but the men only marched day after day
week after week at first it was an
unwritten rule that the women stay at
home the Union gave us rations and we
had to figure out how to feed our
families on them but then one morning
mrs. Alice I went to the picket line her
husband had been killed in a strike many
years before and she wanted to be there
nobody remembers just how it happened
but one day mrs. Salazar started
marching with them and she kept on
marching with them
after a while some of the women began to
bring coffee for their husbands and
maybe a couple of tacos because a man
gets tired and hungry and picket duty it
was about that time that the Union
decided maybe they'd better set out the
Ladies Auxiliary after all I didn't come
to the lines at first my tan was near
and besides Rahman didn't approve but
Ramon is a man who loves good coffee and
he soared that the other ladies made it
taste like things watch so one day I
made a copy
faithful service can fit though MCM for
three days hey I moon listen to this
chief woman come to last night's a make
shift Foreman out at me if the snow it
back twerk movement Jenkins why string
along was him tamale I just said I come
like tamales fine those calves got
thrown the other side of the hill we
chased the rest back reckon item angle
smarter town but they're not miners I
could tell that they don't know is a
from shinola okay take five to get
yourself a cup of coffee arrow wrong
here comes the super
mornin how's it going well those new
Fellows you hide from out of town we
brought him up here but truck this morn
they took one look at that picket line
turn tail they don't look so rough to me
well mr. Hart where they've got some
pretty tough hombre there especially
that picket captain what's his name ray
Raymond something or other oh yes I know
that one that's their main picket line
have another post on the back road
roving patrols all over the place on
company property why don't you have them
thrown off his old company property mr.
heartland store of the housing area
everything are you gonna throw them and
who does the throwing well are they
gonna let us pass eventually this is
just a little ritual to impress us with
their power now why don't you let this
gentleman pass but you know who is in
that car the paymaster from Moscow with
our gold no no it depended on the
company himself come all the way out
here to make Jenkins general manager
childish well they're like children in
many ways sometimes you have to humor
them sometimes you have to spank them
and sometimes you have to take their
food away well here comes the one who
we're talking about he's quite a
character claims his grandfather once
owned the land where the mine is now
what have dropped your office mr.
Alexander naturally you think I park
here for a cup of coffee you're welcome
to one no thanks the men would like to
know who this gentleman is that's none
of their affairs oh all right it's no
secret my name's Hartwell I'm from the
company's Eastern office you mean
Delaware no new york new york you're not
the company president bandaged head no
too bad the men have always wanted to
take a look at the president to come out
here to settle the strike
oh if that's possible it's possible just
negotiate are we talking to a union
spokesman well not exactly well I wish
he were one he knows more about my name
when those PI cards we got to deal with
I mean it I know your work record you
were in line to performing when this
trouble started did you know that yeah
so you had a real future with this
company but let those register yup now
they'll sell you down the river why
don't you wake up ray huh that's your
name isn't it right my name is Quintero
mr. Quintero we gonna let us pass or do
I have to call the sheriff there's
nothing stopping you
I was wrong they don't watch Jenkins for
general manager they want me you should
have heard that fella what a line I was
up for a point moniece a FIFA thing
what's the matter it's nothing just a
little cut is that Louise what is he
doing playing hooky again we come back
brother yuan tonio fellow chesta come
with me the rapid return the line
they're dirty coal
yeah sarah young free and won't listen
to me for the love of God you you I'd
expect it of an angle you wanna be my
chamak had to get a job yoo-hoo that
bloodsucker come on my kids to trade or
a tu gente from farewell got my days
without alum you think my kids have
enough to eat you rack ha Noi's just a
lift off just let me go you think I was
gonna work you over
I wouldn't dirty my hands on you
baby get the women speak why do you stop
when I have a little talk with you or
you slug that fella back there but
that's a lie i didn't no way to talk to
a man so that said this bull fighter was
full of pepper don't look Stephanie now
over the years he's bullet chilly this
morning he likes it hot his Takeda makes
it good and hot went on she fought back
Chad we need a doctor quick there's
woman gonna have a baby you take me for
an ambulance driver there's a coven a
doctor we don't have a car you just get
him you kidding company doctor won't
come to no picket line
Cody had a poncho let's not wait is that
I'll not leave you all you like forgive
you should be never oh my god
Ramon was in the hospital for a week and
then in the county jail or 30 days
charged with assault and resisting
arrest but I made up my mind to postpone
the christening till he got out of jail
we christened him one that night we had
a double celebration Juanita's
christening Ramon's homecoming we put
all the children to sleep in the bedroom
as usual and the men took over the
parlor and zushi $5,000 athletes 25,000
dog all right this Hume ages work come
to Papa hear those deputies locked NT
yeah been lots of provocation lately
they figure if they can lock up the
leadership on some phony charge maybe
they can bust the strike are we gonna
let him play poker all night I want to
dance with her husband with any of them
even my own if you dance with my husband
you'll have to put up with this and
another thing your attitude towards
angles if you're gonna be a leader what
attitude you lump them all together
angler workers and angular bosses he's a
guest in my house isn't he you're even
suspicious of him maybe I think he's got
a few things to learn about our people
go on stir well movie organizer you work
out strike strategy and most of the
times are dead right
when you figure everything the rank and
file to do down to the last detail you
don't give us anything to think about
are you afraid we're too lazy to take
initiative even though I don't think
that maybe not but there's another thing
like when you came in tonight I heard
you ask you one whos that hes
grandfather that's what is the father of
Mexico if I wouldn't know a picture of
George Washington you would say I was an
awful dumb Mexican I've never seen it
fail try to give her a motor in front of
criticism and he kicks it right back in
your face no he's right I got a lot to
her now we've got that settled Gilda
card makes you feel any better he's got
even less use for women being about
discussing each other's weaknesses I
didn't know they had any all right now
Ramon's on the receiving end if we shut
out the women from the life of come on
bet let's break up that game we can't
think of them just as housewives but as
partners and we have to treat them as
such well look we are talking a new
wells champion of women's right I'll cut
it out Ruth me I'm a camp follower
following its organizer from one mining
camp to another Montana Colorado Idaho
but does he ever think to organize the
women know why does don't count the
Anglo locals either haha nothing I like
the way you treat your wife Ramon I
think you're all wrong but when dr.
burns here gives you his chair off for
female problems just ask him if he's
tried it at home hey Esperanza
esperanzas nursing the baby there goes
that game good console turn off the
radio come on pop up on your feet
look a fighter huh he was born sighting
in plank doing wanito you'll never have
it so good he'll have it good someday
what were they saying about you in there
they say I'm not good to you you are no
good to me in jail hot line my cell and
my cotton I couldn't sleep with a bugs
and the stinking the heat and not safe
to myself think of something nice
something beautiful and they're not
think of you in my heart would pound
against the cut for love of you not just
for nieto you'll have it good to
Esperanza we're gonna win the strike
what makes you so sure because if we
lose we lose more than a strike we lose
the union in the manhood and if we win
we win more than a few demands we win
something bigger hope hope for our kids
veneto can't grow strong and milk alone
this zero place what do you want got a
court order you can come in here with
other one we got the warrant to we don't
on trouble
we hate to break in on you folks like
this but listen fellow radials torn he
got himself a repossession order don't
touch it the or more trouble if you can
kill to get our just desserts this
machine I said don't touch it let them
fix it over my dead body I don't want a
dead body I don't want to fucking game
either but it's yours how old Adam can
see they want to satisfy so they can
lock you all up at one time what are
useful fair about let's have some real
music
but the strike did not end it went on
and on into the fourth month the fifth
the sixth a company still refused to
negotiate they try to turn the anglo-
against us they say that all Mexicans
are to be sent back where they came from
how can I go back where I come from but
check that I was money 500 company
property I don't know buddy I'll tell
the bosses go back where you come from
there would be any bosses of the state
of New Mexico 15 brother live to see the
day Jenkins ain't no boss mean we're
gonna let people like Gingka stay here
you can't send him back to Oklahoma it
would be inhuman but i was born in texas
oh no that's even worse and the seven
months came we couldn't buy food at a
company store
by now the strike phone was nearly gone
a few families couldn't take it any
longer and where they went we do not
know and so it was decided by the union
that hatchet cases should seek work in
other mines and this was done strikers
who found jobs divided their pay with
the Union so the rest of us might eat
Thurman was not a hardship case only
three children to feed even so the mine
owners might have started us out why not
for the help we got from the
international in Denver and from other
locals and we was thought no one outside
our county knew of our troubles or care
that they didn't know how we were wrong
letters came from our own people of the
southwest from far away beauty Chicago
Birmingham New York messages of
solidarity and the crumpled dollar bills
a working men
we women were helping and not just as
cooks and coffee makers a few of the men
made jokes about it but the work had to
be done so they let us stay no one knew
how great the change it was until the
day of the crisis a sheriff was smiling
so we knew he brought bad news
the company had got a court injunction
ordering the strikers to stop beginning
it tuft hartley injunction they called
it it meant heavy fines and jail
sentences for the strikers if they
disobeyed a decision had to be made at
once whether to obey the order or 19 if
we obey the court the strike will be
lost the scabs will move in as soon as
our picket line is gone if we defy the
court our pickets will be arrested and
the strike will be lost anyway so there
it is brothers the bosses have us coming
and going I just want to say this no
matter how you decide the international
will back you up as it's always backed
you up this is a Democratic Union the
decision is up to you
brother Sherman if we give up now if we
obey this rotten cap hardly we are fools
and cowards there is only one way vitam
by tomorrow come we don't gain nothing
elder hasta que no sirve este es todo lo
que les preocupa no se da cuenta que
estan arrest on donut onion-head wawa at
juan de toda la Nova de las mujeres amen
current they made brave speeches it
seemed that brother Barnes was right the
company had them coming and going it
seemed the strike was lost brother
chairman if you read the court
injunction carefully you will see that
the only prohibits striking miners
persnickety we women are not striking
miners we will take over your pickup
line
don't laugh we have a solution you have
none rather king said Oh was right when
you said well lose 50 years of games he
will lose this tripe your wife and
children too but these we promise if
women take your places on the picket
line the strike will not be broken and
no scabs will take your job if that's a
motion only members of the union could
make a motion I still move second you
have heard the motion the floor is open
for debate si el Presidente supremacy mo
skeletal mujeres en esta en este asunto
no vamos a convertir en la verdad todo
el momento Brer Oh hermano te Kyoko ESO
karma no fuera de nosotros ya no se
mancell connor o'donovan vatos so notice
compañeros yes your gustas him which
was worse to hide behind a woman's skirt
or go down on his knees before the boss
brothers we don't count enough on our
women the bosses don't count on them at
all well the bosses went now because
there is no unity between the men their
wives and their sisters
no creo que estaba la Senora Carlota
Sanchez said she didn't think vikatan
was proper for ladies it wasn't nice
maybe even a sin I say let's give the
sisters a chance and what will happen
when the cops come and bitter women up
are we gonna stand there and watch them
know we'll take over anyway and we'll be
right back where we started only worse
even more humiliated brothers brothers I
beg you don't allow that alright the
questions have been called you brothers
know what you are voting on that the
sisters of the auxiliary take over the
picket line all those in favor were so
signified private Chairman's point of
order I don't know anything about these
questions of Parliament's but you men
are voting on something the women not to
do or not to do so I think it's only
fair if the women be allowed to vote
especially if they have to do the job
brothers and sisters would be
unconstitutional to prevent women to
vote at a union meeting there's no
objection we could have turned this P no
no no wait wait and reconvene this
meeting as a community mass meeting with
every adult entitled to a vote I so move
all right on the motion to adjourn all
those in favor will raise your hand all
those opposed the eyes have it now
wherever you don't is entitled to a vote
on the original question all those in
favor that the sisters take over the
picket line were so signified by raising
their hand
all those opposed
the motion has carried the hundred and
three 285
and so they came the women they came
from sink town in the hills beyond from
other mining camps 10 20 30 miles away
women we have never seen before women
who have nothing to do with a strike
somehow they heard about the women's
picket line and they came and the men
came to I think they were afraid afraid
the women wouldn't stand fast or maybe
afraid they would but not all the women
went to the picket line some were
forbidden by their husbands I was one of
them it's not fair I should be there
with them after all I'm the one who got
the women the vote the Union don't run
my house those Anglo Dame's stirred you
up to make both of yourself but you
don't see any of them down there yes I
do there's ghosts spawns she's the
organizer quad she's gotta be there no
she wants to be there and businesses
kolinsky there's jenkins wife you don't
see her oh no picket line and your
husband's can also be backward can be
what awkward
can't I even put in an appearance with a
baby in your arms the baby likes to be
walked kept screaming Burke hey girl
wait a minute don't you almost leave on
pistol shut up what's so amusing they're
funny a court order I'm not sure about
that mr. Alexander better the law you
know all that injunction says he hasn't
no picket done by minors whose side are
you on anyway don't get excited they're
scattered i queer let's get at it for
another hundred ancien all right boys
what about these forget it they'll
scatter nyquil
you can tell yes I should they'll tell
you again
it
Oh
one
why are you standing there do something
relax but women are getting hurt we've
got to take over anyway looks like you
got your hands full
your ears on here we come up evil alien
ears on here we cannot be moved like a
free
fuck your mama she's gonna tell you
don't they run this boy did you see the
way mom what's that deputy not the gun
right what you hanging around there here
you're right sure
what's the things I'm experience for you
huh yeah I get you got enough to date
throughout your lifetime I'll come back
tomorrow listen you might get hurt I
might if you think I'm going to faint
nursemaid to know on your crazy I've had
this scheduled vague I've had them since
the day they were born I'm telling you I
don't stay home with this gift tomorrow
okay and tomorrow I take the piece with
me to the picket line
and so I came back the next day and
every day for the next month I kept for
anythin the coffee shack and when the
weather was good and there was peace on
the lines I brought his creep outside
Stella played with a lil ones and Ruth
Ruth was in school Ramon came every day
just watching the ladies well they could
asides from one from not keeping the
kids but then they cursed off insulted
us call those foul names it started
again
but you steered us again this time the
one was against us we spread out as we
had planned and I took the baby away
from the danger as we had planned
but they couldn't break our line they
couldn't break it
well I've tried everything but shooting
them down you haven't tried locking them
up you are them all arrested no just the
ringleaders that fire eaters ones with
big families Barton where's that boy hey
you come here All Right girls I'm gonna
give you a choice go home I'll go to
jail no ifs ands or buts get off the
picket line there get arrested
okay point him out that one that is her
son she's a leader you're under arrest
home of the hoosegow what's let thee
kept marching sisters let's just um
discipline but Teresa no charges were
resisting arrest kept merchant sister
skip merchants
you
mrs. al-assad yogen shah oviya peruano
to tres news poor Alice Darwin
mrs. condensed query Anglo
Ruth bond she organizes way
and Don Alvarez the pretty one and that
one with the daily sheesham on can tell
us why he doesn't like her being here
she's gonna babies brother don't worry
about finito we can take care of Stella
to know the baby stays with me
I told you 10 times we have no we have
no beds we have no bags so will you
please shut up us a fool I sure don't
we'll get to me the baby can't drink
this stormy if we want a new formula you
want a lot the formula the formula
well you can get the JP to swear out
peace bonds or you can nice the bail
high enough to keep in jail keep them
what am I supposed to do feed him out of
my own pocket well I want to know mr.
Hartwell is when you're going to settle
this thing you want the go she ate both
what do you want anyway how many a
little minds got to see the larger
picture once these people get out of
hand
but you done here ain't you seen enough
of me I come from Mike it during your
jail but you've played every cop in your
hand I'm dead yet not every Trump such
as what I can't shut them beams up they
keep yelling about a formula what a
formula for the baby or something his
kid
Oh looky here I got you some milk for
the baby so what's all the belly aching
about that milk is no good I am not
running the drugstore you girls got only
yourselves to blame for this you'd be
back with your families in an hour all
you got to do is to sign a pledge not to
go back on the picket line don't sign
nothing for the sticker
hey ponch
all right where's his baby little girl
you
tenemos comida que damos comas queremos
bano
will you kids get out of our packets
esto no tiene p three hours just to hit
it off water to watch the stuff I'm
telling you something this track is ever
settled which i doubt i'll never go back
to work for that company i let they
install hot running water for us should
have been a union demand from the
beginning you're telling me
actually because they took consciously
we're saving and the message saving the
woman touching he calls it the woman
question here the problems what to do
about it so what does he wanna do about
him he says given equality equality zing
job equalization home and also sexy
quality what do you mean sexy policy yo
no lo que bueno para el hombre que bueno
para la mujer
here's some organizer that Charlie he
could chew organize a wife right out of
your home papa can't I leave now there's
a media let junior shop steward Oh what
the junior shop stewards there's lots of
ways we can help don't the heavy enough
troubles without them tripping you up
early for school but you need all the
help you can get you've gotta help her
on the house but you've got me doing
everything mom and I used to make me dry
the dishes you should help her without
being asked hasta mañana
how do you feel I'm okay for nice what
did you see we try so much fuss they
finally brought oddly i really love my
what Brad didn't so much think they're
asleep
did you have to find a black man to go
back to the gate line I wouldn't do it
if you go back they'll lock you up again
seems happy enough we're talking crazy
well I'm not to lose my title capacity
sir hello well it's all set cuz little
quad can take the day off tomorrow we're
taking over all right we'll work it out
we've got have a dog you and me all
right but later we have got a meeting
now meetings yes to grab for a pic it
like tomorrow you can sit in if you want
now let us see who's have a level
China's husband a set of telling their
delegation to see the governor and the
whole lot then going on a pure hunting
expedition tomorrow so you're 40 of them
so their wives are out too but we can
ask them to keep our teeth so the rest
of us can what are we gonna do about hey
mister time here was heartbroken maybe
that for negation of us got a
I'd like to work it out myself
I got a friend he's got a friend in
Bureau man you know what he says they
never gonna open that man up again oh
come oh he said George went out so heavy
boom not a bull that's a rich man I know
what's the difference they'll never sell
never hey what you know it's him UT
mattress in anything the president of
the company funny see this listen to
this man of distinction Jay Hamilton
lower the last year Dennis executive
board chairman of continental factors
and president of Delaware zinc
incorporated wait a minute witness amor
and enthusiastic sportsman and expert
marksman mr. Miller manages to find time
every year for an African safari he
leave this mud for Kenya where he hoped
to bag his 13th clan
I'm going to frame it no come on can I
look at the larger picture with the guy
as a lion hunter what you SPECT into her
but throw ball without like to get me
some dimps I take the meat before weeks
how about the move let's take off for a
couple of days huh Why ask me am i
running this strike if you want
formation to go over the hill what
happenes axillary
I waited up til midnight you are waiting
for me that meeting oh he left at 10
minutes
the first night I am home you wanted a
beer parlor what is it can't you bear
the sight of me be still but you wanted
to talk tell me
tell me
we can call this way I just can't all
live in with you not this way no we
can't go on this way we can't go back to
the old way either be all way what's
your new way what's it mean you write
neglect your kids
where are you going hunting plain enough
alone no come on you can't why not I'm
not needed here but you are needed
especially now with most of the other
many ways you are the captain of the
Steinbeck's class sure the standby squad
stand by for the funeral whose funeral
we are doing all right there hasn't been
a scuff near Deepika line for three days
and you know why because the company
know they can start without even if you
take them another two or three months
what's it to them it so much I down a
little longer it's a lot to them they do
anything to open that mine they've got
other minds you don't need a larger
picture they've got millions millions
they cannot matter and they know it you
mean you are ready to give us who said
anything about giving up I'll never go
back to that company on money's never
you want to go down fighting you studied
I don't want to go down fighting I want
to win come on we are not getting weaker
we are stronger than ever before they
are getting weaker they thought a good
break our picket line and they failed in
other Kent we know is that black
something big and when I got back like
what I don't know
it's like a long before they start
Charlie be dusted Charlie me down says
don't go Charlie me that up to me Silas
my friend I need friends why got useless
right to have me as your friend I don't
know what you're talking up
have you learned nothing from this tribe
why are you afraid to set me up your
side but you still think you can have
dignity only by have none stock of
business after what you've been doing
yes I took up dignity the angle Abbas
has looked down on you and you hate
employee stained your place your dirty
mexican that's what they tell you but
why must you say to me stay in your
place do you feel better having some
more loading you shut up you're talking
crazy whose necks and I stand on to make
me feel superior and what we like him
out of it I don't want anything lower
than I am I am low enough already I want
to rise and to put everything up with me
if I go will you be still and if you
can't understand this you are a fool
because you can doing this pipe without
me you can win anything without you that
would be the ultimate never try again
I'm going to bed now sleep where you
please but not with me
so they had a little taste of what it's
like to be a woman they ran away
Ramona's bride I spoke out of the
bitterness in me and he was hurt
anything worth learning he hurt these
changes come with paint for other
husbands too not just from
you mean you're ready to give up you
want to go down fighting you that it I
don't want to go down fighting I want to
win come on we are not getting weaker we
are stronger than ever before the yard
getting weaker
have you learned nothing from this
strike
I can feel it coming
it's like a long before the storm they
thought they could break our picket
lines and they failed and now they can't
win unless they pull off something big
and fully dark fast brother we'd better
go back hey surprise huh what Ramon did
he go hunting with the others where
where can we find him you know no deer
hunters deserters that's what they are
something's wrong Charlie tell us
company has an eviction order babson la
casa de beto you mix it longer and my
carpet big 10
don't worry kantaros gone honey with the
others a victim first thrust will be
easy but their neighbors watch it'll
scare some sense into them
do something my girls get back get back
here he has an applicant
yeah leave their brats alone come on
let's get our work done any tension
don't go back get the rest of the stuff
they've been waiting for what are you
saying this means they have given up
trying to break a finger night now we
can all fight together all of it
now see here until these women are
obstructing justice you make it behaves
Eddie I can't do nothing Sheriff you
know how it is they won't listen to a
man anymore want me to lock them up
again you wanna meet your lock up again
starting over 50 yeah the guys the bill
got any more ideas I don't make policy
I'll talk to New York I think maybe we
better settle this thing for the present
we didn't know then that we had won the
strike but our hearts were full and when
Robyn said thanks sisters and brothers
Esperanza thank you for your dignity you
were right together we can push
everything up with us as we go
then I knew we had won something they
could never take away something i could
leave to my children and they the salt
of the earth with in Harrogate
I