a way up in the heavens far out in space
and a beautiful golden crystal palace
right above the North Pole lives a kind
and jolly old gentleman Santa Claus also
known as Saint Nicholas the best friend
of boys and girls everywhere but let's
move in for a closer look come along
it's almost Christmas and I must finish
the toys for all the good children on
earth I hope you'll pardon me but you
know I mustn't be late
Oh
this is Santa's Toyland a sort of
international toy factory here are
gathered boys and girls of different
races and creeds they have come from
many lands to help Santa bring joy and
happiness to all of the earth children
these little helpers are from Africa are
Santa's helpers from Spain lots from
china lend a hand as well
boys and girls from England Japan also
helps
talented children from the Orient
even Russia has a delegation gentlemen
boys and girls helps attitude
here's a happy song from Italy
the islands of the Caribbean the South
American group includes Brazil and
Argentina
the countries of Central America
children from the USA
a neighborly group of helpers from
Mexico devil no let's see don't think
anybody ordered this well now how does
it work what is the sense of it like
this Anna you must let it let's have it
ah I am Lucifer king of Hades command
you to stop and disappear beyond all of
your accepted finish you it is chief of
all my demons must listen closely the
time is almost here when you must
abandon the brimstone pits and journey
up dryer but this time you must not fail
as you go to the path you must not treat
a fee for that period old dog Santa
Claus if you do not succeed in making
all the children of the earth do evil
you shall be punished and is been a
friend hot cold you will need chocolate
ice cream no no Lucifer king of all the
evil spirits not bad by the hordes of
everything satanic can take you to live
I must have each frozen meal Savannah
baby especially chocolate it's very bad
my education would you so delicate you
yes I promise I'll prices Prince of a
tease that by my many ways I will finish
off Santa forever and season two
children commit terrible deeds and make
Santa Claus angry and so betrayal master
Soviet Lucifer David's of Hades
transport me to earth and sober devil
rose to her you heard what he said to
Lucifer but will he be able to keep his
promise
on earth the children can hardly wait
for christmas day they gazed longingly
if the toys I hope Santa will bring them
here is a good little boy whose daddy is
quite rich this mother on the other hand
is very poor and this is her daughter
Lupita fondest dream is to own a dog any
dog
who are these three say it's rude to
portions shove like that but the devil
likes rude little boys and it doesn't
take him long to find them they're just
right for his evil plan well one thing
is certain the devil has turned them
against an applause suddenly he's with
him again out of nowhere he produces
three rocks and his evil plan goes into
action this is bad devil oh I'm sorry
but that old devil is always annoying me
with his mission if I could only go down
there now I'd put him in his place huh
but everyone knows I can only go down to
earth on Christmas Eve enough before in
the meantime dad no double pistas acid
blizzard Kalani what a quad Archie teeb
nor a short while ago I saw the devil
whispering to four children and one was
a poor little girl you know who they are
I've got their name the bad boys on no
no no the naughty boys are not important
they will get punished into course the
ones I must reward are the other
children like a good little girl I got
their names right here the girl is
called better look through the telescope
Pedro will find out what they're doing
this is Santa's magic observatory what
wonderful instruments the years scope
the teller talker that knows everything
the cosmic telescope the man
mr. I nothing that happens on earth is
unknown to Santa Claus bye-bye magic
powers look for the child we're seeking
whether she is in a cave or behind a
million mountain already
I think I found a girl well where is she
in Mexico
yes it's Lupita all right and she's
still dreaming about that doll she wants
for Christmas
you
lupita isn't thinking of stealing that
doll is she no no Lupita you shouldn't
steal put it back
lupita lupita come here
it's yours nobody saw you take it you
Peter they have warned they won't miss
it what does one little doll man don't
you see you haven't got any toys keep it
don't listen to him Lupita it's bad to
steal and you'll be sorry that's right
put it back good girl remember my
precious semi Carl now I don't have to
do without a dummy little girls must
heal or do without the things they like
now that's not true Lupita if you're
good somehow you'll be rewarded
hooray haha Murray faja all my friends
can ignore the devil all they need to
win is to be good in spirits the other
children come Pedro find them by the
magic powers look for the child we're
seeking whether he is in a cave or
behind a million mountain ok
he's sleeping soundly his dream will
appear on the dream scope connect the
antenna for the dream scope
let's watch the little rich boys dream
how strange and what large gift boxes
would these be toys why they contain
what a child loves best his parents
so Noah Noah no no cotton on no a dream
is a wish that the heart makes tell you
Cho is my father he does everything he
wishes just by asking his parents the
only thing this child was is the love of
his parents don't they love him maybe
they do and maybe they don't but soon we
may find out the truth and who paid that
what do you think she met wish if she's
already sleeping we might be able to see
her dream
I wonder if I child is dreaming
I recall when I was at his girl I often
would dream of great riches but I had
all the things I wish for and not a care
in the world but at times I also dream
with the devil confounded devil why
can't he leave Lupita alone
oh just look at that old busybody he'll
make Lupita want to steal again you'll
be part of a dream how awful better look
at her dream now why super shocking she
got sick and went home
member
I
why don't you steal a written over yours
no you know that they may need bed and I
want to be good but you must earn just
you know you not in his bed and I want
to be good we don't don't like good
little girl no just it is you and I want
to be here you must be able if you want
to do no you know you and I don't want
to be evil still I will all be yours no
I don't want to be evil and can you even
you wanna be good you won't be bad no no
kidding is that and I want to be good
poor little child believe me that 0
pitch is going to pay for this very
minute I get to earth he will pay for
what he is doing and the three little
boys the ones who broke the window maybe
we have done more mischief Santa Claus
salgath Kia commercial / yes look for
them my no majo no chikara de I know no
Connie hey kita mo sono Kavanagh chido
need mo ba tuga cigar stayed oh c'mon
suka
the three boys are beneath the large
beds but they're speaking in a low voice
let's tune in the year scope now we will
learn exactly what they are planning
I've got will break our neighbors
windows yeah and we'll steal that kids
toys he's got a lot of the pyramid what
we've yet to us true what were the funny
dad it is no fun to be good anyway Santa
Claus doesn't care about ah he should go
away let's write him a letter John we've
been good as angels you think he's gonna
fall for that sure you will already
chanted in to see you well anymore too
old to know what goes on what me too old
the devil is very many centuries older
than I am those youngsters have got
their nerve yes to the devil I'm just a
child it's just that I haven't been well
lately haha that really makes me let's
see who those boys are we'll see what
they're up to oh there you are you
little rascals well you might as well
know I can see and hear everything you
say I know when you've been bad or good
did you hear that I'll see let's get out
of here My dear Santa Claus see I think
that I wish for
can stay with me tonight before
Christmas I don't like to be alone but
the most important thing is that you
bring me a little brother who is just
about my age because I get awfully bored
you
I know it's hard for you but maybe you
could get me a papa that would be super
I just even a mama the train with lots
of tracks in the bicycle to a live horse
in airplane that will fly diggin man
look their shoes to wear for Sunday as
my two brothers have behaved very well
you must see that they get everything
santa claus santa claus santa claus
santa claus more santa claus more
sentences off we go santa claus santa
cruz
they don't forget all top of the world
st. Nicholas Santa Claus let's see now
my dear Santa Claus this year behaved
very well I have been obedient and have
studied very much for that reason please
try to bring me these toys a toy
automobile a submarine of football of
bat roller skates of scooter a cannon a
rocket a bicycle in atomic laboratory a
machine gun
and many things so be it
and as my two little brothers have
behaved very well hmm you must see to it
that they get everything a falsehood see
there's no fooling Santa Claus into the
liars box
you Santa Claus please bring your little
brother here's one for you mr. stork
he always drawing near for me to go down
to earth we're all good children expect
my arrival as you know business ivica
mafia and we still have tons of things
to do let's all make a big effort to get
our work finish it up to you
here is Merlin the wizard a little
absent-minded perhaps but sata's most
devoted helper oh well then where are
you mr. Melvin mr. Merlin over request
wet cement Oaks Santa Claus whoo what a
start you came haha it's doing more is
quite unusual huh I suppose you've
changed the colors again this one
worship ass the other when the Rays of
the Sun enter the rainfall poof a
variety of wonderful colors will fill
the entire heaven hahaha well mr. Merlin
tell me if the sleeping powders are
mixed The Dreaming powders that fill
everyone with joy and goodwill and the
flower they disappear by watching a game
on the earth it's the eve of the
twenty-fifth of December oh sure is in
three minutes they'll be ready I should
reveal to you the secret of the magic
Stardust concocted by more info
unsurpassed for sound sleeping please
let me go wide
Jimmy Dean wait you need an urn which is
an alloy of copper nickel uranium
plutonium and platinum we're suree watch
Oh would it kill me I am I fuck up yearn
and without the urn I can't receive
gradient Kerner no u-turns each Hotel
rose-colored pollen from the Marvin's
moonflower name scopes of pollen from
the Navy honor and a great talent from
the Morpheus plant 1230 Shh elastin
greedy is the most important theme who
don't attend another day oh gosh the
dozens of the water which is attention
to me quito quite a memory I keep
forgetting
some powder from the wings of the
butterfly a Volusia press that was among
the nebulous missing vapors of even
child and which only I have been able to
keep in captivity by burnishing with my
magic and a great window there the
lights are the heavens yes oh don't
stick it into J this time I didn't
forget there now mmm you'll freeze it
with the light blue flame of frozen fire
and next thing it's ready so as you have
seen it's very simple right then she now
open up your back and the Dreaming
powder that bill everyone with join good
will you know about them the only thing
you have to do santa is to remember that
you must sit them yes the cmas last
Christmas don't you remember yes I'm
afraid I have forgotten as a man
continued to get over he begins to
forget everything every year my memory
fails me more the change i'm good for
nothing and the flower to disappear what
power to disappear you've disappeared
you're really in bad shape the flower to
disappear oh we're here you have it
smell it and you disappeared hahaha well
hello what what do I have to do to make
myself visible again no what happened to
your memory can't you remember anything
the same is last Christmas
why of course ah much obliged to you mr.
Merlyn I'll be back again to see you
next year next Santa calls on the master
blacksmith and key maker of the palace
fight ya keymaker the golden key that
opens all doors is ready Santa it is at
your disposal
I think you'll agree it's a real work of
art it has no equal thank you my dear
keymakr only you could make a key such
as this which would turn the lock of
every daughter please try it on the
locks of a thousand magic portals and de
Santa tries out the magic key of gold it
opens door after door this is Santa's
training what's this Santa dancing no
indeed Santa must watch his waistline
and reduce his tummy if he is to get
down all the gym
they're see Santa has reduced his
waistline but may not seem so but he
fixin to the chimneys all right trans
heavily airway is white MC 707 super
reindeer special red carpet fight to her
Mars Jupiter Saturn via the Milky Way
now boarding let's have a look at
Santa's famous slave and his reindeer
Santa's helpers from all nations sing
happily as they come to make sure that
everything works properly and that the
sleigh and reindeer will shine brightly
in the Christmas sky baby
30 yeah those comoros we Muslims yell it
Luce I appliance nap Lynette to saturday
from tomorrow that I near tonight you
good dari gone dr. Maura sure it's not a
bad idea to use modern space ships for
our interplanetary flights but to
convert my white reindeer into squid
nicks no I should say not and besides
just to go to earth they suit me well
enough well I guess we're all glad about
that maybe a Sputnik would be faster but
I can't quite imagine Santa Claus
without his reindeer in his sleigh you
here's a list of all the kids names and
addresses well just put it over there
well thank heaven I still have a very
good memory hey and I know every single
child on earth well just to make sure
why don't you take it with you I really
got to hurry it's almost time for the
crystal clock on the wall to strike 10
don't forget that you've got to return
to the castle ahead of the sunrise
because the Sun will turn the reindeer
into death oh no sorry no I'll be here
all right in that case I couldn't get
back to the castle and on what they use
for food I'd perish because here our
main food is pastries nice cream made of
soft clouds and of the earth is no such
thing what food do they understand
o'clock Oh everything is fight they eat
most of the animals the plans the
flowers the roots
words even smoke and alcohol but another
biz talking we're wasting time and I
must be
hurry up my children it'll be your
parking it's the night for Santa Claus
who filled all the stockings Mary Mary
greetings I take 21 and also hurry if
you want to enjoy the you tight bond
merry christmas merry christmas let's
see if i have everything the bag with
the powders for dreaming of joy and
goodwill the flower to disappear the
golden key that opens all doors the
sleigh and now I better make sure my
ranger running
yes Santa's sleigh is really a huge toy
slave and he has to wind it like any
other toy to make it go
my ranger and glide through the heavens
as fast as you can go be my palace of
gold and Chris to the joy peace and
Jesus the Son of God join us on earth so
that we can all have joy and goodwill on
my good Ranger
whew that was close he almost ran into
the moon
and here's the planet Earth I wonder
where Santa will go first Europe Africa
America think of all the nice things you
get them santa claus yes mama that's a
good boy see you in the morning if you
get bored you can go down and practice
your piano lesson see you later my
darling
I knew it the devil is nearby and these
three certainly are up to no good okay
yes and now as soon as Santa cross lines
on the road through all three of us will
jump on him well tie him up and we'll
stick them in a sack and then we'll go
home with all Santa's toys but what
about Santa we can make him our slave
and all his candies and toys will belong
to it so whenever we want something oh
boy this is gonna be fun and our talk
now he can hear to get away
although children to bed Santa Claus
will be here any minute now mama and we
sent her class he's the man in the storm
the one with the red suit and the white
beard that was left him very much and
dance a man oh I but knew uh-huh if
Syria met my daddy and no not really
died one with a dummy the real Santa
lives in a castle and comes here once a
year what does he come for they say he
starts to children who are obedient I
don't think he likes me he has never
brought me any daddy it's not that maybe
you're forgetting to ask you for dollies
and if I ask him for one now go ahead
perhaps he hears you we can see a prayer
dear mama please don't cry the other is
Christmas and Christmas always makes me
feel sad it brings back memories honey
what is Christmas good for well to
remind us that Christ was born many
years ago and he was even poorer than we
are he was born in a bed of straw know
what mama I already asked Santa Claus
for two pretty darling if he brings it
to her give one to know Jesus this my
darling maybe we play without my hmm
while Santa steers his sleigh towards
Earth old devil pitch awaits his arrival
here comes Santa now first stop Mexico
City it's freezing I was your back in
Hades hitting the furnaces he's heard
sample I said near he is I'm glad that
I'm prepared upset is all Merry
Christmas hey we will see your wins out
this is one night that no one can take
from me what's he going to do oh ho he's
going to push the chimney out of place
so that poor old Santa won't be able to
enter this house
let's hope Santa realizes what's
happened well what happened here I can
smell sulfur well that must explain this
that ole devil pitch must be around here
Santa's determined to get in he'll find
a way he's not one to give up well
there's more than one way to beat the
devil Santa will jump down using his
magic parasol old pitch hadn't counted
on this he's almost green with anger
oh oh these two seemed to know that
Santa's in the living room look outside
and they'll see you
why of course Santa can handle this all
he has to do is use the magic dreaming
powders prepared by mr. Merlin
and it isn't long before our two little
stay ablates are sleeping soundly in
their bed now what must be pitched
putting the chimney back in place well
the devil doesn't give up either and he
seems to be quite happy about his next
plot against Santa
could Santa be coming down this chimney
now oh he's all right but that was close
pitch is foiled again but suddenly
thinks of something else to do that's it
he'll huff and puff until his burning
bread turns the doorknob and keyhole
red-hot so the magic he won't work and
Santa will burn his hands
first you'll see if it's hot enough what
do you think of that but Santa sees what
bitches up to and he isn't afraid
meanwhile pitch looks out the window to
watch Santa burn his hands doesn't seem
to know he's right behind him oh ho a
cannon now it's Santa's turn to get even
with pitch
Oh
hiren truth is a poor little rich boy he
has all the toys a little boy could wish
for him yet he is sad and lonely lonely
for his parents in spite of all he has
he lacks the most important thing in
life the company of his mother and
father
I know all those toys don't make you
happy but I'll do something for you that
I only do for children who are very good
I would let you see me as I am and
therefore i will use the powders that
will make you dream that you're awake
and now awaken why you're dreaming
Santa claw you love me don't you so you
love me Santa of course I love you Sonny
just as much as your parents because no
one loved the child as much as his
parents only at times the parents don't
understand their children and the
children don't understand their parents
are you really sure that they love me
when I left all alone yes of course they
love you and you must believe they love
you and now go back to sleep again
it was all a sweet dream
when you awaken I wish you much
happiness
yeah it's been a long time since I've
seen the markings they're both looking
pretty well though aren't they that's a
strange cocktail isn't it's the cocktail
of remembrance which only I can prepare
whoever drinks its will think of that
which is most dear and which at times
for some unknown reason we seem to
forget that's a beautiful thought
perhaps we need a reminder very possibly
we forgot be someone we love love can be
expressed in many ways but the truest
love is that which we give without
expecting anything in return the
greatest reward for those who love
sincerely is love itself so drink my
cocktail and you will become aware of
that love which is closest to your
hearts in those without laughs they
couldn't drink this cocktail as it would
burn their throats well since we are
very much in love
may it always be that way
now that strange where'd he disappear to
I don't think he was just a waiter he
didn't seem to be a stranger that kind
look the white beard I knew that face
when I was a child couldn't be if his
beard was white when you were a small
girl he'd be dead and buried by now now
that's strange I suddenly have an urge
to see our little boy let's go home poor
bellies always alone I feel that he's
needing us too she'll be so glad come on
pitch hasn't done too well by himself
against Santa so he's back to seek the
help of these boys who so far are the
only ones willing to listen to his evil
plans they may think it's smart to help
him now but they'll be sorry for his
advice can only get them into trouble
one of us better get over there behind
the water tape and take the rubble on
when we spot Santa Claus sowwy we'll
pull the root and knock him down got it
that's for me it works you can't kill
you oh boy coxswain get your head down
here comes Ana
how can you be so dumb still be fooled
you certainly turned our plane into our
base he'll never leave be I can promise
you that I'll make him pay dearly for
all this mm that's guarantee the wider
look blind in you that music was so loud
heared me too what annoying a maybe
Santa Claus got something in our house
shall we go see let's go
present for Christmas Santa Claus
doesn't like us we didn't get anything
why don't you that I
it's all your fault it was your idea
don't be a 50 we're complaining well
anyway was his idea that we should go up
by the room my idea the fault is all
yours I'm going to bed i'm tired coward
you kick me when my back was stirred you
be glad it wasn't me and that case up
with you and you haven't got the nerve
to say you did it that's it Betsy
terrific ah beat your brains out please
don't go so badly Lucifer will be very
pleased
oh no mr. bitches decided to steal
Santa's sleigh that's a relief the
reindeer won't obey him tough luck bitch
Oh a pair of scissors look out Santa
that old devil pitch must be around
somewhere oh my mr. Merlins magic
creaming powders now Santa won't be able
to put anyone to sleep on my heavenly
rain gear for this much to be done and
there goes a flower to disappear and now
Santa won't be able to make himself
invisible what are you going to do now
sadder
let us hope the flower to disappear
doesn't fall into bad hands
meanwhile Santa goes on his way not
knowing that his dreaming powders and
flour to disappear are gone Santa is not
afraid of that dog if he goes after him
he still thinks he can disappear Coheed
him daddy cigano go by him PG mall how
can old pitch me so mean seeking a
vicious dog on Santa like that the
powders the flower to disappear no
powders and a flaw what do I do now Ron
Santa climb the tree it's your only
chance
I said it was a very funny site old
white kidney site running as if the
devil himself were going to take him
below your baby or mischief you just
wait to see hmm but I still have to come
down that tree and I can have a lot of
fun before you can get rid of daddy
because you know what I'm gonna do I'm
gonna wake up everybody huh nobody can
hear your voice they hear it is a form
of their own private imagination or
ideas let them see how foolish you
appeared there's a prouder out there
he's got to give your wife hey you
children he's really quite vicious he's
hiding up in your tree defend yourself
he's going to murder you he's going
crazy
mr. morning apparently no one is in
Santa's magic observatory I'd awaken
there's a man outside Marie how you get
up I think the bar in danger huh yes oh
yes there's a seam tits out and back
session I'm not going hurry get out of
bed go out the hams over Oh where's the
pistol where you keep it in the drawer
in the drawer in the drawer destroy why
in this one or this one there it is go
after him come on don't be funny money
yes but i but I cook I can't be expected
to go out i might catch pneumonia mother
come on now it up come on we have no
pneumonia you go but Marie understand
whether you got it your father wait on
us put on my robe here stop fooling
around tomy time
he'll please tell police in the trailers
an assassin please come quickly oh
please my father
bagpipers bourbon firemen the house is
burning I'm on fire you don't believe me
mercy this is a fine alarm fire better
let me have that address please won't
you don't expect anything from Santa
Claus he doesn't bring toys to poor
children didn't I tell you to keep that
doll silly so now you won't have
anything you are poor mama mama what is
it dear don't the poor people get
anything from Santa Claus who those of
that ah no my darling Santa Claus is
good to all of the children who are
obedient it's not matter if they're poor
or wealthy to bed now my darling and
sleep well nope mama it's almost eight
and then there's less hasn't come sleep
now darling sleep now and you will see
pity when you wake up you'll find a
dolly
but God sleep now and hapless box
I poorly lupita who can tell if Santa
Claus will go to our house this year
that did it the whole family's awake now
hurry up were you gonna get away bill
here you go no please ladies fresh got
no time for man where's to go let's all
go back to bed hey everyone I want to
play cops and robbers o malli' mr.
Maryland hey watch a can you run follow
me can I run and follow you better tell
me what's the matter and I'll decide
whether I should run and whether i
should follow you act Santa Claus is in
danger he's calling you urgently on the
teleprompter Oh what in that case we'd
better hurry let's fry now once we Money
two for the show away we go sorry mr.
Mullen this is no time to play horsie
serve is endangered we let her analyze
the situation you're the bravest one
here you can take care of a million men
let the most she now that the only brave
one here is you all the men are cowards
you are a woman put the machine now are
you sure the wistar person well I mean
the pistol works laughs course it works
ah if I were only your age if I were
your age you wouldn't matter if I lived
or not you're both famous bones but
neither of you were laughing alright you
heard what she said you go first no
we're both go we'll both go and see what
happens the Red Cross the fire
department the police what a jam for
Santa's in everyone will see him
you know sirens there for you the show
is about to begin that you'll never get
back before sunrise your reindeer will
change the powder you will starve to
death and I will rule the earth
Santa Claus Santa Claus it's me here in
the observatory well what is the measure
in just a few minutes it's going to be
gay return now they've got me a tree
Merlin I dropped the party disappear and
also the powders for dreaming and this
beast of rock let me come down all this
confusion has been prepared by mr. pitch
way now Hurley mr. Merlin sorry wrong
away can we find Santa Claus he's
already been to Asia Europe and
Australia he must be on the American
continent I think I see him he's in
Mexico Oh golly but he's in a terrible
fix and there's no time to go to his
rescue and the Sun is about to write
fragile mag George against court is bad
his breath is quite against a bad itch
scratch it against first water against
mad dog gets mad dog against mad dog hey
take care to chat to care I can't Santa
Claus attack please be quick Marlon now
here is my time is almost over this time
it's serious against mad dog a cat use
one of the toy cats that you wind up
shoo-shoo shoo-shoo shoo-shoo
now all together now but don't push him
don't push me just a min up you make me
nervous oh come on hurry up I could
handle this but don't leave me alone huh
come on
where's the body how many are injured
they'll surely find Santa nothing in
sight can't see anything better look
around don't do that why should you oh
it's only a hose because with maybe a
whole gang but don't worry try to be
brave be con we must all be brave that's
it the whole hey you baby have time now
I still have one more friend to visits I
mustn't fail her back no buts about it
first come to children I'll see you
later if possible what happened did you
find anyone we've looked all over the
place and there's no one to be found
let's make sure the fires out there's
something over there well that serves
him right the old troublemaker you'll
probably catch pneumonia but he asked
for it
wait the flower to disappear has fallen
right into Lupita's house
did you find work nothing much nothing
mama I feel that a club I'm really happy
again he goes bang and talk to me for a
very long time because he's white
reindeer what turning to proudest day
darling but now go back to sleep it is
very late just go ahead and think of all
those wonderful things it was I just
dreaming mama give me that she miss me a
dolly outside in the patio maybe next
Christmas not this one but he said you
was a beautiful guy
look at mommy is indeed a pretty dolly
no one mom at Alette star the China now
there is a palace of crystal and candy
the home of Santa club he's just
arriving with his roommate and white
reindeer Thank You senator goodbye in
the class thank you for a wonderful and
so once again Santa returns to his
palace from his yearly Christmas round
he is happy gay once again he has
brought joy to the children of the world
blessed are they who believe for they
shall see God peace on earth goodwill
toward men Merry Christmas
you