Thunder all right
Oh
ok
hey
at this time station ki DTV brings you
the special event of the year a first in
television history at this very moment
ki DTV has standing by a television crew
at Santa Claus workshop and in just a
few seconds our special correspondent
Andy Henderson will bring you a person
to person interview with Santa Claus
himself direct from the North Pole where
at the moment the temperature is 91
degrees below zero and now ki d TV takes
you via tell star Andy Henderson at the
North Pole I can't this is Andy
Henderson at the North Pole ooh it's
cold up here from this spot there's only
one direction you can go and that's
south yeah living up here is pretty
rough I don't see how Santa stands it
mmm since we've been here we've eaten
nothing but frozen food at least that's
the way it is by the time we get it and
now let's take a look-see into Santa's
workshop
hello again boys and girls it's just
weeks before Christmas and Santa and his
helpers are working overtime to make
sure that there's enough toys for the
kids all over the world Santa's a pretty
busy man but I'm sure he'd like to say a
few words to you kids hello Santa oh oh
Sean oh oh hello boys and girls hey
sandy you caught me at a very busy time
well do you think you'll be ready by
Christmas Eve well we've never
disappointed the kids yet yeah tell me
is it true that this year there's a
rumor that you're going to use a rocket
sled no siree we're going out the good
old-fashioned way with my reindeer
Prancer and dancer and thunder and
Blitzen and vixen and Nixon a mix
annoyed i get i always crunch on it i
get those names mixed up but the kids
know their names ah there you are we
have so much do and who stand here
dawdling talking to this visitor mr.
Anderson this is mrs. Claus weird if
we're on television how do you do mr.
Anderson now I want you to go and finish
painting those hobby horses television
did you say we're on television whoa oh
oh why didn't you tell me about my
hair's a mess hello there
come along mr. Anderson and I'll show
you some of the new toys were turning on
how's it going winking everything is
a-ok salad for the man link is in charge
of our space depart huh oh now here here
is the latest toy rocket it runs on real
rocket UL daily I've been wondering what
is this strange little creature over
here Oh Twinkie made that that's his
idea of a Martian a Martian wowie Wow
I'd hate to meet a creature like that on
a dark night I wonder if there really
are people on Mars well who knows well
if there are I hope they have someone
like you up there Santa to bring joy and
good cheer to all the Martian children
Oh mr. Anders oh oh oh keep going Winky
Christmas Eve is coming soon now mr.
Anderson I want to show you some more
drapeau drop oh you lazy
good-for-nothing where are you dropper
drop a wake up wait stand up stand up
stand up I'm sorry Kiki mar sir drop oh
you were the laziest man on Mars why are
you sleeping during working hours I
wasn't sleeping chief it's just that I
haven't been able to sleep these last
few nights I forgot how so I was just
practicing well I suggest you practice
doing your work where's lady MOMAR oh
she went to the food pill center to get
some new food pills the children haven't
been any well no appetite at all there's
no wonder they sit in front of the video
said all day watching those ridiculous
8th programs it confuses them where are
they oh and they're watching earth
programs say Santa what have we here
these are new dolls now this little doll
walks talks right and she even sees
almost like a real live little girl that
she is Sir that she is all she needs his
tender loving care bummer what is it
doll I don't know germer what is tender
loving care I don't know either boom ah
gimmeh I told you not to watch those
silly best programs now go to sleep must
we go to sleep now father I want to see
Santa Claus some more I want to see more
toys no go to sleep hello drop oh I see
you're keeping busy I've been working
very hard lady MOMAR I've been back to
bring the room good is the master here
he's in there and key Mars very hangar
to kemah I bought some new food pills I
hope the children will eat these you
have hamburger buttered asparagus mashed
potatoes and a special treat for them
chocolate layer cake pills Moammar I'm
worried about our children so am I
they've hardly nothing in three days it
goes deeper than that they're behaving
strangely they appear to be trouble they
don't care to sleep I had to use the
sleep spray on them again I mentioned
this to my council chiefs today and I
learned it's the same with children all
around the planet in every district
something is happening to the children
of Mars kemar as leader of the Martians
you must do something about it I know
what what why don't you go to the forest
and see coach him the ancient one he'll
know what to do he's never failed you
you speak wisely
I will go attention council chiefs
please report blomus reporting rig now
reporting har go here boda boda our
please report old are reporting
gentlemen of the council we will meet
immediately at cho chums chair in front
of forest what's wrong now you are I
don't know voldar but I mean to find out
you
qwest kima you should be here anymore
what's this all about we'll find out
when kemar arrives we are probably going
to seek the advice of chocha but a
schema think we are a kindergarten class
and we make our own decisions must we
always come crawling to that da thering
old man jochem is 800 years old you
can't dismiss the wisdom of centuries I
can gentlemen thank you for coming
toejam
jochem are you here ancient one of Mars
I call upon you totem it is I kima and
the council chiefs we need you touch him
you called me kima we need your advice
jochem something is wrong with our
children they eat not they sleep not
their only interest is watching
meaningless earth programs on the video
Oh what time of year is it now it is the
middle of sub tuber oh no not here I
mean on earth ah yes it is early
December on earth close to the time of
the Christmas that explains it what is a
Christmas it is an occasion for great
joy and peace on the planet Earth and
procurement there's also what time of
anticipation as they await the arrival
of Santa Claus at his gifts ah What
nonsense what has this to do with our
children ancient one we have no children
on Mars they have children's bodies but
with a dull mind they do not have a
childhood
I see this coming for centuries they are
born our electronic teaching machines
are attached to their brains while they
are in their cradles information is
heading to their minds in a constant
stream and by the time they can walk
they are adult they never played they've
never learn to have fun and now no they
are rebelling what do you advise the
children must be allowed to be children
again they must learn to play they must
learn what it means to have fun we need
us Santa Claus on Mars
Santa Claus on Mars will we get a Santa
Claus only one Santa Claus and he's
honest hahaha well I guess that takes
care of that didn't I tell you it was a
foolish idea to seek advice from that
old man this is a serious matter folder
and desperate problems require desperate
deeds if this head Santa Claus long
enough we will bring him to Mars against
it our children are fine the way they
are I don't want any Santa Claus
bringing them toys and games they'll
start playing and laughing and running
under foot I'll become a nuisance I've
made my decision we leave for Earth
tonight big night nomas prepare
spaceship number one
approaching projected Earth orbit fire
portside rockets number one the number
to one side rockets number one and
number two fire entering Earth orbit all
right hold on now to find Santa Claus
turn on your manga scope to third power
wherever a city of some kind so that's
what the earth people call a city a how
primitive look at all those buildings
above ground why we could destroy that
city with one blast of our fury we've
not come here to destroy anyone our only
purpose is to bring Santa Claus back to
marvs turn the fifth power let's see if
we can locate Santa Claus he wears a red
suit trimmed with white fur and he has a
long white beard but the religions have
people down there it's like looking for
a speck of space dust in a comet's tail
wait a minute I see him I see Santa
Claus I seem to he's standing on the
corner ringing a bell no it's not he's
standing near the entrance of a large
building next to a large black kettle
he's standing on a corner kimani wait a
minute I see another one where there are
hundreds of Santa Clauses down there I'm
gonna bring them all back with us to
Mars just one and with so many they
won't miss one prepare for landing our
next orbit we interrupt our program with
a special bulletin an unidentified
object has been spotted in orbit around
the Earth the Soviet Union denies it has
launched any new space satellites our
radar stations are tracking the
spaceship or whatever it is the US Air
Force has alerted all defense commands
and retaliatory units stay tuned for
further bulletins
sir Burt radar beams are bouncing off
our ship well it certainly took them
along it oh that turn on the radar
shield misfunctioning of radar shield
Brignac check the radar box radar shield
functioning always wrong remit a slight
case of drop oh hi Keith what are you
doing here drywall well Keith I wants a
launching pad so I can say goodbye to
you and I remember I've never been der
it so i thought i wanted i may leave you
there place a Santa Claus I can't below
I'll deal with you later quickly yes
just you prepare the land we're sat down
on that field near the lake rocket
silence is set bro go rockets number one
and two fire all this trouble Oprah fact
little man in a red suit here is another
UFO bulletin the Defense Department has
just announced that the unidentified
flying object has suddenly disappeared
from our radar screen they believe the
object to see the disintegrated in space
or it may be a spaceship from some other
planet which has the ability to nullify
our radar beam because of the ominous
situation the president has ordered the
Strategic Air Command into action
I
fire retrorockets number 56 retrorockets
five and six fire lower landing legs
running legs Lord attention crew is a
team on when we've landed regna voldar
and i will leave the ship to investigate
cargo lomas and drop o will stay on
board on constant alert for immediate
blast off the Defense Department
believes that the object spotted on our
radar screens might have been nothing
more than a meteor which burned up when
it entered our atmosphere professor word
of on green our leading space expert is
still convinced it was a Martian
spaceship stay tuned for further
bulletins Billy what did the mossen look
like I don't know nobody's ever seen one
I don't believe there any Mars you don't
huh won't you do for Martin will put it
behind you I scream
who are you we're from Mars don't be
afraid we have children just like you on
Mars where are those funny things
sticking out of your head those are our
antenna are you a television set stupid
question is this what you want to do to
our children on Mars turn them into
nincompoops like these oh dear Tong fo
da what's your name little boy Billy
Billy foster sir and this is my sister
Betty perhaps you can help us Billy
we're looking for one of your Santa
Clauses is only one Santa Claus we see
many of them in your cities oh those are
his helpers it's only one real Santa
Claus and he's in his workshop i'll put
the North Pole that's what we came here
to find out let's go come on you two let
me go where are you taking us um alone
hold on what and leave the mayor to
inform the authorities he's right kemar
we'd better take him along with us to
the North Pole very well come along
this morning two children disappeared
mysteriously from the vicinity of Welsh
Lake the police have found no clues and
it seems as though Billy and Betty
foster have simply vanished into thin
air this appears to be a day when
everything is vanishing into thin air
while local police are continuing their
search for the missing children the
armed forces are continuing their search
for the mysterious object from space
alright Billy and Betty nobody's here
come on now I'm not supposed to bring
you here the Chiefs gonna be awful man
if he finds us boy well if kids at home
funny I was the real Marshall station no
don't touch anything now here that's the
antigravity generator and these are the
retrorockets does this light off only
when radar waves are bouncing off our
ship then we put up this radar screen
then nobody can find us in space boy
party shot yeah what's this Chavo oh
that's the elevator signal that light
starts flashing when somebody's coming
up from the navigation deck
oh I'm in trouble
thinking of taking another nap in the
radar box troppo oh no sir as a matter
of fact I was just looking in there to
remind myself never to hide in there
again I bet nope approaching North Pole
I can see Santa Claus workshop
I prepare for landing Margo set the
rocket silences Babu sir you stay aboard
and guard those children they must not
leave the ship now now or ever what do
you mean folder if we take them with us
to Mars Santa's disappearance would
remain a mystery no one on earth will
ever know but Santa Claus was kidnapped
by Martians perhaps you're right drapeau
sir get back to those children and Don
them out of your sight understand yes
sir I understand I'll keep alive we've
landed secure the ship Lomas you remain
on garden have the ship ready for
immediate blast off rig now cargo voldar
you'll accompany me come will activate
toward talk to capture a rollie pollie
little man like Santa Claus we don't
need tall we won't take any chances come
nothing could stop toward
they're gone to kidnap Santa Claus and
us too not a freaking hell but we've got
to get out of here in one Santa what's
at all I don't know Brom are afraid of
it it's not going to stop us come on
play 30 why did you do that this ship
Emily's earth by the whole us space
books after them come on
come on Betty
this action must take place swiftly we
can't afford to make any mistakes I'll
go you cover the rear a workshop rig nuh
older cover the front entrance I'll
direct towards old or isn't here bring
ago up until vote up Boulder this is
another one of your delay tactics you've
been opposing me at every turn now I'm
warning you change your attitude you
finished chief yes I am and you will be
too if you're not careful oh but I am
careful chief so careful but I looked in
at the children go before I left the
ship you stay away from those children
ever be easy to do they've escaped
Goldar if this is your idea of a joke
ass drop oh they overheard our plans at
this very moment they're on their way to
Santa Claus to warn him it's true kima
their footprints we must stop them those
children mustn't reach Santa Claus well
them I'll put talk on the trail toward
come out of the spaceship toward come
out of the spaceship
I can't run anymore I'm cold and I'm
tired and it's beginning to snow please
Betty try we've got to want Santa we
can't stop now they like catch us where
is Santa I don't know his workshop must
be somewhere around here he's the mean
one the one who doesn't like us come on
we ran away but boy that was a narrow
escape why did he run away I don't know
don't know Betty I'll go take a look
it's all right nobody come on I'm cold I
wish it wouldn't snow that's the best
thing that could happen it'll cover our
tracks and be harder for the Morrisons
to find us and it will be hard for us to
find Santa's workshop I'm scared we'll
find it which way is north
oh I see it Santa's workshop well bye
dad see the light
Santa's house I don't know
now destroy the crustal rustam Todd do
as I say wha I knew you try something
like this I set torx control so he will
obey only me really some time you were
very lucky now don't try to escape again
you may not be so lucky next time I go
take them back to the ship Lock them up
and rejoin us you won't get away
danger grows with every minute let's get
Santa Claus and blast off will surround
the workshop and sent organ to get Santa
nobody is to be harmed unless I get in
our way ah no one is to be hard what has
happen to the great warriors of our
planet Mars used to be the planet of war
mark my words keema your softness will
destroy us Santa Claus toys games
laughing children we shall see but for
now to your posts God follow me
get in torque
where did you come from you're the
biggest liar I've ever seen before I'm
very well made to buy the great dogs
star Santa's treating him like a toy get
him toward grab him he's become a toy
rig now we'll have to get Santa
ourselves come on voldar what have we
here more toys those are Martians Santa
Claus you're coming with us no you can't
take him now it's truly a Christmas
quiet you but we don't want to hurt you
Santa Claus so come along quietly why
why did you have to do that to my helper
it's harmless it'll wear off in a short
while oh oh why didn't you say so in the
first place now you come with us we need
you on Mars
are you sure this is harmless oh I never
saw such lazy people standing around
like statues there's work to be done
let's get to it oh my oh me oh oh mrs.
Claus is going to be very angry about
this take him toward torg take him obey
my command forget it ki ma regni was
right he's nothing but a toy now best to
leave him here believe me I had nothing
whatsoever to do about this you know my
dear I can't recall a time when you were
so silent for so long let's go all man
and mrs. Santa Claus has positively
identified the kidnappers as Martian
never in the history of mankind have the
nations of the world reacted with such
unanimity and cooperation tonight the
lights will burn until dawn in the
United Nations building as the leaders
of the world map a course of action and
at Cape Kennedy our correspondent
interviewed Verner von green the man in
charge of America's story short program
mr. van green what is the space agency
doing about this well they have
mobilized older men and equipment in our
starship project and we have lost our
roster nothing to an intensive program
for the final phase of their training
now our starship is supposed to undergo
six months of test flights but we are
going to forget about the testing and go
after those Martian monkeys isn't that
risky of course it takes risky but every
one of our astronauts is digging for the
chance to go after the motions who
wouldn't give everything the bling
center back to our children
earth hasn't reacted yet no radar beams
being bounced off our ship looks like we
made a clean getaway how's our captain
he's a few Katai of his life he's such a
funny little man well I have only been
with him for five minutes and he has me
laughing just like an Earthling what's
soft and round and you put it on a stick
and your toasted in a fire and it's
green oh what a margin bahahaha that's
what you're all becoming Martian fellows
soft we that old man is a menace and it
was a very foggy Christmas Eve well I
could barely make out this chimney in
the farm but I found it all right and I
started to crawl in well I tell you it
was the biggest chimney I'd ever been in
and then suddenly suddenly I realized it
wasn't a chimney at all it was the smoke
stack of the Queen Elizabeth well don't
you think that was funny yes and uh well
why don't you laugh Keys Santa's are out
Paul we told them where to find you Oh
older dash in a fiddle dee dee Billy Boy
everybody knows where Santa lives
besides I've always wanted to visit Mars
mommy and daddy are going to be angry
you think that's something I can just
see mrs. Claus now Christmas coming and
I'm not there you have a fit oh me oh my
oh me come and get it dinner time here's
drop oh if I can't cheer you up troppo
can he always makes me laugh would you
have a
Oh dinner tonight older soup and bestow
and chocolate ice cream not thank you
trouble I'm not hungry come on Billy oh
well is it all right if I have your
chocolate ice cream sure oh I just love
chocolate ice cream hmm gee Mars must be
a terrible place to live some chocolate
ice cream pills beginner hey I suppose
if a Martian has a headache he doesn't
take pills he takes chocolate ice cream
haha did okay came off look at this that
small blip is not an asteroid it's a
spaceship and it's on our tail it's
getting closer impossible rig now they
couldn't have spotted this we have our
radar shield on I know that sir but they
are gaining on us is it possible Earth
has a secret device that can penetrate
our radars huge they have a secret
device and his name is Billy Foster I
want you that these fillings are
dangerous they'll destroy us if we allow
them well I won't allowed I think we
underestimate the resourcefulness of
these earth people very clever of the
boy major repairs regni I'll take your
visa cash well and how is Santa and the
little Earthlings my it must be tiresome
cooped up in this little room say how
would you like to see the rest of the
ship you're not fooling me you don't
like us you're me oh come on now that's
not true why Santa makes everyone feel
good even me I don't trust you no no
Billy Boy that's not the Christmas
spirit I of course volgar we'd love to
take the Grand Tour all right children
this room is called that's right sure
this is where you come when you're ready
to go out in space it's air time you put
on your space suit and go out through
that door when you come back the door
closes and it from air back into the
room through there where I reaching the
pressure on the rest of the ship you're
gonna take your space along smart lad
where's the controller opens the door
shut not here that's in the control deck
you see once you pull that switch the
warning bell sounds and in 60 seconds
that door opens best to give us faith in
the chance make a final check up on
their equipment is nowhere out in space
if that door open now it will pull all
the air add this room and us with it you
certainly know a great deal about space
travel son he's going to be a fake man
when he grows up maybe sooner than that
Santa that clock stopped 60 seconds that
must be the good timer he locked us in
oh I don't think so he probably just
stepped out for a moment hi I'm chose
ball dark he's not my team are any
others I don't like him I don't worry
Santa no no children let's not get
excited
it's louder he's going to own the space
door
he said what are we going to do what's
the door opens we have a good chance
where did you say this needs to be upset
for
three
two
one
theorem who's a new york no one now
what's going on Budaj chief sat on the
children are missing naughty drifting
around in space along with the rest of
us space junk
mantra with you fold are you wish you
were fooling around out there in space
merry Christmas everyone Santa Claus
you're all right I I thought you would
wear when bold or accidentally left us
in the airlock and then came up here and
accidentally through the door switch we
knew we had to get out of there in a
hurry or that would be the end of us oh
yeah accidentally of course the air duct
the etta but the air duct is just a
little and you're so big why are you
talking a Santa Claus son yeah oh well
well not you wouldn't want me to tell my
secret would you oh poor man peace
fainted just like someone who's seen a
ghost
begin landing operation firing
retrorockets 1 & 2 5 lower landing legs
big nap after we secured the shift and
lower the ladder you and hard or get
pulled our other the brig and taken to
the council room you'll stand trial
immediate right chief we've landed hatch
open hatch open water down power chip
secure jingle bells jingle bells jingle
all the way oh what fun it is to ride no
one horse open sleigh I Merry Christmas
baldauf alright on your feet come on
drop oh I was handing me food pills
through the bars and drop off him off
come in quickly kima yes we good hold on
his escaped what he's gone I can only
meet all but a constant guard on Santa
and the earth children both are will be
back
honest is folly you yet no go Maura call
you the moment he arrives he's dropout
coming back to yes girma now go back to
your studies Oh chemo are you alone no
well earthlings Billy and Betty welcome
to our home there's someone else to lady
boom ah I'm not accustomed to entering
people's homes through the door but you
have no chimney tener welcome Santa
Claus we hope you make the children on
Mars very happy I'll try dear lady I'll
try there there where are they well
we'll start with my youngsters how are
they Nomar the same quiet remote and
very unhappy they're inside studying
well little Santa say hello to them and
I'm sure these children would like to
meet them I'll tell them you're here why
45 pi r square to determine the correct
orbit from Mars to Jupiter traveling the
long viktor Kee through the 17th
quadrant at the power of 12 Megatron's I
missed you two children I brought some
visitors from Earth
will you come in please children Billy
and Betty this is beau monde and gamma
hi there's nothing in it what are you
giving me my hand to shake how are you
10 I'm 10 2 and lomas eight souls my
sister we have another earth person that
wants to see you
they're laughing boom on gamma before
I can't believe it that's the first time
in months they've gone to sleep without
the sleep spray Santa tomorrow we'll set
up a workshop for you it won't be
exactly the same as the one you have on
earth but I'm sure it'll serve your
purpose good good now I'd like to get
going and have the toyshop operating
full blast so's i can return to Earth
for Christmas her you know mrs. Claus is
a very good-natured woman but anta Claus
you will never return to it now you
belong to Mars oh hello oh hi Deanna
dirty came expec oh ma Oh kemar would
get this off fine away friend in the red
silk oh that's suicide I proposals on
the cost of God we couldn't get with the
20 feet of them without being
disintegrated but I have other plan
someone's approaching the key oh all
right it'll be okay I Jim heads up i
divide out the toy shop is operating
full blast no one suspects me so I
sneaked down into the good long look
it's nothing like the one on earth no
one assigned or averring Kim Juarez
build a mechanized assembly line to the
old man toys are rolling off by the sand
this planet only played with toys you
know they got one little toy it's the
cutest thing it's just a coil spring and
it goes down steps all by itself I was
tempted to steal one I'd like to fool
around with the things ties the K is
setting in it's even affecting you soon
all of Martians will be blithering
idiots or we've no time to lose we was
going to action now we cannot eliminate
Santa Claus but we can discredit him
they come out laughing stock to our bars
come on now listen care that were the
shop closes at ten o'clock the gods will
be aqui mas house guarding Santa Claus
but this is what you do see you
ok thousands of letters from all the
bars Lord
Jill dog chewed are just ready three
baseball bats
look at me Santa Claus a great toy maker
pressing buttons as automation for you
technology please well that's enough for
today hey nice a lady MOMAR made it for
me can I try it on Santa uh-uh don't be
silly drop oh this would never fit you
well you have to fatten up first
well there's another day gone children
as they say on earth another day another
dollar well I don't know Santa how are
you feeling today tired no no I'm not
tired but my finger is it's been
pressing buttons all day long well I
think I'll go in and put my finger to
bed your children here's your milk you
can play for half an hour and then you
have to go to bed daddy hey we watch the
earth program safely dear but only to
have an hour Billy Betty don't you want
to watch the effort oh no sir when I
interested in earth programs I'm going
to sleep goodnight me too just a moment
not mr. keema good night lady robot just
a moment children are you feeling well
oh we feel fine sir good night good
night has someone been mistreating you
oh no sir you and Lady mama I've just
been swell to us good night what could
it be mama they're behaving the way our
children used to behave dad you tell
kima they're homesick they missed their
parents and friends kima you've got to
send those children back
impossible Santa says I gotta fatten up
Walton milk chocolate cake pinellas wet
hmm with whipped cream
that takes too long
oh now I'm Santa Claus whoa whoa whoa
merry Christmas everyone whoa whoa whoa
my finger isn't tired I think I'll go
down to the workshop and make some more
toys
shit over light the light
ah this is gonna shit about these toys
are the same so what's coming quick
break it's Santa Claus always alone no
God da state what's my best little
friends hey said like this toy oh my
friend ask your question antrim Oh quiet
shit put on a nuclear trip tomorrow
marks the end of Operation Santa Claus
and Mars returns to normal drop or you
rascal where are you drop 00 children
breakfast is ready good morning dear mom
I can't find drop o his bed hasn't been
slept in what's he up to now good
morning good morning lady MOMAR Oh Oh my
extra suit the one you made for me is
missing I'm sure I brought it home from
the toy shop last night that's two
things that are missing your suit and
dropper what oh that explains it when
you find my missing suit you'll find
Bravo inside it he's out someplace
playing Santa Claus have take care of
him
no no no I'll let him have his fun he's
probably at the toy shop making toys he
loves it hurry this is ray yes yes if
you don't hurry your breakfast will get
cold rappo we're here Oh played hide and
seek a all right drop oh here we come
ready or not that's funny oh well you
turn off let's get started okay let's go
one teddy bear and one dog one pretty
boy and one girl
I can't understand it or let's try it
again what's next ferry one day fall
back
faceball tennis why this'll never do the
machine isn't working right oh dear what
else Betty toy train a toy train why why
this doesn't make sure this never
happened when we make toys by hand
something very strange is happening here
boomer I think you'd better call your
father father father this is Baba yes
Father we're in the toy shop drapeau is
in here and it's something wrong with
the Toy Machine 2 i'll be right over
it's time to go shit wake up I still
think you're making a mistake it's too
dangerous walking right into the enemy
camp tomorrow's men wouldn't dare lay a
finger on us that's why we're keeping
Santa Claus a hostage now we're not back
in three hours you know what to do all
right sim over the nuclear
just a word of warning if you've got any
big ideas forget it if you walk to that
think of the curtain you'll be just
integrated like that sabotage somebody
switched all the wiring drop who's gone
your suit is missing and now this
machine's been sabotaged put them all
together it spells voldar he was here
and he thought drapeau was me he's got
drop low and I'm going to find him Oh
drop o surprised to see us you're under
arrest hold on hahaha stop playing with
toys put it away kima we have a weapon
that's much more potent than that as you
may know we are holding Santa Claus a
hostage one false move and your little
ho ho ho man will be destroyed oh all
right what do you want folder these are
our terms first destroy the Toy Machine
second we will release Santa Claus have
you promised to send him and the
Earthlings back to their planet third no
more joy through toys nonsense on Mars
well well you win
are you sure you have Santa Claus you'll
know we have him you mean you had him
how did he get out of it hey I it Santa
Claus has powers that you don't know
about I arms up regna cargo Loomis
report this is rigged Matty mom auto and
lomas are with me good I've got folder
and stove oh I'll keep him here in the
storeroom at the toy shop right now you
come here and take them off my hands I
went hard on lomas to look for a man
named Shin tell them to search the caves
along the transfers canal right you mama
alright you two in there all right you
might as well relax you're going to be
here for a while sit down
where are you going oh can't you say
anything else with ho ho ho oh ho ho if
you're thinking of leaving SATA let me
remind you once you hit that nucular
curtain that won't even be a whisker
left what are you gonna do with this
you're gonna stand trial before the
council I don't think you'll be causing
any more trouble
you
well now I think that should do it Billy
Boy closer to our son now I think we
need a little red paint and you'll find
it in the storeroom short Santa yes
that's a good boy this time I'll take
care of Santa Claus but good and smash
that machine well by a number Mary's
strong and they're coming to get you oh
they are are they hey well maybe they'd
like to have some fun with our toys and
we'll see that they do won't be kids
oh ho we meet again eh I don't know how
you escaped sim but you won't escape me
you're through world are why don't you
relax you're going to relax permanent
you
take care of you myself dr. Sternin I
like the topic oh gee I'm glad to see
you all right inside Stovall
fire
alright ring to take them away they've
had a rough day
Oh everybody Merry Christmas you don't
need me here kemo you got a wonderful
Santa Claus of your own goodbye Billy
why goodbye Betty dear you take care of
yourself bye I've got something for you
Billy gee thanks good bye bye see we had
fun we're going to miss you do you think
we'll ever meet again I'm sure you will
children Thank You Center for bringing
happiness to the children of Mars and
the Christmas spirit to all of us sure
from the bottom of my heart I wish you
and yours the very best of everything
Christmas everybody truffle closes here
oh yes no pills
oh if we hurry we can get back in time
for Christmas Eve shall we get going
goodbye dear friends Oh
Christmas everyone oh
we
Oh
here
hey
ok
you