[Music]
maybe
november 14 1994 and we're here with
father mark Campbell for the 29th
session of the exorcism of tracy krause
Tracy can you hear me let me go we
Catholics pages the subject since our
last session two days ago has obtained a
nail file and she has filed for things
down to a point you might want to get in
here and get a closer look at this our
Father who are in heaven when is all
this good stuff you can we care about
this wretched soul demon I command you
in the name of Jesus Christ our Lord to
leave the body of this young woman now
your foul words cannot make us leave her
now
in the name
[Music]
[Applause]
this
Heavenly Father help me
Oh Leslie's Bobby oh Jesus
[Music]
father
all you need to understand about the
Romans is that they didn't think they
were doing anything on just quite the
contrary killing Christians with praise
encouraged even wear these people even
made a sport out of creating torture
methods for these martyrs take for
instance the sweet death these victims
would be bound to wooden planks with a
leather strap painted with honey and
then boxes of flies or bees would be
released to well finish the job those
who were thought to be possessed or
subject to the same treatment now if
you'll turn to page 112 and your anatomy
of the sacred texts we will learn that
more often than not the cause of these
possessions was more rather epilepsy or
some other mental ailment and not actual
deed well elbow starts thinking about
your project you can have groups of up
to three only bring people big needs a
costume and I get to watch people get
tortured all morning well this side of
theology has always been really exciting
to study a bitch of ghoul or for your
songs and I'm out doing my final on
exorcisms you will never have any books
on that topic would you yeah I think I
have some things that could be of some
service you stop by during my office
hours tomorrow and I'll let you borrow
awesome cool all right thanks fella
steam off
what up bag just we're gonna piece of
shit video so check it I got this chick
a little later so don't be here after
tip I'm done with my video I will leave
fuck that dude I've been trying to bang
this chick forever don't fuck my game up
dude Evan trying to get this video done
forever please do not fuck my game up
look just because your ass never gets
pussy don't stop me from getting it and
you wonder why I don't have any fucking
thread
[Music]
okay oh sorry must associate got my
export yeah no photo walk that'll be
good
hey aren't you that one dude yeah no
ma'am you're that fuck get out one guy
come on damn our lives in class you're
the one that gives a fuck palace
subscribe me yeah so you know you're
doing for that project yet exorcism
gnarly what about you no no just shit in
that glass did me say something about
having partners we have three up two
three well you wanna be partners you
just told me you don't do any work I
didn't matter I didn't know you come on
man you know you need you need to get
high come on me like you say her right
now right fucking now get to know me man
come on be fun so yes comment I i wanna
talking yeah I'm play Brandon awesome
good to meet you buddy come on see
Brandon kind of doing today get it is
actually done apartment my brother
excellent really working click play yeah
clay which one is that really don't get
please interesting to do an exorcism
project
this is a really intricate topic of
discussion seen how are you gonna do for
the project portion yet I was thinking
about trying to find a priest who's done
an exorcism for work and interviewing
him making a little documentary creating
the process I'm like that yeah that's a
great idea Brandon I have a list of the
closest one I'll email them to your lair
I think it's only one around this region
don't attempt to see what you find
[Music]
[Applause]
hi why do like wake up call yarn this
mom to get I need to go your glass going
to get habita kind of shit about a
thousand guerrilla find it together
what's in the deal devil worship is
Christ fifth on time we are studying a
ritual of exorcism son of a priest at a
Richmond old house socket wall st but
also signed that about this other
priests in here get extras like 20 years
ago but kill offering them children the
next town over and I got you enjoy sorry
I mean alright man way there's a pretty
skillet or what not just a pretty much a
free hugs and the white the priest
secretion system everyone accepts some
camera guy in kids where the camera
middle is yes camera maxima rethink
their record I'm not but if I'd for
money on it yeah I gotta hit it too man
you get it this patient and we should
probably try to help it
my name is Brandon gentleman and this is
clay Harper and we are in professor
tuggers introduction to world religion
class for final project we will be
investigating the ritual of exorcism we
intend on keeping a video blog a lot of
our findings and we wish to further
investigate a crime that happened 20
years ago which could have been linked
to an exorcism gone wrong based on our
preliminary research we have discovered
that among the victims almost described
as being a cameraman who actually
survived the massacre this further
strengthens our theory that this
happened during English we submitted a
request to the local police department
on to further review on the crime scene
and if there was a recording to find out
exactly what happened
cars fucking shitty chick sentiment
actually dude your mom she loved it she
was here less usually will call me clays
mom you know also if you go girl shut
the fuck up you are doing dusting man
you know I'll just decide probably slam
pussy laughs tonight if you want such a
fucking dork what's your deal man I've
had girlfriends who can't be fun
shooting yet he touching her punching
best oh no I gotta ask you question them
does that really prevent you playing
them get your dick you need to get laid
my foot in fact we need you are wearing
your dude give me the GoPro stops woven
shit or anything why are we we're
getting the evidence coming oh you know
topsail I don't really see eye-to-eye am
teasing someone just shows here with car
I'll do all the work I always is fun
hurry up cuz we only go get some foods
tacos
hey I called in earlier about doing some
evidence on a closed case my name is
Fernandez
all right for you sign this and it's all
yours now not just any my business or
anything but uh that's a pretty old case
but cool projects actually looks great
take that this is saving their evidence
we need your back my moms at school is
there food is there six and I in down in
startling
subject since our last session two days
ago has a painted nail file
[Music]
Tracy
the fuck was that and then why do you
think the tape this cut out like that he
do all that video anything shit why why
why would just cut out seriously I mean
what are you doing I going on want to go
there okay for the record I'm violently
opposed to this idea all right I'll take
you back in order myself Brandon do you
not see what a terrible fucking idea
this is are you serious right now
fucking crazy singing back you please
are you coming with you know here's the
thing i have this mislead sense of
fucking moral obligation make sure you
don't fucking kill yourself
good we're totally lost incredible are
very good at bro alright clay talk to
the audience well audience this is gone
great and keep on getting better
I
seven old camera
[Music]
oh you know no upstairs with you really
single room
fuck
functional what if I ask someone in your
brand and relax relax look around are
you good are you good yeah can we leave
now
we're down here why are you whispering
are you know
with a new domain take on THC make poor
choices
Braden don't touch that why
look like I don't care what it is let's
go
you should all not seriously
[Music]
do some back
fuck you man
[Music]
Brandon you've gone from dude with a
little too much time on his hands to
pull on fucking weirdo man this is that
that is that shit for this project what
if we could prove that possession was
real what we could actually prove that
where do we come from desert God if
there's a god is there a devil there's a
devil disease exists you're cool guy
right but how is this supposed to work I
mean after the project is over what do
you even gonna do what I was to you know
something will happen something's
already fucking happen man I don't even
know what i believe anymore well this
take this tape is real we saw this with
our own on I want to fuck with any of
this all right this is why relation with
this project has decided to use fund
me.com help raise money with the hopes
of conjuring a demon into my body and
scientifically documented medical
effects it has on me I know this may be
controversial to some people i assured
i'm a willing / and mmm found mine and
just think what this would mean for the
paranormal community to actually finally
get respect in the eye of the scientific
community if we could get actual proof
that possession is real and that demons
are too evil for your ten dollar
donation I will be putting up a live
stream of this ritual when I perform it
next week rial to watch and you will be
able to see for yourself what happens no
parlor tricks smoking everything is
going to be real how that sounds welcome
Gettysburg Address man you can pee will
donate fucked up thing is I don't the
Ambu if you don't agree with a good
bargain wanna see that shit we sharing
your facebook
[Music]
you
I know this kind of stuff is exciting so
that might even be my fault but you
don't understand even one percent about
what goes on with this this kind of
stuff for one reason or another is very
real and it is very dangerous you can't
just mess around with things you don't
understand Brandon because guess what
things you don't understand are going to
happen as your educator I respectfully
advise against you carrying forth with
this portion of a project
I appreciate your concern mr. Keane but
I have to finish this sorry true
trending topic no seriously man look
even the famous pre Scott Samuel L
excuse is Sam he's publicly condemning
you for Human Rights aesthetical actions
or what that means and she said he's
under the impression that you're going
to summon the devil and take over the
world evening friends neighbors children
of God I am deeply troubled here you
know we fight all the time to keep the
devil out of our community and now I
understand that there's a young man over
the college a boy name Brandon Jensen
who is inviting the devil into his body
into his heart into his soul into the
house that God made for his soul inside
of these are a medium we need a med
student to can you handle it oh I got
that color check that shit out check
that shit out she's fucking perfect man
like a her name is literally leeda leeda
who gave me a look at that bargain Bobby
well yeah a message to shake back see
what she has access to do we got to buy
my Tommy patient tonight is like we're
gonna add your the fuck oh my god ten
thousand dollars and shit great a
thousand people subscribe oh my god i
was buying fucking pot was as popular as
getting a ten dollar ticket to watch
someone kill themselves you know what
the hot girl just messages the later
girl and so she want to be a taught
school that means we have time to go get
some lunch these stuff steal my fucking
chips and get some 420 goal is
he brings a little heavily mercenary
many brand overnight and I take the
scalar medical maybe not hey hike uh
Brandon yeah that's me this is but uh
hmm really big helpful hi clay no thank
you you told me that you're interested
in helping us what we got going on yeah
we could pay you and any expense you
guys really cover that's it well i mean
really i'm just going to be there for
simple test we're just going to monitor
your vitals she pads on any personality
changes any appearance differences you
know he is always really keep in mind
pretty much so why are we good are you
doing this I'm in yeah it'll be exciting
definitely Bobby Brandon I got snacks
yeah looks good I'm scary are you sure
you wanna do this yeah yeah I don't know
my my parents always encouraged me to
explore every aspect of life the
prospect of all of this is interesting
to say the least I'm excited to see if
it happen why would you want to see why
would you want to be it okay um would
you be able to maybe get a great jacket
no some sort of weird but in case
something does possess me I want to be
contained until we could find a priest
or something to execution I mean I could
probably find one soon on that he found
sweet yet know about that the church so
still fuck ourselves I communicated oh
boy ran in here well I was going to have
to find some out are you guys cool with
me up the other and go
location a man flock day for night yeah
I'm good to me okay well so i will see
you guys shit man hell yeah come on show
you something man come on
thank you no problem just so you know
that I totally brought fault with me
growth with these apples
clay get the Wi-Fi hotspot set up 16
hey I just wanted to take your vitals
real quick
so nervous maybe a little it's good it's
all kind of a little scary you know now
that we're here
power
you do realize what you're about to do
right someone I don't like this I'm not
hanging dick Brennan registry man good
evening everyone why we're in the
basement of former residents of Tracy
and Richard crowd 20 years ago Tracy was
believe hasn't been possessed by some
sort of demon she was undergoing a
series of exorcisms being performed by
father mark Campbell unfortunately for
everyone involved nobody survived except
for their young son and an unidentified
cameraman is my desire to use this Ouija
board to perform a conjuring and feed it
it is scientifically possible to
voluntarily possess myself with a demon
my assistance clay Harbor and later
Morgan will be monitoring me to make
sure nothing goes wrong and our medium
Julie will be leading the ceremony
yes
no you v W X Y is anyone here with us if
someone else is here please give us an
answer what's your name what are you
doing here tell me what happened to you
waiting
waiting for what why should you Brandon
we shouldn't be here where did you get
this board we've done in the wall um why
does it matter
were there any symbol there were some
writing of something on the wall what
does that mean for us we shouldn't be
here no shit I'm sorry I gotta get out
of here we paid you to stay hey your
friend is Brandon and I need mnemonic
for president I add the fuck to allow me
to be your host body
yes yes I saw
I'm sure that get it done
[Music]
so it's been 12 hours since we conducted
the conjuring and I don't think it works
there was definitely something down
there but whatever it was um it didn't
possess me bladah has taken my photos
four times in the past 12 hours and
nothing is changed it's crazy to being
disappointed but you aren't possessed by
a demon something and I was definitely
down I know people think what they felt
sake but it was Israel Hey well neither
are you hey come on now I risked life
and limb to monitor a possessed man so
no weirdness at all something strange
totally happened on there yeah I know
but of course everyone is accusing us of
being a frog or at least bestie trending
consensus from all the fuck yous and
mine bucks hey massive attention is
always going to bring some negative box
your way this is gonna sound a little
crazy Brandon after the past 24 hours
I'd almost kind of disappointed but
nothing happens and
thing right no my gravy you wanted to
believe that all this is real I mean I
get it what better proof and lies that
good Israel than to experience evil
firsthand I honestly just one so what
happens now what's next I don't know I
don't read anything to go on with fear
but I definitely in fear testing that
with my mom should not take a firm well
at all so it could be possessed for us
to keep seeing each other I don't think
that I see the room well it has to be
continued I I have a pretty intense exam
as a setting for can I see you
mom where's that
working late mama far I'm not the one
you need to apologize to ok I need to
apologize do to make this right the Lord
what you did to try to bring something
like that into yourself hi why would you
even play around with something like
that mom's an experiment I tell one at
that were school projects it was wrong
and not only wrong but you look the
whole world see you doing it I love you
honey to my child I can't have you in my
house mom just go just go
you
amen
hey kiddo mom he she doesn't hate you
back but she is pretty upset what's
going on it seems like the whole world
knows what you tried to do and I'll be
honest with you son I'm sure that you
knew this was gonna happen she told me
that she wanted to be in the house
she'll cool down in time she's a
particular woman and to be known as the
mother of the kid that tried to possess
himself she doesn't want that I think I
know why you're interested there's some
things that I haven't told you your
mother wanted to have a baby and for
whatever reason that wasn't happening so
we decided to go another route we're not
your birth parents I'm not your birth
father
how are you just now now now how do you
say I'm not your juicing serving listen
Brendan I wouldn't do that I love you
it's impossible i'm not adopted me you
see the circumstances which led to us
being able to have you or a bit horrific
what does that even mean this priest
that you've been investigating which
killed at the exorcism of your birth
mother the video that you've been
watching I shot that your mother had
nothing to do with she had no idea I
have something you need to see
[Applause]
[Music]
Tracy Tracy what are you doing that's
the least
[Music]
haha
the Brandon
hello my name is leta I'm friends with
Brandon
ok I can go get him
your dad called and said that we need to
go to your house okay now
[Music]
bandana
Morgan all again we meet again No
crazy come in son I need to tell you so
much son your mother's day hey Brad hey
detective Garcia I just want to ask you
a couple questions about no laughter
does it matter Brandon them your father
has a pretty good security system set up
justman chocolate friends wait lucky to
try to help yo let me just what I didn't
find the author lid rattles you
soporific already talking over there
stranger it should have read off the
sound booth
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know what do you want me to do
when i see you just come down too late
but I need you come down tonight hi holy
what what what's happening muddy get out
of my fucking species fucking free
behind me
I thought I told you to stay the fuck
away you're hurting my hands Foley the
hell is wrong no chemistry or closer I
feel like we haven't gotten to know each
other I will be there he's acting I want
to change that I love getting to know
after all it's onion
Oh
[Music]
later come on tell us what's happening
do we really have to film s can't we
just go find him trust me you would be
pissed we didn't get the funk oh come on
fine um we're here looking for Brandon
something's happened and it appears that
Maeby's actually possessed Brandon's
mother has unfortunately just taking her
own life and now Brandon is not right
or the westin on campus where Brandon
storm now looking for
[Music]
have to find them we have to stop him
from doing something else something here
we go like
Oh
that can stay in the car
Brandon you okay man until I can plug
your house on us okay I said legs or
something we need to find someone like
now who are we gonna find later
[Applause]
[Music]
hey jess is the cash business whether
our system let me hear something back
[Music]
someone found a body from creative
okay oh yeah yeah 9pm will be there okay
thank you so much so so that was the
Spiritualist he said he's willing to
perform the ritual for us but he said it
has to happen where it originally did No
so we just have to get him in the car
somehow we have to go back to the house
and not go back there there's no way
record everything I the house Brandon
he's our friend think is why he wanted
help in the first place he's a good guy
clay you know that I'm now worried about
our morale I know what I gotta make a
mountain on the West I mean people are
gonna want to see this shit I don't know
that seems a little bit bathtub yeah it
is fucked up on Jesus later look what
he's gone look what he's gone through
later so we just stopped trying to help
[Music]
as Garcia knee an IP address traced
immediately
hi you're the spiritualist I'm later
thank you for coming on such short
notice Brandon
[Music]
okay all right everybody writes stream
I'm here to help you
[Music]
my rod is the front penetration of my
venom shall shatter the thing key of
that mine which is there enough love
[Music]
doesn't see this policy will show the
fear is that feeling brain helps
according to my
the great job may my spot be Marshalls
into the movement of the black
[Music]
free to do
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
granite
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
ready buddy let her go Brandon place
like this six-man I can help let me help
you come on Betty domain I read it don't
make me shoot you friend
[Music]