because I'm like very upset if they're
like a writer guide to hold things I
says bitch must fall down because they
had the most unprovoked unrealistic
fucking tumble I've ever seen and I've
seen a lot of fucking horny a menacing
just pay man it's like she's waiting for
clown face to get you up to her I think
I need to write a manifesto for how to
make good horror films because this
genre has just gone to shit what are you
talking about we got the screen movie
nothing beats the original random shit
came out like 20 years ago okay well we
got the conjuring and insidious movie
that's not the point that is the point
you just said that there were no good
our line there's some good war movie
that came out but their shitty ones
outnumber the billions that's the
problem alright so according to Parker
what makes a good horrible I don't know
the essential good dialogue characters
that I actually care about characters
that are able to use their better
judgment like if you're home alone and
you hear weird noises don't just yell
hello get the fuck out of there right I
see you're very serious I well you got a
wee wee wee wee pull them what pause
my bone crazy or do you hear that you're
going crazy I'm being serious I don't
hear anything because you're not
listening can you stop does your not fun
not trying to be funny I hear noises
yeah right we're sitting here watching a
horror movie talking about horror movies
and all the sudden you start hearing
weird noises stop playing I'll agree
that this is bad timing but I really do
hear something I'm not joking it sounds
like it's coming from downstairs if you
tell me you didn't hear today I will Bob
you okay fine I heard that but your
mom's working the night shift right so
we're the only ones here park up I don't
think that's my mom down there
[Music]
you
so what do you want to check it out I
guess why are you didn't we just have a
conversation about and I want to go do
the same thing don't allow the fuckers
doing the movies first off it's two of
us therefore we're more of a play and be
this isn't a horror movie this is life
and life motherfuckers run away what are
you talking about besides I don't know
it's not a group of intruders down there
intruders equipped with guns or equal
armful sharp as objects on assortment of
both i'm not running out of my own house
it's about the principle fuck principles
principles don't keep you alive look
I'll grab the bag you grab the broom the
broom do you want me to swoop the shower
I'm not going down I don't care what you
say how you saying i'm not going on
you
Oh
what the fuck are you doing here you
ready I live here I know that Kenan but
I thought you were at Nia's house we
were and now we're here yeah I'm like
some fucking pussies you know what I
think your voices might be a little
higher than mine oh yeah funny now which
almost got fucked up wahoo Mia Parker
bitch no not quite not quite if those
were really intruders then we got fucked
up with a quickness no doubt can we take
a little break from the hormones on the
same I'm come on
okay so it's not some other component
good dialogue from our characters that
kind of thing what is the one ingredient
needed to make a solid work I don't know
the OS doctor what the oh shit factor OS
and what's the effect are thinking about
the movies you name screen and Sidious
the conjuring they all have that OS
factor you know something fresh
something that throws you off and makes
you say oh she hints the OS factor I
just feel like nowadays for movies abide
by saying formulae blueprints and in my
opinion it really belittles it was on
influence I shouldn't have to turn my
brain off to enjoy a war movie you see
what I'm saying I want to be surprised I
want to care about what's going on I
want an experience
yo one more week to what so what so
you're fucking birthday dum-dum really
going shit like me yo I was thing about
it he goes to a strip club you are you
here yeah man please don't toy with my
emotions Erie's man but let's hook that
shit up how am I the only one in here ok
just pillow mr. roll mr. rose mr. Rome
notice me what does the board same house
sorry I'm not asking for an apology i'm
actually determine what the board says
if you have a question raise your hand !
he could read I had enough doubts but
you came through why I gotta raise my
hand though I'm the only one here it's
not like you have hands to choose from
the rules don't change rules are for the
majority I'm above the law mr. Roman if
you above the law you wouldn't be in
detention now would you ok mr. Rowland
coming with a file models I'm losing my
patience you is it okay if I go to the
bathroom Beatrice 10 free minutes before
you got here yeah but I didn't have to
go then as much as I'd like to I can't
control the actions of my bladder mr.
road you have three minutes starting
snap say I never came back what would
you do now you have two and a half
minutes you want to continue I could
make go down to 30 seconds I leave now
[Music]
what happened he didn't hit me in the
face with a fucking rock it was an
accident dudeski I said I was sorry I
was trying to chase with the rock with
Kirk got in the way oh okay what a
fucking trying to hit me in the face of
the rock it wasn't a big rock you would
have been fine Kurt's fine no I am NOT
Aidan you're clearly missing a larger
issue at hand heals her rocks at people
do chief you totally had it coming you
were being an asshole how's that being
an asshole Nick give me one example of
asshole wreath at woodworking smashed in
the face of fucking Rock whoa whoa smash
is a bit excessive I didn't want to
smash you I just chucked it in the air
with the hopes that it would hit you in
the temple I don't want to hit you hard
enough to do any serious damage but I
did want to hit you hard enough to get
my point across that you can't keep
being an asshole to people all right
well you still haven't told me what I
did you know what you do chase okay yeah
sure I do deep still in pain Kurt well
seeing as how i got hit like two seconds
ago yeah Aidan I'm still in pain but
thanks that's what I'm here for dudeski
not to throw rocks at you but to ask if
you're okay in the event you do you hit
by a rock so this cage coalition and
Sloan so long which kind of sounds like
a brothel both places are downtown so
it's like a 15 minute walk from here I
think you got between 104 Sloan's
because they serve alcohol Katie's
Coalition is 18 and over doing it into
we made into when it was living yo today
I was washing my hands in the bathroom
and this urinal flushed by itself I was
the only one in the bathroom and the
urinal that flushed it wasn't the one I
was using and I wasn't even close to it
revenge of the peepee monster Parker I'm
serious and it actually has yeah
actually happy man I can't talk in my
for me I'm not weird shit is happening
[Music]
don't touch it man does it hurt yeah
this shit hurts I know it wasn't here
last night what do you think it is oh no
man maybe scratch yourself in asleep no
how can you say no for sure if you did
in your sleep you want to know I didn't
do it in my fucking fleet park this
falls into the category of weird shit
and I need you to acknowledge that okay
what do you know about your house
whether any crimes committed here not
that i know of why i'm just thinking
about how goes and movies man you know
weird stuff starts happening and then
you find out the house that you're
living in contains a secret portal to
Hell or i don't know the last family by
left ear was all murdered under
mysterious circumstances that kind of
thing or remember nightmare on elm
street what if your mom killed someone
and now they're evil ghost has come back
to haunt you as a form of retribution
for our sins you want to turn the tv
back on the fuck Keenan I need to know
what you know about this house what must
what do you think I know that you don't
I don't know do you know anything about
any secret portals or or vengeful
spirits and give me something look
before you mock my sufferings look at
the shit how did you get that I don't
know looks like you scratched yourself
or something my nails are not that sharp
I'm telling you this has something to do
with the house Keenan has anything we
have been happening to you nope not to
my knowledge seems like you're the pond
target miles why is that
in the mocking continues I had to yeah
okay it's all fun and games until a
motherfucker gets possessed boys lost
his fucking mind you remember when we
went to the kitchen because we thought
someone had broken into the house but it
was really just Keenan Nia yeah well
first split second not even I thought I
saw something else in the kitchen what
do you mean something else it was so
quick I don't even know how to I just
felt like I caught a glimpse at
something that was I thought I was going
crazy that's why I didn't say anything
about it but now hey ma question hey
miles answer what do you know about this
house like did you get one of those
deals that was too good to be true
because something really bad happening
here oh boy no I don't know what you're
expecting to hear miles house is fairly
new it's in a good neighborhood the
crime rates lower than low that's why we
moved here doohickey up leave a message
please I promise I won't get back to you
know I know that since we've been here
things have been kosher but what about
before the worst thing that happened
here that I know of believe it or not is
mr. Huntley's cat going missing and they
found it the same day so I why are you
asking me to smile you ever kill anybody
before mom no why would you even ask me
that cuz he's mental no cuz I think I'm
being haunted by something in this house
I'm sorry did you say haunted don't miss
me ma I'm telling the truth things have
been happening to me at school then I
woke up with this it looks like you
scratched yourself that's what I said no
you know what it could be an allergic
reaction I use a different detergent to
wash your clothes why are you still
doing this for as long as ma he's about
to be 18 and you're about to be 23 yet
you still live at home with your mom
explain that to me you graduated from
college you have a job why are you still
here go home Roger knee and I are in the
process again our own spot and you know
this so leap off my testicle so
apparently I'm not sitting here sorry
mom well back to what matters well I
don't think this is an allergic reaction
I'm gonna give you something to put on
it after dinner it really doesn't look
that bad this is just I gotta say this
is delightful I'm being neglected by my
own family I just want the both of you
to know if anything happens to me you're
going to be like all men maybe we should
have taken miles as concerns more
seriously it's only we can go back boo
by then it'll be
too late and you have to live with your
mistake pass the gravy came two words
here it is over dramatic mmm actually
that's one word but thanks for playing
yo mama you can't be doing stuff like
that man my bad I thought you heard me
pop tart no I'm not really hungry
yeah what what are you doing eating my
poptart yeah but why are you chewing
like that like what would sound like a
fucking to ass i realized i was chillin
out well if you don't know now you know
I'm over here in my zoning you messing
up the flow and mother huh I'm magic
called me a giraffe though anyway you
find anything yet nope there hasn't been
a murder here in over 30 years 30 years
already used and even then it wasn't
really a murder it was a vehicular
manslaughter case so we got nothing to
work with nope I just asked there's no
reason this shit should be happening to
me okay don't get mad I know what I said
before about possibly seeing something
the kitchen but i was thinking what if
this was just my mind playing tricks on
me you will flip flopping motherfucking
you just said well I know but what am I
supposed to make of everything I mean
this is a good house there's a good
neighborhood I don't know what's going
on Oh either okay so why don't you try
to enjoy the next couple of days you got
your birthday coming up the strip club
find shit look maybe there is no
haunting I don't get you at all park now
everything is a hallucination I just
want you to enjoy your birthday you want
to make some more pasta I know you
wanted
miles miles mutt happy birthday baby
make a wish day he's still here wouldn't
you have time to make me a cake don't
worry about this looks good eat it for
breakfast youthful mother of mine
embrace me yo I love it I'm here my g
q-tip you tomorrow you got me something
yes miles to never give me anything for
my birthday how she was it just open it
I do enjoy dunkin donuts with ten
dollars that's it that's it and that's a
good deal you get a dozen donuts you can
get a box of munchkins you got
possibilities man high-value fine thanks
Kim yeah you're not welcome oh I forgot
to ask you um any supernatural
occurrences last night nope that's
surprising i expected up a full-on
possession by now yes
named miles hi mom not even subtle about
it all right let's take a trip
downstairs there's lots of cars and you
don't that mean a lot of moolah baby so
any more weird stuff nope for the last
two days nothing see happy day of birth
we got tobacco scratch off and titty and
boom oh the fuck is this strong strong
shit Miley all I did the sniff to stuff
and I'm buzzed how you doing the Harlem
shake come on Dukey glug glug glug don't
be a little whore chug that shit now
who's ready for some booties on some
booties on some food animal rimac
already
celebrate celebrate here for the trip I
ran out of ribbon I was drinking new
things two thousand on the tab on the
stupid a thick full of women dance and
like Jim k ain't none to it I'm enjoyed
life ain't a shutout dog the ball is in
the DJ fucking Club up keep it on replay
over your minutes bitch like a hundred
feet honey food truck as fuck rolling up
the best weed gangsters don't dance
always do it bump all eyes on me like I
shoot took the headsup girl D&D truck do
it like airplanes let me see if I turn
up there's only four o'clock in the
moment turns out give me and my dinky
about girls damn pic talking ball the
ball Charlie there's a gnome is no Penn
State Oh everybody wear your hands in
the air wait a motherfuckers like you
just don't care don't care if you came
like the party tonight maybe hear you
say oh yeah
drank here boys elvish ahh I'm withdraw
cool but the rock way to celebrate in it
fits like its new you drink in the air
five women what ask you to you would you
rather drink tea flavor lemonade or
lemonade flavored feet I mean either way
I lose exactly but it's about how you I
don't know man alright so if i drink p
flavor lemonade yeah it's lemonade but
it still tastes like pee so there's
really no difference from drinking
actual p but if i drink lemonade
flavored p yeah it tastes like lemonade
but it's still p you got to make a
choice either way you look at it urine
is going to be involved who that that's
the forgiving but it's l to you to
decide whether or not you actually want
to taste it i guess i do the lemonade
flavored ping ah good man thank you what
what's this if you kept this in the
strip club what about how don't question
my ways broseph that can't be a sanitary
this was like fucking butterflies what
do butterflies smell like wait wait so
fuck bitches get money does that mean
fuck bitches like have sex with bitches
and get money or is it like forget
pitches we don't need them and your
money I see I always thought it was like
fuck bitches like we don't want them
just focus on the cash flow what was it
well I think it's deliberately ambiguous
it's like I hit a baby with a check did
you hit a baby using the chair as a
weapon or did you hit a baby they just
so happen to have a chance oh I saw a
woman with binoculars did you see the
woman with your binoculars or did you
see that the woman had for dr. ok yo you
know what I could go for right now I'll
Patti LaBelle sweet potato pie yo nobody
sleep in too late tomorrow because we're
all going out to lunch little post
birthday repast say 1230 in front of
park plan plan nighty-night whole bag
yeah tonight was dope that yeah yep my
son is legal now but you know what I I
still don't get why don't you stop like
wow let it go I can't Oh Parker can you
please tell me how the fuck you go from
being just as convinced as I am to now
downplaying the whole situation I don't
want to keep talking about this all
right look the weird shit is over if
there was ever any weird shit to begin
with you're fine you had a good night
it's dunzo man yo all the horror movies
you watch and you still not hit anything
are you trying to brush everything off
and that's when shit gets serious Parker
come on I will see you tomorrow Oh
[Music]
now
but you gotta let me borrow ten dollars
I don't got to do anything Aidan urity
owe me ten dollars pay you back yeah but
you can't ask me for more money when you
haven't pay me back from before oh look
at it like this if I borrow another ten
dollars oh you twenty dollars so you'll
get back even more money no I'll lose
more money because you're not gonna pay
me back eating you still owe me photos
will loan me another five and then
you'll be even with Kurt met chase is on
some bullshit still not taken up no this
was his idea how are you gonna invite
somebody somewhere and then not answer
his phone and you think he overslept
probably you wish i had us waiting in
that Park for two hours Cole is shitting
my boy shit man I give up what are y'all
calling Ned
yeah but nothing's real right fucking
went and listened to it I don't know I
know it wasn't any of him that's a
voicemail in 10 42 p.m. we were all
walking the kitties at that time I was
seen them do it look I believe you all
right I'm sorry I believe you did you
tell your mom she's at work Kenan he's
at nice place okay let's get some food
on her systems and then back to the
drawing board I'm done with this shit
let's just go kick down dudeski door
this is simply unacceptable I got to
tell you maybe no seriously yeah I
wouldn't wait in that
[Music]
we were just with them though did you
catch with those detectives were saying
they said he was ripped open fire from
what I heard his parents came home and
they found him stuffed in the closet no
sign of a break-in nothing like that so
the corn in a freak accident which makes
absolutely no sense it's crazy I don't
like this partner I got that weird ass
voicemail I don't know who is from I got
this whatever this is on the back of my
neck and now chases I knew this wasn't
fucking done we got to figure this out
yes but we can't do shit by ourselves
here listen to it now what's this that
thing that's been following you is not
human it disguised his voice to sing you
get message you see those look like
Riddler headphones but they're not they
were designed to identify the money
pitch that is what it sounds like in its
real form some scary shit right so we're
dealing with the game that's right you
say they left a mark on your neck right
yeah that's the mark of the gar NAL's
the colonel yes
nothing but evil is a demon from the
unseen the unseen see there's heaven and
there's hell and in between there's
purgatory but just above purgatory is
the world of the unseen these are evil
entities that have their own sort of
agency if you will we're talking about
evil that has separated itself from the
constraints of hell and purgatory what
does it want with me you're 18 now your
soul is in its prime it's ready ready
for what and a lot of people turn 18 why
do they want me unlike other evil forces
the gory nose needs to be summoned but I
didn't summon it yes you didn't but
somebody did somebody made a deal with
this thing and the reward was your soul
when you turn 18 now what's so appealing
about the gory knows it can grant you
one wish and returned for a soul so why
hasn't it already taken because it needs
you this is a process the going nose has
its own way of doing things first it
stops you you won't even know it's there
that's probably what it did but those
weeks leading up to your birthday and
then it makes this presence
it hurts you that would explain the
strange stuff has been going down and
found me it means a mark on you it
always you
but it's already left its mark there's
so what is that the good news were not
good news but the upside if you want to
call it up fat if that's going to let
you lay low for a while why so what you
feed off your soul did the boros guilty
almost definitely but how it uses your
body as a host and it feeds on your soul
at night which gills is stripped to go
out until this thing gets a little
cottage that's what the people who call
for it don't realize the only reason
that leaf our soul is to have something
to feed on when it kills it uses so much
of his energy that it has to replenish
and that's where you come in basically
you are a nutritious meal and it's going
to keep on doing what it's doing until
it has nothing left to feed on and by
that point I'll be dead how's the trees
on its victims it has dibs on anyone
that mouse come in contact with even you
me not so much it prefer to younger
flesh but if your version you would live
unless you have been offered directly to
the going oh so wait virgins are really
spared that's like an actual thing so
i'm good i'm sorry that aren't that was
really inappropriate so how do we stop
it give me some time a pact with the
going nose is strong but i'm going to
see what i can find out what what am I
supposed to do in the meantime here's a
suggestion by now who fucked you over
and why we'll be in touch you guys got
my information thanks for reaching out
thank you for being who you said where
I really do want to help you all right
and this is you still have time that's
the part you cannot lose sight of the
gory knows things at night when you are
sleeping that's when you actually tis so
don't go to sleep
yo the voicemail is gone it was on here
and now it's not all year fuck man yo
who would give me up to a fucking demon
that's the golden question I'm a nice
guy right I have beef with nobody you
don't wasn't you yes mam it was me
mother fuck I in summer no demon are you
fucking cross dated oh shit what no oh
shit the OS factor what remember the OS
factor that's what separates the good
horror movies from the shitty ones that
moment that makes you go oh shit and
what about the OS fact this is a
real-life case of the OS factor I think
I know who set you up who Keenan what
makes you say King now I could be
totally off but if my observational
skills are as good as I think they are
all signs point to Keenan I mean when
he's not minimizing your turmoil he's
blatantly ignoring you he refuses to let
anyone else believe you either guilt
disguised as contempt
who is it open the fucking door teeny yo
you got a fucking problem did you some
of the gore knows I'm going to take that
long pause as a yes
what do you know about the gore knows
wouldn't you know about the gore knows
how did you find out you're good after
Keaney you're good at shit why would you
make a deal with it it's complex man now
it seems pretty cut and dry to me look I
know we've had our discrepancies with
goddamn Keenan I'm still your brother
why are you doing I didn't think it
would work that's not what I asked you
why did you do it I'm sorry miles
sorry's not gonna protect my fucking
soul Keenan I was 16 man you remember
when me and I got in that accident where
I'm my biking got hit by a pickup truck
he was a fucking vegetable I just messed
up my wrist didn't she slammed her head
in a sidewalk
they declared her brain dead
I had to go home that night she didn't
her parents went to keep on life support
but there's no recovering from that had
to bring her back
[Music]
I'll remember they did all those stories
she just woke up one day and she was
fine right yeah I always wondered about
now you know what happened bikini here's
the part that you overlooked death is
inevitable everyone has their time to
die in these timeless at that hospital
you fucked with that and you shouldn't
have you'll have the right to decide who
lives and who doesn't I was 16 exactly
you were 16 you old enough to understand
what you were doing how did you even
know how to summon the gore knows I
found everything online it's just
disturbing they came into our room one
night it was this
I can't even describe it
but I asked it to bring me back to life
all the friends you have all the people
you know when you choose really I didn't
choose you per se the Gorn no saw you
sleeping and it implied that it would be
interested in you when you got older and
I said okay all right because that makes
it so much better why don't you bring it
into our room want to put me at risk
like obviously I wasn't concerned with
logistics okay I wanted to act fast
anyway the next day he was fine and
everyone was saying it was a medical
miracle i I'm sorry miles you've
sacrificed me in order to bring back
your girlfriend and then you didn't even
give me a heads up even after I told you
what was going on you trivialize the
entire thing do you think I wasn't won't
catch on look I don't expect you to help
actually even if you offered out I tell
you to go fuck yourself but just so you
know the Colonel's has big plans you
know why I went to me what's the feed on
need because my soul is a source of
nursery this thing is a killer and after
it killed it needs me to refill itself
back up and already kill chase won't
kill again and I won't even know how to
stop
[Music]
I'm going to tell mom about this
so did you tell your mom she's working
late tonight did you call her I've been
trying but her phones off and honestly
she's not gonna believe me anyway what
about the Lark what about chase Kenan
has her convinced that I'm crazy man he
knows how to absorb himself just like
the fucking movies John he did the
adulterer in my a are they refuse to
accept the existence of supernatural
preach so no news on how break the pact
we can't just have an exorcism nope this
isn't really a possession it's more of a
bodily draining so what do we do I know
what we don't do we don't go to sleep
what's that shit man said I never sleep
because sleep is the cousin of death if
I'm sleep I'm weak and if I'm weak it's
nap time so we just got to stay up well
technically I could go but I won't thank
you and Ashley speaking of snack on I
think we need a little incentive for
pulling an all-nighter
marker Parker oh shit exactly what time
is it 132 in the morning yeah guess that
sugar overload was a bit much how do you
feel I don't even know wait I was
sleeping he got me in fact that's what
it feels like and it took third and it
then it's out there again and you
remember what he would say anyone who
comes in contact with me is up for grabs
she already got chase who's next I'm
assuming that's going after our friend
group now I know Curt still a virgin but
reg isn't and I'm pretty sure Aidan
isn't either since you're more positive
about rach let's start with him what up
my break where are you right now I went
on the walk I'm at the part where are
you going on a walk for it's almost two
in the morning I'm in sleeping now I try
to block it out but I keep thinking
about chase that's isn't going on these
walks trying to turn my head and then I
go home French I tried to tell you guys
sooner but you've got to come over my
house listen I know what killed chase
and I know that it's after you and
potentially aided were you talking about
I'm talking about the gore knows that's
what it's called it's redeeming from the
world of the unseen look it's a really
long story but
person event its meaning on my soul and
going out and killing my friends because
that's what it does it's fucking evil
sounds like you haven't been getting no
sleep either Rick I'm serious Wow my boy
there is no demon trying to kill me all
right and even if there was a demon out
here why would it be after me I do
nothing because that's what demons do
they got an appetite for mutilation
they'll kill anybody fuck a motive look
how I get some rest i think you needing
more than
fuck do you thinks I'm crazy where is
you haven't let go pass out do we this
is more over those people is they here
take it easy I'll go look Barker what
not gonna do anything to me you said you
feel weeks just stay here and relax
don't go to sleep over last if he's not
[Music]
you
love you
today
fundillo
[Music]
listen I don't care what the news
reports say it's all warm Chiefs didn't
die in a freak accident in reg wasn't
killed in an animal attack I believe
you're okay everything is just too close
together to be written off as a tragic
coincidence you know Kurt you should be
safe since you're a virgin Aiden I know
you had your little thing with Nikki but
I didn't know if you guys actually did
ever yeah we did not a virgin I two
miles what is in swing since I got
together with Mallory right Kurt I asked
you about that he's so you guys didn't
do anything first time you asked we
didn't but we got together again and it
happened you're both targets now why is
it only after people who had sex because
sex out of wedlock is the same there for
your souls are impure which is very
appealing to a murderous demon so what
now how we stick together you guys
should stay at my place tonight by the
way I'm sure you know this already but
that was a really really sick thing what
your brother did bring in the gore nose
here and everything yeah that yeah what
a dick move hey y'all gonna cook for
real hey baby he want some lasagna
Keenan near cookin no thanks but I would
like to talk to you about something sure
I want you to know your eldest son your
firstborn child Keenan levar grant is a
demon worshiper either what oh yes oh
boy looky me mania got into that
accident Mia was brain dead do you know
the odds of regaining brain function
after that they're not very high which
means Nia was basically dead but what
happened she came back to life and you
know why it wasn't some miraculous event
Keenan some of the demon called the gore
nose and it gave me a back in return for
my soul what is he talking
you're not supposed to be here knee I
that's what I'm talking about no it's
true mom didn't I tell you is gonna do
this anything to make it believable this
is real it left its symbol on me it's
right there you think I'm making this up
it's all a lot of stuff about the Goron
else is fake just like slender man just
some stuff to scare kids moms you taking
this too far no I'm not changed you need
to own up to what you did Nia should be
today okay look that is the second time
you said that stop you don't even want
to believe me but could listen to you
demon demon okay in what world am I
supposed to believe any of that you need
to stop no you need to wake up things
are happening that to fly let it go
right everything I'm telling you is true
but if you're still going to take team
inside you're fucking stupid don't you
ever in your life talk to me like that
unclench your jaw ma I'm sorry for
cursing at you I'm sorry for yelling but
I'm not sorry for what I said oh really
look everything happens for a reason we
might not have all the answers but we
don't need them and that's the part you
need to remember Quintanilla were her
real bad by the grace of god they're
both here they're both well and we're
not going to talk about this anymore
miles I'm sorry about chase and reg I am
I don't even know what to say is
terrible you are angry and rightfully so
all right but you do not have a right to
take that out on all of us especially
Nia Oh her an apology I knew this was
going to happen to be clear this is not
optional I'm sorry
I'm sorry Keenan did this cursed at me
like that yeah I'm sorry you didn't do
anything
I can't fall asleep if I go to sleep for
all at risk not all of us yes Parker
your virginity has made you untouchable
yes I'm all in for the group bonding
sesh really and truly I'm loving it but
you do realize we can't stay attached at
the winners forever right well obviously
but for right now which united we stand
divided we die if anything happens at
least we got each other's backs Kurt
Kurt oh wow wanna get something to eat
from downstairs we should stay here
we're just going downstairs we'll be
right back you know you're hungry
without you in the bathroom this whole
time yeah why hey Kurt if you can hear
me say something Parker who are you
going really 8
what happened you passed out man okay
where's Kurt I'm always about to call
911 Kurt we're glad he's awake I feel
like nobody's parents are ever home for
this shit right what the fuck this has
got to be child neglect I still feel
weak mint and that thing's probably
getting stronger yo can you dream when
you're unconscious I don't know I don't
think so cuz then you pass out it shuts
off the part of your brain needed for
sleep what I'll educated did you have a
dream I don't even want to get into it
but just know it was very unpleasant and
parker you were fucking pussy I'm sorry
I'm just glad that shit was it real you
know excluding my being a pussy this
dream could be one of two things either
you just had a final destination moment
where you envision the inevitable or the
Gorn else is on that Freddy Krueger shit
invading your thoughts using your
nightmares to fuck with you man it can't
do that Kenny all right it's 245 you
guys got to make your exit before my mom
gets here which gives us until
six-thirty by then the Sun will be up
and the gore knows can't do shit during
the daytime so for these next few hours
we've got to tough it out and please
don't let me fall asleep or feet are
they waiting stop you from fainting life
yeah we'll just be alert and if you
can't prevent the act itself trying to
wake me up as soon as poss it's still
not that easy when a per card just go
with it yes and ok
Connect four
[Music]
you
I know what you're trying to do but you
and I both know I'm not your type all
right you can't touch this
personally I think you wasting your time
in mind
you know what I mean click the shit
[Music]
you ain't gonna scare me off I hate to
let you down lets you like the first
demon that's been after me you fuck face
[Music]
that is bipolar
I know how to stop the Gordo's are you
serious how what do I have to do yeah
either you see it and done but you have
to kill the person that summoned it in
the first place and you have to wreak
ill the soul that was brought to life
they don't tell you this online but it
took several trips to seven different
libraries to find this book so I have to
kill Kenan Amy well it's a little more
intense than then you have to use a
knife and you have to stab them in the
heart that's the only way this would
work why does it have to be in the heart
the only way to guarantee that Kenan and
me'll can't be brought back it has to be
in the heart I kind of feel bad though
Nia didn't even do anything well you
didn't do anything neither did your
friends but y'all had to suffer am i
right look I am acutely aware that this
is a shitty situation but at the same
time I don't know if I'm capable of
killing someone even if it's the person
who had no regard for my own life miles
I understand where you're coming from
completely these are some heavy stuff
but killing those two is the only way to
end this if there's no Kenan there's no
gory knows he's the only reason why is
here and you're sure this is the way to
do it says it right there doesn't it I
can't do it I can't do something like
that that's my brother violence begets
violence and that was dr. King and
sometimes you
have to pick the gun up to put the gun
down that was Malcolm X he would look
I'm beyond grateful for all your help I
can't do it I'm sorry maybe there's
another way to stop it and if not I
don't know but I'm not a murderer miles
I'm going to give it to you straight
this is not the right time to become
Marley afflicted alright that thing is
feeding on your soul you understand what
I'm saying you are getting weaker but
it's getting stronger you said you've
been feigning right and that's only the
tip of the pen sir believe me miles your
friends are dying you run dying if not
going to stop unless you do something
about
[Music]
hey Mouse look I know I'm not your
favorite person right now I get it but
have you tried to empathize me is my
fucking everything I've been in love
with that girl since I was 10 while I
let her die if there's an opportunity a
clear opportunity for me to prevent it
you're gonna sit there and tell me you
wouldn't done the same thing if it
happened to someone that you loved I
don't think you realize this but the
more you defend yourself the more fucked
up you see what more can i say i'm sorry
that your friends are yeah i'm sorry the
gore nose wanted you it is what it is
just try not to think about it try not
it yo your fucking dick man are you
gonna be home tonight
why
we know
nice commute
I know what's done is done but if I can
go back if you could go back you do the
same shit yeah
not really sure what I was going back
you
[Music]
where the fuck have you been I've been
calling you all day my phone was acting
up what's wrong what yeah but it was on
the news Kurt's neighbors said they
found a scalp in his backyard turns out
the scalp with skirts and that's all
they found but that thing is getting
stronger if you kill in the daytime now
people on the news so fucking retarded
they're saying a wild animals roaming
the streets I can't they understand the
fact that this is not a worldly matter
where's ed he's fine i called him like
ten minutes ago but who knows how long
that's gonna laugh I feel he would today
what happened I know how to stop the
gorn's
kini kini what happened there's some
stuff that hasn't been sitting well with
me and what stuff would that be this
whole thing with miles hey I told you
he's in a bad place right now I just
need some time to get it together yeah
that's what you said before and I went
along with it but in the back of my head
I couldn't help but think that maybe
there's more to it and what does that
mean it means I did some research okay
and I think miles is telling the truth
no he's not Kenan I was brain dead do
you know what that means the complete
and irreversible loss of brain function
know for years I thought I was this I
don't know Wonder Woman because I was
able to recover from something like that
and no one knew how I did it not even
the doctors everyone just called it a
miracle and I mean the publicity was
awesome yeah it was but then I guess you
could say that I became contemplative
how is it that in a matter of days not
even I'm back to normal it was like you
just said it was a mirror it was
bullshit okay it was a lie and you know
it was a lie no one can recover from
something like that and if they can they
were never brain dead to begin with
Kenan you're caught the gore noce brings
people one wish in return for a soul I'm
back to life and everything's all good
and then miles turns 18 and it all goes
downhill why you sacrificed your own
brother for what for you Mia I love you
did you think I could function without
you maybe not at first but you have to
all right you don't have a choice that's
how it goes we die some of us die sooner
than others but it happens of course
it's sad of course it sucks but you find
ways to deal with it this was the only
way that I could deal with it and no one
seems to understand that not even you
Keenan different not only was this
selfish but it was just a really
fucked-up thing to do I mean honestly
who does that in thinks it's
okay and then you continue to lie about
look at how you're acting me yeah it was
selfish but that is the point you're
such a big part of my life but I've mild
was right I shouldn't be here what miles
[Music]
you
don't open the door why can you know who
it is let me go Tina I'm sure we all
know what this is about the fuck is that
it's called the night see this was not
how wanted things to play out but then I
saw how remorseless you just empty
[Music]
and I guess that prompted it change at
heart so you go stablish a happy I want
you to know that I believe you about the
glory know the team and finally admit
about fucking time
so I now know how to stop the born to
kill you
I have to kill me I'm feel terrible
about cooking this wasn't even your
fault in here but I gotta stab you guys
in the heart so you think we're just
gonna let you stab us fucking retarded
what you balling up your fist for Kenan
I mean let's use our heads here beast
versus nice not really a fair fight Nia
me let's go I'm not going let's go cute
i love you okay yeah I love you need to
use I think we should say why because
I'm not supposed to be here yet here you
all yes Here I am it as long as I'm here
people are going to die mile is going to
die khaitan I love you so much but you
got some really evil shit here and I
cannot get behind it I know a way but we
can get rid of it and still be together
[Music]
look I can't force you to do anything
that I know what I'm doing please listen
to me I don't want to be without you
don't
[Music]
seaside folks found both Canyon and
Nia's fingerprints on the knife so they
inferred that was either a joint suicide
or murder suicide and as far as I was
concerned I was at parkers when it
happened so I don't know shit my mom
thought the easiest thing to do was move
out and I don't really blame her we got
an apartment downtown that worked out
better for my mom anyway since it was
closer to the hospital and with me going
to college soon didn't make sense for
her to live in a big house like that by
herself especially after what happened
[Music]
you
the