[Music]
you
Oh
[Music]
well boys I hate to break up a good
party but you can't keep a woman waiting
tell you you know how did you can't sit
I can see you all understand all right I
believe you me boys I'm at the time of
my life tonight and speaking of time I
have a 14-karat 17 jewel timepiece and
not only like because the man i'm giving
it to is a 14-karat 17 jewel Kesha Thank
You longer boy it's a beautiful lush
greenery in all wonderful Nana cinelli
equal watch this
[Music]
three was engraved inside read till my
friend Christopher Cross in token of 25
years of faithful service from JJ hoga
1909 1934 come on great well I I I
hardly know what stage AJ mr. why it's
beautiful I never expected own a watch
like this and those there I well all I
can say is that we've got the best boss
of New York boys for thank you Chris
Thank You miles and hopeless thank you I
was hope for go well IIIi don't usually
Jay joy and pride made special for me
Murphy you're not superstitious are your
pick no no no
I don't think of a good party just
because I gotta go everything is charged
to JJ drink are you on honey don't
coming late Monday morning rang oh why
aren't you out of it Hey look look
coming
[Music]
get a load of that game just Kiki's life
oh the vault is stepping out if I had to
do you and I step out to my pillow and
laundry tonight
nothing like the smell of spring which
way do you go I guess I'll take the east
side subway gets me to Brooklyn a little
quicker hey you you haven't got an
umbrella I'll take you to you but call
them all all that's out of your way well
I don't mind walking and all fresh air
Springs hey fellows rock
[Music]
well never mind i'll text selection you
go on over the subway oh I don't mind
waiting on I feel kind of lonely tonight
they cali yuusuf Allah JJ is running
around with a young lady it looks like
way I I wonder what it's like what great
well to be to be loved by young girl
like that do you know nobody ever looked
at me like that not even when I we can
there's when we only have dreams that
never pan out with we go on dreaming and
I was young I wanted to be an artist you
know I dreamt that it's going to be a
great painter something so I'm okay here
you still think yeah every Sunday well
that's one way because I'm you know
sundays one day of the week cuz I don't
like never know what to do with myself
let us come over tomorrow and see thanks
good night Craig g'night Cholly I see
you tomorrow dr. life
you
stop raining yeah half hour so we clean
to the east side subway round the corner
past the old four blocks Thank You
officers I guess I got turned around
these streets are all mixed up and
credits village at
[Music]
is he hurt I'll go call a policeman go
away wait
[Music]
there they go in that direction how does
it look like I don't know I didn't say
thanks he took fifteen dollars they
didn't believe what though i had so i
began pushing me around and this gentle
ran in and knocked him down that's right
officer he was right there I couldn't
hold him he got up and ran wait here
come on let's get out of here but we
have to wait for the officer I don't
want to get my name in the newspaper to
you with the news for sure we'll have to
gravitation house make a complaint and
every time they're making a red they
send depicted for your house so we know
it's a nuisance won't you take me home
why yes but well then sure that was busy
well if you think that well cared for
oh sorry I kind of you to come up but I
share my apartment with another girl
Millie good night thanks for everything
uh-huh don't feel that I don't you want
a cup of coffee oh hello sorry oh this
is mr. cross glad to know you mr. Clark
uh-uh how do you do you seen Johnny and
no not take City best here there are two
coffee I think I'll change my mind I
could stand a drink or I'm calling one
level Colin oh yeah oh come on keep me
company well make mine the same
innocence I first saw your line is one
which may want kitty it's really can
Katherine half and March my friends call
me see what do your friends call you
great head ha ha ha he has a boy he's me
about it that's a hide online
why are you looking at my face dirty
I'll better this damn sight oh thank you
cheers chris Louis miss March hey yes
miss offending their shitty
well look a kitty since I'm old enough
to be your father old you don't think so
we're not a border thank you I like
mature people well what I wanted to say
was it you shouldn't be alone in the
street so late at night I'm coming home
from work what this late what do you do
yeah
you're an actress oh you are clever now
that you know all about me 20 about
yourself what do you do I i well you see
uh don't tell me we're gonna be all at
stake greenwich village is full of
awesome I mean to in Greenwich Village
he must be an artist white well uh yeah
yeah yes I paint how could your a
painted I love painting I think I took
you for a cash yeah you know those art
galleries on to value the prices they
charge I saw one little picture that
cost fifty thousand dollars they call it
uh he's a safe an old you is a great
French painter I like to own that baby
it was the 53rd I what you you can't put
any price on that two pieces like that
they're worth well whatever you can
afford to pay for them you know what
Chris are the hot sauce on your pictures
there doesn't know it next time I'll
look for your name oh no no no no III
don't sell my pictures well not in New
York no I yeah I know I bet you sell
your pictures in Europe has in some
place like that until I don't know much
about painting I bet you get as much for
your pictures in France and those
Frenchmen get right here in New York and
you never appreciate in your own country
well that's one way of looking at it but
you know what I painter I don't think of
money I just paint for fun fun yes I
think it's the most fun I no oil
painting I wish I had all the time to
paint but don't you have time oh no oh
well yes there you see aya
well you know business takes a lot of
time I wonder when you get all that
money well what what player you acting
in my clothes tonight which one come on
ours at what time
[Music]
it's only ten past 200 times Achille to
be in bed so you won't forget thank you
can I see you again I'll do it sometime
what if you're giving your telephone um
have you gotta top of me I write you
that's your dread good i cook kitty
who's counting why do you ask that but I
just heard you ask the bartender hello
oh sure he's at the fellow I know he's
done Lily's boyfriend you know the girl
I loved was good night kiss good night
kitty
[Music]
please
ok yes I del
[Music]
well well this is a pleasure I didn't
expect to see you Charlie but critics
you ask me why well it's that you
couldn't see you anyway yeah say enough
that was a 12 party last night was
McCauley yeah yeah yeah what kind of
wood we go home but after midnight
wasn't it you know I have been to bed
yet you haven't I get a lot is over I
thought I was a charlie no oh I got to
do the dishes for Adele you know mine
Charlie did no no ready
hey did you paint this Great Scott no it
isn't painting that's mud done by
photographer who is the late departed Oh
your wife's for my husband Detective
Sergeant Higgins oh hey that's a really
talented yeah and L got it your wife
yeah after he was drowning me Stuart
jumped in to save a woman neither body
was found oh but yeah is bad oh thank
you I'm stuck London people are afraid
five years went on Lao Shi Jie didn't
want to spend his insurance money so she
rented out the spare room twenty-four
dollars a week well I was trying to save
money to buy paint some so I moved in oh
she was sweet but I wouldn't melt in the
mouth and
oh you know how these things go smoke oh
where are your paintings great they're
out in the hall would like to see what I
did today yes I'd like to we need to
find a flower like that you mean you see
this when you look nice well yes that is
III saw feel it you see when I look at
that flower I see some very tied in the
top I'm sorry I do hola
[Music]
Oh
whoa whoa
whoa
or as you get those lazy legs off that
couch Vinnie commit can't you do any
better than that that's all you think
about lazy lengthen what else is there
to think about
if you want more heat in this apartment
you'll have to call it gentlemen he's
awaiting it I'll come your vote not on
me baby oh stop talking about saturday
night I'm not talking about saturday
night I'm talking about this sounds like
a schoolboy trying to make a date you
must be robbing the cradle what's so
funny you are you don't enough to be my
father the old Selim came to my rescue
Saturday night my hero no kiddin see you
were too tight to remember anything if I
hadn't told the cops gone the wrong
directly to pick you up this your fellow
but it is the painting he's rich and
famous and very sweet to Johnny he
doesn't pull any rough stuff like you y
de gently clean up in a crap game all I
needed was sexy buck and what did you
show up with 15 fantastic that's all I
had besides you kept me waiting two
hours in the rain and then you gave me a
dirty look I didn't get you a dirty look
less than any girl awaits two hours in
the rain for a guy is gonna give my
dirty look trouble with you baby is you
have no imagination would expect me to
do I expect you to use your brains but
cats make this tempest crazy about you
this is a setup isn't it big money you
said fifty thousand I pictured here I am
knock on my brains out trying to raise a
little capital and this is right in your
lap you don't have to call what's his
name and get a measly 50 this bird is
goofy about you write it datarow oh I
can't take money off an old man like
that
as I can't say it be carded and smart
lazy lake why she thought in a big go
without have my brains but ability is
one no you're gonna have money to make
money capital but the boys at the acme
garage it cut me another happened is
that I can put up the money how much do
they want Oh three or four thousand yay
hope I can't sick i'm not talking about
chicken feed use your imagination you
get an interest in a business like that
lets stitch to squeeze out your partner
then you're uneasy see she through the
pipe dreams you have thought what about
the letter so i can get 50 really
perhaps but i can't get the kind of
money you're talking about wouldn't at
all Johnny Johnny where you going what I
won't be wasting the time John hey jump
I don't know why I'm crazy about you oh
yes you do so what about my proposition
you don't have to have the hotel for
lunch not at first look at their decent
apartment someplace where I like to come
and see another don't like this well
lately I come into my own apartment
hello funny face I could just go get
Johnny then I can move out I'm Ellie
stop to be on my fiance how do you spell
that word whether they're like a funny
thing she plays at the renters would be
that was a dental idea Big sharply time
to leave well I don't mind if you want
this base yet though fielding you mean
by that nothing you know Johnny yeah I
know Johnny all right they bought to
that engagement ring yes I you seem to
worry more about it than I do
[Music]
new $45 model Rogers let me have a great
team that he made a profit of that
pursue a modeling girdle for the catalog
I have been oh I ate like a dog causes
never come back I swear I'll quit
modeling why don't you go back to work I
figure you want to dawn lately what do
you think you are my guardian angel not
me honey I'm also wings a long time ago
hmm that's what I saw one you got farted
on snippy you never could get to work on
time after you mess that jolly nice
happen to you don't you wish it could
happen to you I'm in love crazy in love
the man that pushes you around the way I
would with the cataract you mean Johnny
out of it you don't have to figure could
any man you want to but there's only one
I won't yeah anything you travel I guess
you wouldn't know what of it hitchin
update that word
[Music]
that Robin think just like I feel they
looked at fear of them up ever building
their nest hey where'd you learn man oh
when I was a kid yeah but I haven't done
that for years yeah I feel like a kid
myself today
sold any pictures lately why don't you
paint my picture right I do could i
bring my use with your apartment oh I'm
afraid my girlfriend wouldn't like that
how long does it take you to paint a
picture well there's some times a day
sometimes a year you can't tell it has
to grow I never knew paint could grow up
feeling gross you know that's the
important thing well I you take me well
nobody ever taught me out of drawer so I
just put a line around what I feel when
I look at me yeah it's like it's like
falling in love is you know could you
see someone them and it keeps crying and
kid he can't think of anyone else well
the way I look at things thats all art
is every painting is it any good is a
lovely I never heard anyone talk like
that oh well
that on maybe what you can talk to this
way tell you keep it to yourself you
walk around with everything bottled up
yeah that's right that's where is with
me too I'm keeping things bottled up to
Chris and truth is I'm gonna jam you can
you probably guessed that i'm broke in
this bread belongs to Millie I can't pay
my rent well how much is it out I get it
I shouldn't have told you destroyed a
day Oh cutie huh get out of it I
couldn't take anything from you Chris no
oh yes I mean no no I couldn't I've
never taken money from a man and I'm not
going to class and I'm not going to
spoil our friendship oh good kitty huh
could you pay you back Oh Chris maybe i
could pay if you put up the money for a
studio apartment and i have a place to
live you could paint don't you see if
you paint my portrait
what's the matter don't you want to
paint my picture something I got can you
kitty what i deceived you I lied have a
married man G I did you tell me you know
i'm not the kind of girl to run around
with a married man don't you you know
what you said about meeting some how you
begin to like them and you can't think
about anybody else tell me I had a wider
Chris but I'm not in love with a kitty
you married it I was lonely I couldn't
stand my loneliness
well then you're not angry with me I
suppose I ought to be I'm not not with
you Chris and would like to help me how
much do you need five hundred dollars
[Music]
I need five hundred dollars i could pay
it back ten dollars a week that's all I
was crossed can I have a cosigner thank
you property owner company on it just a
formality thank you very much right on
well I kinda don't stink plant hold up
if you away you don't even make enough
money to buy your radio at the one
downstairs every night to listen to the
radio and I have to say and you're
wasting money on peeps I'd like to love
it you do without me Roma if only you
had a great but I could put to the
flowers how are you nice little area I
had for the word with your mouth I've
been better off a widow the only reason
I would have with you is because I
married till your eyes duck yes and I've
stuck to me oh I have been expended
bread are you fucking at me well you
keep blaming me for not buying you a
radial but you think I like running
downstairs they denied service for the
radio 1 into x ray do you have money
he's been short and funny well I don't
want a radio you wanted never catch so
spawn there's my old age home over the
live I'd have a radio he made a good
salary he gave me a good home well
you're living in the same apartment
aren't you yeah okay didn't spin up
paint i fantasy percent of paint i know
i don't see any pictures cutting up the
whole if you don't get rid of that track
I swear they were gonna do man that girl
I swear I will people and the things you
baby it is bad enough when you used to
copy be super spa well who truly all
copies postcards and he's considered a
great painter not your coffee too old
and his plane is getting crazy and all
the time
I still want people did hey they still
retain d we're not cool I never saw one
without me fo the happy household our
just coming on dear I'll be right down
door the cops came home late go ahead
and eat I then do the dishes this is a
happy out sold out at this time by a
happy hour bubble / no soap gives you
more happy more watching and more suds
for package than happy hour bubble third
ask your new role for the large economy
size package today and now for the next
episode of illness hope for happiness I
do remember that filled a long
what you Kelly I was I was looking for
paper hey blind oh so I didn't show if
you like the radio if they're not quite
a bit of a problem I wouldn't have to
generate him there did you read this
week what this murder in Queens a man
killed his wife was a winter weight put
a body in the trunk ship to the
California it says here I break the
paper thank you you just get away with
the city you go to the chair as he
should yeah man has got a chance with
these New York detectives and to put
that paper down through the ditches
Adele you didn't mean what you said
about getting my paintings away to the
junkman we will find out
well you won't have to a friend of mine
is taking an apartment in Greenwich
Village I'll know everything there what
he's old enough to need to do it go
ahead the sooner the better top floor
you'll get plenty of life lots of
privacy you've heard of tony romera
illustrated he had the department on a
three-year lease pretty fucked anywhere
else this was excusable their sketches
on the wall over there to do that with
his model sometimes when he's working on
magazine cover some people pay a lot of
money for those are you an artist miss
March haha where's the bedroom going
this way what's the rest mr. dome 150 oh
there are some things that Rivera left
your stores the basement they go with
the apartment compared to using here
vigil I don't like the wallpaper well I
change the paper I guess so long on
year's lease I'll pick it up and up
Oh
pull don't break the bank hello lazy
late I heard the doorbell
[Music]
so this all you've got I'm lucky I had
that left the way you were throwing it
around last night you even bought me a
book honey you're supposed to be an
actress thank you Shakespeare pete's
sake
hey so I have loved you know where to
get more done to lady Knight told me how
solid is acute for a long time and I'm
is hot roll
[Music]
look Kitty I need at least a thousand
dollars ouch we had kind of softened up
now pushing around a bit seems to get
scared when I talk about money listen
baby you got him right where your water
he's on the hook and can't get off he
can walk out Connie he's got away
presently just drop a hint that his wife
might find out about this apartment your
shell out there that's blackmail it's
only blackmail baby when you're dumb
enough to get caught that Hamlet told
you hear the doorbell but that's it get
rid of it
[Music]
ah go down to doraville but you am at
peace offering scotch thanks hi I didn't
think you were all twenty ten thousand
twelve all right I rang dog doesn't
Obama door was open when well when
they're doing all right for a working
girl don't start that again
don't tell me he's under the sofa to
know bright-eyed doesn't come out Johnny
all you have to do is call but I say let
me to kill Ian Wallace a misprint
Christine last time I saw Johnny he was
talking about going to Hollywood I might
try it yet well I read in a movie
magazine about a fellow who landed in
Hollywood stone broke and cleaned up a
million no experience easy all he had
was look and he worked in a drugstore if
he was Johnny he didn't look like you
owe you two stop fighting I'm not
fighting baby she just has no my speed
why you're a movie actors getting five
ten thousand a week for what for acting
tough for pushing girls in the thing
what do they do I can't do you're so
clever why don't you do it I might funny
face I might
good I brought over some of my things
kitty I bring some more tomorrow arrest
on Saturday oh you have company no I'm
Johnny sure you know Lily's boyfriend
come on I want you to meet now even have
a friend of mine that's across that's
ray how do you do miss ray please meet
you at the cross and Johnny print glad
to know you mr. cross how do you do
seems to me I've seen you before
somewhere could be could be mr. Grubb
yes I I just don't seem to remember
maybe I'm mistaken could be well I'll
run along yet I'll go with you
sweetheart oh don't bother Johnny I
wouldn't think of let me go alone
darling you might get run over by a
streetcar goodbye mr. car oh nice to see
you thanks for the Scotch Mellie that's
okay bye dog duty oh darling and what's
the matter Chris I I don't think I like
that young man she's in love with Oh
Johnny's all right oh I know he is there
wouldn't be a plane but there's
something about him that she crazy about
would you what would you like to see my
pictures not come sit on
you're happy for the first time in my
life very happy I think of you all the
time all I wanted to see you be near you
i know i have many right to ask you this
but have you ever well that there must
have been another mandible just one you
still see him
I forgot look Kitty if i were single if
i had no wife but you have a word yes I
know but if she did well if something
would happen that would make me free
would you marry me oh let's not talk
about it now there what I'm worried
about is getting a job living like this
is expensive I don't like to ask you for
anything more because they haven't
thrown any pictures late but don't you
have enough money no idea what a problem
money is for an actress Chris town
doesn't count mascara everything is cool
contact knowing the right people have
you got an agent they charge plenty
where's my clothes in creston open kitty
you're beautiful ah faith doesn't mean
hey clothes perfume is making the right
impression finances maybe thousand
dollar to get a decent wardrobe I was in
dollars at least love you Ivan Bart for
milling auto boyfriend John pick up
plenty of money oh no no no kitty and a
lot from Johnny I know well I'll get you
the money you're in some way you're a
dog I really believe you're in love with
me I am today I am thank you here at
caveman I I like you to like me but well
as a limit if I know
well I've got to go I'm supposed to be
back and I'll coming of Marvel kitty
I'll be waiting for you I'm sorry you
have to go bye bye you don't forget the
money I'll get it
[Music]
I don't get it the puss Pat let's be a
hophead since snakes on the l imagine
anyone paying money kind of stuff hey
are you sure he's not a phony ah he's
too dumb to be a phony right there and
how'd he get all of money why is he had
to work for a living he couldn't make
fifty dollars a week we just don't know
hard maybe not but I'm gonna find out
about it I kind of like this one where
would you find flowers like that I
wonder if I couldn't sell it and what do
i do and yeah where they are then you
put them in storage you know you gotta
protect him it can leave valuable
paintings lying around where somebody
can pick him up you'd get in trouble any
gallery know his work he tried to kiss
me today and don't think I liked it oh
you've been kissed before saini they're
not even sign how that doesn't matter
they'd know him that's where I take him
baby Johnny I can't stand to have
anybody touch me but you uh I hate him
when he looks at me like that they were
meaning they're vicious or he bore me
out is something I'd like him better ah
you don't love me you don't defend what
I mean no
no well maybe
working late tonight which cross I
levoxyl then you can let me out come in
it yes sir
[Music]
just caught you in time
this is all I will you Chris careful yes
yes yes of course okay
choose me thank you good good night
thank you
hello where you got the fella that
painted or get 50 grand a single picture
hey what's the matter would you lick
where'd you pick them up over watching
those where the village long hairs are
peddling junk like that for the price of
the canvas these were tainted by any
village long hair that's my pawn shop in
it and that snake is strictly from the
Bronx the fella lives in Brooklyn he's
favored you know what is name well I
look Nick I go to stuff before you never
asked for any name on it that was
jewelry bring me some more that we can
do business Johnny take this junk back
to Washington Square where you got it
I can see you've got an eye for art and
that's one of my best in telepathy oh I
didn't know you were painted I'm not
having any good well they've got
something peculiar honking but no
perspective is that important I should
say it it look at my baby where did you
write I didn't I am I want to sell them
or you want me to tell them on
commission how much is it worth I always
start everything and winning fine then
you know it's a hard business selling
pictures and people don't buy art malady
no appreciation no taste no perception
and no perspective
let me have your name and address I'll
come back later salon hiya honey which
is bad ethnic what about my ring and I
would take the diamond course I came to
nine hundred dollars but you pipe down
you've been telling me what a dope the
old guy is maybe yellow big dope he
tells his paintings are worth a lot of
money did you check up on his toy what's
wrong with us there was just 25 bucks
apiece that's what's wrong here crazy if
I worded gentlemen don't get somewhere
when I don't tell me I'm crazy
I generally old boys are folding his
money is in finance they could borrow
dough or have it stashed away or even
steal it Chris deals jeepers Johnny he's
not the type he wouldn't have nerve
enough to be well it didn't get us some
ass pictures may be dumb but not about I
a day he took me to the museum he
explained how everything was done you
should have heard him people sit around
with what do you Sam the metropolitan
yipe they've got pictures there with a
million bucks
[Music]
are you going I'm gonna make a monkey
out of you let'slet's you can taking
pictures to the museum who says I can
you know who welcome k today with Jane
why don't you delete to take me haha
he's an art critic the best authority
New York and mother part he took one
look and bought the boat I couldn't even
get hit like and cares not for nothing
he wants to get hold of you they told me
to telephone him you like you know
[Music]
fantastic what's so funny you are Marty
pan you're the mr. Fixit was going to
make a monkey on a poor dopey little
kitty so you gave away two pictures for
a couple of times and now you can't
collect the dime Oh dry up pieces now
what when i'ma go tell Chris he won't
find out that ahead he won't that Jenny
way the critic he writes for the
newspaper Dalia got us in a thought I
told you not to do it you're just
nervous the old guy solo don't know me
from Adam give me that drink I can use
it good huh he's gonna keep go ahead and
see what is here
boy I beg your pardon but we're looking
for a man and I'm afraid I don't know
his name oh and I'm afraid I can't help
you I'm sorry
there these are you oh there he is why
did you run away from you like that huh
here fifty dollars left way to put can't
I don't know what you're talking about
what the big gears you brought me
perhaps the better introduce ourselves
my name is Jane way Lizabeth develop how
do you do what is it you want we'd like
to find out who painted the picture you
don't know of course they don't know
that's what we're here for look if
you're a friend of the painter you put
the favela in touch with him why did you
buy those pictures if you don't know who
painted them because they're good who
created
no John no oh don't be so modest let's
part now you see it got me in bed she
made me promise not to tell that's why I
mean I like I didn't know haha she's
funny about a painting never let anyone
see it doesn't mean put her name and I
picked you so I am good your next
partner I'll just look much oh no these
you can't stare for anybody to talk
about it because the idea pictures
weren't any good that's why I took those
do to you to give me confidence I knew
they were good now I'll take that money
I never wouldn't get it was a woman all
right your work is very strong as much
maybe see some warming sure go ahead
look at this duty of a
you're crazy to try anything like this
which I think I thought they were cops I
know what I'm doing they don't know from
nothing I can't fool my critic you
always wanted to be an actress not a
chance you've been around the old boy
long enough to pick up his lingo be
Janeway coming ahead I'll get him in
here alone with no way how long has she
been painting ever since she was a kid
mr. Janeway never one dog school did you
know she just picked it up I guess I'm
the only one with an encouraging her
kind of hopping along as a friend you
know just at that oh I didn't get your
name Prince mr. janely she's kind of
upset maybe he can talk to him Plateau
well it did LOL i love this March let me
have qualities well it depends what's in
it for I still have to be built up mr.
Princeton
I can usually tell whether a canvas has
been painted by a man or woman but you
fooled me completely miss March your
worth is not only original it has a
masculine for how long does it take you
to paint a picture sometimes the day
sometimes be here you can't tell have to
grow of course to matter you know how
how feeling in Rome it's like like
falling in love again that's a very good
description my eye look at every pain
with any good is a lov man ok oh no no
no please don't write about I can see
you're going to be a very high cake why
don't you have confidence in York
because I can't fill you do i I just put
a line around what I feel when I'm with
me not very stimulating person to talk
to are you two getting along I think I'm
breaking me I skinny mr. della roll
wants to handle all your work
exclusively is it all right as a friend
that advise it could you come to be
galleries tomorrow what time any time
that can be how about twelve o'clock
then lunch at food with me well I she'll
be there I'm glad you're around with the
Prince to make up her mind for us I can
see your tiredness March this has been
enough for one evening we'd better go
until tomorrow thanks Teej anyway so
long goody
night mr. Dolan good night good night
basically I don't know what to tell Jane
way but you gotta meet you right out of
your hand it won't stop with lunch Wow
what's the difference if you mean oh
stop acting like a great kid let him
talk about what he wants to talk about
he would talk about art I had any sense
I'd walk out on you you haven't got any
sense
[Music]
right here just like you sent a letter
come on Catherine March good thing put
that one back okay Chris Oh kitty I
happen to be in the next oh hello mr.
girl I just dropped in I thought money
was here see I hope you don't mind my
looking at depicted oh no are not at all
mr. crash fine work that remarkable
paintings you have a little trouble with
perspective don't you yes that's one
thing I never could master perspective
well I guess I'll have to run a lot so
long to god it really dropped in town
i'll be at Tiny's play don't bother I'll
let myself out she went here long you
know why I know Micah Hyde Chinese
alrighty tonight fella Chris really is i
don't know why you don't like him well
lou is he the one one what well you said
there was one man I haven't they won't
you ever forget that it was no go ahead
and paid if you want to i'm not going to
stick around if you're going to torment
kitty Oh kitty Oh leave me alone i'm
going out for dinner hey kitty don't be
angry why didn't it come here if you
want to quad an ass gonna come here oh
please kitty Oh Pete late going paint
and I can't I I can't do a thing when
you're angry with me you want me to go I
want you to stay here and paint
Chris I'm sorry Chris but why do you
torment me about something with over and
done with well because I would you mad
at me you can't well if something might
happen what you better not let your life
hear you talking like that of course I'd
marry with you were free but you're not
so let's not talk about it then you go
on and paint what could I thank you well
I was going to do this myself but paint
me Chris
helping masterpieces
[Music]
hello i do i dropped over the butcher
shop like you told me to I got a nice
piece of liver how long have you known
Catherine mom answer me I don't know
what you're talking about how long you
know her and I don't get excited let me
help you off with your colleagues the
one that's excited if I just take away
the next night wanna cut my throat
all of you know her I don't know what
you're talking about don't like you've
been coming our work for years but then
you created those pictures out of your
own head and all the time you were just
copying abuzz but realized I take you to
dinner rolls every day making know where
you go we're gonna roads are guaranteed
seventh Street I got a window for a
painting by Kathryn March you're talking
crazy get five hundred dollars for a
single picture to the genius no wonder i
used to be sometimes with something in
your work now i know why if you with a
dual pieces around here i swear i like
that woman a letter telling her you're
seeing that idea defeat does it better
watch out or next thing you were
stealing his money not that one honey
dela Rosa is the more effective Chris
just finished and Alyssa Bingley 30
little pictures are the best things
you've done wasn't i right about Janeway
lady lake yeah but he gets on my nerves
I've been out to dinner with him three
times this week and now he's talking
about breakfast he's getting that look
in his eye all you gotta do is keep it
there wow so very well see you say but
what about the wear and tear on my
nerves alpha will take care of kids baby
gonna have a big diamond ring and a
shiny limousine and a penthouse and
Johnny he goes with that plan huh
Chris how did my pictures get into villa
rose window how Chris don't be angry
with me no I'm not angry i just can't
understand it's not possible if you
donated night how can i take the
furniture back haha it was humiliating
us I couldn't ask you before Jesus
Pacific hi Jerome you actually so much
thank you oh I know I should put my name
on him mr. Delano wanted to know paid
him enough I just creep even wanted no I
can't love different Kevin oh ok pile is
it didn't seem to make any difference it
was the funny part is it made a great
deal of difference if I brought those
pictures to a lan like Del Arroyo he
wouldn't have taken them I am afraid
here kitty oh you're a great painter
critical mr. daughter said so and so did
mr. Janeway face me I am well they're
gonna keep on saying oh not door don't
kitty not don't cry I'm happy why you're
just like a dream this is so good so
good who or what difference it make
whose name is on those pictures yours or
mine why just like we were married fully
I take your name well let's give me a
little Authority around here I want to
thank you picture kitty how about it
color
no what we're gonna call this
self-portrait
[Music]
what about Damon hello there hello well
this is the first time I've ever agreed
with you Jamie thank you I find the
paper even more fascinating than
obtaining what you like Mona Lisa
without the prior something hidden
sometimes it seemed as if she were to
people i mention that in my notice would
you more tentative
[Music]
because man outside says want to see who
I get an answer which day was a
detective
[Music]
you the detective well I used to be mr.
car don't you recognize me
[Music]
quite a shock huh I don't think keep
your head I'll explain everything while
I was in trouble at the time I've been
collecting the rule extra money to
speakeasies along the water we're good
around the headquarters I was up for
investigation we might have down the
Brooklyn Bridge trying to fix things up
man comes in the speakeasy and says oh
just jumped off the bridge so I run out
Carol Michael jump in class so i'm
hoping i don't come up again in mine
well there i am swimming around the dark
hell over that one next thing a normal
tired up I heard tug boat whistle on
right down on top of them come to cool
bark so I grab ahold climb aboard I look
down my hand what do you think I got her
pocketbook that's what I grabbed ahold
of when I thought it was her hat and
inside is twenty-seven hundred dollars
and folded money imagine anybody
committed suicide with that much money
well the coal barge unloaded on a banana
boat bounce around Derek well I want
with yes but if you're not dead and then
I'm not really married to a girl and why
[Music]
what's it worth to you for me to keep my
mouth shut just say the way yes / but if
you're at Dells husband and wait a
minute I see you need Adele I need money
your cashier does it being easy for you
to put your hands on a couple of
thousand III couldn't do a thing like
that if you're going back to look now
but not to do you a favor mr. I'm
clearing out for a dell sick and don't
think you're going to get any peace of
mind either I might turn up again
someday she'd kick you out in a minute
from man like me oh I'll get you some
money nothing are using their head and
which you will have to wait here I can't
get it laughs to be close to fix clocks
oh wait hello Johnny Luke easy I am I
getting high don't forget the champagne
baby nice god I'm gonna study you go
fast I'd like to see any cops attic
catch me I give you a four-pitch a
bucket full of that I ok Jimmy
[Music]
can I body I think you give it back
thank you
only 200 good well that's all I could
get don't you think your wife's worth
more than that the guy I want you to get
all that's coming to us take it and what
about the insurance money insurance yeah
two thousand dollars on your life Adele
collected if he is really yours isn't
she keeps it right in their bedroom now
I I wouldn't touch a penny of it mr.
Higgins but if you do good it will be
perfectly legal but just help it but I
get a TV this is the night that she
always goes on to the movies I let you
in you take the money and ritual but why
don't you get it all I got to be able to
say that I didn't touch it you know
Adele what if she don't go out I show up
and goose is cooked and so I can play it
safe huh one will come along the street
and let the clock tonight
[Music]
okay will you whisper become the light
syrup this is Michael's remembers
Michaels don't you oh yeah neighbors
where's the money in there in the bottom
drawer chest please you mean hurt
Johnny Oh Johnny lazy jeepers I love you
[Music]
okay Johnny's Chris call them quick I
gotta push you over on you how do I know
he was coming here tonight I don't know
thank you don't understand anything why
gets all red well what you so my brains
if I'm tied up with a dumb cook like you
I told you to watch your step tonight
that's right blame it on me oh I had to
keep you here and I didn't want to say
John don't talk like that or the truth
I'm fed up with it chillin that's the
only thing you are brothers time
[Music]
hey
people are you
oh lord have mercy upon us sinners the
way of the sooner it makes plain wood
stove but the end thereof is the pit of
hell Oh Lord be merciful to me a sinner
noe yeah kitty hissing Johnny I thought
he'd go to chinese would he getting
tight so just a fight listen he can't
live without me any more than I can live
without him city was coming back here to
beat me up jeepers away that guy shoots
off his mouth oh you don't have to warn
me that's just the way he talks you were
in love you'd understand oh stop it
Johnny wouldn't kill a fly oh that's
love honey curious now Oh God goodbye
hello Johnny come on Johnny I heard you
you lied to me kitty was handlers man
can I help it if I'm in love no just an
infatuation he couldn't love a man like
Bad Kitty he's evil he wouldn't let you
alone isn't that right I wanted to kill
him well that's wrong why'd you come
here to ask you to marry me I like your
wife have many Wi-Fi Spanish a custom
turned up I'm free oh no don't cry to me
I know how you feel but that's all over
now we all make mistakes I don't care
what happened I I can bear you now I
want you to be my wife we will go away
together way far off so you can forget
this other man don't cry Gibby please
don't cry I'm not crying you fool i'm
laughing oh you idiot nah man i'm andy
so dumb kid I wanted to laugh in your
face a dozen bikers met you you're old
and ugly and I'm sick of your 666 kitty
p.m. think you'll kill Johnny I'd like
to see you try why he'd break every bone
in your body he's a man you are marry me
yo get out of here down go
Hey oh look out Johnny you kill it
somebody
[Music]
you
right
so long grace sweeter what made you do
it Chris what he's officers called me I
wouldn't believe we've been tipped off
on the telephone while their name
tickets I check the cash before you came
in here on which is missing over twelve
hundred dollars will take them along you
can make the complètement olgar
homework I just can't do it but mister
holgado you've done your duty and I'm
obliged to you box of cigars on the
table take them along with you ok mr.
holga felt ill
Chris it was a woman was a tough sell
I'm not going to put you in jail Chris
only of course you're through
[Music]
well I didn't do anything i'm oliver i'm
on a lawyer where would you picked up
riverside drive tried to get away in the
murdered girls car that was my car this
is yours too it's got your initials on
it but its heart blood is only the forty
dollars taken out of his pocket book it
was mine sir diamond ring were to try to
stretch our dollars uh you guys know a
lot don't you it costs 1200 this is your
personal jewelry not much value but he
chained around well why would entice you
didn't have any more use for 30
listen you guys I want a lawyer I'm a
citizen I got my right this belongs bo2
huh it's got your fingerprints on it
well naturally I picked it up how did I
know she was dead I thought she was
asleep at first she didn't paint those
pictures old crosses in his dumb as he
looks he paid it up the at youth brought
me two pictures he told me miss March
painted them in my expert opinion
there's no doubt about it she was a very
great artist she told me she was an
artist when she rented the studio he was
with her I didn't like him then and I
don't like him now yeah he was mean when
he was drunk he said he was gonna fix
when he left my place around two a.m.
that's when I tell him you don't tell me
you kill her somebody so he killed her
with my ice pick and dad her to say
hello Johnny before she hung up he was
there all right what I wanted to stand
to talk about her being an artist I
never saw paint that was one of her
peculiar trait she never let anyone see
a paint I've compared the handwriting
with a signature there's no question mr.
clock pink the only copy their work he's
a thief is don't believe with employer
from Catherine much my wife I mean my
former life is correct I really can't
paint
my copies were so bad I had to destroy
them mcafee he's lying how old mr. cross
Oh firm cock reason glow oh yes Tom
Crocker a Joe Williams morning world
Hollywood alleged hi-c retro thang thang
singing yeah I don't like the cover
excuses but I must say this is one I
don't mind you sure coach johnny lewis
with the cost when you testified you
couldn't think nobody cooked Johnny's
goose except Johnny way shot off his
mouth it was a dead pigeon when he
dragged the girl's name for a month I
watched patchouli did he kept you
fractured he might have got off the ride
sure the evidence was only
circumstantial what do you mean not a
fair trial at me yeah but it's always a
doubt I suppose you fellas are gonna
save it as a miscarriage of justice and
someone's getting away with murder not
me there's no such thing mr. cross
nobody gets away with murder how's that
oh don't get it started you don't your
ear off that dispensary all right go
ahead laugh all you like but no one
escaped punishment I figure we have a
little courtroom right in here judge
jury and executioner I don't get it well
murder never solved anything how about I
told you covered let the trial I'm sorry
but I have to admit you're right the
problem just moved in here where it can
never get out right here in solitary so
what so you go right on punishing
yourself you can't get away with it
never now that is make an expense well
you haven't seen as much of murders i
have missed across i'd rather have the
judge give me the work and they have to
do it to myself
[Music]
the time that throw the switch eleven
o'clock
Oh
I didn't do it I said I didn't do it
would anybody believe me gimme a break
somebody is plenty of my life or
somebody Bobby give me a break
[Music]
Johnny nah I'm here baby Johnny yeah
oh you waiting how can they be soaked
down oh no you wanted to marry you you
killed me Chris yo hold and I'm playing
you killed me no no good it did him
you're innocent you were pure that's why
telling you he's a murderer no he's not
not John she loves me hiya have to die
you know what I do you kill John I'd
like to be car I Breaka me
[Music]
Oh
except money
it's all right
get up come on come on get up get up
oh it's you haven't I told you to keep
out of this part you know the mayor's
orders
get on down to the problem where you
belong come on come on
who's that right oh she's got a crazy ID
killed a couple of people private six
years ago can't get it offers mind
always trying to give himself up wants
to be tried and executed you know these
nuts
[Music]
there goes the master
you
I really fun ten thousand dollars to do
I
[Music]
Oh
bye