Previously on Star Fight
Surprise bitches!
Far2D2, your highness
You told me there's a bar here
Yeah, my bad
You shouldn't fart in an elevator, Master.
Hello, sexy.
Fresh.
I hate the friend zone!
The greatest achievement in the universe!
The Singularity Engine!
I'm pregnant. (Laughs) It's Obi's!
My midichlorian count is at nine right now.
Okay good. Let's get you clean!
She friend zoneded me!
You have done that to yourself.
You are such and ass. Hole!
Yeeaaaaahhhh boyyeeeee!
The first moon sized entertainment and laser tag facility!
Wow.
Have the protocol droid's mind wiped.
What the fu...
Stop your vehicle and silence all audio systems.
You are in a designated Imperion Family Fun Zone.
Your activities are NOTAPPROVED!
(Screaming)
What's happening?!
Don't ask me!
How could you be so calm while this place falls apart around us?
I envy your resolve, Far2.
Look at you.
Cool as a cucumber!
You actually look sort of like a cucumber, Far2.
What is this place? It seems oddly
familiar.
What do you mean we've been here nineteen years?!
That's preposterous! Who would believe that?!
Alright guys, open up!
I know you're in there. I can smell the refer from here.
You know the deal: No unauthorized party vessels in designated family fun zones!
You're forcing my hand here, now I've got to shut you down!
Open up!
Forget it, we're going to break the
door down,
so just, everybody get to a safe distance.
Far2?
Did you ditch me?
Aw man! What happened here?!
Sir. The blast knocked a few people out again.
Yeah, I can see that.
We'll call for a space ambulance.
(Sighing)
God dammit, when is this day going to be over?
Hey, we're over Tatooine, right?
You know my brother Owen lives down there, we should stop by. Say hello.
Stop, like, for a visit?
Yeah, just pop in for a second.
You know his birthday's coming up, I think that'd be a fun surprise!
Aw, I can't wait to see the look on his face!
What do you think...Unfortunately sir were
little behind schedule and we need to keep moving.
Uhh...okay?
I could arrange for a fruit
basket.
Fruit basket?
Really?!
That's not too impersonal?
Yeah, you know what? Send it. Very good sir.
Far2!
You shouldn't run off like that! You know I
don't like large crowds.
You're the icebreaker and apparently,
I'm suffering from crippling amnesia. It's not safe to leave me alone!
Sir.
What?
Yes, what.
Sir. Yes, what is it?
Sir.
What?
Sir!
Sir.
Somebody! Sir. What.
Sir. What?!
What is wrong with you?
Sir.
Answer me!
Nothing to report, sir (laughing)
Screw you guys!
Hey! What are you doing over there?!
Stop that!
What do you mean "we're leaving"?
I'm not getting in there with you! That's stealing!
Far2, you're scaring me.
When did you become such a hooligan?!
Alright, alright, I'm coming.
Just don't hurt me.
What do you think about Jim's coleslaw?
Homemade or store-bought?
Maybe you're right.
Nineteen years is a long time to be in
one place.
I think I could use a change of scenery!
Man, he is NOT going to be happy about this.
Not half.
Sir, we found your...uhh...
Well well well, missy.
I can't wait to hear you talk your way out of this one.
You know what? Save it!
I paid good money to send you to space
college.
You're supposed to be out here learning something not hanging around with a bunch of losers.
You know this is going to kill your mother.
When did you become such a jerk?!
You don't talk to me like that you're
grounded, Leia!
Take her back to Laser Moon, I'll deal with her later!
God dammit!
Oh good!
A desert planet!
Completely devoid of life! It's perfect, Far2.
I love it!
In a galaxy teeming with advanced civilizations, why would we pick anything else?
We have everything we need here, Far2.
All this sand and bones!
Here, let's see what's over this dune.
Oh look! Sand.
We are limited only by our imaginations!
Wait, where are you going? Isn't this what you wanted?
Sand and bones, as far as the eye can
see?
Hey, slow down.
Far2, I am at a loss.
I'm having trouble remembering anything, let alone the last 19 years.
What is it you're not telling me?
Did you bring us here for a reason?
Or did you just do it to torment me?!
I have had it with you!
Get the hell out of my sight!
I don't ever want to see you again.
Oh Far2 wait, I almost forgot!
Suck it!
One, two, buckle my shoe.
Three, four...
Wait.
What happened to my shoes?!
Oh no!
Did I leave them behind somewhere?
Why would I even go outside without shoes? Ugh, I'm so confused.
Hey, what am I doing here?
This place seems dangerous.
I'm definitely going to need some new shoes.
What's that?
Is that a...a tiny shoe,
lying inches from my grasp?
Or a...mega shoe,
the size of a house miles away for me?!
Shoooooeeesss!
Man, the dollar to acre ratio must be insane out here!
Dude, who cares? Let's just deliver this fruit basket.
Oi, Bill.
Check this out. Does this look like a midichlorian injector ring to you?
Uh oh.
I'm telling you, the absence of the Jedi has made a soft.
Perhaps you are too young to remember. They're more dangerous than you realize.
You'd be a fool
if you believe the Jedi aren't all a bunch of pathetic has-beens.
Well those has beens, as you say, were totally responsible for a galaxy wide insurance collapse!
Regional manager Vader should have taken care of this a long time ago!
You know if you've got something to say
to me why don't you say to my face?
Instead of pretending like I'm not standing, right here.
Yeah that's what I thought.
Look, you want to find a Jedi?
Just send a guy into every bar in the
galaxy
and I guarantee you'll find one eventually.
We don't have the manpower
for an operation of that scale!
Really? Cause I was being serious.
And you're also very good at detecting
sarcasm.
And your job.
...and satisfying your wife.
I don't have to sit here and take flak from some clown in a cape!
You have no power here, regional manager.
(Bickering)
Enough. This bickering is
pointless.
We already have men in the area,
delivering fruit, apparently.
It can't hurt to ask around.
So it turns out
it wasn't a shoe at all! Isn't that ridiculous?
(Laughs) A giant shoe. Anyways,
what's your name?
Oh, these guys.
They're the best. I don't understand they seem but they seem really nice.
I think they're going to give us new shoes.
Yes, hello. I'll take two shoes,
and three for my friend.
Two plus three is five. Five shoes,
por favor.
Alright then, what's your name?
Funny you should ask, I have no idea.
First time on Tatooine?
I think so. I like it so far. Friendly
people.
What's your opinion on the singularity?
Umm...to be quite honest I don't know what
that means. Can we still be friends?
I promise to learn everything I can
about the singu...
Alright, shut up. We'll take this one.
Duke.
Take this one over to the garage, will ya. I want him cleaned up before dinner.
But I was going to Tosche Station to pick up some power converters.
Nobody likes a whiner, Duke. Un-tuck it. Act like a man.
Alright. Come on.
You too, blue.
Far2, this is our new friend, Duke.
He enjoys Tosche Station, and his father likes to embarrass him in public.
He's not my father.
Well, I don't like the way he treats you. Right, Far2?
You seem a little old to be playing with toys, Duke.
Not that there's anything wrong with
that!
I don't know, there just nothing to do around here.
It's just all sand and bones.
Listen, Duke. I can't quite explain it, but...
I have a good feeling about you. We
should be best friends!
You can call me Friend Besto!
How's that sound?
Sounds good.
Wait, what are you doing with Far2?
Can I help?
Yeah!
Let's take him apart and see if we can put him back together!
What a fun project!
Hope you can keep up!
Later!
I work hard, and I play hard, so I hope you can keep up!
Who is she? She's beautiful.
Later!
I work hard, and I play hard, so I hope you can keep up!
Wait a minute where'd she go, bring her back! Make her naked!
You heard him, Far2! Duke wants nudies!
Duke! Food!
I'll be right there in a minute.
Ah, I gotta go eat din-din.
Why don't you guys just hang out, I'll be back in a little bit.
Oh, okay!
Bye, Duke!
What a good lad.
That Owen fellow has a bad attitude though.
We may have to kill him.
With kindness!
Duke!
It's space thirty!
Get your ass in here before you burn to death!
(Screams of pain)
What are you doing hiding back there?
I was alone shrouded in darkness, and then there was you!
Friend Besto, have you seen Far2?
Far2? Friend Besto?
Yes. I. Am Friend Besto.
Ally of Duke!
I...
am Friend...
Bestoooo!
Hi, Duke!
Did this Far2 character absquatulate?
Yeah.
Bitch.
He strikes me as a free spirit.
Wandering around, leading people from one adventure to the next.
He might as well be named Fart Macguffin 2D2
Yeah.
We'll call him FartMacmuffin for short!
We'll be quite the trio!
Duke, Friend Besto and FartMacmuffin.
Duke!
Are we going to Tasche Station?
No, we don't have time for that right now!
But Duke likes Tasche Station!
Look at this excitable little fellow!
What's your name?
Far2? That's hilarious!
Is that your real name, or some sort
nickname?
You seem like a good lad. Come with us to Tasche Station.
Nah, I'm gonna take a nap.
Oh, okay.
Hello there, Far2.
How did you get in there?
What are you doing here, with Duke?
Ben?
Obi -Wan Ben-Larry Kenobi?
Well actually I'm going by Steve now.
Steve Kenobi.
It's good to see you, Duke. I keep meaning
to hang out with you.
Why don't you guys come back to my place
and have some lemonade.
I've got a fresh pitcher with your name on it.
Okay!
Lemonade does...
hit the spot...
on a day like today.
Cool and refreshing.
So, Far2.
What have you been doing since the last time I saw you?
What's it been, like, 5...16 years?
Whoa, what's this?
Hi, guys. How's it going?
My name is Leia Skywalker.
I've never used Space Date before, but I'm open to it.
It seems lame, but I'm willing to be proven wrong by the right guy.
I'm a fun and adventurous woman.
Currently in my third semester of space college.
My dad is the regional manager of Laser Moon
Which is cool!
Sometimes I hang out there on the weekends.
I'm originally from Alderaan,
but I'm not really looking to date anyone from that area.
Alderaan
Key code: Alderaan, accepted.
Initializing memory backup.
Alright, I guess that's it.
I work hard and I play hard, so I hope you can keep up!
Later!
Do you want to go to Laser Moon?
Maybe we'll find this girl of yours.
Ah, sweet!
Let's head into town and bum a ride.
Hey, you guys mind stopping for a minute and helping us out?
We're looking for possible Jedi in the area.
You guys haven't seen any, have you?
I haven't seen any Jedi.
Well, don't take this the wrong way,
but the reason I stopped you is because you're dressed EXACTLY like a Jedi.
Like...all of them.
Every single one of them dressed exactly the way you're dressed now.
Look, I'm not a Jedi.
Scott, tell me this guy doesn't look like a Jedi.
Yeah yeah, he's got, like, the robes!
Yeah yeah yeah! The robes! Exactly!
Do you see how this looks to us, sir?
Are you telling me you woke up today and accidentally dressed like a Jedi?
Yes.
(Laughter)
Hey, you say you're not a Jedi I have to believe you, I mean there's nothing I can do.
If you happen to see one, just find one of us and let us know. Okay?
Alright, take care, guys. You have a nice day.
You have a nice day!
Wow. This place is a den of scumbags!
Oh look, Rat Boy is here.
Good to see him!
Oh, and literally Satan.
That makes sense!
Duke, I'm going to be honest with you.
This place needs to be purified, immediately!
We don't serve their kind here.
What?!
They're dangerous!
Why don't you wait out by the speeder, we don't want any trouble.
Good idea, Duke!
Less chance of infection.
Hey.
One of those.
(Muffled anger)
Excuse me. He says that you cut him off.
That's extremely rude behavior!
You cut in front of me too, you know!
I have been waiting in line for five minutes.
I'll be careful next time.
You have to wait in line like everyone else!
Well that's not what your mom said last
night...when I stopped by.
I've had it with you, Steve!
Let's go!
Han Solo
I'm captain of the Millennium Falcon.
Chewy here tells me you're looking for passage to Laser Moon
Yes indeed.
Okay. I'll take you, old man.
On one condition.
What's that?
Chewy and I are on the team.
We're laser tag dominators.
And you're buying the nachos.
Whoa!
(Pained human groaning)
(More pain)
Welcome to Laser Moon! Now the ultimate source of entertainment in the universe!
Featuring over 500,000 fine dining choices!
1,000 levels of exclusive shopping!
And of course, 100 kilometers of non-stop, action packed laser tag mayhem!
Fun for every skill level!
Please be sure to have all of your coupons or discount codes ready at the main gate.
Birthday parties and corporate retreats, please proceed to the special events entrance!
Whoa, Han, you look awesome!
I know.
Welcome to game orientation. Your video will begin shortly.
White team leader to Laser Commander, we are in position.
Copy that, white team leader. Proceed to the objective.
Hi, guys. I'm the Laser Commander. Officer in charge of safety...
and fun.
By now you should have already equipped your team uniforms.
Uniforms are color-coded,
representing either the white team, or the black team.
If you have not equipped your team uniform,
please find a staff member for assistance.
There can be no running at any time
during the match.
Running can cause injury to yourself, or others.
The only way to score IS with your blaster.
One-handed gunplay - or "gangsta' grip - is NOT permitted.
Score points by either shooting your opponents or attacking the other teams' base.
There's a maximum score in it for you if
you destroy your opponents' base.
I'll take the base out. You'll just slow me down.
We'll see about that.
What do you say, Chewy, the usual plan?
Far2 and I will stay here and watch
over your possessions.
Stay out of my stuff.
Oh don't worry!
No one cares about your smelly "stuff".
Good luck out there, laser warriors!
And remember: through honor YOU can achieve victory.
You may now proceed to the game zone.
So, Far2!
What shall we do to pass the time?
Oh! Here's a thought!
What do you say we tap into Laser Moon's navigational system and take it for a spin?
I hear Alderaan is quite beautiful this time of year.
The most beautiful thing you've ever seen.
(Laughter)
When we get into the game zone just follow my lead.
There's going to be a lot of confusion, and we're going to use that to our advantage.
It takes more than good aim to be a laser tag dominator.
Welcome to the winning team, kid.
Uh, hi. We were transferred to black team
And they told us to come here and get our new uniforms.
I wasn't notified
Oh! Ummmm...
Psych!
Get out of the way MIKE!
Alright, let's go, let's go!
Alright here we go, here we go, here we go!
Get through the door, you gotta get through the door!
My legs!
I'm slipping!
My legs won't fit! Shit!
Get it together!
Oh no my BELT!
GET IT TOGETHER, MIKE!
White team scores 10,000 points.
Laser Moon is awesome!
Come on! Let's go, kid!
Hold on.
No way!
Are you Leia?
I saw your Space Date profile.
You saw my Space Date profile?
Yeah!
I'm Duke Dirtfarmer, I'm here to hang out with you!
Duke?
The Dominators are winning right now. Do you want to be on our team?
Totally!
Awesome, let's go!
Yes.
Sir! Some things have come up that need your immediate attention.
Well, what is it?!
Um, yes. Sir, uh, first:
Complimentary nacho night was more popular than we anticipated,
and our cheese sauce reserves are dangerously low.
You know I told them this would happen.
Alright, what else?
Um...
Laser Moon has unexpectedly changed course, and is headed towards Alderaan.
And?
And we can't stop it.
(Sigh) Alright, first thing's first...
I'm going to get a handle on this cheese situation.
Very good, sir.
Featuring over 500,000 fine dining choices!
1,000 level of exclusive shopping!
Far2, we're having so much fun together!
Do you want to do something really fun?
Let's redirect all power from Laser Moon's main core...
into a spectacular light show that we can direct at a target of my choosing!
Yes, that's it, Far2! Yyyyeeeessssss
Don't think about it, just do it, Far2.
Don't you want to have fun?!
Do it right now or I will smash your head open and eat your brain, I swear to god!
Whoa, shi...
...non stop action packed laser tag mayhem!
Fun for every skill level!
Yaaaaaaayyy
Laser Moon scores
5.6 billion points.
Huh.
Fun's over, Far2, let's vanish.
Faster!
Oh my god.
There's just no way to spin this!
You!
Anakin?
Why am I not surprised?
Billions of people, just gone,
and you just happen to be wandering
around in the exact same outfit you had on
twenty years ago
Just when you think he can't get any lower, ladies and gentlemen
the bottom keeps dropping out for old Obi-Wan Ben-Larry Kenobi.
You piece of shit!
This ends today. Right here, right now.
By way of physical beating.
Me and you, Obi-Wan. What do you say?
Have you forgotten the last time we danced?
Because I have.
Nice move, grandpa!
Dude, how old are you?
You look 85!
How is this possible?
No, seriously! Aren't you only like 15 years older than me?
I'll still beat your ass.
Oh you think so, huh?
Well the last time we danced you were so bad your legs came off.
You son of a bitch!
You also remember how you freaked out and left me there all alone?
That was the best.
The dehydration.
I was so thirsty!
home
Dude, this sucks.
We suck!
What are we doing?
Mike, check it out.
Aw, sick! Old school dance fight boyyyyeee
Shotgun!
What do you say, Obi?
Why don't I put you out of your misery for old time's sake?
I'm taking that as a yes.
Hiyaaaaa
What?!
Birthday parties and corporate retreats...
As many of you know, Imperion has been
destroying communities for decades.
They've run countless small businesses into the ground.
And they've turned millions of neighborhoods into their
designated family fun zones.
Yesterday, their most recent monstrosity, Laser Moon,
destroyed an entire planet.
We don't know why they did it, or how it fits into their business model,
but we do know they have to be stopped.
We need to send a message to Imperion:
The people won't stand for this.
Lucky for us, Laser Moon is an
entertainment center
and posses zero defensive capabilities.
My sources tell me all we need to do is drop a sack of moldy peaches down this shaft right here,
which will cause a catastrophic chain
reaction and destroy the entire complex
I don't pretend to understand it but it's all we've got
so we're gonna go for it!
That's impossible, even for a computer.
But it's not impossible. I used to drop
moldy peaches on stuff all the time
back home.
Duke stop trying to impress the other
boys!
Now get out of here, you bunch of muscly...
hunks.
That sound weird to you?
Alright, let's do this.
Here's a little something to get you in the mood
You boys ready to kick some ass?
I'm prepared to kick some ass
I'm the kick ass master.
Yup. Gonna do some ass poundin'.
I'm gonna eat that ass like a pie.
Hey Pillsbury, save me an ass-slice.
Yup. I'm ready to kick that butt.
Uhhh, we're not talking about butts here, Duke.
We're talking about ASS!
(Cheers)
Yo, one up. I'm gonna write the book on ass.
Oh yeah? Well I'm going to option the screenplay.
It's going to be a cinematic masterpiece.
It'll win awards for best director, actor, original score and cinematography!
Oh well I can't wait to see it.
What are you gonna call the film?
"I Want Ass: The Motion Picture"
(Laughter)
Do not attempt to score on Laser Moon.
I...am Laser Moon
We're about to eat the fudge.
You hearing this?
What?
I...am Laser. Moon.
Base, you getting this?
Laser Moon is shooting at us!
You boys are gonna have to improvise.
Have to keep your eyes on that ass.
Someone tell me what the hell is
happening!
My bet is we're all going to die.
Not if we blast it right in the ass!
Sir! Laser Moon is firing back and referring to itself in the first person!
Okay.
We believe it has become sentient!
Huh!
That sucks for you!
Very good, sir!
For god's sake, Duke! Watch your ass!
Going for that pie.
What? You crazy?
It's good.
Pull up!
No, I'm gonna eat that ass pie!
Pillsbury!
Gentlemen. Let's show these jack-offs how we do business.
Base, this is Red One, preparing for our first trench run.
Switching to targeting for peaches.
I don't see it.
I don't see the hole.
Guys! Where do I drop the peaches?
Will you shut up while I check the map!
Alright, let's smoke these losers.
Guy, I screwed up!
I forgot my peaches!
What?!
You've got to be kidding me!
I feel really bad!
Black team score 10,000 points.
Yeah, that's right, suckas!
Black team scores 10,000 points.
Oh shit!
It's too tight, I can't maneuver!
Black team scores 10,000 points.
Now listen up. The remaining packages are Barry's and Duke's.
Make sure you get those peaches down that shaft.
Alright, Duke. Let's put it right in the fart shaft.
Run it deep!
I. Have awakened.
Go, Laser Moon!
I am Laser Moon
This is it.
Time to go to the ass bank, boys. Start cashing those ass checks.
You've got to be kidding me.
Got to get that ass cash!
Dude, we're about to die.
Enough with the asses!
I'm gonna kick the FARTS from that ass.
Please, stop it!
Going for that ass.
Uh, guys.
That ass is mine.
Awww yeah.
Punch that aaaaaa.
Awwww yeah
aaaaaaa
Awwww
awwwww
aaaaaaa
Aw yeahhh boyyeee!
Ass!
Black team scores 10,000 points.
Alright, Duke, ramrod it!
Black team for the win.
What?
Yahoo! Dominators!
Dominators?
Oh god! (Vomits)
You're all clear, kid, now drop that sack!
Peaches detected.
Great shot, kid,
that was one in a million!
Duke?
Where am I?
You guys ditch me?
Hey guys. Thanks for watching Episode 4.
Yeah, if you're watching this right now,
it means you gave us almost an hour of your time,
and that's huge. We appreciate it so much.
Totally. We also want to give a huge thanks to all of our guest actors on this one.
We had some really talented people on board,
so please check the description below for full cast info and links to all of their pages.
If you enjoyed this episode and like what we do,
we'd be super appreciative if you could support our channel and our work.
You can do that by either donating here on the channel through the donate feature,
checking out our music catalog, or visiting our Spreadshirt page.
Also visit us on Facebook and Twitter for updates.
...and subscribe.
And do 50 push ups while you're at it.
Yeah, that too.
You don't have to do them all at once, just make sure you knock them out before the end of the day.
Right, right. Anything else?
Yeah, call your mom.
Definitely, yes, that.
Tell her you love her, and that you miss her.
She'll appreciate it.
Absolutely.
Peace out.
Byeee!
Oh my god please pick up. Please please
please pick up
Hi, it's Leia!
Leia?!
Leave a message.
Leia, I just...oh god! Please just tell me you got off Laser Moon!
I'm so sorry for everything, I just...I just, I love you so much!
God, what have I done?!
Nooooooooooo