The Empire Strikes Back second of the
Star Wars films on the patient in norman
with a budget of 18 million dollars and
rising the snow has to be real
it's a test of endurance for the cast
the crew and equipment
the organization and the money behind a
film of this scale are beyond most
people's imaginations ready bro you're
going on all around
yet when the editing is finished the
pressure will focus on one man who's
worked the make or Mar the end result
the composer John Williams the music in
the pics an action picture particularly
a film like Star Wars to the empire
strikes back this this generally active
music it's fast the temples are quick a
lot of flourishing in the orchestra and
so on is no D so that it's a tremendous
physical job of just getting the notes
down in fact I'm a little edgy about
having done only eight minutes I think
one two three the American film composer
John Williams known to his friends as
johnny is one of the quieter
personalities to be found in the movie
world but he's written the music for 45
feature films in the last 20 years
including Star Wars now he's conducting
the london symphony orchestra in his
score for the second of the Star Wars
trilogy The Empire Strikes Back which
opens in London on Tuesday
we had I think one hour and 47 minutes
of orchestral music to compose Orchestra
and copy prepare for the auction system
sometimes it comes very quickly and it's
a nice flower / times I hold my head in
my hand and think is it everybody to
come I guess you want to stand under the
right kind of raised from heaven month
but did the muses will not desert us
in the control room of anvil recording
studio a writer George Lucas director
Irvin Kershner and the producer of the
Star Wars films Gary Kurtz originally
John was recommended to George Lucas a
by Steven Spielberg who had used him on
jaws and we had all like the Java score
very much it was a traditional symphonic
score and we went through a period in
featured homes where traditional scores
were not used popular music scores and
jazz scores were the rage in the 60s
into the early 70s we felt for star wars
that it was very important that it be a
traditional romantic score jolly is
quite adept at finding the point of view
for a scene and augmenting the emotion
that's there and love in cash neck the
director of The Empire Strikes Back he's
he's very good also at maintaining a
long long piece of music and getting all
the variations without making it what we
call Mickey Mouse you know where you
accent every little bump every little
crash we don't do that
Star Wars is a sort of space stable with
a good Republic and a bad Empire rebels
robots Jedi Knights and a princess in
the first film there's a battle aboard
the Empire fit the Death Star which
leads to a duel with lightsabers between
two of the Jedi Knights the basic skill
of composing for films can be seen in
the unobtrusive match of music to abrupt
changes of senior
putting up they may be on level 5 & 6
now
Mike
open the blast doors
uh what's look what's seen we it's gonna
be getting your arm freezing chamber as
before he's emerging is composing for
films is always done under pressure
sometimes the composer Macia scripts in
advance but his first practical
involvement is usually the spotting
session when he sits down with the
director to plan where music is needed
I'll equally important wait isn't yeah
is that that's the beginning of the real
beginning a ratio rescue important law
and and he said land as beginning
beginning to read to emerge as a midi
right every directors very different
some have no idea always so here's the
film to the best you can put music where
you like and others are very specific
and some are very expert at it you with
some there are disagreements rather some
feelings won't want to synchronize with
the composer's my experience has been
vast like it needs be heard in those
looks yeah those to build yeah right
there very good after experience as an
Orchestrator and music director John
Williams started composing two teachers
at the end of the 50s several of the
early films were comedies like how to
steal a million released in 1966
in a scene where Audrey Hepburn as
daughter of a wealthy art forger is
disturbed by an intruder played by Peter
O'Toole the music at first creates an
atmosphere of pure suspense
Oh
don't put annotating once the
confrontation has taken place the
suspense in the music is given a warmer
quality partly by using different
harmonies and instruments this tells
before the pictures do how their
relationship is going to develop anyway
I you frighten me so or even don't be
impudent that thing isn't loaded is it
because it is
are you and do you have a gun
well I'm I'm gonna let you go I don't
know why then
I'm the one who's bleeding with
experience composer will will begin to
have a sense of what's going to work in
the scene what's going to be audible
where he's got a chance to to to come
through where he ought to hold back
where he worried should go into a
holding pattern and let something else
come through and then move into into the
into the next hole if there is one or
introduce a fragment of a malady here
in guide for the married man another of
the sixties comedies scored by John
Williams Walter Matthau plays a
middle-aged married man nervously
planning his first extramarital affair
in this scene where he surprises a
friend in a similar situation there are
no words music is the dialogue
for the new star wars film the music
spotting session involves besides John
Williams the producer Gary Kurtz
director irvin kershner and the man who
wrote the story and directed the first
Star Wars you're George Lucas yeah quiet
you watchin going because it really yeah
uh yeah this is important in here no you
might we might it doesn't that great
open now yeah the great open there yeah
at this stage the film is almost
completely edited as far as the picture
is concerned but the soundtrack is only
a very rough working version without
effects cutting in and out and dialogue
often difficult to hear or even missing
altogether what's going on buddy you're
being put into carbon freeze rather not
to miss the Empire will compensate you
for your loss goody me shout stop listen
to me stop please very touching here I
say good son Osama Nate I need you to
protect their now all that I love that
I said that's where it was and I
probably thinking of the picture of what
something for ya
exist
we're here now that's right home I love
you I love you too violent there's a
love scene we call it a love scene it's
actually a scene that leads to a kiss
which is the equivalent of a major love
sequence of another film and the music
is a very very important part of it it's
integral to the scene because they're
only about seven lines in entire
sequence and the music is the dialogue
and that particular scene it tells us
what she's feeling because actually the
two people are an open conflict but the
music says ah what you're seeing is
maybe conflict but that's a game because
actually I think they're falling in love
hey hey listen to me chewy oh joy
there's nothing you can do although the
film is far from finished it's possible
to compare the effect of this sequence
where the Princess Leia has to watch
space pilot han Solo being put into a
carbon freezing chamber with and without
music here it is on its own
I love you I know
okay yes please now here it is with the
orchestral recording mixed into the
soundtrack the flashing dots and the
lines on the projection screen are a
visual guide for the conductor to
synchronize with the music score
hey
going on jamaican I can't be
to put it in the positive way it helps a
great deal if you'd like to show it
something that one can empathize with or
if it's a subject that you can seriously
benefit or enjoy working on it's a great
help one has to be almost chameleon-like
in the sense that you have to to adapt
your style to to suit the fabric and
texture of the film the period of the
film time in place and all the rest of
it so these are they these are the
things i think that present the greatest
difficulties this business of shifting
into a hand to a new suit really almost
every time out two films with completely
contrasting scores by John Williams are
Jane Eyre released in 1971 and from the
following year a powerful film called
images in which Susannah York plays a
woman confronted by a confusion of
images both over herself and of the men
in her life the score is is almost
entirely a tonal it was a picture for
something boo some of you may remember
about a schizophrenic woman and and
music is very wild sounding it's not
electronic but I use a lot of percussion
instruments and an unconventional
sources of sound it's funny I could have
sworn I heard somebody sure he didn't
come up here yeah absolutely not told ya
at all here's a banana me finish the
puzzle
in one of the scenes where Susannah York
comes face-to-face with her other self
what could visually be a delay it's on
an atmosphere of threat created entirely
by the music
don't go back
back
by contrast jane eyre has a warm tonal
romantic score it's I suppose an
American attempted at what Yorkshire
music should be but I'm a great lover of
British music and perhaps some of that
affection comes through in that score
Jane Eyre also shows the thematic use of
music in a film score when Jane once
again Susannah York first meets
Rochester played by George see Scott the
music she plays on the piano is what
turns out to be the love theme of the
film cristiana play
enough enough
in a later scene when Jane has rescued
Rochester from a fire in his room the
theme reappears to indicate the
awakening love between them
you saved my life
good
I knew you would do me good I felt it
always there's something about you Jane
if its core that has a thematic kind of
material once I've got the theme for
that character a place or time weave it
into the rhythmic fabric of the
particular senior remaining it for sound
effects are a big problem for a composer
you know it's our great competition the
dubbing room which is when all the all
the sounds are being put together
sometimes if a soundtrack is is
completed the sound effects of a scene
i'd like to listen to that to see what
what my competition is going to be if
the if the oral spectrum is crowded in
the high end i might elect to to
orchestrate it and then the lower
frequency ranges to to to make it more
compatible with the sound effects but
this is really this is a this is a rare
luxury usually the sound effects of
being cut for the sequences the same
tongue music as being written despite
the fact that we have a hundred and ten
minutes of music in this film by Johnny
Williams we also have to have 123
minutes worth of sound effects in the
film for the Star Wars films with
special sound effects have put together
by Dan dirt we have to create some 800
different special sounds for the film
these might you know these would be
special explosions they would be the
sounds of the lightsabers hitting one
another the various sounds of the rooms
and the environments of places they go
this one particular sound I'm working on
right now is one of the few really
comical songs in the film and it has to
do with the Millennium Falcon which is
the main spaceship in the film and the
Millennium Falcon as you might know is a
spaceship which has been pieced together
out of old junk it's something like a
hot-rod car it needs constant tuning
it's at malfunctions quite often and as
a recurring situation in the current
film the Millennium Falcon's hyperdrive
constantly breaks down and the
hyperdrive is the system which allows it
to go and fly greater than the speed of
light and to come up with a comical
effect here we've combined a laid out on
a multitrack tape recorder over here
eight different sounds the first thing
is a the inertia starter off an old 1928
biplane which we recorded near here
that's what that sound is and going back
to we also have the sound of a air jet
recorded in a dentist's office and an
air hisses this air as if air is
escaping from something schooling me is
the area's aside from the air hist we
have the sound of an arc light motor
starting and stopping sort of a clunking
sign then we were recording some tanks a
while ago in our armored tanks and
inside was a motor which operated the
turret in the tank the day we move into
this building we do i went to the water
closet and turn on the faucet to wash my
hands and the pipes rattled and jiggled
and sort of talk and loaned and so we
immediately recorded that sound which is
here
right now if we took all these songs and
played them together we get the
following effect of the hyperdrive
malfunction
let's get out of here ready for light
speed hmm one two
no light speed he's not my fault
in towering inferno where the fire in
the prestigious new skyscraper burns for
the greater part of the film the
excitement of action and sound effects
carry the emotional rate for most of the
time the music is reserved for
particular moments often to heighten an
aspect of personal human drama in
contrast to the public one when Paul
Newman the architect of the burning
building is rescuing a child from a
broken fire escape ladder the uncertain
tonality of John Williams music
emphasizes the mood of anxiety you're
right do I hit him I got up all right
but I think I'm gonna have a lot of
trouble getting down you think you could
help me or you just hold on around my
neck real tight come on give it a try
just put your arms rami and you tell me
what to do okay hold on real tight
hold on
you
take them
the ocean
john williams was born in New York and
returned there later to study piano at
the Juilliard School that when he was 15
his parents moved to California and he
now lives there with his own family in
Los Angeles I live a very quiet life you
know composes life is I think just after
a monk from point of view of solitude
you know when I look at my cue sheets
and time all the film I'm alone all day
long composing capsid suits be
temperamental IAM and certainly years of
half of working I enjoy writing and
perhaps a more volatile kind of
personality wouldn't find it tolerable
to spend so much time alone I love to
play and when I have time I like to work
at it I love playing chamber music and
then perform a few times in years much
as I can with friends either locally or
wherever I like making music with my
hands you know it's very different than
conducting where someone else is making
the sound and it's also a very good
discipline and I think for me at least
all the aspects of performance have a
lot to do with what one is writing you
can write better if you are a performer
if you know really what makes a piece
urban flow and really go and that's
something I think it only can be
discovered in performance the heat of
the moment it helps conducting I think a
knowledge of chamber music is very
important for a conductor to also that's
that's the quintessential art of
ensemble
lovely one of the big problems are
composing for film is the fact that it
is a restriction and there is a is the
inhibition of time there's the
inhibition of the amount of sound room
that you've got we talked about sound
effects before and dialogue there's a
lot a lot of things have to coexist with
the music in a concert hall wasn't one
doesn't have to worry about John
Williams has written music for four
films by Steven Spielberg at 33 one of
the most sought-after Directors in
Hollywood well the first thing I think
about is that when I look at a film all
put together it's dead it's like lively
death that the film moves in its action
pace but there's sometimes nothing
behind the eyes the movie and for me
music has always brought out a kind of
spirit and the soul the movie is evident
once there is music to encourage it
along and I've always felt the music was
always a necessity for film ever since
the Great Train Robbery when the little
man in the orchestra pit on the tack
piano played to the images of the
picture the music wasn't integral part
of movies I think in the 1960s people
got away from that they began to equate
realism with lack of a musical sound the
absence of music and those were the days
of the social commentary when young
filmmakers were afraid to be too
theatrical or too sentimental and I
think now we've gotten back fortunately
for you and for me and for everybody
else have gotten back to full blown
symphonic orchestrations behind movies
and in many cases like jaws jaws worked
very very well as they film but he had
to see it without music to realize how
effective it was with that score that
John wrote it was not the same movie
without the score well I think the music
is often the the unseen
we feel its presence through the through
the through sensing music the thing I
picked up on the film in Jaws the
straightaway was the rhythmic aspect of
it what's your name again Chrissy where
are we going swimming that's such a
forward thrust this hasta not o thing
will boom boom box of mindless little
figure in the bottom of the orchestra
that comes relentlessly at you as that
as the film goes on
I can swim just can't walk for tres
myself
Hades take it easy
John Williams second film for Spielberg
was close encounters of the third kind
an intergalactic spaceship visits earth
and a team of scientists tries to
communicate with it using music as a
language Stephen wanted five notes I'm
not sure why I kept that I kept writing
five node groups and then seven no
troops and i found out that seven really
would produced a melody more than 55
didn't seem to be quite enough but your
script idea called 45 nose and a way it
left you guessing what the rest of the
complete complete statement would be in
fact because the was Johnny I think with
with you how many on the piano over
there like a thousand i wrote about 200
actually see 1,250 but do you member we
had you had a math friend compute out of
the 12 notes available starting with
five notes the same and up through the
12 chromatic notes of the scale the
number of permutations possible was I
think 130 4,800 necks and having done
200 mile I was exhausted please wait we
had a long way to go we kept coming back
to this the same little little figure
which is more like a doorbell or a
signal or a message ice cream truck then
the malady
No
you
can be
what was a problem in that picture in
trust counters was the conversation
between the mothership and the computer
Bank of lights and I tried every version
of mogh synthesizer and electronic
synthesizer of noises and all the rest
of the tape edits and everything else to
get a sound a noise for the mothership
and a sound a noise for the light board
and we we eventually tried a tuba
perhaps be double speed reverberate it
put through all kinds of kinds of sound
enhancement devices and and the thing
about the tuba was that the player had
to breathe he'd play a long phrase and
had to take a breath and there was
effort behind it and and it seemed to
humanize the the mothership
it may take two years to shoot a film
but we may have 8 10 or 12 weeks to do
all the editing the mixing of the sound
of composing and recording of the music
for financial reasons and reasons of a
distribution of the film and theater
availability and so on we have not all
that much time that's a composer really
needs to be to write with fluidity to do
well consistently and film
time pressures were never more apparent
than on Superman where the shooting
schedules got longer and longer costs
spiraled but still the score had to be
ready on time and good first thing we
got to do when we get home is find out
who that boys proper family the small
boy who will become Superman first
arrives on earth by space capsule from
his destroyed home the planet Krypton
he's found by the Kent's who have no
children of their own and decide to
adopt him the Superman theme is quietly
introduced when the boy first chose his
superhuman qualities Oh Martin Jonathan
he's only a baby Martha now you saw how
we found Martha Clark Kent are you
listening to what I'm saying
Oh
you
come on come on hurry up come on Clark I
think you better get out of here I think
we better do what he says Lars Hanson
come on later is the news reporter Clark
kent/superman again demonstrates his
extraordinary powers and again the theme
music quietly underlines lower weight
thank you hurt somebody without a car
okay okay okay all today just a minute
vesture just a minute no I realize of
course that times are tough for some
these days but this isn't the answer you
can't solve the society's problems with
a gun you know somebody you're right i'm
gonna turn over a new leaf good for you
sir that's the spirit see he doesn't
really want to hurt anybody uh-huh right
after I rip off this lady's purse of
course now come on Lady hand it over
Lois think maybe better huh well what
are you doing
are you all right Clark
I guess I must have fainted hated you
thank you sorry
the spotting sessions for the Empire
Strikes Back took place in George
Lucas's editing rooms in san rafael a
few miles out of san francisco the rest
of the music work apart from the final
recording is done at twentieth Century
Fox Studios in Los Angeles many of the
buildings here have facades that were
once used as film sets even the front of
the music editing office doubles as an
elegant house exterior after the
complete film has been viewed for
spotting ken wannberg the supervising
music editor prepares short sequences
for John Williams to work on each day
there are nearly 15 music sequences in
all
he also prepares detailed cue sheets
showing the timings of the various shots
in fractions of a second the film is
viewed first thing in the morning as a
black and white print on a movie owner
machine this doesn't have the special
anamorphic lens that recreates the
widescreen in a film so the picture here
looks rather squashed this work is vital
in finding the exact moment where the
musical emphasis is needed it's right
here 111 35.9 okay 135 nah yeah I
haven't got another so it goes in here
yeah I guess the laser supposed to be
here the monster makes a noise teachers
around do when you're back do we see him
shoot it yes
Yeah right
he's attached first
oh go ahead seafood back shoo shoo in
one slider much west another good one
but on yeah
we'll have a good rumble in their 7th
century back in his own office John
William spends the day writing the music
for the sequence he's been viewing
perhaps two or three minutes of music in
the day my own practice in films is to
use an Orchestrator when the budget will
allow and when time won't permit my
doing it myself lately the films that
I've been working on it required so much
music my last eight of ten years that
I've developed a long and wonderful
relationship with herb Spencer Jackie
right here said Jana you what they think
of the pianos similarly to the way we
didn't like at the piano sketch on a
hunt n or eight lines sketch pad so on
six eight or ten lines of sketch I can
indicate very precisely what the
orchestration ought to be but if I then
had to put that on 32 lines or 50 lines
in the orchestra I would be slow that
what about a hundred percent so i can do
approximately two minutes of score a day
with herv's help I let me do it that way
oh ok good
when he's finished his days composition
he takes it back to ken wannberg pro
final check against the picture
my first concern is a rhythmic one I
sense a speed to film every scene seems
to have a an underlying tempo 14 series
of Tempe all set of them perhaps
different levels dialog may go at a
certain speed the action may go another
speed and there may be a variance there
it's the thing that I try to feel in
spotting in the early stages of the film
are simple things like how fast is it or
how slow is it or when is the point in
the film's life that it accelerates when
does it press on press forward one of
the brakes put on I think in my mind
that's my first consideration
both thought
no all right yeah
okay that looks pretty good measure to
really is Darth Vader ship we see that
we see the imperial ship there hence the
the big Vader theme at that far but
finally at the end of a long day he goes
through the score with Herbert Spencer
who will arrange it for Orchestra the
next day so here 25 seconds point 1 some
little objects float by the window and
that the strings would be sustained but
if it Celeste sounding welker I think
there's an old joke about composing for
film that goes do you want it good or do
you want it tomorrow with only six weeks
to the recording sessions but over a
hundred minutes of music still to be
written inspiration has to be immediate
three pickles I suppose composes the
centuries have complained about this I
think of suddenly i'm outside having to
produce a mass for sunday for the
archbishop for hiding writing something
for Esterhazy on demand let me have a
new symphony for thursday nights Dennis
I supposed as old as is the art of
writing music now we come to a kind of a
Tootsie which is this thing with strings
and horns vol.2 horn trio strange double
notes and cellos and basses
a little over seven weeks after the
spotting sessions in California the
orchestral recording started anvil
Studios just outside London an hour and
50 minutes of music had been written
arranged and copied out into orchestral
part
oh boy the recordings will occupy the
london symphony orchestra for nine days
18 three-hour sessions to rehearse and
record an average of eight and a half
minutes of new music possessions 82 one
two three
Bravo gents good reading good for you
Lionel II opening fine Lionel Newlin
head of music of fox studios and a
notable film composer in his own right
sits with the mixer Eric Tomlinson
checking that all the detail in the
score is being heard through the
speakers
producer director writer and music
editor have all flown over from America
for these recordings number ten number
ten from that very spot chance number 10
and going on at the center of it all is
the composer probably unknown to most of
the public but vital to the success of
the film I save it save it save it for
Lionel to set levels for you I'll just
give you bar 13 a few times right 13
please Jensen only 13 just that measure
one two three four winds alone please
let me see what's your profits it is
under a line should be God you never
turn it 13 whatever may happen in the
final sound mix at this moment all the
effort is on getting the music right 13
one two three four
okay for you good all right okay we take
it please even the dialogue and rough
effects are not played while the music
is being recorded damn I please and let
her go all right here it is Jim Shh
settle down 16 357
at this stage no one knows exactly what
the final sound track will be like much
of the dialogue still has to be recorded
or re-recorded sound effects are being
prepared to match what's happening in
the picture and finally all these and
the music have to be blended together no
longer in the foreground the music now
takes on its true function to support or
even create the emotional atmosphere of
the film
this ground sure feels strange doesn't
feel like rock there's an awful lot of
moisture I don't know I have a bad
feeling about this yeah yeah I thought
my not joy check the rest of the ship
make sure they're no more attached
chewing on the power cables minox go on
inside will clean them off is there any
more
if I are still healthy i don't think
it's gonna discuss you give me
you can't make the jug of Lightspeed
this asteroid field I'm sweet hardware
take it off
I see it I see it with you the cave is
collapsing look
you