Eva.. So.
Nick.. Hi.
Eva.. Hi.
Eva.. Can I really try it?
Nick.. Yeah, of course. No l was lying.
Eva.. That's kind of weird.
Eva.. Oh my god that's so good.
Nick.. Can I ty that?
Eva.. Yeah, of course.
Eva.. It's definitely not bad; it's pretty light
and nice but it doesn't compare to that.
Nick.. Yeah, no.
Eva.. That's like so full.
Nick.. I win. Yeah. It's so delicious.
Frankenhousen.
Eva.. Nick -- one.
Nick.. Yeah. Nick -- one.
Eva.. Eva -- zero.
Nick.. Eva -- zero.
Nick.. Is this like the first time you've done
this? This internet dating thing? This is
like the first time I've done this, so...
Eva.. Yeah. l just had one. l like met a guy
at a bar for drinks. That was it.
Nick.. That's it? There's...?
Eva.. It was kind of awful actually.
Nick.. Oh, it was awful, okay now we're
getting somewhere. What happened?
Eva.. Well, you know, nothing, but like, l
was there early. l just got there early,
whatever.
Eva.. And l was waiting for him and he was
like 20 minutes late.
Nick.. That always sucks.
Eva.. Then he shows up and he's wearing
a popped collar and l was like, ''Done with
you. Next.''
Nick.. That's... yeah... totally. l mean if you
would have been wearing a pop collar l
would have been out of here, also.
Eva.. But, yeah, that's the extent of my
internet dating...dating.
Eva.. You're a filmmaker, yes? Sory, l was
tying to remember your profile.
Nick.. l ty to make films. Basically, l have
been working on this one thing for like two
years
Nick.. and l'm like totally stuck with it
though so l am all like stressed and cranky
about it.
Eva.. What's it about? You so don't want to
talk about it.
Nick.. Aside from that, much less stressful
project l'm working on is this music video
for my friend's band.
Eva.. Cool.
Nick.. Yeah.
Nick.. Okay. Here's my stock question..
What kind of music do you like?
Nick.. What?
Eva.. That is so lame. That's lamer than...
Nick.. You just asked me what l do.
Eva.. You made fun of me for ''what do you
do.'' How is... so lame.
Nick.. l didn't make fun of you that much.
Eva.. Eva, wherever l am. Two? Do l have
two?
Nick.. One.
Eva.. One? Whatever, l get a point for
that.
Nick.. Whatever.
Eva.. Anyway... l could start listing bands
but you're not going to know any of them.
Nick.. What? How do you know that?
Nick.. l might know more about bands
thank you've like...
Eva.. It's just a hard way to answer a
question. It's a stupid question.
Nick.. Okay...
Nick.. What's the last thing you listened to?
Eva.. Ohhh...okay...have you ever heard of
this band 'applecury'?
Nick.. Yeah, totally.
Eva.. Really?
Nick.. No, l totally haven't.
Eva.. Oh my god l would have been so
excited, they're so good.
Nick.. Sory.
Eva.. So applecury...
Eva.....you just broke my hearrt. l was like
''Oh my god he's heard of them.''
Nick.. No but now there's this opporrtunity
for you to share that with someone.
Eva.. Absolutely. They're like a...what do
you call it...
Eva.. Actually, are you on The Lionshare?
Or have you heard of it?
Nick.. The Lionshare? No, l'm not on it and
l haven't heard of it; both those things.
Eva.. Well it's like a bit torrent site, you
download like movies and music and stuff.
Nick.. Yeah, l know what you're talking
about.
Eva.. You have to be invited though. So if
you give me your e-mail l could invite you.
Nick.. Oh, that's tricky.  l don't know if l
want to do that.
Eva.. Why?
Nick.. l don't know if we're at that level yet.
Where l could just give you my e-mail.
Eva.. Fine.
Nick.. l'm kidding...
Eva.. Then you'll never hear about
applecury again.
Nick.. Nick, my name. O, as in the letter.
Eva.. Got it.
Nick.. And rette, like nick-o-rette, like the
gum. R-E-T-T-E.
Eva.. Why the gum?
Nick.. l don't know, l like gum.
Eva.. So, l'm going to going to send you
my last invite
Eva.. and you have to download
applecury.
Nick.. l will.  l will, why wouldn't l do that?
That's why l was like ''Oh l want to check
that out.''
Eva.. Well, what if you forget who they
are?
Nick.. Okay.
Eva.. applecury is the name of the band.
Sory does that hurrt?
Nick.. No, it tickles a little bit.  Is there
anything else you want to put down there?
Eva.. Favorite color?
Nick.. Yeah, l mean, just write your whole
profile so l can look at it whenever l want.
Nick.. Okay, cool.
Eva.. Awesome.
Nick.. Thanks.
Eva.. So, how long have you known you
wanted to be a filmmaker?
Eva.. l'm just curious because like l still
don't know what l want to do.
Nick.. Totally yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Nick.. l don't know, ummm...
Nick.. We had my dad's big clunky VHS
camera. Like it was bigger than us. l feel
like evey family had these.
Eva.. Yeah we totally did.
Nick.. And we decided to re-make
Ghostbusters.
Eva.. Cool.
Nick.. Yeah, it was totally awesome.
Nick.. It was weird because all my friends
were really into the whole pretending and
Nick.. being in the movie thing but l like
really enjoyed being behind the camera.
Eva.. Uh-huh.
Nick.. And that was something l knew l
liked more than what they were doing so l
always ended up being there.
Eva.. That's so awesome.
Nick.. l guess. l mean, yeah.
Eva.....l've never seen Ghostbusters.
Nick.. What? Really?
Eva.. Yeah. l mean, like, there's plenty of
things l haven't seen but l've not seen
Ghostbusters.
Nick.. And Ghostbusters is one of them?
Nick.. All right. That...l can't...all right.
That needs to be rectified immediately.
Like now.
Eva.. l think l'd rather see your version of
Ghostbusters.
Nick.. This is -- this is -- this is way bigger
than just me.
Eva.. It was a carrtoon though too, right?
Nick.. Yeah it was a carrtoon, but you
haven't seen the movie?
Nick.. We need to watch Ghostbusters
right now. Like, for real. l don't know.
Eva.. There is a Blockbuster on the way to
my house.
Nick.. Is there?
Eva.. Just throwing it out there.
Nick.. They might in fact have a copy of
Ghostbusters that we could then watch at
your house.
Nick.. And...they don't have it.
Eva.. Seriously?
Nick.. Seriously.
Eva.. Where are you even looking?
Nick.. They have it, but...
Eva.. Ohhh and it was the Collector's
Series too. Should we ask? Maybe they
have it like in the back.
Nick.. Yeah.
Eva.. Do they have a back or...
Nick.. l mean, they might have it in the
front.
Nick.. l don't know maybe they have it at
like... l don't know.
Nick.. l would buy it. l would buy another
copyjust for this occasion.
Nick.. But l don't see anywhere in sight...
Eva.. l don't know where you could.
Nick.....that would actually sell DVDs.
Nick.. l don't know. What do you think?
Eva.. Lionshare...
Nick.. Lie and share?...all right.
Eva.. It's all one word, right?
Ghostbusters.
Nick.. It's not going to matter in the search
field.
Eva.. Awesome. It's downloading.
Eva.. It'll probably take about an hour,
maybe two hours...
Nick.. Cool. What?
Eva.. Do you want a drink? l have beer.
Nick.. What is this?
Eva.. It's my favorite little opener. See?
Nick.. l can't.  l can't handle that.
Eva.. Cheers.
Nick.. Cheers.
Eva.. To...Ghostbusters.
Nick.. Yeah, to Ghostbusters downloading.
Eva.. To finally seeing it.
Nick.. And to me seeing it for like the
millionth time.
Eva.. It's a pretty good job though. It's like
super chill, l can wear whatever l want. l
can like just hang out. It's a good job.
Nick.. That's cool. Do you have a title?
Eva.. Record Label Do-Stuff girl. That
would be my title, l think.
Nick.. That's a pretty awesome title.
Eva.. You win.
Nick.. Yep.
Eva.. That's embarrassing.
Eva.. Do you want another?
Nick.. Uh, yeah. Sure.
Eva.. Oh, you're not actually done. l could
have won.
Nick.. Too late now. That's a pretty
satisfying sound.
Nick.. Your hair's all like...
Eva.. Is it messed up? It does that. It's
fine. Thank you.
Eva.. It's cool. Theyjust fell over.
Nick.. l can't look. l'm not going to move
again.
Eva.. No, it's okay.
Nick.. Are you sure?
Eva.. Yeah it's fine.
Nick.. l'm sory.
Nick.. Do you want me to leave?
Eva.. Out of here. Get out of here.
Nick.. Alright.
Eva.. l've had enough. It's about time.
Yeah, it's almost time. For Ghostbusters.
Eva.. It should be. It's almost time.
Nick.. l can just feel you watching me.
Eva.. Do you feel like there's a lot of
pressure?
Nick.. Yeah, totally. So much pressure.
Eva.. Ready?
Nick.. It just locks?
Eva.. Yeah.
Nick.. Umm.
Eva.. l'm just going to go get a cab
because l'm really late...
Eva.....but the subway's that way.
Nick.. Okay, cool.
Eva.. Yeah.
Nick.. Hey listen, l had a lot of fun last
night.
Eva.. Yeah, me too.
Nick.. Cool. What are you doing this
weekend?
Eva.. l don't know yet. A friend of mine is
coming in from out of town. l don't know
what is going on with that.
Eva.. But l can let you know if you wanted
to like get together or something.
Nick.. Yeah, yeah. Cool. That's great.
Eva.. Yeah. l gotta go.
Nick.. Oh and definitely send me that invite
to that thing, l want to check out
applecury.
Eva.. Right. Definitely.  l'll like chat with
you online probably.
Nick.. Okay, yeah. Totally.
Nick.. Later.
Matty.. Maybe he's just over-worked, you
know?
Bracey.. How long does it take to get from
the fucking front door to right here?
Bracey.. [singing] Oh...l...just got laid last
night.  l...just got laid...last night...l just got
Iaid last night.
Bracey.. [singing] Oh l just got laid...my
name's Nick.
Matty.. Hey.
Nick.. Oh man...hey.
Bracey.. How'd it go buddy?
Nick.. All right man...what have you guys
been waiting all night to do that?
Matty.. Basically.
Bracey.. [singing] All night long...
Matty..  [singing] All night...
Nick..  [singing] All night...
Matty.. So, did you fucking put it in her
butt?
Nick.. Yeah, man. That was like the first
thing we did. We just took it from there,
you know?
Bracey.. l sense sarcasm.
Matty.. All right. Well, you going to see her
again?
Nick.. l don't know. Hopefully.
Bracey.. Work with us here. Work with us.
Come on.
Matty.. Yeah, seriously man. l mean is
there something you want to tell us?
Nick.. Give me a second guys. Geez.
Matty.. Come on man. We've been
camped out here all night.
Bracey.. All night long.
Nick.. You guys know what happened,
man. l said it was a good night, all right?
Matty.. Look at that face. He wants to tell
us but he really can't.
Bracey.. All right fine, fine, you don't want
to say anyything, that's cool.
Matty.. l can deal. l can deal.
Bracey.. You've changed. He's changed.
Matty.. You know, l'm just a friend who's
concerned about my friend getting action
but if you don't want to tell me
Matty.. anyything, that's cool by me. l'm
over here with my little Nintendo, my
internets.
Matty.. l'll be fine.  l'll occupy myself.
Bracey.. That's the song.
Nick.. The demo?
Bracey.. It's the second track, yeah.
Nick.. All right, awesome.
Matty.. Oh yeah. Is that the one you're
going to make the video for?
Nick.. Yeah, hopefully.  If you still want me
to do it.
Bracey.. l do want you to do it, yeah,
totally.  l just want you to, you know, listen
to it first.
Nick.. l'll listen to it, l'll ty to get some
ideas, you know.
Matty.. It is the beginning of bear mating
SeaSOn.
Matty.. What?
Matty.. No, l mean bears, they're starrting
to mate now.
Matty.. What? It's a bear fact.
Bracey.. Bear fact? What are you in?
Third grade? What is that? A bear fact...
Matty.. There's a direct correlation
between bears and Nick.
Nick.. What website are you looking at??
Matty.. This is my world.
Bracey.. You gotta get off that bestiality
kick man, that's really nasty.
Matty.. That's gross.
Nick.. It's too much.
Matty.. Look, l'm just saying there is a
direct correlation between the bears and
you and us...
Matty.....it's hunting season man. It's
potent, it's in the air. You just gotta reach
out and grab it, you know?
Bracey.. What are you guys doing
tomorrow? Tomorrow night, specifically.
Matty.. l think l might see the new James
Bond movie with my dad. It's a
hearrtwarming experience, l know.
Bracey No, sounds good. l'm going to be
playing at Stain if you're free, Nick.
Nick.. l think l might actually end up
seeing that girl again, hopefully.
Bracey.. l mean, that's awesome. And if
you're looking for something to do you can
bring her
Bracey.. and tell her to bring some of that
hot honey with her.
Bracey.. Bear fact, shit.
Nick.. l don't know.  l'm kinda reluctant
about that idea.  l think it's pretty terrible,
Bracey.
Bracey.. Why?
Nick.. What if she doesn't have any friends,
she'll just end up going home with
Nick.. you or some other stubbly, scruffy ,
guitar-playing...
Bracey.. You always do this. No. When
has this ever happened? Why...
Nick.. This always happens.
Matty.. It's true, man. A guitar is like
nature's pussy magnet.
Nick.. Bear fact.
Matty.. It's a bear fucking fact.
Nick.. Equals.
Bracey.. Yeah, alright. Maybe l'll see you
tomorrow.
Bracey.. Matty, have fun with your pops.
Matty.. Uh-huh.
Nick.. Later man.
Bracey.. All right, later guys.
Nick.. Later.
Bracey.. [muffled] God damn door. You're
gonna have to fix this shit...
Matty.. No, what was that about anywa,y?
Yeah l know. Dad? l said it was fine
okay?
Matty.. We can probably just catch another
showing another time, okay? l don't know
even if it's still playing.
Matty.. Well there's a show coming up that
my friend's... no, you don't know him. Dad,
you don't know him.
Matty.. His name's Bracey, he's in a band
and he's playing a show and he really
wants me to go so...
Matty.. l don't know. Nothing really
unusual.
Matty.. She seemed fine.
Matty.. Yeah well l mean what did you
expect?
Matty.. Dad? Dad? l am fine, okay. l
mean, l got paid last week.
Matty.. Alright well when l go to the show
how about you just give me a call that day
Matty.. and then maybe we can see if we
can, you know, find another time to go
Matty.. see it or just give me a call. We'll
see what happens, okay?
Matty.. All right. l love you too. Bye.
Matty.. Oh no. Oh god what have l
starrted?
Nick.. Yeah. We got to put a stop to that
as soon as possible.
Matty.. Yeah, right in its bear tracks.
Voice.. Drive 1.5 miles then keep left on
l-278.
Matty.. Okay. Thank you.
Nick.. Yeah we're gonna be late.
Matty.. We're gonna be late.
Nick.. No doubt about it.
Nick.. We're going to walk in and Bracey's
just gonna be like uhhh-AAHHHH-uhhhhh
Nick.. ''Thank you eveybody. That was our
Iast song.''
Matty.. That's happened to me once. He
didn't care though.
Nick.. l thought of calling what's her face
but l didn't.  l was like, yeah...
Voice.. Please drive to highlighted route.
Nick.. It's too soon.
Matty.. Do you watch Project Runway?
Nick.. Not really, no. Why?
Matty.. Well, the girl l have a massive
crush on...
Nick.. Yeah.
Matty.....is the winner. So, that kind of
perked up my day a little bit.
Nick.. Did you celebrate her victoy with
Jane?
Matty.. Oh, yeah. Actually Jane was the
one that got me on to the show.
Nick.. Got you... oh so you were a
contestant?
Matty.. No yeah, you don't remember when
l was a contestant on the show?
Nick.. Yeah, can't believe l didn't
remember that.
Matty.. Well, you know those situations
where you have a girlfriend and they have
a TV show they have to watch?
Matty.. l basically watch whatever she
watches and she watches Project Runway.
So l starrted watching Project Wunway.
Matty.. Project WUNway. Project
RUN...way.
Matty.. l starrted watching Project RUNway.
Matty.. But yeah, she has all these shows
she needs to watch so l watch them.
Matty.. l mean it's like, l have no shows l
need to watch.
Nick.. l'm like the complete opposite of
that. l'm even worse than her l need to
watch
Nick.. pretty much everything. Not
necessarily Project Runway, but you know
what l mean.
Matty.. Yeah it's true, l mean, l did get into
Lost because of you.
Nick.. Yeah.
Matty.. That's what happens to me, l get
into shows because of other people.
Nick.. Yeah, l don't know...these are
always things that l just discover on my
OWn.
Nick.. Yeah.  l'm like, l was looking at that
thing over there.
Matty.. With the giant George
Washington?
Nick.. Yeah, the...cyborg.
Matty.. Sent back from the future. To give
us democracy.
Nick.. Yeah.
Matty.. That's funny.
Bracey.. Hey eveybody. my name's
Bracey. It's like Tracey with a B.
Bracey.. All right, l'm gonna play this song l
haven't really named yet...
Bracey.. l kinda just wrote it last week.
Nick.. Yo.
Girl.. What's up.
Matty.. Hey chica.
Girl..  l like your shirrt; l like yourjacket.
Nick.. Thank you.
Matty.. Thank you.
Matty.. We put our powers combined...
Matty.....we'll be a totally suave looking
dude.
Girl.. Totally would. Lose the shoes
though.
Matty.. Whoa.
Girl.. Just kidding.
Matty.. l was admiring this picture before.
l thought the guy was throwing up blood
Matty.. but apparently it's fire. But if you go
over here it looks like it's dripping blood.
Girl.. Oh...
Matty.. l wonder who goes about that. Is it
sorrt of like some guy who owns the place
Matty.. has his friends decorate it or is it
just people do it and then...
Girl.. So l recently starrted Netti-Potting...
Matty.. l think you're too caught up in the
content, you know?
Matty.. l mean like eveybody that people
think did totally original stuff was just
ripping on someone else. You know?
Nick.. That's true.
Matty.. l mean Kurrt Cobain said when he
made ''Smells Like Teen Spirit''
Matty.. He was basically tying to make a
really good Pixies song.
Nick.. Right, yeah. Totally. l never heard
that but l can see that.
Nick.. l'm sure like when The Pixies were
making their songs they were like
Nick.. ''Oh let's make a really great Talking
Heads song.''
Matty.. They had that flyer out for their
bassist and it was like someone that has
Matty.. the influences of Peter Paul & May
and Husker Du. And that's how the bassist
joined the band.
Nick.. The Pixies?
Matty.. Yeah.
Nick.. That's crazy.  Isn't the bassist the
girl?
Matty.. Uh-huh. Kim Deal.
Nick.. That's crazy.
Bracey.. l don't know a Marty pUppy
what's a Marrty-puppy?
Bracey.. What are you talking about?
Marrty-puppy... l'll make a song called
''Marrty Puppy''...
Bracey.. This sounds like a dog song.
Matty.. You ever think about just walking
away from it? Take a break?
Nick.. What am l doing if l take a break
from it? l don't have anyything else that l go
back to when l am not doing this.
Nick.. Like, this is my break. So if l take a
break from this...
Bracey.. [singing]...and l'll never see
puppy again.
Matty.. l told you, you should stop buying
these shitty lighters and get like a fucking
Zippo, you know?
Matty.. Light it off your boot and shit.
Nick.. l might as well get a fucking match.
Matty.. Get the ladies and shit, you know.
Nick.. Ah, fuck it.
[Loud POP]
Matty.. Terrorist! You're a terrorist!
Nick.. Did that thing just explode?
Matty.. Yeah. Yeah. Yes, it did.
Matty.. That's fucked up. What if that like
popped in your pocket?
Nick.. God damn it l hate my arrtistic life,
crunch. It ignites my whole pants.
Bracey.. Thank you. Thank you. Tough
crowd.
Matty.. l don't know. Something came up
and we just didn't go. l don't know what.
Yeah l know. Well, it's imporrtant to me too.
l mean if it was so imporrtant to him...
Matty.. Yeah.
Matty.. Yeah, l know, mom. l know.
Matty.. Okay. Mom? l have to go work so
would it be okay if l just called you back
Iater? All right. Yeah. No, it's all right. No,
l'm sory. Okay.
Matty.. Love you too. Bye-bye.
Matty.. Shit.
Matty.. Yo ass-fuck. You up?
Matty.. Hey. Nice pajamas.
Nick.. Fuck.
Matty.. So you going to get up?
Nick.. Fuck no.
Matty.. Okay. You know it's a nice day; it's
3 o'clock, you know.
Nick.. Yeah. So fucking what?
Matty.. Touche, touche.
Matty.. l'm going to go to work. l'll catch
you later.
Jane.. Thyme? No.
Matty.. [singing] Anyytime now...
Jane.. Here.
Matty.. Thank you.
Jane.. It's as hot as it goes.
Matty.. It's as hot as it goes, huh?
Matty.. My dad called me recently.
Jane.. Oh, yeah?
Jane.. How did that go?
Matty.. He wanted to go see, you know the
new Bond movie? But...
Matty.....he kind of blew me off the first
time. So, when he wanted to go see it
again, l blew him off and l kind of feel like a
dick about it.
Jane.. Why?
Matty.. l don't know.  l mean, it's kind of like
this old tradition -- l can't find the thing, by
the way, for this.  l'm looking for my thing.
Jane.. This is your house.
Jane.. You're not...well, you are a dick, but
you're not being a dick right now.
Matty.. You sure?
Jane.. Yes. You're not a dick.
Matty.. Thanks.
Jane.. You're welcome.
Matty.. You should put a little more.
Jane.. No, l put enough. l kept in mind
your spicy thing.
Matty.. Just a little bit more.
Jane.. l have this going on over here.
Matty.. That's fine.
Jane.. You could even put it away.
Matty.. Okay. Ohh.
Jane.. Oh my god, you're such an
asshole.
Matty.. What, l like it.
Jane.. Do you want to cook the food?
Matty.. Yeah, yeah l do actually.
Jane.. Okay, yeah. Well, you can't.
Jane.. And besides...it makes your cum
taste awful.
Matty.....what?
Jane.. l said it makes your cum taste
awful, so...
Matty.....my cum tastes awful?
Jane.. It's the spices, it's not...your cum
tastes lovely usually, but not with this.
Matty.. Well, l know what not to expect
tonight.
Matty.. We're starrting to have an odd
relationship...
Jane.. You just dug your own grave.
Matty.. My fucking cum tastes funny?
Matty.. l'm gonna take a shit and l'm going
to think about this.
Jane.. That's great.
Nick.. There we go.
Jane.. Yeah, l mean, l'm just here for the
weekend, like, l have class on Monday. So
l'm going back to the grind.
Nick.. Oh, that sucks.
Jane.. Yeah. l mean, it's okay. It's nice to
be back in school again doing....
Nick.....something?
Jane.. Yeah, eXactly.
Nick.. Totally, like l wish l was back in
school again cause l don't feel like l'm
doing anyything.
Jane.. Yeah. l mean, it gives you -- it
definitely gives you a sense of purpose.
Nick.. Right. That's what you're paying for.
Jane.. Yeah, eXactly. My thousands of
dollars...
Jane.. But yeah like, l have to pay like over
$700 in textbooks.
Jane.. Where -- l don't have $700 for
textbooks.
Nick.. Right. Because you already gave
them like thousands of dollars...
Jane.. Right, l already gave them my soul,
l signed that away.
Nick.. Yeah, right.
Jane.. It didn't cover textbooks though.
Nick.. That's ridiculous, you're already
paying them to like, spend that time to give
you all that information.
Jane..  l know, it's like...
Nick.. The education, that's what you're
paying for.
Jane.. Right, eXactly, it's like, give me the
fucking books,
Jane.....you owe me that, and then l will
Iearn.
Nick.. Yeah.
Jane.. Yeah, it's really backwards.
Nick.. It's ass-backwards.
Jane.. It is ass-backwards. But l don't like
to think about that on the weekends. This
is my relaxing time. This is Jane time.
Nick.. This is Jane time, okay.
Jane.. Yes. This is my Jane time.
Nick.. Cool. l guess we're all just a parrt of
Jane time right now.
Jane.. Yes. All of you.
Nick.. Yeah. All two of us.
Jane.. Yeah.
Jane.. Matt was telling me about this thing
that you're doing with Bracey, the video
thing...?
Nick.. Oh, l was like, ''l'm doing
something? What am l doing?''
Jane.. l heard. You know, l got the signal.
Nick.. Yeah, totally. The Matt signal. l get
those all the time.
Jane.. Right, yeah.
Nick.. He's like, ''l have this song that l
want to put out on YouTube and MySpace
and stuff just to get more stuff out there...''
Nick..  and so he was like, ''Oh, you know,
if you could video...'' So l was like, ''All
right, yeah, sure. Of course.''
Jane.. That's cool.
Nick.. Yeah l guess, l haven't really like
worked on it all. Like l have like no ideas
for it whatsoever, but...
Jane.. l mean, l'm sure you're gonna think
of something.
Nick.. Hopefully.
Jane.. Like, l've always thought your stuff
was really awesome.
Nick.. Oh, well thanks. Sure.
Jane.. Yeah no like when we were in
school l was always really really
impressed.
Nick.. Okay, yeah, sure.  l -- l'm like, ''Oh,
great,'' l can't like...
Jane.. l mean, you know that though. You
know that.
Nick.. You know... l don't know. You know
how it is, like, with me.  l'm just like, ''Ahhh
l don't know.''
Matty.. Food's ready kids.
Nick.. What the fuck?
Jane.. Too much. Too much. Too much.
Nick.. Dude, what the fuck did you do?
Jane.. [coughing] Oh my god...
Matty.. Water's not going to help you.
Jane.. Oh my god well then what am l
supposed to do?
Jane.. What...?
Nick.. What are you doing?
Jane.. What are you doing?
Matty..  Milk's a base, this stuff'll like cut all
the acidic shit out...
Nick.. That is so nasty.
Matty.. It's not that bad.
Jane.. Okay, you know what? Bear fact..
you're retarded.
Nick.. You too now? With the fucking bear
fact.
Jane.. He was saying it, and now he's got
me saying it. l just... yeah.
Nick.. l did not think that one was gonna
Iast.
Jane.. What is this on?
Matty.. What do you mean?
Jane.. Like is this on TV or...?
Matty.. It's on Nick's computer actually.
Jane.. Seriously?
Jane.. Nick's computer hooks up to the
TV?
Matty.. Yeah. Nick's the man. With the
plan.
Jane.. So cool.
Jane.. Are you going to draw me my
carrtoon soon?
Matty.. Yeah. It's just a work progress,
you know? It's going to take some time.
Jane.. Some time? You do that shit all the
time.
Matty.. Yeah, well, l mean, it's usuallyjust
stupid shit, l can't just will it out of
nowhere...
Matty.....when it's something imporrtant,
you know? For you it would be imporrtant.
Jane.. l'm skeptical.
Jane.. Are you mad at me?
Matty.. A little bit.
Jane.. Why?
Matty.. You said my cum tastes funny.
Jane.. Bear fact.
Matty.. Fuck you. Bear fucking fact...
Nick.. You guys really got to stop with that
or l'm going to kill myself.
Jane.. Aww. ''You guys have to stop doing
that before l kill myself.''
Matty.. Fuck this. We're gonna do a blind
taste test. Nick, l want you to beat off into
a cup and we'll do a Pepsi challenge. See
what she says.
Nick.. Uhh, l kind of already did that, so... l
was waiting for you to ask.
Matty.. Oh, really?
Nick.. Yeah. l mean it's been here for
awhile though...
Nick.....so, you probably have a bit of an
advantage; yours is probably a little bit
more fresh.
Matty.. Let's fucking do this right now.
Jane.. You guys are so fucking gross.
That's disgusting.
Matty.. We've been roommates for a long
time, it's only been a matter of time.
Jane.. l don't even know what that means.
Matty.. It means--
Nick.. --we've been doing these taste tests
for a long time.
Matty.. That's eXactly what it means.
Jane.. That was the one thing l was
hoping it didn't mean.
Jane.. Hey. What are you doing out here?
Nick.. Uhh, l didn't really want to, you
know, smoke in the aparrtment while you
were there.
Jane.. Really?
Nick.. Yeah.
Jane.. That's so sweet.
Nick.. Yeah, l guess. l don't know. Yeah,
that's me.
Jane.. That is you.
Jane.. Can you, like, drink out here? Is
that okay or is it like public consumption or
something?
Nick.. What? What do you mean?
Jane.. l don't know, that sounds stupid, l
don't know. Like, can you do that?
Jane.. What was that?
Nick.. l just got dive-bombed by a moth or
something.
Jane.. Monster?
Nick.. Actually that looks like a monster
bee.
Nick.. It's night-time, you're not supposed
to be here.
Nick.. Oh my god it's right there.
Jane.. Oh jesus.
Nick.. All right hold on.
Jane.. This is really not giving you points
in the masculinity deparrtment right now.
Jane.. Don't step on it!
Nick.. Oh, no. l'd rather have it like stab
me.
Jane.. l'm going to go get my drink, l'll be
right back.
Nick.. Sure.
Jane.. Okay.
Nick.. That was quick.
Jane.. That's much better.
Nick.. Sure.
Jane.. Are my teeth stained?
Nick.. Yeah a little bit.
Jane.. Really?
Nick.. Just a little bit, what.  l wasn't gonna
be like ''No.''
Jane.. Ugh.
Nick..  It's fine.
Jane.. All right, whatever.
Nick.. You're losing teeth points.
Jane.. Oh yeah, all right. Fair enough.
Jane.. Maybe just one drag?
Nick.. You can do what you want.
Jane.. l can, l can.
Nick.. l'm not responsible if he catches you
of course.
Jane.. Yeah.
Jane.. That was nice.
Nick.. Yeah okay cool.
Jane.. So umm...tell me about this internet
girl.
Nick.. Umm. There's really sadly nothing
to tell, unforrtunately.
Jane.. So...is that why you're so down?
Because she hasn't called you?
Nick.. l'm not down, really.
Jane.. Come on.
Nick.. All right, maybe l'm a little down, l
guess.
Jane.. Do you think l could maybe have...a
cigarette?
Nick.. Really?
Nick.. Here you go.
Jane.. Thank you.
Nick.. One of my lighters exploded the
other day. Like seriously.
Jane.. That happens?
Nick.. Yeah, apparently. It just...
Jane.. Oh my god.
Jane.. Thank you.
Nick.. Sure.
Jane.. So wait, you didn't explain it to me...
Nick.. What?
Jane.. Why are you so down? l don't... l
still don't really understand.  It's about the
girl, it's not about the girl...
Nick..  It's not, ugh, it...l'm like creatively-
constipated like all the time.
Jane.. Ugh. Okay, disgusting.
Nick.. What, constipated?
Jane.. Yes. You know l don't like toilet
humor or language or...
Nick.. You're fucking weird.
Jane.. Okay, you know what?
Jane.. You're fucking weird.
Nick.. l am, l know.
Jane.. Yeah but you know it's just like...
Jane.....l know that things will be fine,
eventually. So if things are going to be fine
Iater...
Jane.....they should be fine now.
Nick.. Mmm-hmm.
Jane.. Fine later, fine now.
Nick.. You get that from somewhere or
something? What is that?
Jane.. Umm, l don't know, maybe.
Nick.. Yeah l do feel better.
Jane.. Good.
Nick.. Cool.
Nick.. Are you going to your dad's soon?
Matty.. Yeah.
Nick.. You going to be back for Lost?
Matty.. Is it a new one?
Nick.. Yeah, it's the new season.
Matty.. Fuck. Can you set the DVR?
Nick.. It's already set. You just set it once
and it remembers.
Matty.. l'm not going to make it in time...
Matty.. We're going out for my dad's
birrthday dinner, so.
Nick.. It's your dad's birrthday?
Matty.. On Friday, but l mean we are just
celebrating tonight.
Nick.. Oh, perfect.
Matty.. What is this?
Nick.. It's a screener copy of auantum of
Solace.
Matty.. You serious?
Nick.. Yeah totally, like they give it to the
critics, so it's kind of like a bootleg...
Nick.. but it's not like shaky-camcorder
type, it's like a real DVD.
Matty.. Dude, thanks. No, l mean
seriously like this means a lot.
Matty.. My dad's going to love this. l mean,
like, l owe you.
Nick.. Great, man. Yeah. Don't wory
about it.
Matty.. l mean if you want to like have sex
with my girlfriend or something, go ahead.
Nick.. Well l mean how do you know do
you know l already haven't?
Matty.. Good point, good point.
Matty You sure the DVR is set?
Nick.. It's definitely set; don't wory.
Matty.. It is?
Nick.. It's good. We'll watch it.
Nick.. We'll watch it.
Matty.. Cool. Today's a good day.
Nick.. Yeah man.
Male.. Motherfuck. When l get back.
Nick..  l'll take care of that.
Nick.. Later.
[from TV] Male.. Stop it, you know what l
want to hear.
[from TV] Male.. No l don't.
[from TV] Male.. You played it for her, you
can play it for me.
Nick.. Hey Bracey, it's Nick, what's going
on man?
Nick.. You still want me to do that video
right?
Nick.. Okay, cool man, l got a bunch of
ideas for it, it turns out, so.
Nick.. Yeah, yeah, no l did. Why? What's
up?
Nick.. Well, l mean...why does anybody
put music on the internet? So people can
hear it.
Nick.. Ummm...you were selling it at the
show, so...you were already disseminating
it to random people
Nick.. so it didn't even cross my mind
that... How is that different?
Nick.. Oh, well... dude, l mean, it sounded
pretty damn good to me. l had no idea that
you -- that it wasn't a finished product.
Nick.. Yeah, l guess l'll talk to you later
man. Later.
Nick.. Hey, Eva, it's Nick. It's twenty-to-
five on Thursday and l was just wondering
if you were doing anyything tonight...
Nick.. cause my friend's band, which l told
you about, is playing at this place...
Nick.....and of course you're all into new
music and shit so l thought you might like
to come along.
Nick.. Umm, l guess, if you get this before
this evening give me a call back and
maybe we can get something together.
Nick.. All right. Hope to hear from you
soon. Bye.
Matty.. It didn't fucking record?
Nick.. It's not my fault, l set it. l did
eveyrything l was supposed to do. You
know, technology. It does what it wants.
Matty.. Fucking Time Warner.
Nick.. Yep. No, well actually we don't have
Time Warner. It's not that.
Matty.. Well, fucking SkyNet, fucking
Cablevision, l don't fucking know...
Nick.. l don't know, l think it may be the
show is just so awesome the DVR couldn't
handle it.
Matty.. The show is just so awesome?
Matty.. l mean what little piece of
technology knew l wasn't going to be home
Matty.. so it sabotaged itself so l couldn't
watch the show?
Matty.. It's the principle of the matter, man,
it's the fucking principle.
Matty.. This is why we should not have
thrown out our fucking VCR.
Matty.. l don't need quality. l just want to
know what happened.
Nick.. You don't need quality? You don't
prefer quality?
Matty.. Ah, it's a TV show. It's a TV show.
Nick.. Well l mean, l was going to get it off
the Internet you know with great quality
and no commercials
Nick.. but if you're not into that sorrt of
thing...
Matty.. Well l mean if you're going to do it,
then by all means do it, l'm just saying
Matty.. when you need your fix, it doesn't
matter the grade, you just take it.
Nick.. Right. You'll take what you can get,
yeah.
Matty.. Fuck.
Nick.. Fuck.
Matty.. Fuck. Did you watch it?
Nick.. l watched it, yeah.
Matty.. Okay. Was it good?
Nick.. It was--
Matty.. You know what, don't even -- don't
even tell me. Don't tell me anyything.
Nick.. All right, but l just have to say this
one thing --
Matty.. Don't don't don't...don't tell me
anyything. l don't want to know.
Nick.. All right.
Nick.....it was awesome.
Nick.. How was the movie?
Matty.. Didn't watch it but l did give it to
him and he was actually really happy about
that.
Nick.. Good.
Matty.. l think it made his night.
Nick.. Excellent.
Matty.. Thank you.
Nick.. No problem....what the fuck is this?
Matty.. What the fuck is what?
Nick.. On the radio. Fucking... applecury.
l don't believe this.
Matty.. Oh. Who's applecury?
Nick.. It's that band l was listening to that
one time where you were like
Nick.. ''Oh, who is this?'' and l was like ''Oh
it's applecury, they're so great.''
Nick.. l can't fucking believe this. You
know what, l don't even listen to the radio.
Matty.. Yeah l was about to ask you about
that, why are we listening to the radio?
Nick.. l don't know. l don't have my iPod
with me, l don't know what l did with it.
Nick.. It's under something, somewhere.
Matty.. Fucking machines, man.
Nick.. Fucking machines, yeah. It's hiding
from me. l fucking hate this song, man.
Matty.. It's not that bad.
Nick.. No, they always take the worst song
on the album and make it the single. l will
never understand that.
Matty.. l mean, l'll just tell people that you
heard them first
Matty.. and you're wicked underground,
and that will garner you a lot of scene
points.
Nick.. All right, great.
Nick.. Just make sure you don't show
them this song.
Matty.. l won't.
Matty.. Did you find it yet?
Nick.. Uhh, not yet. One sec.
Matty.. All right.
Nick.. It's not working.
Matty.. What do you mean it's not
working?
Nick.. l mean it's being weird.  It's not
working.
Matty.. Shit.
Nick.. Don't wory, l'll get it for you.
Matty.. This is fucked. This is bear fucked.
Nick..  It'll be all right.
Bracey.. Thank you vey much.
Bracey.. l haven't played this one live yet
so l hope you enjoy it.
Bracey.. l kind of worked on it from
something that happened with my friends
Nick and Matty...don't wory about it.
Bracey.. Give it up for Domi,nick back
there on the drums
Bracey.. my man Dan who's picking up the
bass...
Bracey..  and...l'm Bracey, thanks for
eveybody coming out tonight. Thank you.
Bracey.. Hey guys.
Nick.. Yo, what's going on man?
Matty.. Good fucking crowd tonight.
Bracey.. Yeah l know, l think it's like the
biggest crowd we've had yet.
Bracey.. It's pretty crazy. Some crazy shit
is going down. It's insanity.
Nick.. What happened?
Bracey.. Well, you know how you put my
demo online?
Nick.. Yeah, l remember.
Bracey.. Yeah, well, umm... somebody
from a label, they downloaded it. Long
stoy shorrt, l think l'm getting signed.
Matty.. Dude, holy shit.
Nick.. Are you fucking kidding me?
Bracey.. Yeah it's really crazy...l mean, and
like, you know, well --
Nick.. Yeah dude, don't wory about.
Obviously it all worked out, so.
Nick.. Yeah it's fine.
Bracey.. l told them that we shot a video
and they want to see it, so we've got to get
working on that.
Matty.. Congratu-fucking-lations man.
Bracey.. Yeah, thanks a lot man.
Nick.. Yeah, man.
Bracey.. l'm freaking out, l'm freaking out.
Clearly l'm freaking out.
Matty.. Man, l mean, just go with it.
Bracey.. And l met a girl dude. l met a girl.
Nick.. Really?
Bracey.. She's awesome.
Matty.. Bear fucking mating season.
Nick.. They have a long mating season.
Bracey.. She must have downloaded some
of our music online, l don't really know...
Bracey.. but she ended up coming to one
of our shows and we were talking
afterward...
Eva.. l just got offered psychic reading.
Bracey.. Matty. Nick. Eva.
Eva.. Hi, nice to meet you.
Nick.. Hey.
Eva.. Hi.
Bracey.. So, this is what l'm thinking. Go
to your place, my place, a bar, so we can
talk.
Nick.. We should totally go to a bar.
Matty.. l'm actually kind of hungy --
Nick.. Yeah, or go to a diner or something.
That would be great.
Bracey.. Cool.
Eva.. l mean l was just going to go home
anyways, so...
Nick.. No, you really don't have to, come
on, there's no need for that.
Eva.. l mean l really did fun with you --
Nick.. Yeah.
Eva.. l didn't know he was your friend, or
else --
Nick.. No, it's -- don't wory about it. Look,
it's not like, you know, we were in a serious
relationship or anyything.
Nick.. l mean it was only that one night. Of
course l did have a lot of fun that night too,
but...
Eva.. Right.
Nick.. Well, yeah.
Nick.. Have you heard the new
applecury?
Eva.. No. l haven't been into them much.
Ever since they got like really big and like
played on the radio and stuff.
Nick.. Yeah no l heard them on the radio.
Eva.. l think l heard them on an Apple
commercial the other day.
Nick.. An Apple commercial? Oh yeah it's
for that new iPod that like...probably sucks
your dick or something.
Nick.. Those things can do eveyrything.
Eva.. Blow dy your hair with it.
Nick.. Blow dy your hair...cheese grater...
Nick.....snow shoes...
Matty.. Evey time l ty to get out, they pull
me back in. Fredo! Fredo!
Eva.. What is that from?
Matty.. It's from The Godfathers. It's one
of those moving pictures. You know, like
that sexy one.
Bracey.. Two seniors for Sarica Jessica
Parker's ''Sexy Town'' please.
Matty.. l work at a movie theater, and you
ever notice when old people come in
Matty.. theyjust never remember the title
of the movie they want to see?
Eva.. Mm-hmm.
Matty.. Well, l've kind of whittled it down to
a couple of basic rules.
Matty..  First off, if the word ''the'' is in front
of a title, theyjust totally omit it.  Or they
add it if it isn't there.
Matty.. They also do this thing where they
pluralize and de-pluralize movies.
Matty.. So ''Transformers'' ends up
becoming like
Matty.. ''Five seniors for 'The Transformer'.''
You know? ''And a pickle.''
Bracey.. ''l Transform.''
Matty.. ''l Transform.''
Matty.. This woman come in once and she
was like ''Give me three seniors for 'Failure
to Launch'.''
Matty.. And there's no movie even close to
that title on the marquee.
Matty.. Oh, l fucked it up.
Nick.. You said 'Failure to Launch'...
Nick.....and that's what it was.
Matty.. It was 'Failure to Launch'.
Matty.. Yeah. She asked for 'Full Throttle',
l'm sory. But she was like
Matty.. ''Yeah give me one for 'Full
Throttle'.'' So she went from 'Failure to
Launch' to 'Full Throttle' somehow.
Matty.. l don't know how.
Eva.. They both have to do with, like,
flying.
Bracey.. Throttling....you like throttling.
Matty.. Dude.
Matty.. All right, so give me a title, l'll give
you an eXample. Name a movie.
Eva.. Okay, umm...
Eva.....Ghostbusters.
Bracey.. Two seniors for... 'The Great
Ghost Bust'.
Eva.. That's breaking the rules. You're not
following the rules.
Matty.. Once you know the rules you can
do whatever you want, you know?
Matty.. It's like jazz. You have a foundation
and you just keep going from there.
Bracey.. You feel your way through it.
Eva.. That's awesome. They totally do
that.
Matty.. Yeah it's true.
Eva.. It's like -- what's that thing you say?
It's like a total -- it's like a polar bear fact.
Bracey.. That's cute.
Nick.. Shut up.
Nick.. It's Bear Fact.
Eva.. Bear fact.
Nick.. Yeah.
Nick.. You can't have that joke; that's my
joke. It's not yours.
Bracey.. All right...
Matty.. l think that was myjoke anyway.
Bracey.. l kind of thought it was a
communal thing.
Matty.. Hey baby boy.
Matty.. Coffee's up if you want it.
Nick.. Thanks.
Matty.. l see you had a long night last
night.
Nick.. Yeah, it was pretty long.
Matty.. Yeah. What'd you think of Bracey's
new girlfriend?
Nick.. She's nice.
Matty.. Yeah. Slammin' body.
Matty.. Hey did you happen to download
Lost?
Matty.. You're my man with the hook-ups
SOn.
Nick.. Fuck.
Matty.. What?
Matty.. This site has been closed for...
Fuck. That sucks.
Nick.. Yeah...you just knew it was going to
end this way though.
Matty.. Well, come on man, we'll make our
own. We'll call it The Bear Share.
Nick.. Bear's don't share.
Matty.. Sure they do.
Nick.. No they don't. They don't share.
Matty.. Yes they do...all right, well what do
they do? Lions share...
Nick.. They mate. Bears mate.
Matty.. Bears mate? Okay...
Nick.. l'm not a bear anymore.
Matty.. You're always a bear, man.
Matty.. Well let's see, lions share,
bear...facts. We got tiger...beats?
Matty.. Hey. l just wrote you a song.