a day in the dawn of history one tiny
speck in the limitless sands of eternity
a day before time began Wednesday 25th
may 190 6303 be see
mother nature a young girl still stirs
to greet the new morning while man her
groom-to-be her Conqueror her lover
takes his first proud steps upon the
stage of history
hey
nopee y'all pay incapable of perceiving
as yet his glorious destiny in capable
even of such simple skills as walking
upright man devotes his smoldering
genius to survival and the unending
quest for food
hey what's this looks like a fossil hmm
Jurassic period i'd say hmm almost
stupid em thanks to the rise old chief
man's quest for food is over mama yum in
time-honored tradition man after food
explores the joys of law
can you leave a scar but we can't wait
to try to torture
Wednesday 2050 where e190 6302 bc nine
months later
oh the missing link makes his first
entrance and man greets the unfamiliar
in typical fashion
thus has happened so often too
disappointed parents play their parts in
the mighty forces of destiny
and a relationship is born that will
change the face of history oh the
missing link and his faithful
brontosaurus egg whoa
me
so this is the place croaks the name cut
out shake the hand kid and shake the
hand you new here let me show you around
what's the problem kid oh you can't walk
Oh walking yeah that's nothing watch
this
Oh
how'd you like that huh one listen man
whoa don't you listen him kid he's just
jealous because he can't today he's a
genetic what did I tell you happy what
did I tell you
in brain
Oh Mike Lee's Oh like sky Oh like brown
Oh like trees Oh like Lee's right sky oh
my crown oh my treatise all like leaves
oh mai tai o light brown Oh like 30
light please all right
No
oh hey oh hey oh hey
oh hey cutting classes huh attaboy broke
the same shake the hand kick very good
Oh naked genius you know kid I've had my
eye on you you've got what we here at
that was called potential the trouble is
you're a man and write a dead end a
non-starter a knuckle-dragger a primeval
slime in short the best laughs since the
Big Bang
but I love a challenge with expert
tuition you can be boosted several rungs
up the genetical leather lesson number
one how to fly fly the basic skill oh
let's go good kid good you're getting it
no oh slide oh man man fly hey you you
are implicating an historical moment hey
lizard you know your trouble you don't
have desire my people used to be like
you just big useless bags of meat but we
had desire lizards go figure
and if he cannot fly our tiny brained
hero can at least look and learn
one day Oh makes the discovery that even
the dimmest of men must him so no no no
me oh you Pig wha you not all right you
not man no no no what oh what oh what oh
what oh what oh oh oh god oh oh god oh
oh fly Eagle no fly he who have big
useless bag of meat
oh god oh no mango no no he who are bad
oh no Wandy gwa oh one man yes Oh want
man because man however dumb seeks his
own full of hope Oh sets out on his
legendary journey but discovers only too
soon that things are not always what
they see
kid
snakes it's the fuzz let go don't you
roll goddamn flying and so old flies
away from his homeland is youth and
though neither of them know it his
long-lost brother
not bad huh whoa no bad a mere Bagatelle
my little mud munchers watch this get
phones
I
it looks like an accident so do that's a
dangerous corner
listen dummy wings ain't all right means
is a privilege I'm coming around the
mountain mind my own goddamn business
when here comes this fucking Turkey
ain't looking where he's gonna kiss
black me you are calling me a turkey
listen you genetic joke you know what
these are disposable thumbs yeah how do
you like them apples huh meanwhile he
Guam faithful reptile that he is
searches for lordly for his little
friend
hearing the worst he decides like Oh to
seek out his own kind
Oh God
BRR
rejected by his own species aguar
thoughts turned once more to hope
perhaps somewhere in the world he is
still alive
Oh
neyo pleased to meet you those were you
nice talking with you in fact yo man
we're no lo widows the quarter we're
happiest corner yessiree Bob
wait no no Oh what no no mother nature
need us to keep a secret like someone's
got to do not drop a queer dudes are
just right good food with me good god
let's eat
yo me fly croak big water big rocks I
look the tribal it broadens the line for
food so Greece there's no place like
home hey hey hey hey no no it's great to
be a no no we never get weekends and if
we did you know we send them working
with our friends have a nice day a voice
thing I will those days have a nice day
it's great to be your no lo you never
scale the heights but then you never get
down if alice is real nice
giuliano look damn damn damn damn damn
damn all we do is work and work and work
and work on time and on these work and
work and work and work and work and work
and work
this guy's a troublemaker a weirdo a nut
there's one in every barrel James for
changes sake hole that runs good Oh beat
it scripting clamping hop it beat it
skip it lumping well what do you know
it's raining lunch hey after you after
you after me after me I'm begging your
pardon fellas but then this little guy
is a special project of money well
that's all very well pal but we ain't
had a bite since we ate last Oh in that
case and would you all kind indulgence
I'll do the coughing
be our guest be our gas yeah coconut
croak a weird / oh no one croak what do
you mean your bum without me you're
nothing you're the lowest if you married
a mollusk they call you a social climber
I never but never touch meat until it's
aged at least a week
huh pleased to meet you how's my dear
nice talking with you heap and dad
aren't they adorable look those are you
go we go cutie boy out of you one minute
here next minute boom que sera sera hey
you want to know something
oh damn he's on my side he's 20 over
limit my block what the hell was that
shit look at that fucking lunatic did
good look am I supposed to play
something huh he sings those are on
trees you know he'll be drawing me
that way this way and the boys in the
book
every time but I love
Wow
oh no no oh no no
pleased to meet you how's by you nice
talking with you keep in touch me man
you
oh you know man
whoa one no man me Oh me man
hey hey hey what is this small pink
mistake of nature scores the hottest
piece of ass around brother are you a
glutton for punishment now if you would
had a chat with Uncle
but the lovers escape route is not just
a cave it is the studio of prehistoric
master artist el gorilla
you
I knew it that Dame spells trouble well
this is it for the first time ever let
it be said they shall not pass
hey hey do you mind
Oh
hey no man no man
there's good days and bad days
Oh y-yeah I did Oh at taking the Sun Oh
what drink yeah g1 coincidence I just
happen to be indulging in one of my
favorite hobbies dowsing for water
another race team I just do it for
relaxation what you know it's amazing
this said pivot of a nation only one
person in a million actually has the
power there it goes again this way to a
long pool spa delicious dream and what
did I tell you a menacing it sure helps
to make a person true hey you what are
you doing me want water that's not water
asshole that's dragon food and just for
looking at it I'm gonna crisp you
what is what is its fire asshole how you
make fire how you make fire listen
stupid if I knew you would be crisp
right now fire from whole not good no
it's supposed to come from this hole Oh
help sure a wise guy what you gonna do
is take a cock up my ass oh he's stopped
a cork up my ass he's took a cork up my
ass oh hell no no asshole hey not
fucking their fucking bad at all hey
listen pal I owe you one they call you
one
no need to waste it fellow there's a
shortage of this stuff Oh want water
water Oh waters murder on the stomach
you want water water cool you down like
a bastard but you want water you got one
water water everywhere go nuts there's
your water oh oh here is a big
oh my starman if I ever get my hands on
that little bastard water oh please no
ho hey listen could you could you do me
a favor a big favor is he I have this
core
Adam you didn't you bug out
you too
Coronation alerted you you're never to
hurt anyone in any money oh you man did
you fire your decision or stick Doody by
you earlier players for diversity bird
scared of unknown the scene don't desire
your lawyer
hey you with the overbite I put years of
work into that kid cough up
igri look man good our hero starts the
last and shortest stage his long quest
for man down this gloomy path lies ohs
place in history
man man me Oh want men Oh find men Oh
teach men walk talk make kale make whole
that runs make fire men come old
well we made it croak Oh fine men men
come o.o teach man oh right kid right
but then just remember this it's lonely
at the top Oh believe me I know arm leg
hole Oh make fire man make fire Oh me
want no man me like no man me take tail
hmm hi lizard lizard allow me to
introduce the new chief of all men allow
me also to introduce the special
assistant to the chief of all men myself
chrome at your service mon wed fri
normal working hours by appointment only
hmm did you have an appointment no fire
good good
eat wat good lizard man you met me oh I
like man i no white no home no I'm not
man no long no long no long like oh no
like man no long nitin no no I like men
ah no no no long men or even the engine
I told you so I told you so
no no no it's good man good no go get em
all
let's face it war is hell
c equals MC squared no m squared equals
easy no how about e equal 0
no man no man no man oh
and so humanity achieves its destiny
humanity the noble the savage flawed
perhaps but in the end triumph and far
away on a distant I an old man Ponder's
his life an old man whose deeds will
never be signed and yet who ultimately
bears responsibility for the whole
ghastly mess oh the missing link
you can't make an omelet without it you
can't won't matter pair legs like a thin
is useless without ropes and fish you
can't make an omelet without eggs you
can't fly without a pair of wings we
can't swim without a handle bend to
breathe the lead given half the chance
not prove to you something he just and I
do you can't make an omelet without
breaking it from the time the universe
the game almost from the very first
baseman and the word according to the
books I've read you can't make an omelet
without a living d by breathing instance
all the necessary an event fall without
everything so it's not the first time
for panic craig swapp the first name
ever fan you can't make an omelet
yes lots emerged from the bus tomorrow
earth wisdom words by you can't make an
omelet without a you can't make an
omelet without it you can't walk without
a purely like a chance it's useless
tonight Oh Santa can't make an omelet
without a