101 Bravo liebe coming over 101 probably
my can sit in the middle by runaway
horse respond over this but Kendall
trying again 101
Bravo leaving you gotta move it not me
now not later
why do all the weirdness have to fly at
night
ok want to move move you myself
yeah
ok hot rolled up on the grass
curtains
hey everybody
you indifferent
yeah
what happened here
ok
we have removed the aliens were claiming
any penetration hope the building is
going to be showing up on their way back
to be back side of the double whatever
yeah
me see it hey give that back
I picture my god get baby a little too
much stuff and I told you before you
don't fuck with me more about your
goddamn dead baby you got a problem with
that hotshot taken up
let me tell you what inside your waist
is a microscope a cultural microscope
focusing in on me collective unconscious
of the American populace and what we do
here inside you Cameron's identify and
define the cultural shock type of the
American mind read that list back me
stories i want to look at alien
abductions i'm using animal stories
attacks on the handicapped believe it
has a twist some kind of kinky sex in
there something battered wives is our
body functions breast surgery horror
story that's always good
see celebrities addicted perverted dying
dead and of course back and demonic
possession Merton just because you don't
have any balls that we can cut mine off
morning Richard you wanted to do with
Morgan to get that picture you have any
idea how cold those labs are cancer this
emotionally unstable individuals for two
days are senior reporter can blame he's
found out about all the collective
unconsciousness cracked yet captain
we'll finish this later
sure no problem thank you Miss Morrison
gravity well laid-out welcome to inside
people
what about my picture these we all love
your pictures but in the future just as
a rough timeline
let's keep the victims over two years
old okay let's sit please
sorry my son i forgot my purse
thank you
so anything can happen no Jimmy Olsen
not much experience but sharp good
instincts great ass
did you happen to miss forward position
open to him cause I didn't want to hire
not scare away there's no reason she's
know anything about daddy
anyway your next assignment talk about
those need a break
she's got a 75 times will be allowed to
own you can stare double cares country
star with AIDS that's one way to solve
the story for you
besides this is much more up your alley
this is gonna be a big one Richard
really big well lot of people get
worried about this guy
there's nothing here a man know a man
thinks he's more than fine to the
desolate airports in the middle of the
night kills whatever course my campus
will be around trees the body of the
blood he flies when i get a search of
his next unsuspecting he calls himself
Winfield . just happens to be the first
name of an actor named Dwight Frye who
played the role of rent you the bunny
loaded taking the 1931 version dragon
come on Richard that's not a story
the guy's a movie fans so what vampires
are a dime a dozen attached you know
that besides they for the cycle goes
after naylor yeah why is that you've got
the makeup is playing the tail number
two if you want to rob banks
he doing the same car with same license
plate every single time no it's called
ya know
that pilot license plate here to some
use besides you're good with the hicks
the best thank you
you need this one Richard take we're not
your work has been lacking library card
you have to get the front pages in
months and this this is fun . material
this is a waste of space is what it is
wasting time talking about you know
without you and it's going to be a
spring turkey
what you give the Jimmy
the messages even secretly the to break
yeah
like
alright I'm has been clear about this
morning mr. Morrison's office you
remember me remember Jenny Olsen
reminding you have a choice
no we designed for state has turned out
to be already got my practice assignment
about a psycho pilot thinks is a vampire
yeah i know i really missed me i passed
on why you here Jimmy idea that you
called me all this way just to shoot the
shit find follow you guys just doesn't
matter
you're here now what you want okay
I guess I was hoping that you could give
me the inside of you inside of you gonna
learn from the paper Star reporter maybe
you can share your philosophy with me
awesome we're staying on top of so long
I'd love to hear it
that is if you have one ok here it is
you better take notes never believe
which public never publish what you
believe this matter I talk too fast I
guess I was just expecting something
more from someone who thinks of himself
as to what
well a real reporter asked you question
the fuck you think you know about being
a real reporter huh
god dammit I'm sorry I didn't mean to
offend why don't we start over why I
don't know your story on ER a million
times come from lockport of rockport
bridgeport Eugene Oregon person . can
place it's not get into Columbia Yale
and Illinois State
you could turn for Examiner the the
patriot but I help me please
exactly trying to cover everything cake
sales at dog shows the class reunions
but the couple months think we did it
she gave us her just spice course the
money just lying here
what are you getting at with booze
you've been here before Jimmy you'll be
here again see the faces change but the
end is always saying you won't last
maybe I'll surprise you maybe we will
maybe I'll stick around for a while and
just like dying when you talk about you
want my inside view of inside view all
right i'll give it to you get about
fucking philosophy on believing inside
view is an illustration of the insane
the diary of the deranged and
dangerously sick of talking about
kindergarten teachers setting fire to
the series because they think he's five
years older plotting their executions it
satanic biker called slaughtering each
section just for the hell of it after
talking these crazy people all day every
single day stores and get to you keep in
mind i'm gonna fuckin cancer pretty soon
as she starts making sentences
everybody wash will go get her just like
you start to believe in the unbelievable
not more than a year after . he was
hired at night took a bath of the
dry-cleaning bag restaurant
bye-bye daddy
in particular
I'm sorry about it you that's ok i
thought maybe we could be friends but
yeah well i guess i was wrong
listen I don't have friends and got my
camera my plane my stories that's all I
want it so i need to be one friend my
dog
yeah
alright morsel so goddamn important our
daddy friend has struck again
so last night double Maryland little
pissant down 60 miles outside of
Washington got clean away to you
shouldn't let it bother you Richard
after all this is a young man's business
or young woman's he that's right
Catherine found it so she tapped into a
network of local law enforcement
agencies with the computers search
through a hundred million where women
are bad boys off at the information
waiting for me on my desk as soon as I
walk in the middle
now that is mp3 file
what do you want me to say that was
wrong just that you might be room i'm
happy to I guess you know what a pussy
cat
ok i might be wrong helping out how very
large hard to admit it
ok
first this guy can't believe me then but
Kendall New York and now Ray Allen
starch in Maryland there's definitely a
story that needs to be told and i think
i heard white calling your name Richard
anybody from the street press pick up on
this yet here's even suggesting that
there's a serial killer flying around
the answer's no but they encounter to
keep this thing I should come on it's
more than you know which ones aren't we
got present minutes that tomorrow's
edition if you want that so what's it
gonna be a bitch then yet right
what's that plan b's and Blair that
important know when this guy's back
trail starting with the first murder we
know about all we have been made right
well what about you need a break Stewart
fucking break not me
there is one small problem
Catherine I'll France bad news is mine
mr. Morrison came to well looks like
he's taking it back
can I apologize about this but he's back
on the story not giving your files if
you want mr. Watterson please make my
decision just do it
yeah I suppose you understand my own
plane
yeah
I don't bread
don't believe I know you mr. Richard
these reporters on touching for me
everything yeah next thing you know what
the plane but think that you sell your
home inside you know
yeah my wife my baby needs help me find
no reason other than I use it online our
kid is talking about song stuff that cat
is real good then you won't mind
answering a few questions you want to
talk to me about that killing my friend
club I don't know how did you know back
then other reason
city folks visit these bad except
something bad happens and this was real
bad but I didn't you already told
everything I know to the family's
everything I let the police it slow take
a few minutes so don't mind
nice ball isn't bri just be loud and
clearly and you tell me what happened
about the clear body was murdered
it all began tonight partly I was
murdered like that bastard Flynn here
and that plane was a black Cessna
skymaster right 337 red piping tail
number 101 Bravo lima it was one of them
Sky masters alright he's not thinking
and saying is i remember the tail number
because i don't think the damnedest
thing done yeah they're just go ahead
now
well night shift along the player quiet
most time but lot that night
no sir not that night
I should jump low
that's when he came down
let me tell you mr. right from the
get-go that felt had been seen problem
just sorta off
why was that she was wearing a big cloak
as a fire engine inside
Black is woodchucks asshole outside
wouldn't spread out behind every look
like a bank path leading to come work at
7am next morning headed to chat with
Claire before I went home I always did
one here
yeah
I gotta tell you classing little bit
haha that day not quite himself
yeah
this some sort of new service plan
Claire just doing my part song so I had
my client last night
this him
yeah
light rain here in from dairy
another
different
said he was leaving tonight
said he'd step back to say goodbye
looked like he came back all right and
imagine being anyone else
ok Mac and rip my friends throat clean
off his neck
have them
ugly way to die so the plane was there
the whole day
yeah did claire happen to mention
calling a cab for the pilot to take the
motel it doesn't seem to be anything
within easy walking distance help
I don't remember class an area where
about calling fellow a cab in a limo
anything about no limbo neither he would
have mentioned that checks amazing
services seen one more for you too
I not mean nothing that can again it
might stop me pure so give seeing
something strange under that plane and
had
big pile of dirt and under the luggage
baby
nasty stuff
my class something had died
you're going after him and you can't be
careful Haas his final killed plan ain't
no man thanks for input
yeah
that's scary and clear
well you do with delicious share body
you do this clear
no I didn't think the guy would just
write that way i don't know who you are
what you want
we respect the dead around here mr. not
suggest you do the same rejoin auclair
scene and you think really good thanks
Levi steiger real credit humanity you
get yours yourself a bitch
yeah
I really getting somewhere
the cemetery boozed-up body is
exercising their First Amendment rights
in the motel room window fucking Hicks
take a level never scared anyway I
checked out every hand story with the
police and basically back to the VA
virginia had a city called the barrier
part is not our supposed to go out and
never heard about Dwight Renfield or
blacks as the sky master that tail
number already already come from and
what Khloe question is missing flight
plan
these little care fields are always look
by drug runners the train with your shit
that the FAA found out that clear boy
let mr. Renfield is always that show
male fashion music funk County Maine is
clearly not to worry about that now
order to New York is next where Mr Kydd
Crusader got himself into
you may not know it like you're gonna be
my ticket back to frontpage
yeah
you're a very good was madness it is
only 1i have to be what about my team
and got here don't come on the ground
behind only way i can trigger what he
said well my Christmas right around 220
an easy may have uncle paul got there
regularly but it did get around to make
you sorry you got the right time just
about some damn neck little although
they don't have endured awake
would you want to know
ok
yeah
kept on watching that point yet so you
had a bank where I last saw you had a
knife liar liar
yeah
stranger
yeah stays where I older to New York got
my picture the nightflyer second victim
up close personal dead
the reason they checked his ID for
calling the nightfly now
not bad well I haven't revealed on your
whole town was that there were two big
loads and but candles and I'm not talk a
little Bela Lugosi bite marks i'm
talking about massive holes because you
got teeth the size of bigfooters well
railroad spikes in the next
this is great shit i mean the face and
supermarket lines are gonna love this
guy
god I hope he kills more people back to
your copy send pictures i can go ahead
and keeping your password is not ready
it's gonna get bigger you're weird
feeling
I'll certainly tell you that for
christmas which we want to tease on this
you know that god damned is not gonna be
ready for next week you got that you'll
get your story when i get the fuck out
of my face but it definitely more . they
have something later
we're like he's trying to get that dead
loss lucky dog stars pieces really tough
we're calling him the nightflyer now by
the way sorry mr. Martin I just gonna
let it go
I'm not asking you to and I'll tell you
something you're not gonna find all the
interest is electronic box of yours
they're out there you want this story
back and you know i do then take the
ticket years back together these does
not run this paper i do for me that I
find my charms don't tell you something
you want to be bees can play the game
like these
yeah
that's not Stang
ok
blown off
we got no problems here said move along
but a couple press start getting away
Campbell was a one-night stand for you
you flew in shortly after twelve o'clock
in the 23rd spiked all but dead and took
off again and friendly skies at the door
he wasn't mounted
like to linger
why most times you wait around until
you're really hungry but which is the
big night stick
get under my skin hello
doesn't look like the stories about to
let me love that's ok someone going
funny when you give blood
most unexpected couple issues
when you take blood your headlines
sick fucker
yeah
hi test if you please
wasn't looking for the debris airport
you tell me how to get there I'm gonna
do you no good place is closed done and
I tried to land this morning at the man
in Washington National instead must know
about the sources is one here trying to
find out more about what happened you
copy something something like that to
the charges
oh yeah no actually sorriness walk today
they were murdered and stopping here in
a way home that afternoon I could tell
right away there's something wrong with
them swimming we look all tired and pay
like he was sick or something and she's
almost didn't recognize ur
let's go
he's reading
sleep then I'll end up real good
who select the camera works over in town
the beauty bar that's something you
should be talking to pass on tonight
strange stories he has did you notice
anything out of the ordinary just the
fact that Ellen's visit we usually as
regulars problem mr. she came in at
least two exam now that might not mean
anything to you but for Ellen such to
break the routine she'd been following
the last 20 years it was done right on
LCD tree me somehow like a schoolgirl
with a crush 62 years old or not color
was so high
will it be the usual l something
different this time and maybe and as I
working and talking about that pilot to
crew the night before i do they
definitely
by the way she was talking that was like
it's a long-lost wind rain Ellen welcome
him with open arms into their home even
had dinner actually watched a little
television next morning Ellen came to
see me
he wanted to look gorgeous
she wanted to she wanted to the old soul
eater communities with exam when you
have the boys find some JD swift kick in
the teeth me right now
good people tell me about the murders
tell me about what you found the trailer
not look at ordinary first stepped
inside
yeah
right away when you something wrong
it was a smell
yeah
we found a first sprawled out on her
feet
hardly any blood on that all something
else wishing to what's that
ok
was sitting over the far corner turned
toward the open doorway as if we were
actually something there see
she's not like that in my life and if a
warning for this guy was posted there on
the wall and he was there all night and
all the next day it's still a blow the
whistle on just make no sense
really i can still share now
she was lying there hail snow every drop
of her blood gone to god damned if you
didn't look at peace almost having like
it was what you wanted any strength
puncture marks on the bodies the holes
on Overholt alright holes big enough you
could sign from above and how he did a
splash blood all over the room is
anybody's guess what kind of fucking
games as a plan or somebody tell me that
yeah
nice puppy
good boy
ok
yeah
what stopped him working look like
spikes again the trails cold
that's more the same place something
though there's many activities and
influence over these people i'm a lot of
serial killers charming victims but this
guy's got the Straits garlic
yeah right next to my crucifix it's time
to hit the phones independent goddamn
plane comes over the wires give me a
call from the falling star hotel
you got it from hell freezes over
so you hold will be saying don't feel
comfortable by police officers it just
takes a little practice you haven t
listen where you staying in case you get
old you before yeah I hear the community
. good luck captain
god I love this job
ok
our life
yeah
the next one
position right hand of power . that's
funny
just a second ago
look like could tell by the following
something please bring the drink at all
where you go
yeah
like
fuck you
ok
what the fuck are you doing here take my
story for some lunch after this I don't
see what that has to do with anybody
since you don't piss me off you just
fucking with you don't give a fuck what
you believe what's going home for you
really make me mad on some bitch cover
for school my leaves
I don't you ladies I have my own right
hmm i have a complete set of police
reports from Cumberland County Sheriff's
Department i tracked down a very
cooperative clerk to get the offices in
Washington and I had all three sets of
all types of photos like i said i'm
taking the story home
no you're putting kitchen we can do next
just talking
Jimmy when we cut this competition
bullshit long time to dry so you write
phase of the flight was here he just
left
he's flying like this need to have to
come down slowly he's been very lucky
three times already how many more times
you think that's gonna happen
what is really breaks wide open losing
for good
yeah . . is this got a lead on this guy
and we can get one soon I was fucked
that two people can do that kind of
drama club faster one
don't do it
is investigating that all day if you
work with me on this trip on how their
campus yet against baby because the
truth is if it comes down to just me or
just you
yeah
so anything
it is 101 probably okay things
you see people yes your fucking posted
in every fucking Airport between here
and connect see what has to win this
fucking thing know-it-all
yeah
his name is Dwight Yankee Doodle cash
Renfield white Renfield white Renfield
again
yeah don't know
they're not gonna have woman to his way
to
women control
I building Somerton more than the FAA's
what if you could help me out somewhere
absolutely mr. Parsons always interested
in the FAA and anyway possible before
you working on the coastal air feels
looking for an aircraft we believe is
involved in some illegal activity now
this particular plans accession
skymaster 337 watch reliable but since
the black skymaster 337 is when typing
tail number 101 Bravo name is compliant
certain scenes play sir
he was like you know what
now we get our asses to wilmington
stumble backwards pickup happen
yeah
right thanks for your help Jimmy will
share my byline I'm not sure that's for
either so what did you tell these
stories can get to you can creep inside
like some kind of panzer if not what you
want me about what happened
sorry you lose
information
yeah
you got ladies and sensation seekers
breath bad man is coming your way
he's reliving forget it but that's okay
because what she remembers my name form
is gonna put it right up there with Jack
the Ripper and the Cleveland torso
murderer the black dollar
number
coming soon to check out can be
effective with 34 by adding 10 to make
about 200 fly heading 160 leaving 64
3700 elderly woman mrs. 73 built in
romeo you've gotta skymaster 337 down
there on the ramp tail number 101
problem in Genesis 70 Delta Romeo did
you get my letter admission
goddammit willing to talk to me what's
going on down there
turn around while you still can Richard
I don't want you here
fuck you asshole remember you go
yeah
ok
thank you everybody
yeah
ok
I
yeah
ok
what
yeah
ok
you
yeah
I've been watching you DS have been
watching it very closely
yeah I know you see I know
hello about your address you now
understand that you can have a right to
what you know to never reveal which
we've seen the camera
30 so for now based this is your last
chance my would be going to burn open
your camera or our to it
yeah
you're a bloody street name
we have a lot in common you and me
perhaps you need
materials who need me as well don't
believe you nineties have no intention
to after all we are brothers you we not
the center would be a much sadder case
whether likes of you
besides the world to make very well but
it's including my inquisitive grunt
because they see it only once you do not
finally anymore but I'm sweating that
much promise
yeah
why
your face showing me like
shortly
I supposed to listen
your life
mugs in the graveyards in the faces of
the devil
your whole existence of the search for
me
well here I am my friend might not all
that you can fall
am I not all
yeah
we'll be right and always wanted to know
what it was like that you don't know
yeah
what I have to do it in this region
pull it out of me
so cool
because this one
travel
thank you
I don't think that
yeah
and
ok
do
for you get somewhere
that you just keep your distance
yeah
probably we publish never happened
just fuck is this guy
yeah
Richard keys
call the nightflyer
sarees