good night thank you for being so quiet
good night you really wild mr. Gretzky
music gets heavier and heavier every
year none of us are getting any younger
duty except me of course hey Denise I
really should go to me a favor huh pick
up the violin section for me will you
I'll pay back next week okay I'll finish
up oh thanks baby be ready so on Randy
Randy
Denise what are you doing
I
television last night landlady said the
girl was nice quiet
I know
yeah I guarantee you years ago girls
didn't get murdered like they do today
what he's doing
isn't this your stuff but do I call a
policeman
oh man what do you want me get over to
the car we want to have a talk
you go into the University on a gorgeous
day like this what you have in mind how
about a picnic for to your place to mine
I'll tell you what if what you just
stashed in your pocket is your lunch
your place if not mine which is police
headquarters I'm a detective
come on there's a green car following
right behind this bus with two more
detectives in it so you made your
connection come on the carstache did
this one made the pickup isn't his
inside jacket pocket I never saw that
she planted it
when we get downtown we'll see if my
prints are on it adjust yours yes you're
not required to answer any questions
without consulting a lawyer if you can't
afford a lawyer one will be provided if
you do make a statement it will believe
me be taken down and used against you
hugs it on Tracy Mirax dying to see you
it's about to report princess a widely
read report deputy chief called fatehpur
you kidding no he's on the phone with
him now for the second time hey who's
that lady over there the landlady of
last night's murder victim you're all
come in Fleming case you're wondering
how I knew it was you you're the only
one that raps on my door everybody else
hits it like they're trying to break it
down or they tap on it like they don't
want me to hear which they don't sit
down for me callaway just called me
about this your report good report
neatly typed now your assignment was one
to maintain surveillance on an
interstate transmittal of heroin
callaway said you didn't do it sir you
report removing a suspected sex offender
from the bus yes sir two young girls
would have been involved would have been
you mean nothing actually happened no I
got him off the bus before before
anything happened do you know how lucky
you were suppose your pick up man made
his connection while you were preventing
this this hypothetical nastiness he
didn't have time he didn't have time
suppose the man the raincoat pulled you
off the bus and you blew your cover I
was lucky right you we're lucky okay I
want you to go out and type up a
description the man the raincoat copy to
me copy to callaway copy to records copy
the files with for young ladies raped
and murdered we happen to be particular
interested in sexual deviance right now
we've rounded up every known sex
offender in the county maybe your man
the raincoats the one we missed he's not
the guy what the man of the raincoat
isn't the killer he's an exhibitionist
and what is the killer the opposite
puritanical repressed uptight and now
you're gonna tell me how you reach this
conclusion yes you are come with me
newgen Ruggeri follow me town detective
20 has something to share with us you
know gentlemen our most pressing concern
at the moment is with for young ladies
all of them raped and murdered all of
them living alone none within 10 blocks
of each other no Missouri now we're
certain that it's the work of one man
because he cuts a lock of hair from each
of his victims but up until now we've
learned nothing specific about the
killer himself right right wrong
detective Fleming has determined that
the killer is uh how do you put that
Fleming puritanical and repressed what I
used to call approve Missouri will you
get rid of the pizza now either before
or after he killed them he must have
wiped the lipstick off your mouth you
been wearing some women don't wear
lipstick but not these not with bright
red nail polish like that or a miniskirt
and hoop earrings or like that one with
a low neckline I'm guessing when I say
the killer wiped off their lipstick but
they were at captain Merrick I'm sure ok
Fleming if you'll type up the
description I had your porno thank you
very much gentlemen you remain Johnny I
want you to check the property sheets
still figuring something Fleming
no that's like Velma for us I didn't
hear her liver
what time is it so many plated in the
last five us and now your mother will be
home in a few minutes how about you dad
can I get you anything no thanks don't
want to spoil the appetite oh don't
worry go out with my daughter-in-law you
don't have an appetite for the time you
read let's NAB mega play hard oh nice
catch Tracy ok see if you can get this
one Nick I Nora I and I'm sorry I'm late
it's ok hello how are you it's good to
see ya darling you know we thought you'd
never get here oh I'm not sorry Marik
again you know oh come on mom we got
batting practice oh honey listen Nicki
will you give me a rain check on that
come late and dance here now here's the
best picture in the neighborhood I told
everybody mom you promised I'm fine
okay you just let me get my jeans on I
won't be long well maybe we can catch a
late movie i'll check the paper Thanks I
can't help it if I got the only slow
breaking curve on the blog come on I'll
keep you warmed up
55 girls kill their homes three beads on
a strand and the rest scattered no real
pattern there but in checking out the
last victim Eddie found out that she
worked at 555 West Flower Street Eddie
so that rang a bell I checked back and i
found that claire wellman the first
murder victim had been having her teeth
capped at 555 West flower so I checked
all your reports again it turned out
that each victim for some reason in the
last week's of her life passed through
this area flower Elm 67 one of them
visited her shrink another one was
delivering blueprints for a boss a
target area a link between the girls all
right and thanks to you Fleming we have
a second link that lipstick thing you
were right about then according to
friends and relatives the girls did wear
lipstick so the killer must have wiped
it off wasn't much you're right it
wasn't but it led to something that was
in checking the property sheets for
lipstick we found something else yeah
they all owned a small bottle of perfume
called misty night the bottles had been
open but they were all nearly full
suggesting suggesting they didn't like
it they didn't like it why they buy it
who says they bought it maybe they were
gifts maybe was a gift from the killer a
puritanical man who works or hangs out
in the target area sees the girls it
builds up some kind of make believe love
relationship with them in his own mind
that's possible isn't it it's possible
and we'll know if it's true when we
catch them which we won't do sitting
around here you guys have your
assignment captain can I speak to you
privately please okay phlegm in come on
I request a change of assignment to the
target area you have your assignment
captain I was right about the lipstick
thing if I've got this killer figured
why not let me do the job bait bait yes
working in the target area dress the way
the killer likes them wearing that
perfume misty night his perfume it's
perfect I think I has raped and killed
five women and what are you going to do
sit around and wait for number six to
happen I know I'm new on this squad but
I am a policewoman trained to do this
job no no no you don't go down there
alone well that meant covering you night
and day they'll rotate we'll set you up
as a civilian unarmed if there is any
need for action I know I call a cop
right captain right hi Tracy hi Eddie
hey John noodleman all right good
morning Fleming morning captain Merrick
coffee no not right now thank you ok now
we picked this place because of its
availability for surveillance the whole
place is bugged he comes through the
front door will know about it you come
through that door he's right in your lap
the back door can be checked from the
street I've come with me some coffee ya
got any doughnuts I'm stopped
all right now the apartment building is
on a dead-end street we can park a car
right over there that can cover the
building and the entrance we can put a
man in the used car lot that has a full
view of the whole building alright I'm
back inside now when the killer does get
in we'll have a man in this closet oh
thank you captain that's very reassuring
Clemmy yes sir you don't want the
assignment we haven't signed the lease
yet I'll take it Fleming let me ask you
something what's a nice girl like you
doing in a crummy job like this my
husband was a cop he was killed in the
line of duty now I have a son I want to
make things a little better and safer
for him sorry it's little corny isn't it
no it's what I used to tell my ex-wives
when I asked me why I was a calm Jenna
Oh got you a job right in the heart of
the target area 5 55 south flower and
late for work
what do you say miss honor oh sorry this
is a new route for me for me to regular
drivers on vacation and i gotta finish
it
these are several research reports
interview subjects are correlated by sex
age marital status and so on we have to
type them up in trip with it my last job
was Rodrick with it it does get more
interesting when you're out in the
street doing survey interviews don't
worry I didn't come here for excitement
can I walk me up no fine thank you
anything else you arrest my brother
Karthik Donald power I was in court oh
yes let's see he got a suspended
sentence between you and me they should
have thrown the key away you here on a
key no no I I'm not with the police
force anymore can't no I can them I'm
working right down the street it
selectively opinion research oh how be
glad to have you around even the next
cop will do you have any reason to be
afraid oh no not personally I mean I
love to get dig it when if it's not the
phone calls but where you get the
smellin men yeah I guess it happens to
all of us till it doesn't make for a lot
of laughs huh hey come on over here
Vidya change
hey did you hear me the orders are back
here fuck I don't pay your standard I'll
get that they're jacking yes mr. Olson I
got a boss just like him hey make me to
you nice to meet you
hello there's no hell in here Helen
stands me I'm sorry have the wrong
number Tracy you all right yeah i think
the taxpayers are wasting their money on
you out they're ready you aim loot guess
I'm not as irresistible as I thought
oh yeah thank you you're getting to be a
regular only I was starting to worry
you're a little late this morning well
it's nice to be too worried could I ask
you something true how'd you know my
name oh I ask Big Mike you know the
water garden your building you're a nice
pretty girl I like somebody I want to
know their name now good day Tracy thank
you
sir Sir excuse me I'd like to ask you a
few questions you don't mind do you
usually eat breakfast in the morning if
I do eat breakfast it's only in the
morning what sir I'd like to ask you a
few more questions you could outline Wow
yeah no no I mean I'm in her excuse
could I ask you a few questions how do
me sir could I ask you a few questions
would you mind doing a survey an opinion
research survey I thought maybe you
could tell us a few things well pardon
me sir can I ask you a few questions
hey first matter with you catch add it
cost me nearly up a buck on this check
yeah yeah show you side but I didn't get
me to buck back I don't blame him I
haven't been missing lately what's the
matter Liz more phone calls and well a
couple thank you and the feeling of
being watched food you haven't gotten
any gifts lately have you like a little
bottle of perfume from an unknown
admirer unsigned nobody gives me gifts
unsigned all my life and gave me an
electric toothbrush sighs kisses but
since then nothing but promises uh I
think you're being watched right now
what ya paws oh you met you want some
more coffee no no thanks you know your
mother-in-law's coffees a lot better
than this thanks a lot come on Tracy
join the party I'm just jumpy well
you're entitled to be a little jumpy
maybe Tracy's heard about the particular
problem we have in the squad no problem
no Eddie it's not the time of the place
to tell her I think she's got a right to
know if you guys have a problem you can
talk to me about it well we don't
usually discuss it but the guys in the
squad
they're all bad marksmen in fact the
truth is tracy i have a problem of
lining up these two funny little ridges
here and the last time we had gun
practice i hear that he's target and I
was 50 yards to the right my hand has a
habit of shaking just little and not
much but just enough to throw me off
just a little well thank you for sharing
your little secret with me I don't think
you guys gonna get to use your gun so I
star tonight princess you're gonna stop
worrying and sit down I can't stop
worrying some girl somewhere I mean that
killer has never waited this long
you keep track
we
you
fair please miss
this fair please some world huh I'd seen
it all on this job scum degenerates
mashers tramps nothing bothers me
anymore friend of yours she worked in me
now that's all right this this one's on
me
morning claw me so he got number six
I've been expecting you for an hour he's
is this mrs. followers she did get the
perfume well not exactly he kill her
mail it to her at the restaurant all
right but her boss a guy named Wilson
yeah she couldn't stand him well
evidently he liked her enough to be
jealous he figured some boyfriends in a
torso did what came naturally he dropped
it behind the garbage cans five days ago
I didn't I see it the target area just
the killer's type and a phone call she
kept getting look every grunt / 12 gets
those phone calls nowadays breathers
four letter words hangups I could have
saved that girl you did everything that
anyone could captain if I'm gonna be the
bait you've got to let me do it right
you've got to move the men out of the
apartment moving back gives the killer a
chance to breathe a chance to get to I
don't want any wild stunts do you
understand more flamboyant I've got to
make him notice me I've got a really
turned off for him I'll ground myself
and miss teen height / few if I have to
but I've got to stop him I think this
thing's getting too personal with you
the bait is my assignment it's the one
job you can't assign to a man oh I had
considered it phlegm England nobody's
got your legs
hello voices hello
I like your perfume Tracy thank you
thank you very much who is this never
mind you're a good girl Tracy Fleming
and like you very much
yes sir I'll keep drunk to tell so I
know the survey is useless to you
without the breakdown but I give you my
word we sent that breakdown day before
yesterday all right all right you do
that and we'll check again over here yes
what is it it's me Tracy hi you didn't
call today you're a good girl Tracy
Fleming I love you Tracy I want to meet
you be with you yes when so Tracy
tonight tonight
my address I know where you live tonight
then I'll be seeing you Tracy Marik
please
Johnny hey you are right and they don't
fall asleep on me no chance that's a
funny thing here i am hiding in the
closet in your apartment and I got a
great chick waiting for me in mind well
listen I'm I'm really sorry about that i
had any other place to go to hello hi
mom it's me Mickey hi listen honey I
can't talk you know the code for a drunk
driver if I want you honey I've gotta
run are you coming to the movies with us
friday night we'll see i'll talk to you
about it later now don't you stay up all
night listening to police calls all
right hey I love you Mick I love you too
there's a guy on the outside stairs
could be just under Tracey's window okay
good now look be careful remember we
gotta catch him entering in the act of
committing a misdemeanor we won't make
it stick you understand careful right
you
I think I lost him captain sorry hi down
no problem how'd you gonna do something
about it like we have to go fishing
again
you look like you've lost a friend I
think maybe I gained 1 i'll find the way
mr. Kelso called three more times today
this current report should have gone off
this morning I know they're on their way
in a cab I should have told you why what
happened the messenger service followed
up the team's the regular driver went on
vacation and the land is covered for
improved and sent it to Allied merchants
instead of merchandising we just forgot
that everything changes when a key man
goes on vacation we sure did is there
anything else no thank you Nancy good
night good night yes I Drive a personnel
please yeah I know they'll be closing
please hurry yes this is detective
Fleming Special Investigations I would
like to check the names and roots of bus
drivers who well how am I going to do
that show you my bed over the phone ok
uh uh listen I'm not very far from you i
could get over there in just a few
minutes so please don't go home where
you stayed in just a few more minutes ok
fine thank you very much
ready to fire would you do me a big
favor I'm gonna go out the back way I've
got two minutes to get to the bus
station please listen the demand parked
outside the tan car now his name is
Johnny ruggiero would you tell him that
I'm gonna be at the bus station thanks
Mike
oh please
this is for Giri I need assistance in an
ambulance at sixth in central you're all
right Tracy yeah I'm fine how did you
ever find me I was so going to what's
time we employ turn around the guy from
the hair and would drop on the bus sure
he's out on bail probably had a drop in
the area saw you in the neighborhood put
to rest Jonny I've got a hair and it
won't wait not without me you've got a
book this guy i'm just going to the
terminal right around the corner I gotta
check out a hunch whatever you do don't
go near that apartments that clear okay
uh I'll go home and see Mickey I'll call
you when I'm ready to leave all right be
careful princess
and I'm gonna load it up with Kool & P
and K I want you to take the whole thing
speedily office
you're gonna come in the movies with us
I can't but I came home to see my
favorite son no and mother-in-law mom
you know the pool for a prowler yeah 647
g Oh Mickey that's good I'm gonna go to
the movies with us now from here just
told you I can't uh Mickey if you want
to make the movie I think you better go
wash your face and hands and put on your
red jacket okay hey grandma have you got
time for some lasagna and a little salad
before we have to leave yeah
you really are admit I know foreign
think I'm onto something I think you
figured it out I think so it's a theory
but come on let me know what you think
you know you remember where the victims
lived right here over here and over here
I went downtown by boss but I didn't go
over the same route no three of them on
this route and one over here and one
over here I don't see the pattern
neither did I until this afternoon when
the messenger service at our office goof
because the driver was on vacation
people take vacations other people take
their jobs temporarily my first day at
the office the driver said to me he was
new to the route suppose this was his
regular route the first three murders
beads on a string and the rest when he
was filling in for other drivers on
vacation and it's a possibility and bus
drivers are close enough to their fares
to check them out even their perfume and
if he works the morning rush she's got
the rest of the day to figure out who
lives where who works where well the bus
company would have the drivers worth we
went there they were closed well I think
you've got a very good theory and call
America
hello Tracy one word one sound and
you're dead of understand I thought you
weren't good I thought you liked me I do
you tried to betray me going to the bus
company trying to find out about me I
just wanted to fight that your name I
thought I recognized your voice can I
want to meet you last night the girl
waits to be asked your role is saying
I'm different I really like you do you
let me prove it to you
and then within the hairs I'm gonna get
rid of them going to movies now you'll
give me away today I'll be just in the
next room you can hear every word I say
one move one wrong word and they're all
dead the kid goes first there we I know
oh did you get married no not yet i have
to keep trying you two better hurry
you're gonna be late look we'll have
some dinner when you look so pale I will
enjoy the movie and drive carefully fat
chance we got about 15 minutes to get
from here all the way over to Madison
Boulevard come on love wait a minute you
don't have to go that far the Comstock's
got the same show the Comstock I don't
know that theater 1099 South Comstock it
won't take you five minutes heard in one
time to get ground wasn't back there
wait you didn't kiss me honey up honey
I'm sorry go on now BYE MOM take care
don't worry about the dishes
all night Tracy I kind of date LuAnn
good cook LuAnn my girl back east I
thought she was good too I never touched
her none of me I bought her lots of nice
things present I could afford it then
had a couple of trucks my own isn't the
way new girl a mo I found him together i
just bought her a present some perfume
that found them a lipstick was all over
his face and his knees
it's all right I'll clean your dad
I'm sorry I need to do that
I'm sorry would you like to hear some
music no no music it bothers me hi oh
just sit and talk what would you like to
talk about do you like music yes I do
okay this as long as it's soft music and
like trumpets and things that are loud
yeah like something nice all right
then maybe we could dance yes happy nice
should be it look was all this exterior
in this neighborhood 1091 1097 well
there is no 1099 didn't she say 1099
well she left them at North Comstock
people don't dance so nice anymore I
like shaking and everything here Duke
Ellington nice and easy how's that we'll
see I like to watch people waltz I think
the losses are pretty dance may I have
this dance yes in the walls the man puts
his in real polite on the ladies waist
and then she looks up into his eyes with
this real timid luck and he's so strong
he can do anything he wants
don't dad so close a cheap trick I'm
just trying to follow you all right just
come on follow me
we struck out again it wasn't 1099
southtownstar going to earth and 1099
North Comstock could she have said 2099
no it's 1099 all right just like one of
the police call signals 1099 officer in
trouble oh forget that one that was one
of the first ones I learned
I love you Tracy that's good because the
next time you come to visit and I'm
sorry I'm sorry I have to kill and I'd
like the other girls but that's why I'm
especially sorry if I don't think not
against me I wouldn't do that I'm hangry
with you for thinking that I would do
that I like you now you like me but in
time it will be different all women are
alike and that's a shame My Name Is Earl
say my name say oh let's say my name say
yeah
my your girl treated you I'll tell them
how bad it was I wouldn't let the pair
shoe I wouldn't I wouldn't let anything
happen to you I promise I want you're a
cop you're stinking their back the old
lady and the kids are back let's welcome
Tracy get tougher go
hey chief good night guys
night Tracy good night
got the message by the way the city will
fix up your house just like noon allow
nine months for the paperwork you'll
probably get a commendation of merit you
should get a promotion but there's a
budget freeze right now I'm not an
opinion research they offered me a
ten-percent raise gravatt his job pays
off in citations heartburn and ulcers
I'd take it if I was you know you
wouldn't okay Fleming see you tomorrow
at eight o'clock eight captain I've been
working around the clock for almost two
weeks okay make it 830 don't forget you
got a report to write copy to me copy to
callaway copy to records copy the files
right plumbing goodnight Merrick
oh honey am I glad you remembered your
police calls but what happened