you
Helen Helen stop having stop him watch
sticking fingers in my mouth cuz she bet
you talking all day which you can't hand
up if she can't hear that how she know
talk coming out of my mouth thinks she
trying to talk now she going crazy
eating myself stop that Helen stop it
Helen
Ellen stop stop it okay okay give them
off of the scissors helen ellen give
Mother decisions Helen okay okay
it's my party girl huh well baba I hope
you got your story ready what store is
that one you're gonna tell on the little
savage kill somebody Your Honor I had no
idea that poor deaf and dumb child could
be so violent your sister is none of
your concern James don't you have some
occasion you need to dress for why don't
I ever meet any of your young friends
James how can I about people here but
surely your friends don't think that
Helen is any reflection on you well
helen is the real head of this house
she's probably just pretending she can't
speak all here so she don't have to
answer to anyone your jealousy of that
helpless child is intolerable Andy oh
hello here we are here's a father in an
tan I saw James I hope to you in violin
again no no Oh Katie we're all loved
Helen but surely you must see what an
effect she is having on your house why
James and Arthur can barely speak a
civil word and all your time is given
over to the girl you hardly ever have
time for your new baby James is right
you and Arthur must do something and
soon what can we do Evelyn the only
thing left to do is to take Helen to an
asylum and Kate would never stand for
have you tried we have taken her to
every hospital in two states no one
holds out any hope what about that dr.
Chism up in Baltimore I read an article
in your very own newspaper Arthur they
say he has cured many cases of blindness
that other doctors have given up on now
why not write to him and have Kate's
heart broken again I'm prepared from
heart to break any number of times
captain
all right to myself if you're like Katie
there isn't going to be any cure and the
sooner we accept that fact the better
off we'll all be I will never accept it
to captain I can't i'm going to the
print hmm I know turn my back for a
moment Arthur Helen knows a lot more
than you think about what goes on in
this house nothing is solved by running
all over the country every time some
quack doctor gets his nail nothing is
solved by running through the office e
hmm good darlin what can anyone do the
kindest thing we could do would be to
find a sanitarium in a beautiful spot
where she will be taken care of no never
oh she tore off my buttons its eyes she
wants the dot she wants the doll to have
us I'm sorry Evelyn just tell me what
it'll cost have the buttons replaced I
know she does oh don't mind about that
what are a couple of buttons if it makes
Helen happy i'll sell them on if you're
lying is that what you're trying to do
Maikel unhappy nothing makes unhappy
everything you give only makes a war she
can have these little things that make
her happy
okay why she can have the little bang to
make her happy if you won't send her
away and we must find some way of
confinement oh you want to walk away an
addict like some sort of man woman all
right I'll write to dr. look up Chisholm
could do nothing for the girl and refer
them to dr. lagama Graham Bell does the
girl is yarn and the parents not willing
to send her to us I have put you up for
the role of governess governess or
nursemaid we both need to get rid of me
one of these days you've accomplished so
much here what when you first came to us
you couldn't even spell your name Oh
your eyes still so painful no it's my
ear sir tell me about the child is she
bright or dull can she be taught she's
given to tantrums they say so am I maybe
you should warn the calories about me
I've told them nothing of your history
except your qualifications for the job
here is the money for your train ticket
and here is a gift from all of us with
our love we're going to miss you this is
my last chance to counsel you any you
lack tact and the talent to bend to
others you're hard to fool and hard to
please
the dog saying
we are proud of you
you
go off to meet the train again well I
hope the girl is on this one oh she will
be oh well we'll see you at supper then
you
your mother's not here child I'm here
though I'm your father I'm your father I
used to swing you through the air you
weren't even two years of age yet wonder
if you remember any of that Oh any of us
here you are there's a piece of candy
for you
mm-hmm you want your mama don't you miss
it captain Keller wouldn't like this
it'd be saw it but what's one little
candy gonna head
miss Oliver yes I'm James Keller are you
the brother Jimmy are you Helens at
birla you have a charm yes Anna posit
come over the Sullivan Sullivan I'm so
relieved we were beginning to get a
little bit worried about you man who
told me that take it ought to be tied to
the tracks I'm Catherine Keller I'm
Helens mother you didn't bring Helen I
was hoping you would well her father
wanted to spend the afternoon with her
actually they so enjoy their time
together ok you should be ashamed miss
Sullivan you'll find it in the south and
make up these little stories just to
amuse each other I hope you want my how
much can a blind and deaf child learn
miss Sullivan I don't know does she
communicate with you at all oh well I
always know what you want so that's what
you mean no you don't all anybody knows
that if you give Helen the piece of
candy she'll be quiet for a while can
you teach you to sit stay on the subtle
I'd have to teach her language first
language if she doesn't know words how
could you know why you want her to sit
still miss Sullivan perhaps you were
misled us to Helens condition she can
neither see nor hear but if it is her
senses that impaired and not her mind
she must have language language is more
important to the mind than lightest to
the eye but how will you teach her if
you can't talk to her anyway I can we
are going to do everything that we can
to help you I don't want you to think of
us astray
I strangers aren't so strange to me
piping around all my life welcome dive
the green miss Sullivan I trust you had
a good John I had several thank you
where is heaven Oh Miss Annie we've put
you in the upstairs corner room now if
there's any breeze at all this summer
you're going to feel it I'll take my
suitcase uh heaven miss Ullman no please
let me I wouldn't think of it I have
something in it for hell me I needn't be
treated like a guest now when may I see
Helen well there she is that's Helen
she seems very rough Kate why didn't you
take her glasses off well the Institute
said that the light hurts our eyes
apparently she was nearly blind as a
child blood well she's had nine
operations on her eyes and they expect
one blind person to teach another one
how long was she employed at that school
oh she was employed there she was one of
their best students students now you
have two blind girls to take care of
father you stay out of this James why do
you have to be so mean about Helen what
the confirm my father's view of me of
course
those are mine
yes yes alright then Helen doll will be
your first word it's as good as any d o
el L da da it has name d 0 l Thank You
Hannah thank you puss so what was that
some sort of game it's an alphabet for
the Deaf each letter has a sign d 0 l l
don first she would learn to imitate d
00 she can imitate things alright like a
regular little monkey a bracelet monkey
hmm like she wants her doll back she can
have it back when she spells it she has
no idea what words even off how can she
spell her fingers learn the letters now
then maybe some day for bringing their
own that they have a meaning did you
make up this apple bit me no Spanish
monks under a vow of silence which mr.
James I wish you would take
SI a que é cake see hey okay good cake
d Oh mmm very good very good mmm first
let me girl
oh I wondered if she was bright she's
the brightest one in this house where's
Miss Annie she's in her room didn't
anyone call it a supper James go
upstairs and bring her down suddenly
I'll get the ladder what I'll need a
lotta it won't take long what are you
talking about well Helen locked her in
the room and run off to the key and I
suppose you were going to sit there and
say nothing you told me it was none of
my business father I was just trying to
respect your wishes
the Sullivan are you in there yes sir
I'm in here isn't that key on your side
no sir there's no key sir
I lot oh wait you mean whatever you say
father captain that we can't keep
missing he locked up till we find the
key James bring the ladder back whatever
you say father
aha solve problems not creative quarter
Jimmy thank you both
miss Sullivan yes captain Kenner I hope
this is not a sample of what we can
expect come out and sit on my shoulder
I'm perfectly capable of going down a
ladder by myself do as I say missile
very chivalrous of you this is not shell
away this is practicality you know go do
is trapped in a room not in the house 10
minutes honestly I don't see how you
managed it i'll look for the key sir
like you just don't look in any rooms
that can be locked all right everyone
excitements over what do people how
better leave the la dee dee ER
ah if you think you can get rid of me
that easily you're wrong
I have nothing better to do and nowhere
else to go to rest of my knowledge no
one in this house has ever tried to
control the girl but
discipline her without breaking her
spirit what if she won't obey me oh look
it has a name pen no bad no never you
mind me sayin it's not the first time
captain thinks that your spell and
everything that Helen does is like spell
into a fence post you talk to the baby
don't you does she understand what you
mean have yet but she will someday she
hears enough words I'm letting Helen
hear the words how long will it take a
million words maybe hen
did you see that i spelled pen she
spelled cake she wants to see if I can
tell the difference there is nothing
impaired in that head mrs. Keller helen
is smart and angry I can use that can
you teach me those letters I'll start
tomorrow if both of us are spelling to
her that makes only about half a million
words each oh why does she get a reward
for stabbing me I I don't know I'm sorry
miss Sullivan breakfast is ready shall I
get the ladder that's enough Jimmy oh
good Mona Miss Annie good morning
morning I hope you've settled in
comfortably miss Ellen Thank You captain
hi hop please help yourself Miss Annie
if there is ever anything that you need
please let us know tobacco prices up
father we should own a nice profit this
year for change used to be a man you'll
make a good living running a farm hmm
well perhaps if you leave your pet
newspaper and come some in my business
we can make some real money not in front
of Miss almond why not in front of Miss
subtle Miss Annie helen is used to
helping herself from our plates I'm
afraid I'm not used to it no of course
not oh honey please bring the Sullivan
another plate there's nothing wrong with
my plate captain only
Helen's hands don't belong in it one
plate is hardly worth spot on our
breakfast / you see she's just gonna
keep trying until she gets away I must
insist that you let the girl go hmm
thank you hmm now she's hurt herself no
she hasn't I know tantrum when I see one
and badly spoiled child I'm Sullivan hmm
please show some pity for this kind of
behavior he's the one thing she doesn't
be house waits on her hand and foot yeah
yeah you stay out of this letting Helen
have her own way yeah it's really such a
small thing smell it seems you've all
decided it's easier to feel sorry for
Helen and to teach her how to behave
well I've not seen that you've taught
her anything yet miss Sullivan wait
right captain well observed yeah starts
right now if you leave leave the room
yes pls kappa right now if you leave the
room miss Sullivan if you're not willing
to stand up to one tantrum I cannot
teach her anything hmm mrs. Keller you
asked if there was anything I needed yes
but I I need to be alone with Helen
right now miss Sullivan Oh Captain James
captain may I speak with you outside
give us a moment please this is absurd
Arthur I am sure that she is only trying
to do with his best I will not have my
house turned into a circus unless
there's a change in attitude miss
Sullivan is dismissed Arthur and then
what hope do we have for Helen no less
than we had before and then perhaps we
can regain some quiet
what you want me to do miss Kate it's
noontime in the breakfast dishes ain't
been cleared
Helen ate from her own plate with a
spoon all by herself and she folded her
napkin Durham's erect but she folded her
neck I'll be in my room mrs. Keller
don't belong now Miss Annie lunch gonna
be ready right away
you
what are you reading dr. house account
of his patient Laura Bridgman she was
deaf blind and mute from the age of two
did he succeed with her he did it's
possible with patients I suppose
something they did not give me a
certificate foreign proteins after this
morning's lesson the captain wants me to
dismiss you but i am going to insist
that you remain thank you where's your
family miss annie my brother Jimmy was
the last I had he died 12 years ago I'm
sorry I I tried to protect him I failed
it's no use trying to protect or speak
for other people not really the only
hope is to teach them to do it for
themselves that's what I'm trying to do
with Helen what you demand of her now is
all she'll ever be
step captain
and if what happened this morning wasn't
enough Helen can't stand to be near her
things have gotten worse and I want you
to give her notice no well if you won't
almost what do you mean captain mrs.
Keller miss Albin I find that I am not
satisfied with this that is this
arrangement will you please take off
your glasses I find it very difficult to
speak to you with them on of course if
you must keep them on now miss Sullivan
please tell me captain is the little
house in the grove of trees being used
for anything the garden house this is
just what I am talking about miss
Sullivan if you expect to stay on here
there must be a change in your manner
and you must convince me that there's a
slightest hope of teaching a child who
flees from you like the plague you could
show some sympathy you're absolutely
right captain there is not the slightest
possibility of teaching a child who runs
away from me it is hopeless here and the
sooner we realize that the sooner we can
get to a solution it is not hopeless
Helen could talk by the time she was 10
months old before this illness she was
such a good child yes she was an
extraordinary job I believe that but
she's not that child anymore I've seen
pets behave better than she does and
it's your petty that's the cause of it I
beg your pardon I'm afraid your love for
helen is greater handicap to her than
her blindness or her deafness and here
before you came we spoke of putting
Helen in an asylum please don't give up
obviously miss Sullivan thinks it's
hopeless here it's hopeless here I'm
only just beginning
please let me show you please follow me
I believe I can only make progress with
Helen if I have complete charge of her
but you already have that no I mean day
and night she must depend on me for what
for everything her food her clothes her
playtime her sweets all of these things
are tools that I can use to reach her
and how do you propose to do that when
she runs away from you if she can run to
you I have no hope which is why I must
live with her somewhere else you can
bring Helen here after a long carriage
ride she won't know where she is and you
can still see her every day provided she
does not know you're here how long would
you keep her as long as it takes I know
this is the way and Captain I cannot be
rude to you if you're not around to
interview with me might understand that
if I say no to this you will abandon
your charge to an asylum an asylum is no
place for Helen captain believe me I
know I grew up in an asylum in the state
poorhouse my brother and I until it took
his life our playroom was the dead house
where they kept the bodies until they
could dig the graves it made me strong
but helen is strong enough already
please give me this chance give her this
chance to save herself miss Sullivan do
you like this child do you captain with
your permission
I'll give you two weeks you have two
weeks to get the child to tolerate you
Percy could stay here he could run
errands for you two weeks is not enough
two weeks is what I am offering I'll
take it
where would you like her suitcase masala
Oh anywhere is fine how do you expect a
winner over in this place you plan to
tie to the chair how is it you have no
pity for hella to have pity for someone
as a waste of energy
feeling sorry for ourselves is even
worse
well I hope you win my solo
well we wrote in the country for two
hours all she knows she could be in
another town bring her inside please
yeah oh she wants me she can have you
back in two weeks Miss Annie please take
good care of her I will
dragon
let me go she's gonna pinch me thank you
John the toe she can talk she's got to
use her hands here let me show you she's
mad at me now so she doesn't want to
play but she knows a lot of letters SI a
que é cake SI hay que é she spends
cake she gets cake she doesn't know what
the word means yet but she will mercy
we don't need her how would you like to
learn when she doesn't know em is easy I
is even easier just to thank you oh ok
and why should I talk to you I'm
teaching / see em I am okay no I'm
teaching Percy whoa jealous
I okay at least I'm back to where I can
touch you
you can go back to get Percy thank you
I never thought that life could be so
quiet
I miss her too baby don't say a word
it's gonna find the Mockingbird don't
sing it's cool I diamond ring caption
and there are rats on I can't we little
else you don't have anywhere else to me
please can I stay with you just for
tonight
baby don't say a word
Laur
you
leaf
what watch her
why is it so hard to understand man we
were just about to have lunch how is she
Miss Annie I mean I told her that stitch
yesterday now I can't get her to stop
it's so quiet in the house without her
well when the captain and James I'm
bicker and that is I noticed they don't
get along oh well they used to when
James's mother was alive but then Helen
came along and well she takes up so much
about tension
soup oh such a lady she'd rather starve
than eat without a spoon you have taught
her so much in a week and a half it's
not enough obedience is not enough she
knows so many words if only she knew
what they meant and how will she learn
bird learns to use its wings it has to
come but how Miss Annie I need more time
alone with her yes why not because I
can't they spell it if he ever learns
you're the first person she's going to
want to talk to her
me she needs me to know you have three
days Annie that's all you have
gee gee egg that word is the thing it
has a name
is coming out of its shell Helen you you
come up to
whoa French I'll blame on something here
huh Oh Francis James thought I'd come
take a look around we had an idea last
year and tried something and it looks
like 22 inches 20 plants gives us by
twice at you twice the yield I had that
blue mold pretty bad last year sir well
we think it scanned over the winner and
the roots so we're gonna try to get all
the roots and stalks out of the ground
after the hop well if the roots gone we
get a bad rain we stand to lose a whole
layer tops off well i was thinking of
that too let's plan some low grads for
the one look for some would you fast
did you need something father I think I
have it Jimmy ah sorry to interrupt
horse
how I have waited for this day I only
hope we won't be disappointed Helen does
never disappoint you Father why are you
jealous James I'm not jealous I'm
envious it's not only Helen who needs to
learn how to talk things will be very
different if helen is better know who
will I blame them for my unhappiness if
only there was someone to help me I feel
I need a teacher as much as Helen does
captain miss Sullivan I've brought
Helena playmate kind of graduation
present please wait outside captain dog
well I miss Sullivan two weeks up not
until five o'clock Oh what difference
can half a day make you don't know how
eager we are to have her back I dunno
it's my main concern you've done wonders
for and you've done us a great service
I've actually missed her I oh that debt
to you pay it to heaven captain give her
another week look what you've done for
her already she's well behaved she seems
quite contented certainly cleaner she's
cleaner is that what you care about
she's learning to talk captain the words
are in her fingers already I can't risk
her and learning it when she goes back
to her old life in the house ah look
what is she spelling water miss Elam
that dog doesn't know what words are any
more than she does dogs happy enough Oh
God may not have meant for Helen to
speak miss Sullivan I mean her to
captain give her half a week
you have until five o'clock Kate cannot
bear to be separated from her for
another night where she your miss
Sullivan insisted on keeping her till
five o'clock no not what her dog dog
this this this is water how do I take
her understand
how do I tell you I don't know anything
they're satisfied I'll give them back
their child and their dog both
housebroken everyone satisfied everyone
but me and you reach reach
Oh what I wanted to give you Helen
everything in the earth everything that
we are would we dream of what we leave
behind what think can feel and know and
share it's all in words if I could give
you one word one word I could give you
everything wool it means this
chair dress
please
tears
let's bring a home
let's put your things away you are going
home helen is going home
that's right put your things away how is
she so please give me more time I can't
Helen
I have to go to him he's got no one on
the earth with me do you think I wanted
epidemic on my hands you can
may I escort you I'm not very good
company right now why I didn't come to
keep you company I came to keep it from
getting lost in the dark maybe that's
just what i was looking to do are you
feeling sorry for yourself my sullivan
just this once yes
my father has a great respect for you
that's not easily on father vicksburg he
had its newspaper and he's always daring
you to measure up if you have any advice
for me I wouldn't mind hearing it I
never really had a father so I'm the
last person to ask but you've got to
stand up to the world that's all I know
what if he's the world then you can just
look around James and see how much
bigger it really is he's a man James
that's all so are you
and Evelyn well come in come in it is so
good to see you you have to come and see
how Helen now the sweet child this son
of them must be a wonder miss Sullivan
I've brought you your first month's
salary you've done quite a job you've
taken a wild thing and giving us back a
child I taught Helen one thing no don't
do this don't do that I wanted to teach
her yes well you'll have all the time
you need now will you help me captain
yes how told undo what I've done the
world is not an easy place for anyone to
give Helen her way in everything is a
lie to her you've got to stand between
her and that lie don't give in we're
certainly going to try I used to wonder
how would earn living now the question
is can I survive it I'll see what's up
oh we glad to have you back mrs. white
Helen what ah yes keys yes um I think
we've had another lock doors around here
yeah jaicko was left alone
for the breaking up day and he wrestled
with an angel
an angel said let me go for the day
breaks Jacob said I will not let you go
until you bless me amen baby I a mamey
that's a very strange grace strange I
thought it was a very fitting grace
considering the circumstances so are you
an expert now on the Bible and tobacco
is that right James because they're deaf
I should say so you know my opinion of
your pickles well this is the last time
I'm afraid I didn't put up nearly enough
last summer but this year I intend to
Reverend Tom can stop by the office
today to complain about his weevils I
told him she tell him to I told him to
talk to you about his weevils James I
think it's marvelous what a successful
farmer you have turned out to be James
no no please I have hardly had an hour
with her captain Katie we uh we had a
little talk miss Sullivan feels that if
we indulge chillin in here but what's
job done she's known not to throw things
on the floor and kick it's a young man
and it's not as if it was something
breakable either give Helen to it or you
keep her from kicking please what do you
want me to do let me take her from the
tape but this is her first ignant bed
Lutz hurts so amazing I have made all of
Helens favorite foods she's testing
testing you I know well she's not
kicking now this is what I was worried
about is this what you promised me less
than an hour ago
give in to her then she's the one who
would pay for it please pass me more of
Helens favorite foods take a Miss Annie
thank you yeah take no i won't i don't
see that we need to send her from the
tape let me hold hell into what she's
learned and she would go on learning
take her out of my hands and it all
comes apart she is the guest of all
bring her plate back if she were seen
child you would not stand for this no
she's not I think some allowances are
called for bring her plate like you
now let's start all over no no no
don't get what are you doing aight
retelling like a scene child because i
asked her to see i expect her to see
well are you taking on to make her read
in this picture you let her speak to you
like that Arthur I don't let her go what
let her go she's right she's riding
Kate's right p job miss Sullivan away
from here then we're lost no helen is
lost captain please Jimmy
thank you where we are you recognize
this place pump nope your mother's not
here hum
you
sure yes water it has a name yes yes
water
pump
grout
yes
Oh
flower
mrs. cannon she knows she knows mother
captain
papa
teacher
yes teacher
he's she wants the key
k e why k
take
teacher
you
I love
Helen so much so much
you