let's go
build a giant airship and sail into the
sky
watch the
as they
if we will
come on grubby teddy my feet are getting
sore I must have stepped on every rock
between R alonia in here it didn't tell
me that adventure second would be this
hard on my feet yeah grubby octave feeds
do have a lot of feet to worry about you
hmm why don't we camp here for the night
that sounds good to me grubby are you
sure those roots are edible well I don't
know what the red oval or not but they
sure are the date uh hmm they're good
raw a fried for bait but you're about to
have my specialty mmm roasted root
rested route to yell your have one well
how do you like it um well uh yeah
aren't they good mmm teddy do you miss
home any yes I guess I do a little hmm
but we've only been gone a few days why
no but you're the first illy up to
Weaver alonia in a long time then I
thought you might be getting seems like
it's true illy apps aren't very
adventurous at least they haven't been
for many generations but somehow I've
always had this desire to go on a
journey to grund oh and I want to find
out if this old map really leads to a
treasure yeah you've been talking about
that since we were little hey you want
some more roots uh no thank you
beware all founders hmm what do you
suppose that means i don't know but
there doesn't seem to be any other way
to go yep you're right well let's go
bounders founders huh I wonder if
whoever wrote that sign meant boulders
you know it could be there lots of rocks
up there look at that popping loves you
and the malls are full of teeth
they're going to catch us run faster
grubby I'm trying I'm trying
right
this thing
take that oh my here Oh treacherous
little bounders
I lose more fire work that way how do
you do and my name is a Newton gimmick
but you can call me yeah yeah gimmick
they say aren't you in Ely up yes I am
you see grubby and I came here from our
homeland in vilonia we're on a marvelous
journey y-yeah yeah that's wonderful ah
I have an idea why don't we all go to my
house and dagger you have a bite to eat
okay that would be very nice gimmick
yeah what sort of journey are you on
you'll think we oughta talk about that
oh I'm sure we can trust gimmick and he
might recognize something on the map me
this map has been in my family for
generations we think it belonged to my
great great grandfather
don't bother me lb I've almost got it
hmm to stop that what is it you want oh
oh you've got that piece of wood stuck
in your mouth again all right me Oh
Oh guess what pretty quiet I'm sure I've
got the right combination this time just
think to actually make gold out of
buttermilk gold out of buttermilk gold
out of buttermilk tweed the closest
you've ever come to making gold is a
buttermilk donut he'll be how many times
do I have to tell you the name is twig
twig hey tweeze your gold is getting
stale I'll be I father I told you to be
quiet gimmick as visitors listen I've
told you for the last time gimme his
visitors yup a two of them why didn't
you tell me sooner I try oh I knew that
gimmick was up to no good I've always
known he wanted to steal my formula yeah
he's probably dying to make buttermilk
donuts yeah
all right i'll be there they are this
must be making plans to attack it'll be
run down there and find out what they're
saying you'll run down and find out what
they're saying run down and find out
what they're saying okay this'll teach
chemica singer too what was vile day oh
nothing it's just twig firing his
panting at us whoa oh I don't worry it's
been going on ever since I moved here it
used to bother me too until I had I
realized that he is without a doubt it
appeared the world's worst shot well who
is this tweak anyway we'll then yeah I'm
not sure I've never actually seen him
there's long as he's shooting at my
house it's probably the safest place in
the valley to be now why don't we take a
look at your treasure map this was with
the map but no one has ever been able to
explain what it is well it looks like
part of a medallion it appears to be
made of very area gold and kind of
crystal yes and there's writing on it
spirit treasure ledge some spooky to me
and now let's see this is indeed an old
map it says here that the treasure is in
the ancient hard to find city which lies
high in the treacherous mountains I've
heard that they are impossible to climb
which brings me to why you were
fortunate to have met me come with me
the fact is I'm something of an inventor
gentlemen this is my latest invention I
call it an airship and I'm about to try
it out for the first time you kind of
looks like a boat well yeah yeah as a
matter of fact it did start out to be a
boat but then I realized I'm not very
close to water you know you're not very
close to water yeah it would be kind of
good for a boat to be close to water
precisely and that was my exact
conclusion but then the idea hit me in
if a boat could float on water it could
also float on air if the air is hot that
is with this airship we can fly as high
and is free as a bird we can fly right
over the treacherous mountains to the
hard defying city that's wonderful you
are more than welcome to share the
treasure if we're lucky enough to find
it that is yeah there should be plenty
of treasure you all right let's get
underway if you fellas can begin loading
this firewood I'll
inside and daddy air packs some
provisions all right horrid little
bounders look at you that's twice in one
day you've had that log in your mouth
had to do anything right Oh can't I do
anything right I oughta take that
treasure map somewhere else yeah y'all
treasure map what treasure map the one
you're holding in your hand twing did
you put my gold samples and form you
lied in a safe place it's all taken care
it's the wagons loaded and that's all
taken care of tool hoppity now sneak
back to gimmicks with this Pony map all
right twins
good keep the fire hot grubby okay Lee
dude gimmick do we have all the supplies
yeah yeah yeahs yes where's the map oh
I'm yeah yeah let me see her and now
where did I put that map I don't see it
here anywhere the world and I'll go with
a check in the house what happened you
know 30 and something about the design
of this airship doesn't seem quite right
yes grubby I've had that feeling too but
I can't put my finger on what it is have
you mentioned it to gimmick no I haven't
you think I should oh here's the map yes
I found the map oh good here I'll put it
with the rest of the supplies say
gimmick something about the design of
this airship doesn't seem quite right oh
don't worry my boy you get share their
working just like I expected we're off
the ground we're really fighting it's
amazing gimmick they were flying but
something has passed off the line okay
so cool
thousand soon Floyd
and I think I know what it is hmm yeah
parently something wasn't quite right
I've got to hand it to you grubby and
this design does seem to work a bit
better just the line your multiplication
all right and now that everything is
working properly and let's check the map
once more so that we can head in the
right direction well gimmick how do we
make the airship head in the right
direction oh and yeah we just an yeah
yeah hmm that's a very interesting
question teddy well you better remember
the answer pretty quick Dimmick before
we drift into that big tree over there I
don't remember making a provision for
moving in the
running into the three
now what we do what are you doing in my
treat ya did oh who said that I said
that now say it again just what are you
doing in my tree it's a tiny flying lady
hey would you look at that what is it
I'm a wood sprite no there is no such
thing as a curve here a wood sprite oh
no and I suppose there's no such thing
as a big bag of air stuck in my tree but
there it is big as life golly she is a
real wood sprite no bigger than a bird
and very pretty well how about moving
this big Oh do you read it and I'm
pretty oh yes I certainly do oh I you
switched and who are you well I'm Teddy
Ruxpin and this is grubby and this is
Newton gimmick how do you do my name is
Liotta I'm pleased to meet you and I'm
sorry if we've damaged your tree oh
that's all right is there anything I can
do to help hmm well I'm not sure you do
understand the simple basics of
aerodynamics don't you did huh well
first of all let the hot air out of that
bag so you can get down out of my tree
oh all right now in order for your
airship to move in any given direction
you must apply a force in an opposite
direction such as in this large manually
driven propeller then you will have to
know something about the effect of wind
and various aspects of navigation it's
really very simple
Oh
everything's ready gimmick all right
release the tether lines I are you give
me okay gimmick that's working oh it's
working perfectly Thank You Liotta oh
you're lucky goodbye goodbye Liotta
goodbye toodaloo don't get stuck in any
more trees
Oh
gimmick shouldn't we be getting close to
the mosque forest yeah yes I think so we
made good time yesterday how far north
is the moss porous em here oh it's a few
hours on foot aren't we going south but
look according to the map we should be
going south then there must be something
wrong with the map you know the map does
look a lot newer than it used to and
look it says the treasure is buried in
the Great Desert hmm when unhealthily
off only map a treasure supposed to be
in the treacherous mountains but who
could have switched maps on us tween
oh hey fellas were about out of fuel
we're gonna have two lamb all right and
let's set her now and maybe we can
determine which direction to head in uh
I don't think we're gonna find much wood
around here hmm I fear you're right
teddy this must be the great desert
great my feet are getting hot whoa are
you all right yes I I'm fine I just
tripped over this rock hmm what is it I
thought so this isn't just a rock did
you it's cool you mean the kind of coal
that burns yes and if we can find more
of it hey there's lots more coal in that
cave how about one more load just to be
on the safe side all right there but
we'll have to hurry it'll be getting
dark soon
gee it's getting dark in here a little
say fellas it don't suppose anything was
in here do you an idea and no I think
that for a region is arid and
inhospitable as this desert to support
any form of life as we know it would be
virtually impossible
impossible
put this one to work and take the other
tool to the dungeon and lock them up
i'll research what is it we've done if
it's the call you're worried about we'll
be happy to pay you for it why are those
things so unreasonable yeah I don't know
teddy what kind of creatures are they I
don't know that either they're mud Blops
did huh hello my name is Teddy Ruxpin
and this is my friend Newton gimmick
well how do you do my name is Prince
aren hey ba ganyan a prince Aaron the
son of king nog Burt yes well yeah hey
what are you doing here well my sister
princess arusha was kidnapped and taken
from our land I've been searching for
her when I was captured by these horrid
mud blocks they captured me with ease
I'm I'm a failure in the coward they're
just because you couldn't fend off those
brutes the mud lobster you called them
and that doesn't make you a coward by
any means it's true Prince aren you
shouldn't blame yourself we'll all I
know is I've been here for a long time
there's no telling what's happened to my
sister by now what do you suppose those
mud flaps are going to do with us
gimmick no I wish I knew teddy ya hear
what's going on I don't know what do you
suppose that was all about today I
haven't a clue my boy this stuff is
horrible it's almost like glue yes the
food here is awful although this smells
worse than usual seems like I've tasted
this stuff somewhere before
what else can happen
oh look I see light up there maybe if
you stand on my shoulders you can see
where it's coming from it leads to the
surface come on we can get out I thought
we'd never find the airship
I don't think we should have left grubby
behind I know teddy but we had no choice
no we didn't yes you're right but I just
hope grubby is all right
it's morgan gimmick it's working be
naturally my boy didn't I tell you what
would now all we have to do is locate
grubby Robbie Robbie play tolls I'm in
here Robbie are you all right Teddy
gimmick oh hey it's great to see you did
they let y'all know we escaped and we
came back to free you come on let's go
well okay you as soon as I finish this
patch of mmm roots do you mean you were
making that stuff we were eating yeah
ooh these blood guys love my roots do I
even talked them into giving you an
extra portion oh thanks well more mud
flaps are coming come on grubby let's
get out of here
low light
you
afraid you wouldn't make it gimmick was
right about the mud lop size being extra
sensitive to light his plan worked
perfectly Oh Prince Aaron this is grubby
hello Prince aren collar you grubby oh
ok Thank You Gia are you a real Prince
that's right but just wait till you meet
his sister princess her Lucia Wow a
princess too new what do you mean teddy
I don't understand well gimmick and I
have discussed it and I'm sure grubby
will agree the search for your sister is
very important but but I only ask that
you take me to the edge of the desert
you're looking for the treasure and I
don't expect you to the treasure can
wait besides we've made up our minds so
please stop arguing indeed Prince aren
teddy is right we want to help you find
your sister yep we sure do well thank
you thank you all very much
twig are we almost there yet selby will
you stop asking that besides we'd
probably be at the treacherous mountains
by now if you wouldn't keep getting us
lost i don't get us lost wig you're
driving well I've got my hands full
reading this map and of and thinking
about all that wonderful pleasure
summary of LD we're down there I see a
waterfall oh good set her down what's
that thing hmm yeah I don't know but it
looks a dangerous we gotta get it out of
there cuz I'm thirsty oh excuse me oh
hey excuse me
do you think we could get some water
please hey you get out of there what are
you say well built on we gotta be off on
our mission to find princess arusha and
the well you're holding us up you say a
princess yeah princesa lose a yellow a
sister of Prince error here oh she's
laws well actually she's been kidnapped
why would anybody kidnap a princess
that's bad well we don't know who took
her or why all I know is I've got to get
her back well then what you're to do is
talk to her wizard the wizard wizard he
knows everything well i hope the wizard
can help well there dear we'll soon find
out who
to disturb the solitude of the wizard oh
damn yet oh I thought I said to go a
word yes you did sir but my sister
princess Rosie is missing and I
understand that you might be able to
help you says her just stay there a
minute what was that oh I lowly what sir
well you stay outside the rest of you
come in now now what was that you wanted
Wilson my sister princess arusha has
been kidnapped and were trying to locate
her all right come with me
hey Louis yeah we got any footage on a
princess and rusia animal what does he
look like well probably like her brother
sitting out there take a look he's the
one in the soldier suit mm-hmm oh yeah I
think I remember a kid that looks like
that yeah he is but the getting's
wondered what she was doing with them
well according to her brother she's been
kidnapped really well this information
ought to be worth something okay put the
film on the machine now everyone
concentrate so that we may bring forth
the mystical powers of communication
yeah I said concentrate
good good everyone concentrate on where
Princess aroosi accan G
yes good tangs
yes I see it now princess arusha is
being held by the flying attains what's
them or trapeze act but she's afraid of
heights hey attention look into the
magic I high in the treacherous
mountains the ancient hard to find city
provides the stronghold for the guitar
which were smoking or the point city
that's what from their mountain fortress
the evil detains maintain a constant
vigil with their many weapons and bat
like aircraft they stand prepared to
fend off an attack by even the strongest
of phone oh the change latest villainous
act is to have carried out the
successful kidnapping of the beloved
princess Eruzione look look there's my
sister how do we get to the treacherous
mountains to the north east but no one
has ever been able to scale the
treacherous mountains Thank You wizard
thank you oh yes thank you again sir I
hope you find her Thank You Willy
you take good care of that princess i
will divide
Chloe I'll never get up to that age it's
hard to find city y'all no help at all
well we've only been trying to climb
these mountains for two weeks haven't
you had enough yet oh all that treasure
a plan and I can't get at it it's
gimmick and those other guys so did they
get hit anyway they had the road map
what could have gone wrong they'll fly
right up for that hard to fight City oh
they'll take every bit of that treasure
their landing there won't be anything
left for me until landing why does it
always have to happen to me the landing
Teddy I'm glad you wanted me to make
this root stew I was beginning to think
that maybe you didn't like it oh not at
all i think it might come in very handy
yeah and yeah we're ready to cast off
korean el bang
hey come on now let's find that treasure
look there's a guard over there yeah
what's get'em okay but be quiet got him
he's home pull this helmet off keep him
from yelling here is the rope tie him up
okay oh there it is that's the building
that was in The Wizard pictures that's
where they took my sister okay let's go
we've been ordered to take her out of
here just who ordered you to take her oh
and Ed it was
what's going on in here Oh huh nothing i
just dropped something well keep it down
I was winning that hand a rosier are you
all right oh yes I'm fine now that
you're here I came as soon as I could I
knew you would I never once gave up home
I wouldn't have made it if it weren't
for my friends we better leave Prince
aren before were discovered grubby get
another helmet Robbie I think I know
this place it it looks like the shrine
on the map Tony I think you're right
look look it's the other half of the
medallion look it fits perfectly
only the pure of spirit may find the
treasure of knowledge
honesty
breathe
trust
friendship
hail be where do you suppose they're
going and what are those things they're
carrying uh well I don't know twig but I
see where they're running from and it
looks like that building on the man
you're right i'll be that's where the
treasure supposed to be
princess Aisha game
oh oh we've been discovered more fuel
oh here come those aeroplanes
the shooting at us get down a rusia
rookie we have to get out of range of
those weapons oh no we're not going
anymore
back to the CD grubbing bring out the
roots to walk okay but the seem like a
strange time to be Ellen breakfast put a
spoonful of the stew right in this sling
good shootin to eat the bottom look at
that
on the little port sorry took me some of
that stuff buddy
the people that solution
they're going to launch more planes
there's Louie
and I thought no one
get a room
airplanes coming at us from the left
give me some more routes to go shop wake
up from it's going down Marse to me
what a stool
Louie are you all right saved our lives
hey all right yeah are you princess
parousia oh boy hurry yo princess thank
you for helping us Willy why you're
welcome I was worried about you thank
you all for helping me we were glad to
help you princess yes I guess we took
care of those gettings well Teddy maybe
you don't like the taste of my route
spoon but you did find something that'll
is good for ya you're right grubby it
worked very well I think we should all
be proud of ourselves especially you
Willy indeed what can we ever do to
repay him oh I've already been paid I
got to see a real live wit says
hey teddy there sure was a lot of
treasure up there in that shrine yes
there lies and what do you suppose these
things are I don't know grubby but
somehow I think they're more important
than all that treasure I think you're
right teddy only the pure of spirit may
find the treasure of knowledge it's as
though whoever left this message wanted
us to take these crystals and I think
that what we will learn from these
crystals will make all that treasure
looked like just an illusion ah your
bottle be give me a hand I still can't
figure out why those guys left all this
treasure here how could those things
they were carrying be more important
than this treasure
let's meet a lovely princess and stand
rocky
let's dream under
and let us leave that magic dream
and
yes
than the wondrous dream we dream tonight
someday just might come true
you