first in Alaska and then invading
steadily southward there were reports of
a new species the Giant Killer shrew
shows well quiet
almost smelly kids no but I can feel it
the precious drops a fast it almost made
my ears pop
hurricanes got different ways of telling
his their ways
get ahead
was that mean us boy that puts our port
right in the middle of it
there's a cove on the lee side though
we'll snuggle up close to the bluff and
ride it out what about the bottom the
chart shows it's good holding grounds
clay
you know something if this thing had on
automatic pilot i would have to put up
with you then you would handle better
get you out should be there in a couple
of hours these mills of yours keep
running look automatic pilots can't play
Dixieland jazz on the vendors like I can
hey ruff ruff come here
take a look
there she is dead ahead
man that show who do look good
man named Craig is on this island that
he has the name or Lecrae dr. Marlowe
credits will then load tomorrow on his
perhaps sitting high net water when mo
hits go rats turn to a lot of water
under that's right and see we'll make up
in that code and win we'll have a
whipping around like a kite mr. forward
break out the heavy weather hook track
with maturity run our mouths shut
you
oh she arrived like a duck if she swings
too far to starboard we might have to
take a check line to shore hey rook take
a slant up that trail
that's a red estranged set up when you
say black somebody's getting rid of
somebody I'll cap may be hard to tell
I'm dr. Craig Thorin Sherman have your
supplies aboard that's good nothing
wrong with Captain Ferguson I hope all I
wouldn't know i just bought he's Ryan oh
I see you will yay with the kalawa order
everything on the list here's the
manifest missing last week's supply has
drawn us a little short you know captain
after you ever loaded I have a passenger
for you and captive Sherman this is my
daughter and crazy well so you're the
passenger that's right cat oh it's gonna
be nice having you aboard I'm getting a
little tired looking at Griswold but
we're we're not leaving today
we're not even unloading that load will
cut the roll in half you expecting an
invasion yes animals game or otherwise
there's certain conditions it could be
dangerous
hey ruff you want to shake the kinks out
limber up a little not meek am glad you
go right ahead stretch your leg that's
just gonna be bucking like a bucking
bronco long sighs I got some work left
to do if you do come ashore wear a gun
got ya
you
and I told you about the hurricane you
act like you didn't know anything about
it what's the matter your set broken
down you have enough communication for
more than a week can it be fixed it's
totally out of commission my assistants
mr. Phil Jerry fellow
father perhaps the captain would enjoy a
dream
of course would you join us in a
cocktail well I've never been known to
turn down a drink yet I'll be glad to
accept that case we'll have martinis
mary 0 CC on Nick's them please right
this way captain come in
you have everything here you need whoa
we are self-sufficient here we have cows
for fresh milk chickens for fresh eggs
we even have saddled horse sort of a
world all your own that's exactly about
tried to create well to each his own if
you have to be isolated for your work
you picked a lonely little island excuse
me please I think I'll change
she's a little worried because you
aren't leaving until tomorrow well I can
understand that but there's something
else bothering her
radford Bradford ratha would you please
step over here like you to meet someone
just a second doc go up our doctor
Baines there's no need to shop doctor
I'm right here I like it to meet captain
phone chemin this is my other assistant
Bradford beam how do you do two new
litters cents lunch doctor both support
GT 116 that's good we can breed them to
the 205 group in about three weeks but
I'd prefer to wait and expose about half
of them to the Hoskins factor first if
you agree good idea do you notice a
hurricane coming freaking well I don't
suppose there's much we can do about
that glad to meet you Sherman wasn't
you have to excuse Radford anything that
does not concern this project and does
not get through to him brilliant mind he
would stop it if someone didn't remind
him to eat must be very interesting work
what's his field biology we specialize
the genetics had entity I'm afraid my
interest doesn't run in that line you
know think what would happen if you
could isolate and identify the inherited
fact than each gene now wait a minute
I'm afraid I'm not very good with pure
research this is practical research
delri among mammals the smaller the size
the haida metabolism end the shorter the
lifespan there right well I'm attempting
to to decrease the size by maintaining a
low metabolism and resultant along a
lifespan what reason overpopulation not
a problem now but it will be in time
every what half as big as we are now we
could lift twice as long in our natural
resources father may I speak with you a
moment will you please excuse us captain
well providing you drop the captain
after birth on
you
tell me something doctor has a her can
ever hit this island before that you
know of I wouldn't know you've only been
here nine months at his place has been
unoccupied for years we'll have you ever
been through one only the fringes well
this one's building up very fast
pressure drops very quickly in the
center I'd advise you to get some doors
and windows open in this place until
eight us on the road and if you're fresh
and hands drink I'll go and check them
I'd be happy to thank heavens you're
right why are Asians getting short parts
more than that much more will surely be
able to save tomorrow and we possibly
but not probable not too late anyway
takes a long time for a sea like that to
quiet down well if you're worrying about
me you needn't I'm a good sailor well
I'm not worried about you will say all
the time's right got them opened all
right Oh captain let me freshen you a
drink one for the road I'm trying to
rush you but it will be dark soon I've
invited tone for dinner funny oh I see
if you not worried about your ship
you're welcome I'll take a rain check on
that dinner if you wish father I've
asked thorne to stay progress doctor
this is the sole survivor of group 30 28
months old today well it's equivalent
240 years to us that's right yet it
still maintains low metabolism without
any sluggishness not the breakthrough
but it certainly sets our course Radford
suspend series 52 through a 96 and we'll
concentrate on the rest why is that it's
a Sorak cerissa t looks like a small rat
smells like a skunk they have must
glands in their needs these little
fellows our subjects they have birth
cycle of 10 to 14 days and using them we
can establish traits we can trace the
progressions to a number of generations
over a short period of time well how big
do they get
that's a little
see their muscle is longer and thicker
than the rats it extends over the lower
mandible to see does he bite only when
he's hungry maybe you better take him he
doesn't know me all he knows is his next
meal then he just been fed to be alright
one of eight hours I should have to open
Bradford I got it see you let that scare
you gonna get worse storms always
friendly ever since she was a child
they're not climbers they are digging
animals like the mold they feed only at
night unless they're starving and when
they are hungry enough stayed they'll
tackle anything regardless of science
okay mm-hmm if you leave two of them in
a cage for 12 hours without food the
stronger will eat the weekend right
cannibals precisely you see their
intense activity requires a tremendous
amount of energy to supply they they
must eat three times their own weight in
food every 24 hours four-star Radford
Radford would you please take this take
it hey yeah some call them bonitas when
the flesh is gone they'll eat the bones
for marrow all their livre teeth oh my
teeny do you Mike of course my dear I'll
get you one
Mario Mario and keep off of all Mary oh
sure to the bathroom oppression of it
yeah BL senior al bano Cesar you see on
the power
akiza
you got a problem too que paso nada
nothing Senor about you we leave on the
chip tomorrow well I think that all
depends on the wind and the sea don't
you see season you know ah you may jogia
I feel before it I see I'm glad to hear
that now if anybody else is concerned
about my sailing tomorrow why you see
they feel the point too huh I don't like
to repeat myself okay see you
you
I know but I'm not saying that you
created them Jerry I am saying that
because of your drunken stupidity and
leaving the cage door open you created
the horrible situation that now exists
what can this is a mistake any one of us
might have made and I'm getting a little
sick of being called an irresponsible
drunk now believe me I am excuse me
care for a cigarette Thanks thank
heavens you ride today you said that
before what's the string I don't make
sense please excuse me but it seems like
everything is coming to a head at one so
I want to leave but I want my father to
go with me well then why doesn't he we
discussed it many times but he's adamant
I'm sure Jerry has a lot to do with this
decision it had to convince me that the
crisis will only last for a few well
this is certainly a cozy little scene
might even be called enema boy meets
girl wow thank you mark is uncalled for
but I do I have to say does not concern
you I can't disagree with you more my
dear I'm concerned with everything you
do and I intend to keep it that way on
my book and engagement isn't a casual
thing my book it isn't either and last
night and it ours
you
Oh
be reasonable everybody in the world is
scared to death or something that's
evident when they came with us last
night you knock me down getting inside
the fence it's just that I can't stand
them and I've discovered something I
can't stand all right but I advise you
not to mention it to anyone I'm gonna
complete these experiments with your
father regardless of anything do you
understand that nobody is gonna take
this chance away from me let's get the
chemin checking the weather I'll get him
captain time for dinner
Oh
this as good as a mile away Staind you
need one of those trees crashes through
it might just not be any tree on this
side of the house a fall away from it so
just relax but I think I'd better go
back a board I don't think I'm not
grateful for your hospitality I am I'll
see you mom so on your ship is safe
please stay here with me why you're
scared or lonesome I'll take a rain
check on it dawn you can't leave no one
opens that gate after dark well who's
gonna stop me you what's this no one
opened that gate at night now look I
don't ask questions because it's against
my principles when you like to explain
that all right get down in half way give
me the gun not very becoming anyway you
believe in fairy tales well I'm a little
old for that sort of thing but what you
have in mind I lied to you about one a
true fairy tier are you right in the
middle of it Oh have you ever heard of a
shrew as in taming IV animal Brad will
call them sorcery City when you showed
you one no and shrew must be the common
name for those cute little and cute
that's unless what you can use to
describe those little monsters they're
the most harm animals on the face of the
earth as father told you they breed
within three weeks after birthday laughs
yeah I know what your father told me but
what's that got to do with me opening
that gate
there are two or three hundred giant
truths out there monsters weighing
between fifty and a hundred pounds fifty
to a hundred weight a night you must be
kidding i'm definitely not kidding
that's as big as a full-grown war and
what's more they are beginning to starve
no wonder you didn't want me to go out
there thanks for saving my skin well I'm
sorry I had to threaten you with a gun
but I didn't know how else to stop you
it was very effective but all you had to
do was tell me about it well I hoped I
wouldn't have to but you changed
everything when you started to lead and
I had to stop you some way you say
there's two or three hundred out there
man
that's right captain thorn and if you'd
stuck with your rowboat and played
Captain instead of trying to play
detective you wouldn't have to worry
about how many are out there would you
that's enough Jerry what's wrong in
Lathon decided to leave to dissuade him
I started to tell him about their shoes
he might as well know the whole story is
half of it
I guess you're a little jumpy captain
yeah I'm sorry six months ago be managed
to Ashley the factor control insides to
let us are born six individuals to get
the study they were about the size of
buckshot at birth but the rate of growth
was abnormal they continue to grow road
there were mutants but they inherited
all the negative characteristics of
their breed somehow they managed to
escape but a month later we saw one of
the old speakers they will multiply we
did everything in the world to
exterminate them but no apparent luck
then we haven't seen any since de la
vida blinds them in there they forage
only at night or less starving
but the fact that two of them charged
and and Jerry at the gate last evening
in the case that they're available food
on the island is nearing depletion then
what dr. they will exterminate each
other till take a couple days what do we
do during that time stay indoors will
wait until it's over I guess some wires
been down on the transformer I'm sorry
I'll get some lamps mario mayo sees a
good there's a ladder in the pantry why
didn't bring it in here
bradford light all the candles you can
find all right I will where is it
generator outside can get it at night
here let me help lanson will give you
all the life you need I will join you
Charlotte Jerry
well Jerry I felt she was sincere and
made sense from her standpoint wanting
her father to leave the island with her
makes sense I'd be much better for the
project of Iowan weather for a few days
as a matter of fact I think I'll taught
the doctor about that that might be the
answer and another thing I don't take
much to this thorn Sherman he looks to
me like the type that had try anything
that left-handed dinner invitation I was
just to keep me here till after dark
wasn't it
I wanted you here tonight I've had
something terrible was going to happen
well you still feel the same way about
it not as much that says you're here and
know everything
I love an open fire don't you mm-hmm
the wind has a lonesome sound doesn't it
sure does
I guess when we don't have a windy
strong
you're a strange man thought I never met
anyone like you
oh you seemed so disinterested in
everything aren't you the least bit
curious don't you wonder about the
unusual things around here the guns the
fence they shattered windows my accent
anything I'll tell you something I'm
only interested in anything that
concerns me that I do something about it
you're gonna sail with me tomorrow with
your friends
I don't think he was going out Jerry I
can't take a chance is fool enough to
don't be stupid I don't intentions are
going out there opening a date now
somebody needed it did you hear it dr.
it sound like a human voice I'll sing a
look with the livestock the shoes got
into the bomb
what I said father there's a life stuck
did Mario forget to borrow those doors
no I've put him in the barn myself there
couldn't get through the wood doors that
dug through the dirt floor let me ask
you something doctor how could you
expose all our lives yourself included
with those things out there all you had
to do was get the Coast Guard or the
nave to come in here and burn them out
those things got loose any unusual
experiment can produce unusual results
that's why I chose this island isolated
miles of open water in any direction our
project is practically financed it's not
a problem for the government or military
and the world is no danger his species
does not swim and as far as the shoes
are concerned this island is their world
very soon right here on this island is
going to be a miniature reproduction of
an overpopulated world and you'll see
the importance of what we're working to
avoid I'm not concerned about all this
theory what I'm concerned about is our
lives there'll be ample time to panic
when they run out of food and go on a
24-hour forage how do you know they
haven't already that's possible their
main diet has been a small animals on
the island that source could have been
depleted 18 or 20 hours late and that's
why they weren't after the livestock
there's still some food on this island
before they reach the crisis where
no worry about them digging in here the
floors are tiled but the walls aren't
dr. their Adobe our safe spent would be
on that boat you may be right you can
reach your boat and daylight the shrews
will gorge themselves on life stock does
she keep the mythology for several hours
there's no sense looking at the dark
side and there's no sense minimizing a
serious situation it leaves you
completely unprepared to cope with it
now we certainly can't make it tonight
that's out of the question maybe
tomorrow I haven't will get some sleep
tonight but we'll have a watch an hour
and a half a piece dr. you go first and
in radford Mary Oh Jerry and then me
shudder all the windows make sure
they're locked good and tight check all
these walls come on no I think I stay
here by the fire I feel safer I couldn't
stand it in that room alone alright as
you wish but try to get some sleep
see your forehead here is Mario you are
next to make the patrol Oh sir Mario
come on in open been waiting for you to
finish I must have dozed off you kind of
startled me sit down here I would rank 0
help you know relight lets you see you
sit down Lester wild is this checked
every room in the Hoskins you see fine
you're good man Mario a man that can be
trusted
you know what I've been thinking about
Mario and and that captain you and me
imagine uh intelligent girl like her
going for a common see tramp like him I
know why you do to case anything goes
wrong she's looking out for own hi
that's why I keep thinking about you and
me anything goes wrong we're gonna wash
them all
I'm going to trust you to take my turn
if it's all in the house but when you
finish don't wipe the captain come back
here and get me see I'll probably feel
good enough by in to take his turn okay
ma'am see okay
you're it is Mario my mind what is there
a serial a tony la bodega a shrew in a
cellar see I hear him singing down there
well Haredi Kenny disturb break out the
kitchen window but I closed it off he
went down there why should he go down
there the fool for delivery at Tony's I
pulled out and frost I love it what did
you tell Jerry no Senor here is your
turn next here is a una Luz we're
killing know yeah
and wake up a shrew got him it's all
right he's down in the cellar now we're
going down after him but I don't want
you to let anybody open that door till I
tell you to you understand good girl
open just a crack open hold on to it
ah
Mario a key you see anything I see where
he was I do not see what it is morado si
Senor I will be careful
he also gotten busy
you all right down there dr. get out
here quick
video
hey he's dead yeah
I got this on him right away you
couldn't have bled to death might as
well let go of it well do many good now
what could it kill him I'm not said till
the autopsy hemotoxic syndrome I'm
afraid so we'll know after pathology
doctor that's not the same animal you
showed me that's a monster as I said
there are mutants in controlling the
size factor we seem to have crossed some
of the other characteristics well you
certainly did a good job of it I've
known that for some time captain
picture please give me a hand with nati
Oh graphic bring up the animal
extremely high poison content in the
Shrew saliva I'll compare it with this
careful Compton necessary any indication
the same poison that Mary's blood will
give you the answer yes you're right
look at
brooding about it's not gonna do any
good now why don't you try to think of
something else tell me yeah what do you
do around here are are you a scientist
Mama's artist oh that's the study of
animal life in it what do you specialize
what are you specialize in they died I
had a hand in his 29 partly to blame let
these ends it we ever get off this
island I never have anything to do with
it again what will you do if normally
like normal women do you see it seemed a
little don't after the life I've been
living draw there darlin alive and
excited and I'll take a doll alive woman
every time
sathorn the autopsy has proved what we
suspected several weeks ago I concocted
the most virulent poison I could with
the materials ahead at hand have you put
it out as bait area was killed my poison
doctor I wonder if you thought the
system of the sorex enabled them to
assimilate that poison it remained in
the salivary glands of their jaws isn't
that wonderful I am sorry of course I
always speak from the clinical point of
view well don't you have something to
counteract that poison once Mary it was
bitten I'm afraid as nothing anyone
could have done this indicates that they
cannot afford to get even so much as a
scratch from these animals down more
poisonous than snakes what do you think
they're all affected best way to find
out is let them all bhaijan see which
bites yet died after we might just all
get that chance Jerry you included
doctor I've closed all the doors in the
house I suggest we do the same thing
with this hall in this lab and cut down
the chances of getting in the front of
the house I think if we keep up close
watching those walls and windows in
there we might make it till daybreak the
balls are two feet thick dude do you
think they have a chance to dig in of
course there's a chance anywhere that
plasters off that Adobe's as soft as
mush where that rain hit
did huh but here's another possibility
doctor it's very light out it's gonna be
daylight soon would take the Shrew that
killed Mario throw it over the fence use
it for bait if they show up for it
course the run to the boats out if they
don't then I'll go down have rook lay
two with a lighter then I'll return to
the band and the trail and give you the
all-clear signal sounds fine captain
good then you explain it to the rest yes
I will
I'll abates than out for 20 minutes
nothing's touched
even if when desk I'm John isn't that
wonderful I'm afraid it's not over my
dear it's just alone he'll be a lot more
he's right I'll be back at the bend
shortly now you watch for my signal huh
you can't go now i'll go with him not
you Father you haven't even fired a gun
take graduate Jerry sure I'll go and
you'll be sure of getting a signal
don't shoot that gun unless you have to
you've only got 20 rounds altogether I
know that as well as you do Sherman you
stay away from her you have a gun
pointed at me right at the middle of
your back look we got enough problems
out worrying about an telling you stay
away from her when the shrews gets
through with you they won't even find a
buckshot
where's this gift
I'll follow that check line I gotta find
him since last night you won't find much
of it would you shut up I'm not going
back you're what I'm staying here all
right you suit yourself but if I were
you I'd swim out to that boat can't swim
and stay here wait a minute you got to
give me a gun give you a gun
Sherman wait
this is a gun we had on the boot
they don't leave much do they
Sherman we got to make a deal but what
is it they've been trailing us on both
sides where I didn't see anything look
Sherman you got to give me a gun but if
you do don't you run you stay in front
of me cuz i don't trust
you
they're coming
the shoes rocker I couldn't take a
chance
you
for heaven sakes doctor stop
all right didn't he have it coming or
didn't he what happened out there oh
nothing much sure I just tried to kill
me twice in the last five minutes Brooke
came ashore last night he is dead his
saw was left who do Senecas got no ammo
I'm deeply sorry captain I wish you'd
followed yours look doctor you casually
mention animals you didn't explain to us
what we were facing out there that every
right to feel the way you do my mistake
was only mine what our judgment I didn't
know about the hurricane I didn't
anticipate the effect it would have on
the shrews I thought the house would be
safe for the crisis how could you expose
your own daughter how could you expose
an to that she was going to leave last
week but the boat didn't come I could
drink anybody else care for one I could
use some coffee Oh me aren't you idea
sign the door you all right doctor he
just ripped my trousers that's all are
you sure that's all and I said I'm
completely aware of a doctor that was a
stupid waste of ammunition everyone I'm
a clean mess let's go for them in there
how did they get in to that kitchen
window I wrote must be rough he's dead
recorded every symptom and reaction
right up to the moment of his death
Jerry turn down one of those dreams and
cover him up sure sure gregus of color I
am and I'll cover him you cover me but
who covers you shut up we can get on the
mantle slavery are you stop sniveling
thinks everything is trying to get a
Sally here
don't take them all to dig around this
you're right I'll tell me where else
they're digging too
come on
come here to barricade those walls okay
we'll pass them in his crate up over
there that routes our last chain
yes these chemical drums us as tanks
individual tanks all right it'll work
it'll work but these drums are too tall
for the base if the shoes don't push it
over the wind will not realize them
together hey are there any more
more slack his stroke and put it on that
latch so we can read from the ground
alright
alright to the beach where's Jerry
there's a poor devil hope he makes it if
you can't leave he's not responsible for
himself go now
everybody ready I'm gonna open a date
ready Freddy okay here they come
and what's the matter your size drag you
wanna rest you tired go see everyone go
see how can I did see it would you say
she says she's all right he's keeping
their eyes closed all right keep your
eyes closed they can't get at you
through the slit this empty drum is too
heavy for her I can barely hold up
myself I'll be all right in a minute
alright you walk i'll drag for a while
don't get the head gone under they'll
flip us over
check your foot is there a scratch
keep moving let's go
we'll hit the water soon
didn't sound like they're following us
anymore
we better work deeper
have I turned out okay let's swim for it
okay
where I missed our unfortunate we are
safe aren't we I'm in the store sure she
wrote out the first half all right
that's always the roughest anyway
writing an anchor of a chance to learn a
little more about that Swedish accent 24
hours there'll be one shrew left on the
island and he'll be dead of starvation
an excellent example of overpopulation
well you know something doctor what's
that I'm not gonna worry about
overpopulation just yet
you