attention please aoa flight 19 x London
to New York will be slightly delayed
passengers are advised to check in
baggage and await further announcements
attention s'il vous plait vol uh-oh I'm
bored is no fix a destination to New
York so Alberto they became a minute
late passage a sorta busy dovish is
truly oh my gosh inter tompa not
emotionally
oh come on dude is no mystery about it
it's a selsun motor not a human female
I'll put check and see what's wrong it's
an instrument it won't lie to you
hey oh x4 New York is now open for 12
all right mr. Holcomb they're all set to
go sir you'll be the party lounge for
thank you flight 19 x which is x rating
partner spot a lock for you so actually
it's an extra flying you'll have the
bird practically to yourself this true
yep I surely would like that let me help
you with that ma'am No thank you I can
manage hello I'm Schuyler O'Neill has my
husband checked in yet that he has mrs.
O'Neill he just went to the cargo office
Oh fine obviously when I get my passport
out we'll take care of that boy sir not
to worry thank you it's a lot of fuel
for such a light passenger list we
expecting a hurricane you're pretty
heavy on cargo mr. manifest
architectural features 11,000 pounds
what the devil could that be in this
case part of an abbey what I kid you not
the guys shipping it told me names
O'Neill fact he's board your flight it's
a chapel room from some ol English Abby
even an altar he's gonna set it up in a
place he's building on Long Island final
call for AOE 19
New York boarding at gate 12 don't worry
about it now Acacio simply an era and
pull up one more dish new things for you
now you're sure you're sure I'm on the
extra flight the cargo flight it's all
taken care of mrs. Peter thank you and
mrs. fender what you please leave the
door kiya Damon he's coming with me in
the hole madam can't don't worry it's
very comfy down there and he'll enjoy it
but you have very few passengers on this
flight please can t come with me prick
relations madam
you understand don't you Damon I have to
hmm but I'll hold you personally
responsible for his safety nice well mr.
O'Neill your wife went on ahead she
should be on board like that lady who
was just here is she an hour flight mrs.
pinder yes do you know her huh yes
number seven hmm
hey you ready for this ten passengers
and nine students is you know just the
two of us come on up front huh Jenkins
says they all go first cabin okay
but what happened I don't know hey away
control one-niner x-ray say what is with
the weather no change one night I
surface when northeast six knots are you
kidding we've just been hit in the face
by some of the North Pole see again
wanna thank you one Niner I think we
just had a lesson on the famous not that
he believed English summer weather
you
and should be fine I'm sorry it's quite
all right good heavens US flight 19 x
that's boring right now sir yes it would
be what it
it's an hour
seat belts no smoking flight attendants
check check check you just made it yes
sir gosh Oh any seat just let me sit
back thank you very much
let's get the show on the road
place the mask over your face and
breathe normally until your advice is
not necessary now in accordance federal
safety regulations the cabin stewardess
will demonstrate the use of the life
jackets which you located under the
seats the one
rotate d 2 plus 10 do a 100 explain
you're telling you your first Rannoch
direct and j-3 Bravo route climb
maintain flight level 370 squawker to
100 the party frequency will be 1 2 4.1
bullet raja a 0 a 1 x rays glitter to
your place and make direct route
maintain flight level 370 spot to 100
departure 12 4.1 rata 103 here is
correct
you know I think maybe I'm gonna put
some black stone on the floor here
around the altar very nice if you're
planning to use it for a bar that's a
little nasty isn't it dear yes I suppose
it is I guess I'm just bloody tired of
the old business it's your ancestral
chapel we're riding on darling over a
hundred dollars a mile you can afford it
Alan it's fortunate I can't afford to
save something ancient and beautiful
when your family estates are becoming
condominiums in parking lots well maybe
that isn't all bad you really want a
quarrel don't you I'm sorry I I guess
I'm just a little edgy tonight
here you go oh thank you kindly haven't
I heard of you somewhere mr. Holcomb gee
honey my business manager to be
disappointed if you hadn't I've been
starring in the Western in Italy my last
when rimrock made 15 mil no I think I
must have confused you with someone else
mr. own here I thought it only fair to
warn you that I'm on board miss spender
I thought we had all this out in English
Court and I came prepared to try it
again in an American court mrs. O'Neil I
cannot believe that you would acquiesce
in the uprooting of these priceless
relics please leave me out of it secret
secret I heartily regarded as that you
really don't know what's down in that
hole do you I'm sorry mrs. pinder but
this forward section is reserved for
first-class passengers you'll regret it
that's all I'm going to say
i'm sorry mr. i hope that part of it was
over as a cause for every crank these
days but if i'm gonna be attacked by a
lady crusader I need a drink come on
thanks I'll stay here you know you're
really a barrel of laughs tonight I'm
had you know find somebody in the bar
who is Alan I'm sorry
oh why don't you cool it huh okay I
don't care you know this sounds a little
off naturally closer to heaven the more
discordant oh man why don't you just put
me on your back and walk us across the
water there was a time no I'd sink
sir you know that's against the rules
Johnny sounds like I'm bored
everything okay mom well my little girl
is just a teeny bit nervous but I'm sure
when she's expected it's okay Annie I'll
tell the captain no more bumps tonight
what do you see Frank clear all round
negative on build up beats me with that
one could have been seat belts captain
save them they pay to walk around this
flying hotel let's let him live a little
Cornwall 26 hmm it's three minutes late
must be a headwind building they didn't
tell us about
something wrong man it's just this
gadget likely just the phones let's try
some others oh no please don't my
pleasure my name's Steve leave yours is
Sheila am I right spit excuse me Sheila
just get this out of the way here now
I'll put these in here we go right as
rain that ain't Dave Brubeck I'll buy
you a drink hey Ben ain't Brubeck dog
karna fight on owe you a drink I'll
think about it pard maybe later you got
a deal
how does it read on your side miles from
Cornwall sun at 24 correction online now
at 25 same here so i guess they must be
working all right airspeed i read 630
little gyros check fine so what do you
make it impossible my last video are
recovering ground about like a lady
bicycle rider we must be bucking a
headwind of 620 miles an hour there's no
such wind that's right there's no such
wind so what are we doing right smack in
it
one will Senate a 0 a one-nighter x-ray
had assigned altitude 370 we got a small
problem Roger aoa one-niner Apes right
we see thought we'd fouled up here in
your position we haven't changed
position in 10 minutes problem seems to
be a jet stream dead on like it 600 plus
600 come again we show winds aloft your
vicinity westerly at 70 knots Conwell
Center I'm gonna maintain my heading for
two minutes more not out of it then
request clearance for 180 back to London
put that in the work so let me ask you
something do you think we should let our
first class tourists upstairs I don't
know I've got one who's packing a flash
oh no karate yeah feels funny tonight
feels very funny Hey lay off that oh
yeah you know how I hate flying coming
up two minutes mark
Conwell Center one night our x-ray how
am I for that turn you are cleared
one-niner Thank You Cornwall starting
180 turn in one minute here you are mr.
Farley
your fellow book this slider oh just the
car go home must have cost you plenty
hey charge by the pound for this gun
afraid I don't remember my people set it
up you have to ask we can't afford it
right glen farley caledonia we never met
but I know you you gave me a bid on a
teller built down in Orlando you were
too high on that I didn't hire you yes I
made seven million dollars in the last
three years I'll tell you I'd know how
much this airplane was costing me to the
center well I'm an architect not a
businessman you're telling me
the stuff you're shipping uh I heard the
woman downstairs giving it to you what
is the part of a church there remains of
an old Abbey it's been my wife's family
for centuries we met a little resistance
when we took it pay it all the way
canapes excuse me hold your Adson watch
the miles go by we've got a 600 plus
tail one now let's see we ought to knock
off a ground mile in about three seconds
we're not moving
we've got a 600-mile tailwind and not
moving when Wallace Center heyo a
one-nighter x-ray confirms quark setting
at alpha 2 100 we have your big one
Niner the devil you doing up there
flying in circles your position
unchanged when will center stand by one
Niner what's up wait caught in a win
like none there ever was we've done a
full turn around and it's still smacking
our teeth somehow Cornwall center aoa
one-niner x-ray we'd like a right turn
2090 and permission to descend to 260
it's funny the lights aren't moving what
to kill you ugly illusion motionless
suspended I run my get nor did you know
this happens to be the summer solstice
Midsummer's Eve
is that good or bad depends if you're a
witch it's a night for bonfires
incantation sounds like fun beautiful
moon tonight huh what is this turn RT
honor what's going on well I don't think
there's any problem I fly my own plane
sweetheart the custom jet they keep
changing altitude and power set now be a
good girl go find out what's happening
tell me are you a very good architect
toomas doing it I'm oh very successful
architect is that the same thing yeah I
used to think so you tell me now are you
a very good model how did you know I was
a model that's it easy one were you
dressed try some drinks magazine whole
package Touche
what's going on in here anything we
should know you can don't panic we've
just got a little bit of a problem my
god it seems as if we're caught up in
this crazy kind of jet stream it's as if
we're hung up here in a hook what does
that mean
you were right mr. Farley there is a
slight problem but nothing we can't
handle I'll let you know as soon as I
can
no I'm not gonna try and figure it out
it can't happen but it has a wind or
whatever it is is affecting this plane
only just us I don't get it it's like
being in a whirlpool we can't move in
any direction six hours and 20 minutes
of fuel left we're burning it up let's
reduce to two hundred we're not going
any place anyhow let Morgan know what's
happening and tell her that breakout
more drinks for the passages all I want
okay
Shh
what happened she fainted I think she's
six years hey champ I'll get a cold
cloth excuse me please I'm a medical
doctor doctor in color hey even a sancti
spiritus casa turn on kavita spirit or
ba ba
latin is it not yes yes is it serious no
merely an aesthetical episode of some
sort perhaps what would help her most
isn't food what am i speaking only of
myself Oh a Maya right we really are
running behind is it all right that I go
yes of course I said like the lady's
husband present when she returns to
consciousness he'd be so kind as to look
after her your subconscious she's a
beautiful woman isn't she or are you
just working on a Getwell prayer pool I
was just thinking I might become a
doctor why why not I can be anything I
want and they have stuff power over
women it's that paternal thing except
doctors are free to use it
what's the matter you don't look well
yourself I'm just sick from watching you
bleed
Oh what happened to him Oh what did I do
nothing just faint if it's it's a doctor
on board he says you're all right
there's nothing serious I'm sorry to be
such a bloody nuisance not a law gives
me something else to do besides get
drunk I'm Paul Cove Alec oh thank you
mr. Corrigan I'm grateful uh has anyone
told my husband yes the doctor went far
did you know that you were speaking
Latin that's impossible I've never
studied Latin
sorry toots were you a good time oh come
on get off it will ya I've never known
you to faint from lack of attention I've
never fainted period so if i were you i
should not leave her alone tonight I
don't intend to not that it's any of
your concern Alan please excuse me I
presumed
did I tell you someone cried for help
smart girl will you let me a testing
wish here try this yeah all right we
have you been assisted this emergency
door on top it's cold down there come on
up come on yeah all right there's really
nothing to worry about folks it's just
your run-of-the-mill airplane elevator
accident blowout in the cargo hold
blowout it's freezing and there's a
wyndham hold it negative on that what
negative I tell you there's ice down
there I saw it there's a wind howling no
way baby we did have a blog you know it
zero flat then where did the ice coat
from the wind are you saying it came
from inside the plane but I heard
something in the elevator when gonna
take a look I'll be right there Barney
you pull yourself together I'm gonna
need you
Sheila
my turn to say sorry right what is it
I'm frightened I think I maybe I keep
hearing strange things voice is some
kind of chanting I can't understand and
then they caught me sometimes over and
over you've been under a lot of stress
it's my fault I guess you don't believe
me don't you I mean you you don't think
I'm ill
I don't know what to think
howdy captain what's up not leaving us
are you yeah we're gonna take a bus and
leave the driving to you
mr. O'Neill yes you don't have anything
in that shipment of yours we don't know
about do you pretty me no I don't know
yet you don't have anything live of
course not why just curious about a
little problem we have down there sorry
captain um you say anything wrong Thomas
nothing serious
captain if you're going below would you
be kind enough to speak to my dog his
name is Damon you know were you sure of
course
well Jim all right I'll get it open
Oh
I jack
look at this something like moss on the
bulkhead hey
it's frozen
Oh
help me word it stewardess
hey Jim he's dead flight engineer he
says he's dead how did it happen she's
frozen the wind a flight deck gotta get
into the fight dang
please don't mention anything that's
happening we must avoid
what happened the flight engineer has
been killed Jim's dead water something
in the cargo hold chillin chillin what
mr. captain gonna be okay as far as his
physical world is concerned yes as for
the rest not sure cuz I'm going on I
want to know what an elevator still
stuck it's the flight engineer he's dead
what something Awful's happened back
there
oh here try this oh look at that what is
it
mr. Farley oh you can't prison your ass
feel handle is baby you gotta get down
splitsville don't play games with me
honey regulations don't count now your
flight engineers dead your captain's
hurt and there's something happening
this airplane I don't know what you're
doing about it but you know you some
kind of a blowhole you're doing anything
about it there's no blow outs if it's
show on my instrument I don't give a
damn about your instrument do something
you're the one who's gonna do something
funny ya know doc what's happened to me
but is sometimes known as shock you call
this shock that is somewhat more
difficult your armors been frozen to the
point of being burned can you understand
that miss wick suppose the instruments
were all if it wasn't blowout at the
loss of oxygen it could have caused
hallucinations I respectfully captain
your arms not a generalized condition it
could not relate simply to the absence
of oxygen it's more specific as though
something incredibly cold it touched you
there I'll get my bag
right dry Cornwall or use the radios on
what about the backups
they're out to
excuse me what's happening back here he
heard this is a little trouble at the
plane you do know mr. O'Neill you know
very well those things which this man is
taken removed from the soil where they
have rested for thousands of years Oh
lady whatever are you talking about they
are sacred things they have their own
powers that is what is happening to us
oh come on I'm not gonna listen to this
oh do you know what she's talking about
the dro otter mrs. pendant of course the
Druids believe it or not here we are in
the last half of the 20th century under
these circumstances and what are we
worrying about the grotesque practices
of a primitive cult that was stamped out
before the coming of Christ not entirely
mr. choleric there are still drew it yes
of course there there's still witches
and Satanists and those who believe that
jimsonweed can make them immortal
there's never been any shortage of the
idiot things to believe in our idiots
today chloride what if true it's got to
do with what's going on here everyone on
that Heath knows the legend they've
faded for hundreds of years inside the
altar at Grove Abby was a druid
sacrificial stone that stone is on this
plane hey lady you trying to tell me
that a piece of rocks got something to
do with killing the flight engineer the
abbey was built on the sacred grove of
the Druids a place where they committed
human sacrifices to the ancient gods of
darkness cold wind the old ones they
cough and every hundred years at the
summer solstice they still need summer's
eve
poor you said that was tonight for all I
know it's Halloween how do you know I
was stuff anyway well if it's any of
your business I like to look at ruins
preferably religious Bruins why don't
you just knock it off confession is
supposed to be good for the soul isn't
it boy is a priest was very definitely
was they have enough trouble without
sticking them with me okay okay so he he
struck out as a priest so what what's
that got to do with us well all this
crazy business this lady's talking about
demons and spirits and stuff on this
airplane well I'd sure like to get some
answers and I quick perhaps you're too
eager for answers sometimes there are
none the only magic I know is it man can
resist gravity and fly at 37,000 feet I
hope that makes you happy it hasn't me
what would I'm gonna open a bottle of it
right now it might not make me happy but
it will amuse me to think of all of you
back here worrying about your lives as
though they were of some importance
he doesn't matter we have to find out
what once
nullus whatever it is is Becker so let's
get everybody up front away from it
Oh miss nobody goes back there until
this whole thing is cleared up your ass
and nobody is everybody here where's a
little girl come on honey we have to
move come on
hi baby I'll get everything you run up
front now okay
Oh
put it down right here watch your head
so against the blankets it's very nearly
frozen it's all right sweetheart it's
all right come on over here with me come
on the blade break it up there's a crack
ho structural break it's inside the
plane I understand we're stuck up here
how to demand you money back wish I
could find something funny at all this
stick around maybe you will where you
beyond fear you just drunk both but if I
were you I'd worry more about your
fellow passengers then whatever it is
you're brought on board come on Oh
Sheila Sheila what is it you're hearing
something out you haha my wife has been
hearing voices but she was treated for
nervous exhaustion a few weeks ago what
are you here I don't know voices they
keep calling my name
it stopped do you remember what you said
when when you fainted
woody igneous and espíritus yes I heard
that one of the voices what does it mean
well do you know her don't you it's from
a black mass a prayer to the devil do
that thing back there my white is
imagining things that's all she's
hearing voices Paul says she was
reciting a black mass sounded like it I
was probably wrong i was aware scholar
than I was a priest it was a man's voice
wasn't it yes do you know who that was
my beer in 1407 Lord Canton the owner of
the land on which the abbey stood your
ancestor was burnt at the stake for
heresy and murder he had worshipped the
druid God's offered human sacrifices
members of your own family and now the
old ones want your the sacrifice they
demand maybe she's right what else can
it be everything's gone crazy you know
all about these things you were a priest
weren't you what can we do you know what
a priest mr. friar you want a parachute
don't you laugh at me
feel lousy drunk what good en e way the
sacrifice the child where's the child
you've gone crazy no please perhaps we
could offer this you mean like voodoo
you want to offer the door instead of
her god that's hideous we need to dress
it will need something of mrs. O'Neil's
you can't do this stay out of it but I
understand what's happening here I'm the
only one that does I'm warning you it
won't work you'll only make things worse
it's real work it's worth trying
anything is is this yours wait a minute
you leave my wife statement you got us
into this youbrought that thing aboard
now stay on or you'll get hurt I wanna
fuck me on it
yes will do we need something more you
know death are you too good too holy for
this to holy
Adam Annja you of all people should know
better than that
we need some of her hair no mr. doesn't
matter let them it doesn't matter and
some of your fingernails I know he
called these
hey
yeah take another pain killer might as
well know you saving them
I know what you're thinking about what
could I do she wouldn't let me help mr.
O'Neill I would never dream of sitting
in judgment on another
it's working it's working
I heard them down there charming bunch
of people I think that thing only wants
me they'll believe anything mail that
offers a low barest hope of survival and
they'll do anything no matter how stupid
or question hello satya in all his glory
do you really hate yourself that much I
always wait for that the defrocked
priest delight of the armchair analyst
where did you lose your faith I didn't
get lost me I'm frightened can you help
me I'm sorry i'm fresh out aren't you
afraid of dying i gave that up along
with the rest of my emotions I don't
understand you those are only words
words yes we talked a lot my church it
keeps us from asking why we can't have
one side lunge tiny infinitesimal
science sustain us in the darkness to
touch to see father
don't look to me
I have nothing
I have no help
find your way
look adul
it didn't work nothing will you have to
go down there you have no choice why
because it's used they won't you're
afraid of them the old ones because you
think of them as evil but you're wrong
the spirits of nature the force that
holds this plane is as old as the world
itself and aren't you a part of nature
you are as much from the earth is the
Sacred Stones below why should you feel
something here that Sheena there's no
problem you're a tree a rock how simple
it is those feelings you're having your
gut love fear all nothing more than the
stirrings of atoms and molecules what a
pathetic excuse you are a man how do you
set yourself above anything you who
betrayed your own pitiful faith pitiful
mrs. bender and what are you selling
powers that are old when this universe
was young powers that you know more can
withstand in an ignorant Savage
fire mrs. been there is that it no the
way the ancients held off the demons on
Midsummer's Eve they built a bonfire the
highest hill we're at twenty or thirty
thousand that ought to be high enough
and then those poor ignorant savages
would huddle around the light and smoke
pray for the doll at the first shaft of
sunlight demons go back to hell or
wherever it is they come from yes a fire
well fire for the burning of witches
fire will fire work ask her you've given
them hope for nothing we gotta take a
fire
shit me is to be in some sort of coma
you can't burn the plane to save it get
those ventilators up I asked you when is
the sunrise 342 out here I wouldn't
count on seeing it well maybe we could
climb to meet it catch it early as it
comes over the rim of the world so what
is this rim of the world jazz we climb
we burn more fuel ready if there's any
chance at all we ought to try it
you
the
going to full power
come on downstairs you've got to help
come on
the pillars get just Phyllis there's
more like you're upstairs get it paper
over there
savages yes frightened savages waiting
to be led and they will be led the
darkness are a delight be my guest what
did I have that strength of purpose but
i have only words and they are far
beyond that now
that's it
there's nothing more we can do you want
to know what's gonna happen to you just
look in there is one more thing
it's none of this one life against how
many all of us the doll worked fire to
work it just wasn't enough
get back back
fine you gotta go back there you gotta
do it for the rest of us
ok
stay on this path
oh yeah please
Oh
you
soon boss we're going to make it
oh I see
whoa decompression
alright everybody we've reached an
altitude where it's safe to breathe you
can take your masks off now
feeling better hmm see here's gonna be
all right
I don't know this is pinder mr. Hill
what happened
I don't
my beautiful talk
I'm sorry
you
cornwall center hey yo a one-niner x-ray
please give us priority clearance for
emergency landing with full standby
Roger aoa one-niner x-rayed you want
clear experiment landing negative
cornwall negative no instruments
I don't understand why did he do it
for those people
you talk to arrest why
perhaps somehow it was a final act of
faith there are Devils must also be gods
I don't know I have no thoughts
wrong