Jessie, I don't think we should date anymore.
What?
I don't think we should date anymore.
Why?
Look, it's summer break. It's time for a transition.
But we were supposed to go to the movies tonight.
Sarah?
I just don't think it's a good idea.
But, I love-
No you don't.
I've always said you were too nice. You need to be meaner.
It's my nature. I can't be mean.
Perhaps with that acid you just bought, you could reprogram yourself.
Wait, what acid?
Jessie bought a sheet of acid after Sarah broke up with him.
Isn't that like fifty hits?
One hundred.
How much did it cost?
Four hundred dollars for the whole sheet. He said it was a friend of a friend discount. I just had
to promise I wasn't dealing.
Are you dealing it?
No. I'm just sharing it with some friends back in St Louis.
My buddy's friend took a dose for Mardi Gras and he disappeared.
Disappeared? For real?
He painted his face half black, half white, like down the center.
He erupted, like stopped talking. And then he walked off.
Where did he go?
He just, disappeared.
Why are you all trying to freak me out?
So you're careful with that LSD.
How about sharing it with some friends here? Will you sell me a fish? And Maya. Oh, just sell one
each to us.
Each fish is 4 hits. I don't want to run out.
I don't want any.
You're not going to run out.
I'll give you 2 fish. I'm not a dealer though.
Why are you giving me this?
Let's take it.
No way. I have a final left tomorrow afternoon.
Come on. It's twenty hours away and this will only last like 9 hours. Maybe ten.
No way.
Do you guys have a cigarette?
No, I don't smoke.
Hello?
Hi, mom. Yeah, I just crossed over Lake Ponchatrain. I'm going to get off I-55 at Jackson and
get on route 61. I just need to get some extra time to unwind on the road. I think it would be fun
to take the old highway. I know about the stoplights. Nobody's going to murder me. No, they're
not going to bury me in an earthen dam. You've got to stop watching those documentaries, mom.
Ok, I think I'm going to get off now.
No, get off the phone, not the road. Ok, I promise if I get tired I'll stop at a motel. Alright. I love
you. Bye.
Hello?
Hi, Sarah.
No, I'm driving. I didn't see your text.
Um.
Home. Back to St. Louis. You told me you didn't want to see me anymore. You broke up with
me during sex. We're not broken up? We are? Yes, I still want to be friends. Ok, I'm sorry I
didn't say goodbye.
Goodbye.
I hate myself. Jessie you gotta be stronger. You're weak! Be tough! Nice. Doesn't. Work. Fuck!
Fuck!
Hello.
Whatcha doin?
I'm just looking for something to eat.
No-no-no. What are you doin?
I'm having a bad day and driving to see my family.
You talk like you're from a big city.
We'll it's bigger than this but, it's nothin-
You don't like my city?
I didn't say that-
It was the way you said it... Chief.
I'm just gonna look for something to eat.
Get me somethin'.
What?
Somethin' to eat.
Here. Buy me this.
And... this.
And this. You'll like this. I like it. We'll both like it.
But, I've never eaten pork rinds before.
Yeah, you have.
No, I haven't.
They're good.
I can't buy you anything else.
That's all I want.
Buy me a drink.
Okay.
No, I can't buy you anything else.
That's it.
No, I'm not gonna pay for what you just put on the counter there.
Why not?
Because I told you I wasn't gonna buy you anything else when we were standing over there.
Oh.
And I'm not buying you anything else.
No, not the bag of fish.
It's on the counter.
He put it there, not me. Do you know him?
She's my cousin.
Ok, so who's putting the fish back?
I'm not. He put it there.
Hey. City boy. Someone's been hanging around the old schoolhouse. You should come over.
I really gotta hit the road. Sorry.
Behind the schoolhouse. Be there.
He's not my cousin.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
We've been working on your car.
Preventative maintenance.
Did you guys move any of the wires, or mess with the engine or anything?
No. Just cleaning.
Yeah, we're not the mechanics. They are.
I haven't been talking to them. Maya has.
No, I'm not taking these. I have to get up to St. Louis tonight.
Just wait a day, and chill with us.
No, my family and friends are expecting me to arrive tonight.
Keep them, seriously. I'm only going to get into trouble.
Let's hear you turn her over.
What?
She said, 'let's hear you turn her over'.
Alright, let's hear you start her up.
Start her up! Let's hear what you got.
Well, it's not turning over, that's the thing.
Whooooohooooweee, what a nice lookin' car.
Oh yeah, my uncle had a car like this. My cousin, he bought it off him one day to use in the
derby. Ooooooh they did smash him up! This here car is real solid.
I said, it was a nice lookin' car.
You from Missouri?
Yeah, Missouri.
Misery?
Yeah. St. Louis, Missouri.
A city boy.
City boy, what'ch you doin out here?
Just drivin' home.
Ciiiiiitttty boooooy
I live way out of the city, like near farms.
C-C-C-cit-cit-cit-city-city boy
Start your engine.
Okay.
Pump the gas.
No, no no no, you'll flood your engine. Hold down the gas.
Sounds like there's somethin jammin' up your engine.
How the fuck did this get into your air filter?
What the fuck!?  Those mother-fuckers. I'm fucked!
Chillax dude.
Hey ya'll, this detour's over man. Let's continue with our Sunday fun day.
Aw yeah, we got to go.
Sorry babe.
Bye.
Chief, I gotta go. Just get all your little sex toys outta the air filter and put the cap back on. If
you need me, you wanna hang out and play music, just come around back to the trailer park.
Can you take us to the tree of life?
Ugh, the tree of life! Thank you Jessie.
You from Missouri?
Yep. Missouri. It's a small town near the Mississippi river.
Hey, we ain't far from Mississippi neither. I'm Paul.
I'm Jessie.
And I am Luke.
It's a sweet ride, what's wrong with her?
Somebody put beads and shit in my engine.
In the gas tank?
No, the air filter.
That's weird. Let's turn her over.
Hey, I'm gonna go get some A/C man.
Alright. Hey, don't mess with my cousin.
I won't.
Hey, so turn it over.
Hey, you see, that's why you're not supposed to put Mardi Gras beads in your air filter. It's a
good thing I got to you first Missouri. Them bad boys would invite you behind the old school.
The old school?
That's where they bash folks heads in and takes their money.
What?
Sometimes they don't take their money, they just bash their heads in for sport. Let's go check
the fuse box.
What about the police? What do they do about the bashing?
Police avoid this place unless something exciting happens.
Yep, this car ain't gonna start. It looks like someone got to your fuses and your wires too.
Well this isn't good.
No, it ain't.
Great.
It ain't that bad Missouri.
My mom is gonna kill me.
You goin' to see your mom in Missouri?
Yeah, she told me not to get off the interstate.
See, I don't listen to my mom neither. She's a mean bitch.
Well, my mom is not really that mean. She's just always gettin' in my business and I fuckin hate
it when she's right.
Where you drivin' in from?
New Orleans.
New Orleans, Bourbon Street! Boozin' it out, smokin' that weed, girls showin' their titties for
beads, right? Titties for beads.
Well, there's more to New Orleans than just Bourbon Street. I only went to Bourbon my
freshman year.
Fresh, for what?
College, I go to college in New Orleans.
Got any weed?
No, sorry.
Damn. I knew you were smart when I saw you in this SUV. Wish I could visit New Orleans.
It's really not that far.
I ain't got no money to travel. Jackson's an hour away. I ain't never been there.
It doesn't cost much money. Just get in the car and go.
That's exactly what a rich kid would say.
I'm not rich!
It's a nice ride.
This car isn't that ride. Everybody in my school drives much nicer things than this.
This is a nice car
'Til it broke down.
That's true. Is there a car shop around here?
Not on Sunday. I can get it towed. My buddy owns a wrecker.
Can I borrow your phone?
I ain't got no phone, chief. Guess you ain't rich.
I have a phone, it just broke.
You are rich.
I'm not rich! You know where I can find a phone?
My cousin works in the store, she'll let you use the phone, she's real nice.
Okay, I'll ask her. Thank you.
Hi, my car broke down outside and your cousin suggested I come in and ask to use your phone.
He's not my cousin.
No, not the guy who conned me into buying all that stuff. Paul.
You know your cousin Paul, that stupid fucker.
Oh, no, Paul's my cousin. I don't know how but, oh he's married to my cousin Mary or
somethin'.
So, can I use the phone?
I'm already over my limit but you can use the store's phone.
Well, it's long distance.
So don't go over a minute. But, you know what, don't because my boss will kill me if he sees
the charge. Use my phone but don't go over a minute, okay?
Okay, thank you. Hi mom, no everything's fine, I'm just callin' to let you know that my car
broke down in Mississippi. Yeah, everyone's real nice.
I won't be if you go over a minute.
Come on, my phone.
Look, I'm just calling to let you know I'm gonna be late. I'll probably have to leave the car to
get repaired and - no don't worry- okay, love you.
Thanks.
That was sweet, tellin' your mom you love her.
I guess.
Well, what you gonna do?
I need to find a way back to Missouri.
Misery?
Missouri. Is there a car rental place or a bus station or train depot?
Yeah, there's a bus station. It's, I've taken it before.
Where is it?
The other end of town.
How would I check the schedule?
You could call 'em. Here, it's already programmed into my phone.
Thanks.
Hi, I was wondering if there's a bus leaving Cleveland, Mississippi to St. Louis. Yeah, tonight.
8pm. Okay, can I buy my tickets there? Okay great, thank you.
It's all good?
Yeah, it's all good. What did you say your name was?
Sara.
What?
That's my ex-girlfriends name. We just broke up.
Oh, I'm sorry honey, that sucks.
The whole car break down thing has really distracted me from all that stuff, so.
What's your name?
Oh, it's Jessie. Thanks again for the phone and everything.
And it's Sara without an h.
Oh, that's better. All the evil Sarah's spell it with an h. Thanks again.
Boy, he did a number on this.
My cousin let you use the phone?
Yeah, she did. She was real nice.
She's a whore.
What? Dude that's your cousin.
Don't you think I know?
So anyway, I just talked to my mom and she's freaking out. I need to get back to Missouri
today.
Well it's gonna be somethin'. It's gonna be some trick gettin' this car started.
Yeah, I think I'm just gonna leave it here to get repaired.
Have somebody to pick you up?
No, I don't have anybody to pick me up. What I'm wondering is -well I'm wondering- if you
could get your buddy to tow my car to his shop and then you can take me to the bus station.
Oh, I can get your car towed, but I ain't got no way of puttin' you at the station.
Someway, any way man. You're the only guy around here I trust.
Ah that's nice of you to say Missouri. You have my mom to thank for that. She beat it into me.
Not with a belt, with the Lord.
Okay, I know I don't have any weed to trade, but-
I like weed.
I do have this.
You wanna trade me a scrap of paper?
No, it's acid.
Acid-acid? Like in that Dennis Hopper movie where they ride the motorcycles in the cemetery?
Exactly.
Maybe I could get Luke to get you a ride. Can you get one for him?
Yeah!
We gonna get you to the bus station, Missouri!
Awesome, thank you!
Oh Jessie, we gonna have us some real fun man!
So, you will bring me to the bus station?
Ah, I dunno. I am kind of busy, you know.
Man, you ain't busy.
Am too. I'm still trainin' for my next fight.
Quit Fuckin' with Missouri.
Shit yeah I'll drive you man, I wanna try some of that shit.
Can we have it right now?
No, that's not a good idea.
Why not?
Cause it's really strong.
How you mean?
You know my friends who took it last night?
Uh-huh.
They're the ones who put the beads and shit in my engine.
Oh, don't worry Missouri, it's cool!
No, you guys will really drive off the road!
Relax Missouri. I am a terrific driver.
He is.
I don't know.
Okay. Luke, we're just gonna have to wait a minute. Let's get everything loaded into Luke's
car. We're gonna get you to the bus station.
Where should I take it?
My house. Follow me.
Let me close that up for you there Missouri so nobody sticks anymore teddy bears in there.
All set.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Well, here she is. My kingdom.
He's real proud.
Yes, I am.
I'll get, I got it Missouri.
I'll be right back, ya'll. I'm gonna get somethin' from my trailer.
Alright.
Hey Missourah, you need to meet my wife. Come on, I'll introduce you.
Luke said he was just gonna be a second.
This will only take a second. Hey, how often do we meet a city boy?
I still gotta get to the bus station.
We're gonna get you to the station. Come on, you'll like her. She's a peach.
Alright kids, snack time. Snack time.
Mary! Oh, don't even pay this no mind. We don't even have a dog. Mary! Hey, where's Mary?
Mary, where's my sweetness?
Are y'all about to fight? Who is that?
That's Missouri. This is my sister Rose Marie. She and all her kids live in our trailer.
Hi.
Where's Mary?
Y'all are about to fight. Alright, come on, get in back kids. Back of the trailer. Go, move it. Go.
Eatin' all my munchy foods.
One on the way, we're not even sure if it's hers. No, not sure.  There she is.
What do you want Paul?
Hey, baby.
Who the fuck is that?
I wanted to introduce you to my friend.
Does he have a name?
Missourah. We've been callin' him Missourah 'cause that's where he's from.
My name is Jessie.
Hi, Jessie. What the fuck are you doin' here?
Well, my car broke down and Paul is-
Mary, this is our guest, why are you bein' such a bitch?
Bitch? Imma show you bitch. Y'all get the fuck out of my trailer.
Whoa, Mary, what did Jessie do to you?
Jessie did not do anything to me. It is you randomly bringing strangers into our home. I'm sorry
Jessie.
Really, it's okay. Paul's just gonna take me to the bus station and then I'll be gone.
No baby I'm sorry, because I'm projecting my anger for Paul towards you.
Projectin'? Mary what's that all about? I don't even know what that means.
It means I'm directin' my anger towards you, towards poor little Jessie, here. And for that, I
apologize.
No worries, really, it's ok. Really.
Look I'm takin' him to the bus station and then you don't ever have to see him again okay?
Okay, no you makin' me out to be the big bitch and that is not me. See what you turn me into? It
was nice to meet you Jessie.
Likewise.
That's my wife.
Hey, Mary!
You need to stay away from my husband.
Acid, please.
After the bus station.
No, now.
What you talkin' about Mary?
That kid in there, Jessie. You better not be plannin' on robbin' him.
Now listen Mary, we ain't doin' nothin' but takin' that kid to the bus station, you hear?
Yeah, well this was a nice place until you moved in here.
Mary, how're you gonna say that to me? I'm a good person.
Yeah.
That's just unfair. Ya'll ready?
Yeah, we're ready.
In a minute. The acid, please.
I really don't think it's a good idea to take it right now.
I understand your concerns Missouri, but if you want a ride city boy, you're gonna have to give
us what you promised.
Yup.
It's just really strong. I don't think you'll be able to drive.
No, for sure, we'll get you there.
I just really need to get to the bus station.
Is it really that terrible to give us the acid before we leave?
No, but my concern is ya'll will take it and trip out and won't be able to drive me.
Now, from what I understand, it does take a couple of hours for it to hit.
I heard it was an instant.
No, man.
Almost an instant?
Almost.
I've never taken it but according to my friends it takes about 30 minutes.
Well there you go, the bus station's only about ten minutes away. That's perfect.
Come on.
Do you have a scissors?
Well sure, I can find some.  Rose Marie where your kids put them scissors at? Oh, bingo.
Here you go. Careful, sharp.
Look at that little fish.
There you go.
Here's one.
My turn.
Put it on your tongue like that.
Like that?
Like that. There you go.
You're not takin' one?
No, I mean I'm gonna be hangin' out at the bus station all day.
Come on now, Missouri.
Yeah, come on.
Come on.
Come on, man.
It'll be fun!
Come on.
Okay, I'll take half.
He gonna take half.
Save some for later. There you go. Nice, alright.
Alright, on three we're gonna do it together.
Alright.
One, two, three.
The bus station, please.
Let's go.
Gotta perm my maw-maw's hair tonight, but I'm gonna hit you up.
Hey, hey, hey, where ya'll headed?
Takin' Missouri to the bus station, like I told you.
Why ya'll look like you got into somethin'?
Nothin' got us into.
I just need to get home.
Well when you get bad you need to clean up your fuckin' mess in our home. Excuse the
language, Jessie.
No worries, nice meeting you.
See how sweet he is? Paul. Polite.
Fuck Mary, why you always gotta be bustin' my nuts? Bye.
I hate this place.
I despise this place.
I dunno it seems nice. All the neighbors are friendly. My neighbors ignore me back home.
Sounds better than this crap old life.
Yup.
It looks closed.
Maybe they're tryna-they got the lights off-tryna save electricity or somethin'.
Or hiding.
Why would they be hidin'?
I don't know. A surprise of some sorts.
Why?
I'm gonna go check it out.
I know you've seen the movie. It's got Dennis Hopper and that guys been in everything. He was
in that scary movie where he comes to the door -that marine movie with Tom Cruise- we
watched that at Jezzabel's trailer.
Yeah.
Wasn't that you that hooked up with Jezzabel?
I always hook up with Jezzabel.
Right?
Okay, so slight problem. It only opens 30 minutes before the bus departs.
Well what time's your bus leave?
Eight-oh-clock.
Well it's only noon now.
Just hang with us, we'll bring you back.
Yeah, come on. It'll be fun man.
Okay.
Get in the car.
Luke, I'm startin' to feel it.
You are?
The pavement is shimmerin'.
Oh man, I wanna feel it too!
Maybe I should just wait here.
No man, it's like seven hours away. Come with us, we'll get you there.
There's no way you can drive in seven hours.
I can drive after drinkin' two six-packs, and smokin' some weed.
I can see blowin' wheat, in the gravel.
Holy shit! My windshield just disappeared. No man, it's still there. That was weird.
It's really comfortable back here.
It is? Hold on switch seats with me. No, I liked it better up front. Wait, it is comfortable.
Wow, there isn't a windshield.
Don't hit it. Just touch it.
Wow, this is cool.
My hair feels weird.
Your hair is weird.
You should take your other half.
I should.
Let's roll boys.
You were right, you were right Jessie. It's so good. You're gonna be okay.
He is right, you are our new friend.
I'm glad, you're nice guys.
We are nice guys.
That's what I've been tryna tell everybody. You pretend like you're me.
Hi everybody, I've been workin' all day. Makin the engines. Whoa!
Fuck you man!
What're you honkin' at? We didn't do anything to you.
Takin' acid, and havin' fun.
Watch the road! Where you goin'?
Don't open that, it's bad luck!
Whoa, whoa whoa whoa. You're drivin' like a bat outta hell. This your new boy?
He is indeed.
What's his name?
Missouri.
Jessie.
Welcome Jessie.
Thank you.
You came back.
Alright, alright, alright. Move ya'll. We gotta go to Paul's trailer.
Bye baby.
Bye.
Whoa, whoa, we're here.
I'm sorry Paul.
I'm alright.  Hey cuz, you off work early?
Yeah, I was just fillin' in for Susie.
Ah, that's good.
What's he doin' here?
Missouri?
Jessie. Hey Jessie.
Hey Sara, without an h.
You wanna play against me?
Cool. What game is this?
Ultimate Fighterman
What's he still doin' here?
Missouri? Bus stations closed.
We can't take in anymore people.
Ah be nice, the station's gonna open 30 minutes before the bus leaves.
When does the bus leave?
The bus departs at 8 P.M.
Ya'll went and got drunk?
We ain't drunk, we just in a good mood.
Why?
Because we get to spend more time with our new friend Missouri.
You are all messed up. Outside.
Hey, how'd you get out here?
I have no idea man.
That is really green.
Ow, dick!
Hey look, green, green, green, green, rocks.
Oh, that's purtty.
You guys aren't drunk?
If I move fast enough, look I can move faster than the stick, see?
You aren't drunk?
No.
Nope.
Then what kind of shit did you get into?
Acid.
LSD acid? How the fuck did you get into acid?
Whoa, go get 'em.
I'm getting' 'em. To the head!
Do you know how to ultimate fight?
I'm doin' it baby.
No, in real life.
No, I don't do any kind of fighting.
Luke's an ultimate fighter.
Luke's an ultimate fighter?
You ever seen patterns in the dirt?
Yeah.
See, wait wait, hold still.
No, I see 'em.
It's like one of them ancient civilizations.
It done-it done-
Holy Shit.
It done left its mark.
It's that kid isn't it?
Where did Luke go?
Outside.
What did you give those two fuck-ups? Did you slip them acid?
Mary, Mary, Mary-listen. Missouri did not give us anything we did not want. Did you, no.
No.
You are all fucked up-
I love you Mary.
You are surely,fucked up.
Why, why Mary?
Because that's the nicest thing you've said to me in three years.
How many? You're my lamb. I'm your lamb. Mary, I'm like a little lamb that follows you to
school. I love you Mary.
Mary knows where to go-
Fuck.
For grass and shit.
I follow you home.
I'm going inside, into our house. Do not come back until you're normal.
I'm normal. I'm normal! I'm just enhanced.
Stay out of the house.
I'll show you enhanced-
I feel like, we're in this giant dome.
It's like we're in a room with no walls!
Yeah, yeah no walls. But it's still a room. Our voices are here, wait. Hello?
Hello
Hello?
Echo.
I didn't hear it that time. Did you say it? Echo.
Same time.
Echo!
Echo.
Hi Sara.
Echo!
I want whatever you're on.
It's acid.
Yeah, I want that. It's clean though. It's not laced with anything right?
No, I mean it's clean. My fingers are fluid though.
That's nice. Is it blotter or liquid?
What?
Is it liquid that you put in my eye, or is it blottered?
No, I wouldn't put it on your eye. I put it on my tongue.
So it's blotter.
Yeah.
What image is on it?
A colorful fish.
Fish, cool. So, can I see it?
Sara, you're shimmering, there's like light coming off of you everywhere.
You're fucked up, Jessie, seriously.
Yeah.
Yeah, so.
What?
No, can you give me one?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Here you go.
Put it on my tongue?
Yeah, like a doctor, open up.
Will you be my guide?
Guide? For what?
My trip.
No, Luke!
Tell me I'm the ultimate-ultimate fighter!
You're the ultimate tripped up, tripper.
Luke! That's enough! You're ruinin' my trip!
I'm the ultimate-ultimate trip machine! The mind explosion!
Shit man, what ya'll gettin' into? I want some.
Yeah Luke, what's up with that?
I don't know, but it's awesome!
What is it? Meth?
It can't be meth. I'm on that right now and I'm just wired! They's into somethin' else!
Paul, what is it?
Acid.
Like that motorcycle movie?
Yeah.
Ya'll got acid? Where'd you get it?
From Missouri.
Missouri? When did you go to Missouri?
What you talkin' 'bout Paul, you never left this town.
No, Jessie. He's from Missouri.
Your new boy? From the gas station?
Where is he?
I saw him talkin' to Sara over there.
Were they talkin' talkin'?
I don't know if he was talkin' talkin, but he was speakin' with her.
She's a slut.
Hey! Watch what you say about her, that's my cousin.
That's my cousin too! She's a whore!
What we waitin' for? Come on! Let's go find him.
Here's your shoe baby.
Thank you. Damnit! Quit messin' with me Mary.
Come on Doobs!
Quit, bitch.
Can you see it?
No.
It's been like 30 minutes.
Wait. I just saw something go slower. Yeah, it's bending.
Pretty cool, huh?
Don't stop.
I'm kinda thirsty.
Okay, wait right here. I'll go get us something from the store.
Okay.
That's some good shit!
Hey kid!
There he is! Why are you hidin' Missourah?
We're friendly.
We just wanna get some of your acid.
I don't have anymore acid to give away. It's for my friends.
Well we're your friends.
I don't think I know you.
You know me.
Yeah, from New Orleans.
Fuck no dude, from like two hours ago.
Chill Doobs.
We are friends with Luke and Paul. We live here. In the trailer park.
I know Luke and Paul, they're the ones taking me to the bus station. They're nice.
And we're nice.
It cost me money.
How much? We'll pay.
I'm not a drug dealer. I just need to get to the bus station.
We'll make sure you get to the bus station.
Luke and Paul will get you there. But in the meantime, can you take us on a little trip?
Come on, just a few hits.
I don't know.
Spread the love, for a fair price. Come on, spread the love.
Okay, I guess I can sell a few at cost. Ten dollars a piece.
Fair Enough.
It's in the back of Luke's car.
Well let's go get it.
Alright, we'll get our friends and we'll meet you there.
More friends? Paul are you okay?
I am so okay. I've been workin' on a plan to get outta here. I've been stuck here for too long.
Cool.
Yeah, it's time for me to get unstuck.
Unstuck?
When I lost my farm, my head wasn't right. Now, it feels like the gears in my heads, workin'
again. It makes sense.
I understand. So what are you gonna do?
I dunno. Maybe become a nurse. I need to get my GED first.
Paul?
Yes?
Do you think it's okay for me to give acid to more people?
Sure.
Okay, well I need to get it out of my luggage. Hey Luke, you think you could open your trunk?
Anything for you dude, but I can't stop movin'. Just push the button.
Thanks Paul.
Welcome.
Hey Baby! I got some sweets for ya! Bye baby! Goodbye!
Okay, I need ten dollars a hit. Does anybody have a scissors?
I got one!
Do you have change for a 20?
I can't even handle change man.
I'll tell you what. I'll give you 40 for six. That's roughly six-something a hit?
Make it seven.
I'll spread it out among these guys.
Make it seven!
I heard you!
Fair enough. I'll make it eight.
Even fairer.
There you go.
Alright guys. Here we go.
Put it on your tongue.
Hold on ya'll. We'll all take it at the same time.
Ready? One, two, three.
Man, I need some more wine coolers.
I am out of wine coolers. Fuck. Not a good time.
You have any family around here?
Just some cousins.
What about your parents?
I don't have a dad. My mom had some problems so I moved out over a year ago.
What happened?
I don't want to talk about that.
Okay.
Thank you Jesus.
Is there anything else you would like me to work on while I'm here, my son.
Yeah, please. Please get me out of the trailer park.
Luke, I'm freaking out man. What the fuck is going on?
You're on acid, dude.
I want to make it stop.
You can't make it stop.
Stop, stop.
You just gotta ride it out man.
I should sit down. Make it stop Luke.
I'm sure it's gonna wear off man. But for right now, you just gotta let it ride.
This couch is comfy.
This couch is comfy. That boy Jessie has brought me to Jesus!
Jesus?
They said I look like Jesus.
But he's not.
Maybe like a fat, old Jesus.
That escaped the cross and got fat and old.
Yeah, I can see that.
I'd get a lot more respect if I was Jesus.
No, you wouldn't.
How sweet the sound.
That saved, the wrech, like me.
I once, was lost, but now, I'm found. Was blind but now, I see.
I baptize thee, in the name of the Father, and the Son, and the Holy Ghost.
Hey, does anybody wanna play ultimate frisbee?
Ultimate fightin'?
Whoa, that's too intense, dude.
Jesus turned water into wine cooler man!
That's awesome! Did he help?
I don't know what the fuck he's doin'.
I wanna play Frisbee.
Alright, come on, let's go.
Come on, gorgeous.
They actin' like a bunch of fools out there. I'm expectin' the sherrif to drive up at any moment.
Why, because they're havin' a little bit of fun?
I want it! I want it!
Hey only one person can guard me at a time!
You ain't plannin' on takin' any of that LSD are you Rose Marie?
No. I wish I could, but bein' pregnant and all, I probably shouldn't. I shouldn't should I?
Damnit Rose Marie. You know, it hasn't stopped you from doin' anythin' else has it?
Now that's just mean.
Look, I'm just trying to look after you and your unborn baby. Come on Rose Marie! Rose
Marie! Shit.
Why are you throwin' it backwards? Our goal is this way.
Doobs!
Hey Missouri.
Yes?
I heard you're holdin'.
Holding?
Holding the trips.
Oh yeah, yes, I am.
I want two.
Okay, I can't just give them away for free.
If I wasn't gonna pay you for them, I would've already beat them outta ya.
Okay, they're ten dollars a hit.
I'll give you ten for two.
Deal.
These scissors are-
Okay those will work. Thanks.
There you go.
This better work.
It works. Really it does. Really.
There you go.
Alright man, here's ten bucks.
Are these any good?
Wow, paper, I've never seen that paper before.
What's the fish for?
Liquid, fluid.
So this stuff's pretty good? Should I take a half, or should I take a whole right now?
You know what? Just take the whole thing right now.
This stuff real?
One for me, one for the dog.
Hi.
Hi
Can I have my scissors back?
Oh, yeah.
You are so beautiful. You wanna ride with me?
Jessie's gotta come help me with something.
There he is! Missouri. There he is.
Mind...explosion! It's my new ultimate fighter name!
Whoa, I like it!
He even spelled it right.
You're the one that motivated me Jessie.
I did, how?
By openin' up, our eyes.
Wanna come help me find some lip balm?
Oh, don't forget, your bus.
The bus, yeah, I have a bus to catch. What time is it?
Hold on, the numbers won't stop movin'.
That's cool, they're dancin' look at that!
Your bus don't leave 'til eight right?
Yeah.
It don't get dark 'round here 'til 7:30.
We're fine, the sun's still lit.
Lit?
Hey, let's go build a fire!
Hell yeah, man. Let's go burn shit!
That's the best idea I've had in awhile.
Help me find my lip balm.
Are these supposed to move?
Everything's moving. Look.
I think we're peaking.
Peaking?
Yeah the acid. When it peaks, the experience, the trip.
Well I don't want this to end.
Me neither, but it does.
Well can't we just take more?
Well we could take more-hey! Lip balm.
This burns, this burns!
That's muscle balm not lip balm!
Jezzabel says, you used to have a farm.
I did! Yeah I had acreage.
Paul, have you seen Jessie?
Hey Puddin'. Remember when we had that acreage?
You mean my parents place that we lost to the bank?
See, I know a thing or two about farmin'. You gotta rotate the crops, keep the soil fertile. Like
one year you'll have corn, the next, soy beans. Gotta keep it in rotation. You overuse one crop,
you ruin the soil. Kinda like with drugs!
Has anybody seen Jessie?
Baby, every time you smile.
Jessie, anybody?
He was hangin' with Doobs I think.
Or he could be with that skinny bitch.
Who?
Sara!
Okay.
Anyways, it's the same with drugs. So acid's for onetime use. Then you gotta rotate in the weed,
or alcohol on the next go around.
Found the lip balm in the bathroom. Here, let me see.
How many days have I been here?
I think it's like weeks.
I have to go!
You don't have to go.
Don't forget about your bus.
How long have I been here?
Where, in here?
In the trailer park.
Since this mornin'.
I have to go!
Yes, you do have to go. You've given every damn person in this trailer park, LSD. And you
know what? Most these people were fucked up as it is. They don't need you here gettin' them
more fucked up.
I'm sorry. I'm tryin' to get home and I didn't wanna get my head bashed in behind the old
school.
Man child, you are messed up. What made you think you were gonna get bashed in the head?
When I broke down at the Quickie-Mart, this biker dude invited me behind the old school and
Paul said that's where they bash people's heads in.
Yeah, that's right.
Paul and Luke saved my life!
You are messed up.
No, I don't know if I'll ever be able to leave.
You said you would say.
I have to go, my family's expecting me.
But you said you would stay.
Sara, you were on drugs. Jessie, you were on drugs. Hell everybody in this fuckin' trailer park is
trippin' out of their heads except for me. There's some people wanderin' around the woods with
sheets over their heads. And I saw a group of people with their faces painted, dancin' towards
town.
It's paint! It's paint! You have blue on your face! Look at you, come on I got some stuff we
gonna talk about. I started stackin' rocks about nine years ago. It started with just one and two.
You're gettin' me all glittery!
I'm gonna put it on the tip of your nose like Rudolph!
Magic stick!
Thank you for bringing me.
What is that?
I'm Picasso!
We're all in heaven. The universe, the universe and God and Jesus Christ love us.
I need to move you outta here.
Will you help me?
Yes, Stay here. I'm gonna find Luke, and I'm gonna get his car keys.
Don't leave me.
It will wear off, you don't really like me. It's the drugs.
You're the best thing that's ever happened to me.
I like you too but, you won't like me after you come down.
No it's real, I liked you before the drugs. Do you remember when we first met?
Yeah, at the Quickie-Mart.
Okay, were you on drugs then?
No.
See, so the acid just sped things up, you do like me.
I do like you.
Bounty Hunters!
What do we do?
Where's Luke Mcgee? He skipped his bond and we're takin' him in.
We should wait here. We need to find Luke!
Are we gonna be on T.V.!?
No T.V.'s maam, we're just lookin' for Luke. Where is he?
Oh please, please put us on T.V.!
Put us on T.V.!
T.V., T.V., T.V. T.V., T.V., T.V.!
What are these people on? Some type of Ecstacy or somethin'?
No, I think this is some kind of religious cult shit.
Kinda!
What would I do? Hey!
Hey!
Have you all seen Luke?
Yeah, ya'll need paint!
Yeah, we do, wait, have you seen Luke?  Where is he?
Okay. I'mma get her some paint.
I would do that.
They finally found me.
Hey! What did you do?
It must have somethin' to do with my old meth lab.
You had a meth lab?
Well, no. But I never got past that Sudafed, cold medicine, shit man. I got busted five-finger
discountin' that shit. That's stealin' to you city boy. I guess I forgot about my court date.
Well let's hide inside this trailer.
No, I'm gonna put all that shit to rest, and I'm gonna follow my dreams. I love you man.
I'ma turn myself in, but I'ma have myself some fun first.
One, two, three.
I am Luke Mcgee! The Mind Explosion!
Mind Explosion!
Did you say you're Luke Mcgee?
Luke, I need your keys. I need your keys! I gotta take Jessie to the bus station.
They're on my belt.
Ya'll got some crazy shit goin' on over here.
Yeah, well it's a holiday.
What holiday?
Holy of Holies.
I ain't never heard about that.
Luke, Luke! Thanks for everything!
No, thank you Jesus.
It's Jessie.
Not to sound corny at all, but you saved me man.
Saved you?
Okay, okay. Not really. But I had the time of my life man, thanks to you. We all did! I'll see you
in five to ten Jesus!
Hey, I'm startin' to come down now.
Yeah, me too.
I still like you.
I like you too.
So you'll come back?
I don't know. Should I come back?
Yeah, you should come back.
My lips still burn.
They're probably gonna do that.
Can I call you?
Jessie, get in the car, we gotta go.
You're leavin' us?
Jessie, I'm gonna miss you man. You're a trip. Get it?
Got it, got it.
And now he needs to gets goin' ok. Ya'll say goodbye.
Jessie, I want you to have this.
I will take it.
Bye Jessie! Bye!
Hey!
Hey Mary!
Get your ass back to the trailer!
I can't stop! Help me when you get back.
Bye Paul, thanks for everything!
Bye, Missourah!
Are you really jugglin' fire?
Uh-huh!
Go buy me some boiled peanuts.
Okay, just peanuts.
The acid does wear off. Right Jessie?
It's supposed to. Though there might be some flashbacks, I don't know.
The bus station.
Captions by GetTranscribed.com