I
ribes are gathering right so gathering
in the Eagles scream
ways of oh god surely love each lonely
soldier Hawaii what
god will forgive each lonely soldier and
understand the things here
and under slain
the things
I let buzz I love move move get on that
bus right now last man on that bus a
blade of grass novel on board so get
your feelings ella footprints now move
it bright pink teddy all right you
dummies my name is Drake dr AK e gunnery
sergeant Drake do you I am sir nothing
else just sir as I claim understand
garbage what you saying yeah dr. Drake
sure I didn't tell you to say yes sir
sergeant Drake say tonight I just told
you to say sir just a moment ago at
night what did let me have it yeah
whispering yes I will be your mother
your father your legal guardian your
sister by the entire period you're here
at Marine Corps Recruit Depot you will
be treated like a man if you act like a
man you will do things you never thought
possible you will use muscles and
availabilities you never thought you had
left pad turn it on left you Dodos drop
those bags and funny or anything this is
a shopping cart I will now explain to
you a position of attention you'll
executed and maintain that position
you'll place your heels together in line
and turn your toes outward at a
45-degree angle get on oh what a 45
degree angle is cover the yellow
footprints he will place the thumbs of
your hands along the outside seem to
your trousers curling your fingers
slightly to the touch of material of the
trousers your arm just straight your
wrist is straight your stomach is in
your shoulders are up your chest is out
your chin is parallel to the ground your
head and your eyes are straight ahead
and your
office shut and will remain that way at
all times you will speak in a loud and
clear voice at all times the first words
out of your mouth and the last words out
of your mouth will be sir and at all
times you will maintain the fact that
your United States Marine boot is that
clear when I say you are I don't hear it
sorry and don't you ever forget it right
lucky got in fat lady I just saw him and
you lose that oh my are we pretty one
cut your finger there straighten up your
shoulders I hear your eyeballs moving
boy
dear show up at a military reservation
in that phat phat a marine boot come on
honey your business going on back here
oh I get it the paisa send you here
right he picked you up downtown put you
on the bus enjoy their right woody
failure no I will shut your mouth lady I
try not to remember faces it's not a
good idea for a d I'd if I start placing
faces and names together because then he
starts thinking about you boots and
human beings but lady I will remember
your face I will not get your face out
of my mind and that's bad that's very
bad because when I want something done
you're gonna weigh heavy on my mind why
did you do this to me I didn't have a
choice I was drafted sir he would raft
in the Marine
but why did you pick my Marine Corps hi
Frank face big up yet junkin follow me
maintain positions double time
hey let's go handle you skinheads let's
go get back get in there move it move it
bhutan you for those phones the table no
one who didn't get them over there drive
double back through the day now there
are certain items you are you chewing
gum sir yes sir I need a mouth yes sir
aye sir tonight in your personal
possession which an unaligned upon E&I
st. maline base i want to relate those
items all intoxicating beverages all
photographs and obscene literature also
person village all lewd and indecent
pictures all firearms and live
ammunition all knives all brass knuckles
and black Jack's all narcotics drugs of
all kinds gambling device with all kinds
all combustible and explosives all
prophylactics all armed forces ID
Liberty cards food in any form candy and
any hypodermic needles and syringes is
that clear now if any of the
above-mentioned items are in your
possession and you don't want them sent
home to mommy and daddy you'll take them
now out of your personal belongings
everything will be collected now hey oh
let's go get a void your placement favor
boxes
you may serve this what's my name sir
who gave you permission to scratch sir
no one sir then why did you scratch sir
in it sir are you turn around I didn't
listen to me petunia you listen good
because i only say things once now you
don't do nothing i mean nothing without
my permission if i say yes and it yes if
i say no then you don't breathe you
don't move is that clear yes sir garbage
yes sir you and me just ain't gonna get
a long hallway boy why not sir because I
said so you think that's funny so no sir
you want to keep those teeth so get
Center and keep them coming
all right gravity bump get in there come
on get in there hurry up hurry it up
dick those covers on your head in my
house the pucketts one of the rats start
again 10 minutes the full inspection now
hey aren't you gonna do anything man he
just told us to store gear okay my
name's scrunch scrunch Gordon arm song
let's keep a last name Jordan that's all
really counts around here you've been in
before yeah I was in the rotc three
years really makes you stand tall no to
me yeah now you take that guy over there
laying on his bunk he's gonna make it
tough for the rest of us know what I
mean is it lousy mattresses how do they
expect to gotta get any sleep around
here are you kidding me great do you
know anything about this jazz not baby
but the man does and I'm sure you'll be
back names Washington Sydney Washington
wha she did say baby my name is
Washington to my cell is Washington
that's wild do you think they'll get us
confused I don't know man but for now on
this bug is a depressed area hey better
start folding your clothes yeah come on
we don't want any goo pops in this
outfit even sorry wants anything done
yet
you better get yourself in gear but just
told him like you do at home yeah well
move it just like home sorry everybody's
been asking me for my autograph yeah why
why for my record cats on the front pero
you see that boy yeah sure okay you're
so lucky till you look awful sad yeah
well you never even build a catch Pole
let alone babe we got hat you look like
well thats how my granddaddy's turkey
Hannah's brought me luck the last lost
the first time in ten years of fishing
the diver called warn you it'll be the
last time to run a story on boy yeah
edge enhanced I opinion yourself hey did
you read this story in the front pager
huh yeah yeah but our boys and getting
them you know before they go into battle
here it says they've been smoking
marijuana well I don't believe that boy
yea verily will ya it says you're about
thirty percent Oh Kim I never did that
I'd kill you don't have any kids don't
make any difference I kill him anyway do
you know what that is that's coming this
propaganda board so that is waiting icon
yeah sure it is man they grew what they
sell it they sure don't smoke it that's
not true at all i remember up and don't
vanishing losers of our youth that's
where it's a communist plot after we do
for him to go out of here everything
goes right down the drain America man
buddy that's what we are
miracle man who else but a miracle man
can take these sisters in tournament US
Marines in a year well I time feat lay
into him you better frame this they're
chanting listen if you will put my fun
out which way is up meet me for game 8
ball tonight hey better breakfast yeah
good later than that right you know
sounds like an opinion in the else and
that Claire not sitting those rags and
that clear sorry doing those buckets oh
very well you don't do that sorry Isabel
sir whoo sorry my mate sir who you made
it shut your mouth Isabel your may
taught you to do that isn't dad did you
also teach you how to make your pop sir
no sir you'll learn well you gonna fold
your skinnies like that sure yeah that's
the way we do at home sir my mother
taught me how sir your mother yes sure
our mother is wrong all your mothers are
wrong all your maids are wrong there is
only one way to do it and what way is
that didn't have one yes the marine way
sure yeah sure Isabel was better yo TC
teach you how to make that bunk sorry
yes sir turn up turn turn up sir yes sir
you were wrong which your writer than
they are hit the deck do push-ups I tell
you to stop one to bring but stop why
aren't you wearing skivvies I never wear
shorts sir on your feet what do you mean
you never wear shorts I like the freedom
sir now hairless there will be no
freedom in this camp is that clear yes
is that clear I don't hear you hey
ha
I didn't yes sir you idiot BAM I didn't
yes sir that was even beginning now you
will lose weight a little cut that one
or a few is that clear oh you're so
skinny Washington yes sir any now you
will gain weight i will take and shove
it down your throat is that
whoo and I feel like a monkey in a cage
that's right man 1984 gets a little
closer every day then every time he
yells at me my stomach gets all twisted
up in knots he makes me nervous he's
supposed to hey what are you standing on
your head for him head when I'm really
tired this relaxes me who two years in a
bolivian food never made me feel as sick
as i feel right now Olivia are you doing
Bolivia Peace Corps you know that's
crazy I come back and I'm home three
days man and get my draft notice yeah
i'm gonna show you the peace corps
pirate Bob about heading to Canada for a
while why didn't you go I don't know
what are you doing on maybe it's my
karma to be here huh I thought that you
couldn't be dropped it out for the Peace
Corps chea now where are you from well
lots of places I've been all over
hola what you do whatever comes natural
kind of hard to get an answer out if you
win then I you ever been in one of those
communes yeah for a while well well it
was anything like the magazine say it is
you know free love and everything well
that was a small part of it after a
while the Torah started coming around
look at the Freak you got all crowded up
for the kind of people we're trying to
get away from whole thing just sort of
fell apart that's too bad man sounds
like a great life mmm it's all what you
make it took me a long time to realize
that yesterday can't be changed and
tomorrow really can't be controlled any
certainty I just kind of shoot for the
minute oh I wish I'd met you sooner
before I got in this place it's all
where your head's at man that's all it
counts
10 pull up your pants you'll have ten
minutes you're writing a bigot or
another home and then you will explain
that you have in process that you are
well and that you will attend the Church
of your choice you will use this
barracks number as you return address is
that clear try ten minutes starting now
our di is all marine he keeps everyone
in line with a crack of his voice I
Marines marine dad I like it you were
right we all look the same here you
can't tell a rich guy from the poor one
it's the only time in my life I felt
like everybody else tell coach pittman
that I'm in real good shape the
exercises here even easier than the ones
he gave us the guys already looked to me
as their leader st mando Papa mama que
vea los tienen corriendo todo el día
desde que hemos pasado del camión y
greetin mucho tambien todo comienzo otra
vez a las cuatro Sigmund Donna mañana I
really hate it here everything about
it's de personalizing is depressing I
wish I were anywhere else and there's
another guy here named Washington but
I'm positive he's no relation tell
Leona's if he thinks they're square on
the outside you got to take a look at
him in here
by later on the low iron would pack up
my door sir private in reporting as
ordered sir and they're like you stand
on your head sir yes sir I don't want to
need my troops standing on their head
sir yes sir don't like the we do you
push ups either sir yes sir but I'm
doing him exactly as instructed sir I
say you're doing him wrong I front mat
zo's eyeballs you will do 100 pushups
tomorrow morning before breakfast sir
yes sir the marine way sorry yes sir you
scored higher than anyone in platoon on
these tests you know that sir no sir
said you're you need a year and a half
high school what happened to kick out
sir no sir I quit thought it was a waste
of time sir
you think learning as a waste of time
sir no sir but what they had to teach me
just didn't interest me sirve then you
tell me how you learn so much to score
like this sir I don't know sir just
hanging around I guess you try to snow
me lady so don't sir every penny
organized sport sorry no sir never
really cared for them Sir I don't
understand you private no high school
teens no supervision enter in better
condition the rest of my recruits why
does that bother you sir oh that's the
questions around here and there will be
no more standing on your head in my
barracks miss that sir yes sir but the
private understood that he had five
minutes to relax sir oh the private did
sir yes sir prior finds standing on his
head relaxes him Sir it's it's kind of
like a drill instructors drawing it
that's very good sir it has a great deal
of freedom yet it's it's precise yep
very natural sir it's not my drawing sir
yes sir get out of my sight aye aye sir
hey big boy I just come to a big
decision on the way over here all right
I'm gonna let you beat me tonight in the
game of 8-ball Shh you don't have to let
me do that let's go come here I got
tonight come on a bye your bear way sir
Thank You river here you are be here
hello boom we'll never finished high
school scored the highest of anybody in
these tests that's impossible look look
thank you some kind of a genius a dress
I thought that hippie yeah I guarantee
you something he got the high school man
he cheated talking you cheat I know but
I'll guarantee you cheated that's a
tough test man what's going dude no no
no later later I got it will I up with
the babes today ten-hut pick up that
bucket lights on three minutes on those
teeth brush you ready for inspection in
one in one half minutes move you all
enjoyed your push-ups today didn't you
sir yeah but you're going to enjoy them
even more tomorrow aren't you sir yeah
you think you look silly into a hairdos
don't you know in like a girlfriend to
see you now wind you sir yes sir get all
that you go to sleep now when you sir
what you don't really want to go to
sleep do you know you'd like to run a
few laps wouldn't you sir yes sir you
are Marines aren't you but you're going
to become Marines aren't you I don't
hear you people I still don't hear you
people
you
interacts ladies will enjoy your pushups
want to go to sleep your people were
lost and on your left eyebrow whoa yes I
can't hear you girls yeah this is stupid
you people are stupid aren't you
alright chickens is 450 let's not sleep
the day away I love those rags I'm like
on your feet are changing my past by
move it geek or Sanchez kind of the next
let's go out on wash its head on the
neck pull it what do you think you're
doing I said what do you think you're
doing sir exercising sir what yep but no
sir my mind forget your mind I'll tell
you what to think when do they and how
to think of that Claire sir yes sir on
the deck now yes sir 1 sir 2 sir 3 sir
the ground you're gonna pick up your
toothbrush here you go all right gun get
a bone Washington come pick it up
Washington pig and I'll pick it up all
right bye wash yourself down outside fit
into the body once again
all right you're gonna drop na check
them out all right surely you can drop
them now
I said drop em Shelley hey five Lycidas
banging order surely yes sir
Oh
what are you boys dad a mystery nap sir
I feel sick I really feel terrible I
don't hear you boy sir I feel sick sir I
really feel terrible at snow good
private plane you tried that yesterday
one more time I'm gonna put you back you
still feel sick boy yeah nice trip
private sir yes sir surely will not
demonstrate how to do stationery dumb
time for it Oh huh stationery no time oh
and make sure as surely doesn't daydream
during drill anymore the entire platoon
will do stay sad all the time Oh poop
sale a long time hey
get not hey left leg hey hey hey that's
something I'm being fixed how'd you hold
up those buckets the sea wall it wasn't
easy boy didn't hurt I mean it seemed
like you weren't feeling anything I
didn't then before I sure do now well
loved what about when you had all that
double time to do you actually smiling
it seemed like you enjoying the whole
thing I was you just got to put yourself
in the right frame of mind Sydney well
could you uh could you teach me how to
do what I mean could you give me a few
pointers
we'll see it's it's not like self
hypnosis or anything like that it's it's
uh it's magical it's kind of like taking
your mind to another planet you know
yeah you separating your mind for your
body right controller look if I can do
it you can do it right I've just about
had enough of this you know you're out
of your head you know you're messing
with these guys lines amen so does Uncle
Sam we're sick of your anti-american
talk come on sweats we don't want your
kind around here thank you Father for as
hippies propaganda people back in the
room second-guess belong here you can't
listen to it
I'm sounds patties but if you fall out
and follow me what do you think you're
trying to do sir how do you get those
things to hold up those buckets for so
long sir just some basic freaking dial
medicos given you that double talk
you're destroying the unity of my
platoon no sir I'm only trying to help
that little guy Sydney sir he's the
weakest I say you are destroying the
unity of my platoon do you hear me lady
yes sir I'm considering sending you back
to motivation platoon do you know what
that means no sir you will have di is
much tougher than me crawling all the
way up your back 24 hours a day six days
a week every hour of those 24 hours you
wish you were dead how is that what you
want private no sir wouldn't you shape
up and you join my platoon yes sir now
what were you telling him in the
barracks last night sir I was explaining
the fundamentals of reconned idle
meditation served knock off that
double-talk I said whatever it is I
don't like it yes sir sir the private
would like to know the point of holding
up the buckets is it to strengthen our
arms and determination to instill pride
and self confidence sir the point of
this exercise is to save your life
whether you understand it or not is
unimportant that I order it done is
sufficient for you to do it yes sir
without question yes sir
get back to your platoon hi sir very
nice chap sir gee I didn't think
religion was gonna be part of our basic
training well you know many of parents
and it's a boy with the Lord's help
Scott in back of marine sorry muscle of
my boys teaches some more help come on
wait a minute you guys hey that's right
if you can do it with the buckets then
we can do it with practically anything
else indeed did see in the blue Mao rush
even that's dictionary double time right
anyway wait a minute drill drill drill
pusher hey you know it really involves a
lot of deep concentration you really got
to get into it are you kidding it's
really important to us how about it Hey
look Jordan the club scrunch Gordon hey
guys yeah I'll be right there see inside
huh got yourself some Downers huh I
don't think I'm gonna be able to make it
Adrian yeah I can dig it I'm not so sure
I'm gonna make it myself do you want
some of mine no I'll pass oh I couldn't
start the day without him yeah I'm hip
to it for two years I couldn't leave the
house without Downers yeah just really a
drag trying to face all that every day
it's insane huh that's just the way I
feel man yeah but you know what happened
then quit I started doing uppers to
counteract the donors and
function in a normal level which is
really just where i was at to begin with
oh that's that's what I mean I just
can't function in this place think about
ready to flip out maybe you should what
tell them the truth tell me sick you so
nervous you don't think you can make it
you think they'd really believe me no
you look awful sick to me back in look
man I'm looking better right I mean
check this out yeah you're giving me
nightmares Oh baby I didn't lost a lot
of weight Sanchez I mean just look at
this muscle rub your neck my neck what
about my neck it's still fat it hasn't
lost any weight at all look at it it's
disgusting man say Sanchez what are you
saying man how's the person supposed to
lose weight in their neck that's Drake
he's probably got an exercise for it
well it's like the key to the whole
thing is calmness intercall its
tranquility it's feeling good and it's
not being where the pain is that's like
you have to take yourself on a real
mental trip
you have to separate yourself from
what's happening it's like divorce
thought from action by breaking thought
down to its essence and
then you have to visualize something
that something that's felt good to you
before that you remember is good to take
the places of the pain think of think of
of the thing that you've experienced
before it's like re-experience until all
becomes more real than real and then you
have to visualize and taste and smell
and feel and it just fills your head
there's nothing else there nothing else
exists and then you're there
youporn yeah that's hot I keep bringing
my coffee out to buy some
you feeling okay you get anything you'll
talk to me but quietly doctor I've got a
lot of troubles I mean a Drake Drake
everything's AR Kait peanuts in oak
remove it all your hand seems to me
things have been hanging pretty hair
with you lately all come fight it come
from life time today it's true though
now that the only one who's noticed it
I've a lot of other guys resented things
too yeah like what well like your whole
attitude that's like he is soften up or
something it's like you just don't care
that's crazy oh let's jus like a drill
this more let me help it's on in 10
degrees out on that grind a new platoon
look happy yeah so well it's not like
you Drake you should have been out there
kicking yourself a few bucks in watching
with superior I'm not talking about the
marching I'm talking about their
attitude that was wrong I notice the
cliq Ross surprise oh thanks thanks a
lot thanks thanks for checking up on me
Frank old buddy checkin up on you what
are you talk about checking of it so I
get this done gave the same with this
one shut I think it's got something to
do with the hippie now has it I don't
know it seems to me there's some
peculiar rank listen I'm behind in my
paperwork thanks for giving me the tough
talk right ok boy trouble anything just
come to me okay
watch Adrian Adrian you have to fire
sooner or later you're gonna have to
qualify there is no way around it it
really you fire so help me I'll send you
back for motivation but to now do you
hear me boy yes sir and fire yes sir
oh come on the black the weapon
hey hey Melvin look no loan for you
listen uh she all heard about you boring
i find out there today on the range yeah
I'd hear about that how does he hear
about anything nobody you can't let some
hippie pump follow up your platoon
average and tell you what I'm gonna do
I'm gonna take mark your hands Drake I'm
gonna transfer oh I wish you wouldn't do
that I really wish you would yeah come
on how are ya just because you cheap dia
pull rank on me you can't privilege one
recruit over another day you know no I
don't care what the book says the kids
got a problem I can handle this all
right oh he's got to drink he's got
himself yeah well I'm gonna transfer him
don't do it funny he'll rip you down boy
I know that that's my problem not yours
I'm making them up get off my back huh
I'm gonna get off bug me just bug off
okay buddy i won't bug you you can count
on I hear termite night would work sir
fuck when reporting saucer back back
back will give Mishnah come in this well
sir in study some ahmed matter here and
I falling you on the grinder today when
you know you're lifting you're right sir
yes sir how come your rifle was on your
left shoulder when I distinctly ordered
right shoulder arm sir the part of
corrected that mistake sir a private
crack without mistake I said let's order
I'm saying you are willing to Rachel run
it sir mr. and when i said lets older
I'm your
on the right shoulder Ryder sir desert
do you know your left from your right
penguin sir yes sir with your armor not
that one the element you with it now one
arm is that sure but right on sir robin
left arm up top right on top left I'm
who do you drop that on keeping up that
way or you not do Robin left arm up
private when you keep that arm up near
until I decided you should take it down
and then maybe you remember which is
your right from your left get out of my
son hydrate oh the rotation babe dad
yeah hey I tell you about last weekend
no tu stood have been there Larry and I
went up Snake River about five miles
past a campground and we found a spot I
can't even tell you about yeah in the
first hour we caught 10 of the biggest
trout you could ever want to see I'm not
good listen I'm not telling everybody
back if you want to join us this weekend
you and Sergeant if I stir we got room
no no thanks Michael I'm a mid-cycle so
what you even left your people on a
Sunday before they're probably better
off without you anyway what's the matter
something eating you know the other
probably is but nobody ever tells a
chaplain anything are we in a talking
play pool Mike now come on let's go it's
your shot let's go Oh two shots
All Right girls let's not sleep the day
away
turns but on your feet now
must stand for any more smiling during
drill is that clear yes I will not stand
for any more positions is that clear sir
I will not stand for any more meditating
during chow here's that Claire I will
not stand for any more trips is that
class get down my way this place we're
having full inspection in one hour is
that clear I thought now wow what a
waste
I can't do anything from it they're
always on my back yelling at me every
time I turn around there's old sergeant
Drake man staring right down my throat
he just waiting for me this way for me
to make mistakes are starting on me when
you know it's not only you it's all of
us no it's me man it's me I'm the one he
picked it miss me miss me you know
something you're nuts man come on quit
gotta get it together man I thought we
were doing pretty great we are
let's turn the momentum as always let's
go see your hand hey you up there what's
out here knocking this panel sir he
didn't push me out who's Josh sooner I
just climb it again sweetheart so I
didn't push it up you don't talk back to
the iboot you have to offer come on get
on it start this course over again get
on back at them again let's go i watch
my bag whats the whole app give me look
back talking a sweetheart are you
disobeying the orders of a DI no sir and
you do what the chief says you start
this course over again hi sir but let's
get these lines here you do you sit
Baker manacle back there anybody inside
the course again hi I shall remove it
let's get these lines up here let's get
him up there come on come on jumping in
head let's go all right 15 minutes of
scrubbing the specification let's move
it
that's where you're going you idiot
chapter bo I'm talking sir yes sir look
at you I never got this close to the
flower child before gonna fly are you
boy huh are you a daisy sigh no sir
United Daisy are you sweet people side
now sir I bet your sweet feel your sweet
pea sir no sir say no sir why I hear you
boy sir no sir check ups or what sir no
sir I'm not a sweet piece target don't
your voice boy think you mad at me would
you like to at me promise would you like
to have me private sorry no sir I think
the private like the hidden well I tell
you what private I'm gonna put my hands
behind my back man you take one just hit
me once right here go ahead give me one
come on give me a knuckle sandwich boy
I'm come on man when you like to give me
a little slut when you like him with
your purse sweetheart the one that
mullet you wear me since Robin I know I
can't I get me what it is hey Drake I
wouldn't do without your disciplining my
troops Frank hey you what you don't want
what you heard me I want you touching my
men well a Drake but you know I can
discipline any recruitment is that way
off my men for
can I mean it hippie Clint this has got
to be the worst I can't even believe it
just a giant effort just to survive
every day here oh that the paste oh you
can't be considered normal not even in
this place what hey quit
weather
stupid stupid jerk no Adrian no it's
quite cheap it all it's a I dig it all
me there is no ticket home you idiot oh
ok Drake at a doctor oh my gosh now move
gone get done you know ok ok no hay true
leave me alone somewhere you anyway
leave me alone they did tibi get the
doctor please what do you mean no ticket
home Adrian if any of you are thinking
the same thoughts as private Quentin you
should read this little book you will
notice that the text and the
accompanying illustrations show how to
kill a man including yourself including
slitting your wrists properly this makes
the whole process much more efficient
and much less time consuming for all
parties concerned I want you all to read
it pass it on among yourselves when
you've completed the assignment you will
sign your name and serial number on the
last page is that understood I don't
hear you very clearly tonight gentlemen
duty
since you kitties I so eager for fun and
games I have decided to arrange an
exercise for you this morning to work
off your excess energy now I will take
great delight in watching you ladies
beat each other with usual sticks now
there will be winners and there will be
losing the losers will find yourselves
assigned to remedial miss duty forever
is that claire lady private Adrienne get
some on your head final was you sir not
you fat skinny Washington in the bucket
Wow
yo mess do you got it hey Peter denied
me what didn't you doing sir I thought
that you thought what what did you think
did I tell you to think no sir as well
you not to think did not yes sir pic of
that pujols dig yes sir bat Washington
yes sir get that bugger i had
finish it finish it boniva this exercise
is steel garden yes sir in the bucket
baby don't what are you gonna do it
anyway Smith's wiped out I ask your
opinion go no sir and fight
get back in your positions get back you
to garden get back get back get back
are your feet planted you'd run in that
rack we think this is nap time no sir
what are you doing here anyway he's
supposed to be with the others on free
time 2px yes sir well maybe the private
doesn't one leagues barracks private
does sir maybe he doesn't want his free
time the private does sir well then move
out yes sir Sir I thought it was
privates privilege to spend free time
where he wants sir oh you didn't well
you're wrong but I say go you go by your
leave sir your hang on don't you you
still hang on yeah the whole trouble you
don't understand private yeah you have
to change I haven't changed sir
physically I'm gonna be a full-fledged
100% basic marine in two days but you
really can't expect change me and ignore
my mind yeah well we've been doing it
successfully in the past one hundred and
ninety five years maybe but that doesn't
work anymore sir not today not with us
you know you really don't know us sory
you expect us to buy us a name of
patriotism like with some sort of a
privilege to shut your mouth I know you
and I know you're kind of in your
philosophy and I don't want and I don't
like it for your information it is a
privilege to serve your country more
than that it's a necessity because we're
at war and war is a fact of life private
Adrian good bad or indifferent
has not been able to survive without war
there's a balance of nature lady yes sir
I guess I'll never make it as a soldier
sir God surely loves he's only subjects
on this soldier
understand
sing the silent soldier to these task
that must be done he's the hero he's the
villain he's the victim
right doc gathering right
doc gallery must we wait oh god surely
on this subject
what
what he was God will forgive each lonely
soldier
and understand
things you do
single silent soldier disease task must
be done he's the hero he's the villain
he's the victim
announcing the departure of scenic
Cruiser 497 to Phoenix Albuquerque and
ward work for mayor
better leave the country after 30 days
you were deserted Thanks as a matter of
fact
you're a wall right now I know you're
out of uniform he could be arrested hey
leave me alone will you I'm not
listening to you anymore
yeah this isn't the voice Scouts you
know now you can't just quit simply
because you disagree with we're from
different tribes sergeant two completely
different worlds you don't understand
mine yet you forced me to accept yours
your whole world is four walls in some
bunks I think you've lost touch with
life your whole bag is death my whole
bag you're defending my country I don't
equate militarism with patriotism i
can't i'm never gonna carry a gun and I
won't kill anybody and that's where it's
at isn't it
not quite I carry guns and I've killed
men simply so that you and I can sit
here and talk like this and death is
still a common denominator
ok
why haven't you left yet what do you
take first bus out of here I don't know
I'm scared they're not a what you people
can do to me either yeah
that's just it i'm confused
I always thought I knew my own head you
know it's like I know what I left back
there is wrong but I'm not so sure that
running away is the right thing to do
why don't you go back
sergeant I knew what that camp is and
what it represents and there's not a
thing i can do to change it anyway i'm
only one guy I can't fight all of you
then why don't you leave
let's go buy your uniform back
you get out of that graduating uniform
beginning your dungarees all right sir
just told him right there product snap
to clown hey drink listen buddy it looks
like your boy graduating his orders have
been changed she's been sent back to a
motivation to town that's impossible
he's graduating tomorrow I passed him
yeah i guess the co didn't fail you to
qualify on the rifle range i think it
says there whose idea was just don't
give me any starting that Drake you cuz
you're in enough trouble already boy all
right it's a kid you're after isn't it
applies to it's not for the core you
want him well I want to pretend I didn't
hear you say them all right sweetheart
lady you're in my hands now I'm gonna
start you at the beginning very
beginning girl and if you don't get it
perfect i'm gonna set your tail back and
we're gonna start it all over again
you're slouching lady you're still
slouching lady I said you're slouching
lady I bush you get in there you get
your gear together and prepare to move
out now move aye aye sir
well everything I do is for the corn
don't you forget it
hey Kate how's it going waiting for your
new herd of ladies huh yeah hey listen
about the other night I'm sorry okay
yeah I mean I mean you maybe we
shouldn't fly off the handle like that
come on being at the club tonight was
late ball I'll skin you alive oh by the
way but that hippie Adrian yeah well
whatever his name was he evil over the
hill last night man I sure hate to be in
his shoes when they catch him you know I
knew all along he was wasting your time
Drake you just didn't have what it takes
my name is Drake dr AK e gunnery
sergeant freak I will be your mother
your father your legal guardian your
sister for the entire period you are
here at Marine Corps Recruit Depot you
will be treated like a man if you act
like a man and in all times you will
maintain the fact that your United
States Marine boot is that clear yeah
when I say you are