I was just
I asked my mother
here's what she said to me
futures
I
I was just
pictures too
sauce
I reply
seven
damn it's your turn Heather now Heather
it's Heather stern Heather
sorry Heather
me
dear diary Heather told me she teaches
people real life she said real life
sucks losers dry if you want to fuck
with the Eagles you have to learn to fly
I said so you teach people how to spread
their wings and fly she said yes I said
you're beautiful God come on Veronica
what is your damage heather don't blame
me blame Heather she told me to haul
your ass into the CAF toronto back me up
Heather yeah she really wants to talk to
you for Annika
hello Heather Veronica finally I gotta
know to Kurt Kelly's I need you to
afford to hot and horny but
realistically low key note Kurt's
handwriting and we'll slip it on to
Martha dumptruck some lunch tray shit
other I don't have anything against
Martha that stock you don't have
anything for her either come on it'll be
very the novel give her shower nozzle
masturbation material for weeks think
about it I don't think Veronica needs
something to write on Heather bend over
dear Martha you're so sweet I'm telling
you man it would be so righteous to
being abroad Sawyer Heather Chandler
sandwich oh hell yes I want to get a
Heather and put on my Johnson spinning
around like a goddamn too real what you
did
the world come on people let's get that
leftover lunch money to people who don't
have lunches those tater tots are bad
yet today even have Thanksgiving in
Africa oh sure thousands Indians tater
tots it's a real party continent Sawyer
guess what today is ouch lunch time Paul
switch question yeah so was the question
Heather god damned Heather you were with
me in study hall when I thought of it I
forgot such a pillowcase this wouldn't
be the bizarro thing you were babbling
about over the phone last night would it
of course it is I told Dennis if he
gives me another political topic guides
fiorito chunks
Oh Branca I'm sorry baby Finn gosh hey
I'm really sorry I could make it your
birthday party last month it's okay your
mom said you had a big date got probably
miss my own birthday for a date don't
say that what I'll just me around the
other day and I dug up um he's old
photographs oh great come on horn Akash
talking
great Heather hi courtney love your card
again Thanks it's gotta last time too
limited like totally blew my allowance
now check this out you would 5 million
dollars from the poetry sweepstakes and
the same days that big head guy gives
you the check aliens land on the earth
and say they're gonna blow up the world
in two days what do you do that's easy I
just slide that wad over to my father
because he is like one of the top
brokers in the state if I got that money
I'd give it all to the homeless every
cent you're beautiful if you're gonna
openly be a bitch it's just ever why
can't we talk to different kinds of
people fuck me gently with a chainsaw do
I look like Mother Teresa if I did I
probably wouldn't mind talking to the
geek squad huh did you see that Heather
number one just looked right at me does
it not bother you that everything in
this school thinks that you're a piranha
like I give a shit they all want me as a
friend or a fuck I'm worshipped
Westerberg and I'm only junior
I can't believe this we're going to a
party at Remington University tonight
and we're brushing up on our
conversational skills with the scum of
the school so this is called a lunchtime
whole you in five million dollars in the
publisher sweepstakes and the same day
that what's-his-face gives you the check
aliens land on Earth and say they're
gonna blow up the world in two days what
are you gonna do with the money I go to
Egypt with a girl and use the money for
an end of the world get together I
payment on a million bucks to sit on my
face and have a ride like a Kentucky
Derby it's gotta be a little spooky ask
question I have heard all right this is
important after taxes all in the
beginning she should pay me though you
go to the zoo and you get a lion and
then put a remote-controlled bomb of its
but then there's social security legal
fees push the button on the bomb and you
lion die like one what
oh god here we go
Veronica Clive keeps neighborhood alive
you wanted to be a member of the most
powerful click in school if I wasn't
already the head of it I'd want the same
thing come on Veronica you used to have
a sense of humor Veronica could you come
back you're a minute true friends work
is never done gross grow up Heather
believe me is so 87 no maybe you should
see a doctor yeah maybe come on Heather
let's take another look at today's lunch
godhra I got drool much his name's Jason
Dean is in my American history
Jason Dean greetings and salutations you
Heather now I'm a Veronica Sawyer this
may seem like a really stupid question
and there are no stupid questions you
inherit 5 million dollars the same day
aliens land on the earth and say they're
gonna blow it up in two days what do you
do that's the stupidest question I've
ever heard who's that guy in the code
think years anyways bo diddley her
raunchy sinewy Zach no doubt nope really
roll out to the middle of a lake
somewhere bring along a bottle of
tequila my sax and some Bach how very
come on Veronica later definitely
let's kick his ass shit ramp was seniors
man too old for that kind of crap let's
give him good secure though you're gonna
eat this and what did your boyfriend say
when you told him you're moving to
Sherwood Ohio answer him dick he RAM
doesn't this cafeteria have a no fags
allowed rule uh yeah seemed to have an
open-door policy for assholes dog don't
think what did you say dickhead I'll
repeat myself God they won't expel him
not to suspend him for a week or
something used a real gun they should
throw his ass in jail no way use blanks
all JD really did was ruin to fairs of
pants maybe not even that can you bleach
out urine stains he seemed pretty amazed
I thought you would give it up in high
school guys never say never so what are
you gonna do Heather take the two shots
or send me out
did you have a brain tumor for breakfast
first you ask if you can be read knowing
that I'm always read shit it's your turn
another easy shot Heather no way no day
give it up girl all right I wasn't shit
so tonight's the night are you too
excited I'm giving Veronica her shot her
first Remington party you blow it
tonight girl and it's keggers with kids
all next year
why why not Heather your mother's here
come on over once a ride hey take a
break Veronica so now so what was the
first week of spring vacation withdrawal
like oh no it's okay I guess hey kid
isn't the prom coming up I guess any
contestants worth mentioning maybe
there's kind of a dark horse in the
running god damn will somebody tell me
why I read these spy novels cuz you're
an idiot oh yeah that's it you too great
pate but I got a motor if I want to be
ready for that party tonight
corn nuts BQ or plain BQ you gonna pull
the Superchunk over then
no but if you're nice to let you buy me
a slushie see you know your convenience
be pretty well yeah well I've been moved
around all my life Dallas Baton Rouge
Vegas Sherwood Ohio has always been a
snappy snack shack any town anytime and
Papa ham and cheese in the microwave him
feast on a turbo dog keeps me sane
really that thing you pulled in the CAF
today was pretty severe yeah well the
extreme always seems to make an
impression you saying cherry your coke
slushie I didn't cherry
Frank yeah just a humble perk for my
dad's construction company seen the
commercial right bringing every state to
a higher state wait a minute Jason Dean
your pops big bud Dean construction must
be rough moving place to place
everybody's life has got static your
life perfect oh yeah I'm on my way to a
party at Remington University mmm no my
life's not perfect I don't really like
my friends yeah I don't really like your
friends either it's just like there are
people I work with in our job is being
popular and shit maybe it's time to take
a vacation
hello ladies are you coats on the floor
Veronica this is brett thanks did you
girls bring your party and slippers on
it's party she loves to party
dear diary I want to kill and you have
to believe it's for more than just
selfish reasons more than just a spoke
in my menstrual cycle you have to
believe me it's so great to be able to
talk to Bill Nye Jesus what's your major
so when you go to college what subjects
do you think is studying come on David
should we get back to the party we will
it's just so hot tonight I can't control
myself
oh Christ I can't explain it but I'm
allowed and understanding that my
parents and these Remington University
assholes have chosen to ignore I
understand that I must stop Heather
how's my little cheerleader huh I know
everyone at your high school isn't so
uptight come on Oh like I don't feel so
good okay see one of the coats will be
excellent huh you know I have a little
prepared speech i tell my suitor when he
wants more than I like to give him Jay
black I had a really nice save the
speeches for Malcolm X I just want to
get laid you don't deserve my fucking
speech Betty Finn was a true friend and
I sold her out for a bunch of swatch
dogs and diet coke heads killing Heather
be like offing the Wicked Witch of the
West wait east west god I sound like a
fucking psycho
what's your damage Frances you're being
a real cooz Heather I feel really sick
like I'm gonna throw up so can we please
jam now no hell no
tomorrow I'll be kissing her roba sized
ass but tonight let me dream of a world
without Heather a world or I am free
you stupid fuck you goddamn bitch you
were nothing before you met me you're
playing Barbies with Betty Finn you're a
bluebird you're a brownie you're a girl
scout cookie I got you into a Remington
party what's my thanks it's on a hallway
carpet I got paid in puke lick it up
baby lick it monday morning your history
I'll tell everyone about tonight
transfer to Washington transfer to
Jefferson no one at Westerberg is gonna
let you play their reindeer games
dreadful etiquette I apologize it's okay
i saw the croquet set up in the back yep
for match
hmm thank you that was my end first game
or strip croaky welcome it's a lot more
interesting than just flinging off your
clothes and boning away on a neighbor's
swing set mmm I was like to be said for
a strong enough here tonight what a life
you wanted to move me into high school
out of the sixth grade because I was
supposed to be this big genius mmm then
we decided to chuck the idea cuz I'd
have trouble making friends blah blah
blah now blah blah blah is all I do i
use my grand IQ to decide what color
gloss to wear how to hit three keggers
before curfew
the Chandler is one bitch that deserves
to die killer won't solve anything I say
we just grow up the adults and die
before that I'd like to see Heather
Chandler puker gotta trust me she skips
the Saturday morning trip to Grandma's
even when she's not hungover and we'll
just concoct ourselves a little hangover
cure that a lot induce her to spew red
white and blue then what about like milk
and orange juice what's the upchuck fat
drunk I'm a no rust buildup man myself
dick go kill her I know you can cook up
some soup and put it in a coke it splits
pretty sick okay now should it be
chicken noodle or bean with bacon put a
lid on that stuff see we go with big
blue here talking about she would never
drink anything that looked like that
anyway so we'll uh but it in this she
won't be able to see what she's drinking
we gonna cop jerk Luke an orange juice
well maybe we could like cough up a
Fleming operative well Logan orange
juice little boy nicely hmm chicken not
funny
Franken mi no carry the gun
warning Heather
Veronica Jesse James kalsa please about
Veronica's affection for a gorget ation
Heather I think last night we boasted a
lot of stuff we didn't mean did we how
the hell'd you get in here um Veronica
need have a hangover so uh I whipped
this up for you it's a family recipe
where did you put a phlegm clobbering
under something I'm not gonna drink that
piss in this stuff be too intense for
intense grow up you think I'll drink it
just because you call me chicken just
give me the cup jerk
oh my god I can't believe it I just
killed my best friend and your worst
enemy same difference should we get in
tell the cops what fuckin if she can't
take a joke Sarge this is my life oh my
god I have to send my estate you scores
to stand Quentin instead of Stanford hey
just a little freaked here at least you
got what you wanted you know got what I
wanted it is one thing to want somebody
out of your life it is another thing to
serve than a wake up couple of liquid
trainer
i we we we did a murder that's a crime
but this were like a suicide thing you
know like a suicide thing yeah hmm I
mean you can do Heather's handwriting as
well as your own right right you might
think what I've done is shocking yeah to
me those suicide is natural answer to
the myriad of problems life has given me
that's good but Heather would never use
the word myriad this is the last thing
she'll ever right she's gonna want to
cash in on as many 50 cent words as
possible yeah but she missed me read on
the vocab test two weeks ago that only
proves my point more the word is a badge
for failures at school oh okay you're
probably right huh people think just
because you're beautiful and popular
life is easy and fun
no one understood I had feelings too I
die knowing no one knew the real me just
good we've done this before any other
principle take the same position keep
things business as usual tether channel
is not your everyday suicide she was
very popular come on Paul if I let these
kids out before lunch the switchboard
had light up like a Christmas tree I
must say I was impressed to see that she
made proper use of the word myriad in
her suicide note I find it profoundly
disturbing that we're told at the tragic
destruction of youth and whole weekend
thing to talk about is adequate warning
times and misused vocabulary words first
we must revel in his revealing moment
look I suggest that we get everybody
together both students and teachers in
the cafeteria and just talk and feel
together thank you Miss Fleming you
called me when the shuttle lands now is
this heather big cheerleader that would
be Heather McNamara damn i'd be willing
to go half a day for a cheerleader god
it's unfair just so unfair we should get
off a whole week not just to a power
right the school board watch it Heather
you might be digesting food there yeah
where's your urge to purge fuck it look
Heather left pond on of her swatches
she'd want you to have it Veronica she
always said you couldn't accessorize for
shit sorry to hear about your friend
thought she was a usual airhead bitch
guess I was wrong we all were what a
waste
oh the humanity
Veronica Veronica what are you doing
I'm just so thrilled to finally have an
example of the profound sensitivity of
which a human animal is capable that
example is Heather Chandler I have her
note now I want to pass this note around
the class so you can all feel it's
pathetic beauty for yourself and while
we do this I think it's a good
opportunity to share the feelings that
the suicide has spurred in all of us now
who would like to begin I heard it was
really gnarly she sucked down a ball of
multi-purpose deodorizing disinfected
mints yes now Tracy let's not rehash the
coroner's report let's talk emotions um
Heather and I used to go out but she
said I was boring but now I realized I
really wasn't boring it's just that she
was dissatisfied with her life that's
very good Peter
are we gonna be tested on this you know
we were in the same size that sometimes
we could borrow each others clothes and
mix it up it was fun I remember I wonder
um a rhino at the 4-h club her asshole
yuddam you know we we like same kind of
clothes Heather how many networks to do
a lot of the same things it's just not
gonna be the same here with otter what
are you talking about you hated her she
hated you every English class I look
forward to seeing her Heather Chandler's
more popular than ever now scary stuff
hey son I didn't hear you come in hey
Dad I was work today it was miserable
some damn tribal withered old bitches
doesn't want us to terminate that
fleabag hotel huh all because Glenn
Miller and his band once took a ship
there just like Kansas you remember
fucking Kansas yeah that was the one
with a wheat right yeah save the
memorial oak tree society showed those
fucks yeah 30 of those fourth of July
fireworks attached to the trunk I rain
but acquitted guys pop I almost forgot
to introduce my girlfriend Oh Veronica's
my dad dad Veronica hi so much you ask
your little friend to stay for dinner I
can't uh my mom's making my favorite
meal tonight spaghetti lots of oregano
oh nice last time I saw my mom she was
waving from a library window in Texas
right dead right son
right take a break Veronica sit down so
what was the first day after Heather
suicide like wow it's okay I guess
terrible thing so will we get to meet
this Dark Horse prom continue maybe god
damn will somebody tell me why I smoke
these damn things because you're an
idiot oh yeah that's it you too um great
pad tape drying up to motor for I want
to be ready for that funeral
I blame not heaven but rather a society
that tells its youth that the answers
can be found in the mtv video games we
must pray that the other teenagers of
Sherwood Ohio know the name of that
righteous dude who can solve their
problems it's Jesus Christ and he's in
the boat
oh god this is a tragic thing and
sometimes I have a hard time dealing
with it and stuff please send Heather to
heaven and all that dear God please make
sure this never happens to me cuz I
don't think i can handle suicide fast
early acceptance into an Ivy League
school and please let it be Harvard amen
Jesus got in heaven why'd you have to
kill such hot snatch to joke man geez
people are so serious Hail Mary who
aren't in heaven pretty for all the
sinners so we don't get cly another joke
I prayed for the death of Heather
Chandler many times and I felt bad every
time I did it but I kept doing it anyway
now I know you understood everything
praise Jesus Alan louia hi I'm sorry
technically I did not kill Heather
Chandler but hey Who am I trying to kid
right I just want my high school to be a
nice place amen that's so bitchy
Veronica what are you doing tonight I
don't know morning maybe watch some TV
why Ram asked me out tonight but he
wants to double with Kurt and Kurt
doesn't have a date Heather I have
something going with JD please Veronica
took Billy the Kid on hole tonight your
best friend so we all night matter what
I don't know still gonna talk to Heather
dude wait a few more huh what club
laugher just stepped on my foot let's
kick his ass off we're seniors goddamn
geek ah well sit and spin all right now
he's shit fat you like to suck big dicks
oh say i like to suck big dicks leave
him alone rent
say it
say it okay okay you like to suck big
dicks oh oh oh I like this up big dicks
oh hmm I can't get enough of them are
you satisfied don't worry Rams been so
sweet lately consoling me and stuff
it'll be really very promise okay just
as long as it's not gonna be one of
those nights where they get shit-faced
and take us to a pastor and a tip cows
he's asleeping dude i did so mean
come here shit got to be fucking great
punch it got a three guy 12 when I get
that feeling I need sexual healing
you're right asshole what is this shit
doing a favor for Heather double date I
tried to tell you at the funeral but you
wrote off another fucking Heather yea
sorry I'm feeling a little superior
tonight seven schools and seven states
and the only thing different is my
locker combination our love is God let's
go get a slushie
I'm not belittling the foodless fun
Peter sister brother talking teen
suicide here and ask Alison the number
one song in America today his teenage
suicide don't do it by big fun but Jesus
men Westerberg finally got one of these
things and I'm not gonna blow it great
so Heather gets the front page and I get
crammed in by the taco bell Cooper hi
guys came to check up on this week's
lunchtime cool topic hey don't worry
about Veronica sit down the funeral
yesterday must have really been rough
huh oh yeah what we were wondering if
you had any poems artwork that Heather
did that we can put in the Heather
Chandler yearbook spread Oh what I'm not
gonna take a look it's a two-page layout
with her suicide note right up here in
the Horner it's more tasteful than it
sounds I don't know Dennis this stuff
leaves a bad taste in my mouth like last
night veronic excuse me I don't get it
well you did last night Kurt told us on
your little date yeah and I left him
drunk and flailing and cow shit well I
don't know he was really detailed shut
up Courtney no don't shut up I'd like to
know exactly what I did oh come on
Veronica I'll show you the lunchtime
poll top what the fuck okay now I rarely
listen to Neanderthals like Kurt Kelly
but he said that he and RAM had a nice
little sword fight in your mouth last
night you know what I mean hmm Oh son of
a bitch hi Kurt hi this is Veronica
Sawyer yeah I didn't expect to be
calling either i guess my emotions took
over yeah I was wondering if you wanted
all those things you've been saying to
really happen it's always been a fantasy
of mine to have two guys at once sure
you can write to penthouse forum
yeah in the woods behind the school at
dawn don't forget Ram I don't get the
point of me writing a suicide know when
we're just gonna be shooting them with
blanks but we're not gonna be using
blanks this time you can't be serious
yeah listen my Bonnie and Clyde days are
over wheezing wheezing do you take
german french all right these are a clue
ghable 'it's my grandfather snared a
shitload of them back in ww2 they're
like tranquilizers only they break the
surface of the skin enough to cause a
little blood but no real damage so it
looks like the person's been shot and
killed and really they're just lying
there unconscious and bleeding right see
we shoot curtain ram make it look like
they shout each other and by the time
they were gained consciousness they'll
be the laughingstock of the whole school
the notes the punchline how'd that turn
out first tell me the similarity is not
incredible it's incredible similarity
hmm ram and i died the day we realized
we could never reveal our forbidden love
to an uncaring an understanding world
the joy we shared in each others arms
was greater than any touched down yet we
were forced to live the lie of sexist
beer-guzzling jock assholes it's perfect
ah let's take a look at some of the
homosexual artifacts I dug up land at
the scene all right I'm issue is stud
puppy great candy dish Joan Crawford
postcard
mascara all right and here's the one
perfecto thing I picked up mineral water
oh come on a lot of people drink mineral
water it's come a long way yeah but this
is Ohio I mean if you don't have a
brusque in you and you might as well be
wearing a dress oh you're so smart hi
Veronica hi guys
glad you can make it
so should I just whip it out well I've
made a circle on each side of the
clearing Ram you come over here Kurt
when you get to the circle strip what
about you I was kind of hoping you could
rip my clothes off me sport oh good idea
okay count of three guys one
two
three you miss him completely Gavin
don't worry it was worth it just to see
the look on don't move holla I'll get
him back
now
hey I heard at that time what another
gunshot from the woods oh shit let's
roll Kurt doesn't look too good just
remember he's left-handed mother of shit
call in heard something out there I'm
checking it out yeah this is officer
McCord I've got two dead bodies in the
woods behind Westerburg high
you
everyone's going down uh yeah yeah i
think what i heard back there was just a
bunny rabbit all i got here is a should
not pry them apart no no forget it i got
all the answers back here I there naked
yeah so what's the deal suicide double
suicide the shot each other hey that's
Kurt Kelly yeah and the linebacker Ram
Sweeney Shh my god suicide why does this
answer your question oh man he were
facts listen up we realized we could
never reveal our forbidden love to an
uncaring an understanding world jesus H
Christ the quarterback buggering the
linebacker what a waste oh the humanity
so we killed them didn't we colors
if we both I'm such it hits look you
believed it because you wanted to
believe it your true feelings were too
gross and icky for you to face I did not
want them dead you did too I did not did
till I did not did too i did not sit
down did not do i didn't know what come
on you did you're just letting little
innovation young love did you hear
schools canceled today because curtain
ram killed themselves in a repressed
homosexual suicide pact no way God
football season is over Veronica curtain
ram had nothing to offer the school but
date rapes and AIDS jokes sure can we
make an ice run before the funeral
there's any way you can hear me Kirk
buddy
I don't care that she really were some
pansy you're my own flesh and blood and
no you may be proud my son's a
homosexual and I love him I love my dead
gay son and you can keep react to his
son that had a limp wrist with a pulse
dear diary my teen angst bullshit has a
body count the most popular people in
school are dead everybody's sad but it's
a weird kind of sad suicide gave Heather
depth Kurt a soul Ram a brain I don't
know what it's given me but I've got no
control over myself when I'm with JD are
we going to prom or to hell now it seems
we were in a similar position on Monday
when I thoughtfully suggested we get
everybody together for an unadulterated
emotional outpouring but no you took
this as an opportunity to play yet
another round of let's laugh at the
hippie Pauline shut up halt I've seen a
lot of bullshit angel dust switchblades
sexually perverse photography exhibits
involving tennis racquets but this
suicide thing guess that's more on
Pauline's wavelength well we're just
gonna write off today and on Friday she
can hold her little love you know
whatever whatever
please this school has been torn apart
by tragedy i'm here today to fuse it
back again togetherness i want everyone
to class pants we need to connect this
cafeteria into one mighty sark excuse me
please hey llama through competiti crew
lucky paws let me we're ready when you
are hi there looks like Miss flem's on
another one of her crusade fusional
success of course
this is good for you as it is for me
greetings and salutations I'm gonna need
to be addressed copy of all this by
monday for my princeton application
that scene this afternoon I'm so angry
was chaos fucking chaos are you talking
about huh I mean today was great chaos
is great que haces what killed the
dinosaurs darling face it our way is the
way I mean we scare people in the mouth
being assholes our way is not our way oh
yeah tell that to the judge alright tell
it to Kirk Kelly oh I'm telling it to
you God you can be so immature oh you
kids are making too much damn noise we
beat division beautiful the Beavers home
judge told him to slurp shit and die I
put a Norwegian in the boiler room hmm
masterful and then winnett flu and set
up a pack of thermals I stuck upstairs
now some days it's great to be alive do
you like your father never given the
matter much thought like my mother I
said her death was an accident but she
knew what she was done she walked into
the building two minutes before my dad
blew the place up she waved at me and
then boom dude if I get one more request
for that big fun song I'm playing our
song
that's it we're breaking up what she
can't bring him back you must know that
i am not trying to bring anybody back
except maybe myself and i think there
was a time and i actually thought you
were cool man if you can't deal with me
now then just stay home and shoot your
TV blow up a couple of toasters or
something just don't come to school and
don't mess with me you'll be back
me and Martha dumptruck where did you
get this huh I just had the nicest
little chat with Miss dump truck got
along famously it's kind of scary you
everybody's got a little story to tell
him you don't want to see the canoeing
counts what is this blackmail I'll give
you a week's lunch money I don't want
your money I want your strength and
Westerberg does not need mushy
togetherness it needs a strong leader
Heather Chandler was that leader but but
she couldn't handle it I think you can
Moby Dick is dunked the white whale
drank some bad plankton and splashed
through a coffee table and now it's your
turn to take the helm what about the
photographs I don't worry I'll ask you
to do me a favor that'll be one you'll
enjoy and you get the negatives and
everything back then but in the meantime
strength here's a little gift
guess who ever
oh hello Betty this is Veronica I don't
believe it i'm winning don't you start
getting cocky on me now girl and i
really missed you i know i'm not as
exciting as your other friends that is
bullshit shoot you know i'm still a
virgin ok i french-kissed Alice bring
her once it was a total disaster shoot
the ball
no Betty your daydreams are a lot better
than my reality is believe me but now
prepare to die Ronnie
well you're not just gonna go for those
two shots I mean go ahead knock me out
it's the only way to win it's not my
style nice guys finish last I should
know
Bravo Ron Oh tonight I gotta get home
okay okay thanks hi Betty hi Betty
leaving so soon I'm red
the Westerberg suicides were tough on
all of us but we shared the pain of
losing three very popular service I came
into the cafeteria asked them to hold
hands it's not that like we met at the
open house burst of cleansing
synchronicity TV cameras having onto our
path the couch encina synchronicities
emotional outpouring of emotion
outpouring of emotion look there's
Heather on his Heather were you bronica
before a teenager decides to kill
himself there are certain facts that he
should know after all this is a decision
that affects always and there's only one
chance to get it right
getting some super dick turn that back
on can't you see these little programs
are eating suicide up with a spoon
they're making it sound like it's a cool
thing to do are you trying to tell me it
is not a time for troubled youth stand
up straight all we want is to be treated
like human beings not to be experimented
on like guinea pigs or patronized like
bunny rabbits I don't patronize bunny
rabbits treated like human beings is
that what you said Little Miss voice of
a generation just how do you think
adults act with other adults you think
it's all just a game of doubles tennis
when teenagers complain that they want
to be treated like human beings it's
usually because they are being treated
like human beings yeah well I guess I
picked the wrong time to be a human
being well you will live
once in part a hi everybody door is open
Veronica have you heard we were doing
chinese at the Food Fair when it comes
over the radio that Martha dumptruck
tried to buy the farm she belly flopped
in front of a car wearing a suicide note
Bobby is she dead no that's the
punchline she's alive and in stable
condition another case of a geek trine
imitate the popular people of the school
and failing this family is that partay I
said I was sorry you were out of control
I mean heatherton court was shocked but
Martha dumptruck get crucial she'd out
suicide hotlines in her diapers you're
not funny look Martha couldn't take the
heat so she got out of the kitchen just
like what a better place this world
would be of every Nimrod followed her
cue to shut up hot probs is on oh shit
yeah i mean like skippers okay but still
sometimes I feel like like I'm on that
island and Gilligan can just be so
stupid sometimes yeah well dude just
remember you know if it wasn't for the
courage of the fearless crew the middle
would be lost and you are too next call
can I found it like you've got the dog
catcher my name is Heather no it's not
Heather no it's Madonna geez no not that
hey babe I need a name
my name is tweety tweety whoa tweet God
has cursed me I think the last guy I had
sex with killed himself the next day
failing math my whole life is a mess I
was supposed to be captain of the
cheerleading team she knows we listen of
this show me who we shit well cruise a
buyer Heather told everyone about
Heather yes dear diary I've cut off
Heather Chandler's head and Heather
Dukes head has sprouted back in its
place like some mythological thing my
eighth-grade boyfriend would have known
about
Heather's even doing the old note trick
I've seen JD's way I've seen miss
Pauline Fleming's way and nothing has
changed I guess that's Heather's way in
Jesus what about JD I can't get him out
of my head wait where's Heather going
what's Heather going she's going to cry
fucking child tip your caps now where's
she going
tell me what are you trying to do more
sleep suicide is a private reading
Heather you're throwing your life away
to become a statistic than us fucking a
today now that is about the least
private thing I can think of what about
Heather and curtain round everyone jump
off a bridge would you probably if you
were happy every day of your life you
can be a human being a big game show
host what do you say we knock off early
by some shoe something lame like that
okay
so it's come to this Heather Chandler
did polls I want you to do a petition as
a favor as the favor you've heard of the
group big fun right that's right teenage
suicide don't do it right some
teenybopper rag says that they want to
play a prom now it could be Westerberg
if we get everybody's John Hancock I'll
get right on it coach Oh a little gift
for you I won't be needing it
you
Heather Veronica culinary stoked girl
I've gotten everyone to sign this
petition even the ones who think big fun
are tuneless euro fags people love me
you know you haven't signed yet people
love you but I know you Jennifer Forbes
told me the petition she signed was to
put a hot tub in the cafeteria and Doug
Hilton said some people need different
kinds of convincing than others look
just sign the petition okay don't talk
to me like that okay Luke it was JD's
idea he made out the signature sheet and
everything so why don't you just sign it
no jealous much Heather why can't you
just be a friend why are used to Jamaica
bitch because I can be Veronica why are
you pulling my dick do you think I mean
do you really think of Betty fins fairy
godmother made her cool she would still
hang out with heard we bet friends no
way Veronica uh-huh
want to go out tonight catch a movie
house miniature golf just thinking more
along the lines of slitting Heather
Dukes wrist soap and making it look like
a suicide ah now you're talking I could
be up for that I've already started
underlining meaningful passages and her
copy of Moby Dick you know what I mean I
need be back Veronica I knew it was
positive sure
it's over JD / grow up I do get it I
mean you were wrong I was right strength
dammit ma come back
yes
your friend Jason Dean stop by he seemed
very concerned about you he said that he
thought you might try to kill yourself
you have been depressed lately oh he
left this for you oh my god he said that
we should keep you away from sharp
objects are closed garage doors chemical
substances brick prescription drugs
you
neither love nor reverence kind and even
for hate how can speak ill and all I
killed I like it it's got that what a
cruel world's let's toss ourselves in
the abyss type ambiance huh come on so
there's copy a Moby Dick aren't you give
it a try huh underline something get off
of my bed you're fucking psycho your
rebel do you actually think you're a
rebel on a rebel you're fucking
psychotic you say tomato I say tomahto
older Eskimo it's one word I love it I
usually go for the whole sentence myself
but this is perfecto Eskimo you know
it's so uh mysterious has chemo
mag mag mag mag neck name is filthy do
you think I'm gonna do it take out her
tonsils excuse me I think I know Heather
a little bit better than you do if she
was gonna slit her wrists the knife
would be spotless hi how's it so I can
see your fucking reflection and the
thing
tomorrow someone else is just gonna move
into her place that person could be me
there's only one of us who knows how to
drew Heather's handwriting and if you
think I'm gonna write another suicide no
you're wrong so get it do you Society
nods his head at any harder the American
teenager can think to bring upon itself
hello nobody's good care about exact pan
writing
sucks it's perfecto
please I've got a meaningfully marked up
Moby Dick what else does as soon as I
need huh have you excuse me
Eskimo
Heather Duke underlined a lot of things
in this copy of Moby Dick but I believe
the word is school underlined all by
itself is the key to understanding
Heather's aim on the surface Heather
Duke was the vivacious shoveling we all
knew her to be but the soul was in
Antarctica freezing with the knowledge
of the way fellow teenagers can be cruel
the way that parents can be unresponsive
and as she writes so eloquently in her
suicide note the way that life can suck
we'll all miss Sherwood's little Eskimo
let's just hope she's rubbing noses with
Jesus is this turnout week what at least
70 more people at my funeral Heather
from okay
right after life is so boring if I have
to sing Kumbaya one more time what are
you doing here I need your favorite
spaghetti lots of oregano
dear diary last entry no one can stop JD
not the FBI the CIA or the PTA he once
told me that the extreme always makes an
impression well now it's my turn let's
see how the son-of-a-bitch reacts to a
suicide he didn't perform himself
can't believe he did it I was teasing
loved you churros was coming up here to
kill you first I was gonna try and get
you back with my amazing petition it's a
shame you can't see what her fellow
students really signed all right listen
we students of Westerburg high will die
today our burning bodies will be the
ultimate protest to a society that
degrades us fuck you all it's not very
subtle but neither is blowing up a whole
school now is it talk about your suicide
pacts huh when our school blows up
tomorrow it's gonna be the kind of thing
to infect a generation I mean it's gonna
be a Woodstock for the 80s
dammit Veronica we could have toast some
marshmallows together where's she want a
written invitation Veronica Veronica uh
I should have let you take that job at
the mall it was it was just that I I was
afraid of you coming home late at night
or not hey mom why so tense hey brah I
need some help with my homework ah not
right now Tiger I'm busy
JD told me you committed suicide last
night where is he where's JD we have to
talk whether to kill yourself or not is
one of the most important decisions a
teenager can make kid
where's everybody going it's Friday
should be you damned episode wait yeah
now these things can get pretty
artificial but at least you get out of
class Rodney what's underneath the gym
the boiler room
may I see your Hall Pass I knew that was
too news I mean nuff news truce damn you
like father like son a serious is fuck
bomb in the boiler room to set off a
pack of thermals upstairs okay let's
start by putting the bomb down on the
ground I knew that I knew that okay put
your hands on your head you didn't say
Simon Says
mmm
think just because you started this
thing he can end it I'll kill you I'll
fucking kill you I swear to God how do I
drew up the goddamn phone asshole fuck
you
all over JD help me started
I'm gonna clean the slate as much as I
do all right so maybe I am killing
everyone in the school there's nobody
loves me let's face it hurt the only
place different social types can
genuinely get along with each other is
in heaven
winch button do i press to trade off try
the red one right seriously people I
gotta look at the ashes of Westerberg
insane now there is a school that
self-destruct did not because society
didn't care but because the school was
society its reach deeper
the middle to turn it off that's what
you really want you know what I'm hot
babe
cool guys like you out of my life
let me impress you really fucked me up
pretty bad Veronica hey you um you got
power power I didn't think you had slate
is clean
Tendai did blow up the school all the
schools how that you're dead what are
you gonna do with your life
veronica you look like hell yeah I just
got back rhyn'athel are you doing
Heather my love there's a new sheriff in
town hey Martha my deep for the prom
kind of flaked out on me I was wondering
if you're doing anything that night babe
could rent some new releases pop some
popcorn I'd like that yeah so would i
I asked time
well
d
you
future
well will