[Music]
an illuminating history bearing on the
everlasting struggle for world supremacy
brought between the powers of technology
and magic
the world grew up in a thousand atomic
fireball first blast was set off by five
terrorists
it took two million years for some of
the radioactive clouds to allow some sun
in by then only a handful of human
survived the rest of humanity had
changed into hideous mutants these
mutant species floundered in the bad
areas radioactive lands that never
allowed them to become human again and
made each birth a new disaster then in
the good lands they came back arising
from their long sleep fairies hell
dwarves the true ancestors of man they
lived happily in a good areas it was a
big day in Montague our diria queen of
the berries was presiding over the feast
of Plenty celebrating three thousand
years of peace in the midst of the
celebration
Delia felt a pool from the skies she
looked up and saw dark clouds forming on
the horizon in every direction she fell
into a trance and left the party heading
for home on a high hill
at first the fairies puzzled but then
they too felt the force drawing and
follow Delia was alone inside the storm
grew until it was a raging cyclone
hovering over the dwelling one of the
older fairies ventured inside the house
air lady on her bed holding a pair of
twins in her arms
the older very instantly knew that these
were not ordinary twins but magical
Wizards the baby Wizards were polarized
like magnets on attracting with a
magnetic draw the other repelling and
impossible to get me avatar the kind and
good wizard spent much of his boyhood
entertaining his mother with beautiful
visions black or the mutant wizard would
never visit his mother and spent his
time torturing small animals more years
passed and do your continued to slip
finally all life drained out of her and
avatar held her hand trying desperately
to use his magic to restore her he
cradled her in his arms when black or
found that his mother had died he was
excited for now he felt he would take
over her leadership and rule the land
when avatar confronted black wolf he was
in rain
aged began a furious battle each using
his magic they continued until they had
nearly destroyed each other
but avatars magic was stronger because
he had the emotional loss of his mother
that drove the black was defeated the
day will come my brother when I will
return and make this a planet where
mutants rule black wolf headed off
leaving avatar very disturbed
[Music]
time has come
he is called necron 99 he is one of
black wolf assassins he travels the land
destroying the believers of magic
[Music]
my children the only true technology is
nature all the other forms of manmade
technology are perversions the ancient
dictators use technology to slave the
masses
[Music]
tonight
no just for a few hours risk
I sense something but the road is clear
we haven't seen the fasten four days a
clever assassin stays hidden Avatar must
be warned missions over west wing but
now it's time for one final run
[Music]
[Applause]
camera
well they're not back yet
my president they really late now i
think oh you reserve bad magic isn't it
and if they don't show you know no more
than you did be four how true very got
us in a new world but if they don't show
i think that will tell us something to
damage avatar if there's any danger
maybe we shouldn't maybe we should arm
our state's science and technology and
is no time for that even if we could
impress our people with the dangerous
science and technology were outlawed
millions of years ago and we must admit
it's been a peaceful world since then no
out Panik takes me all that's left on
the Avatar can meet folks next fair you
can see I'm only half they're all right
all right I'll tell you
if you think you can handle what do you
know about war about bombs and to turn a
planet molten liquid think it could
start again and million years after the
final one
[Music]
sometimes I get tired of being so old
sometimes and a wizard is probably at
the time we're waiting old old wizard
you know about my brother
well as a years past i search for my
brother in vain he had settled in the
dark land of Scorch where people still
died of radiation for 5,000 years
black wolf studied Black Arts increasing
his wisdom 10,000 old he built a small
following of frog like creatures but
needed more troops for his evil plans
he then formed an army whose generals
were called up from the black shadows of
Health souls who waited for untold
eternities for a new leader black Wolf's
tremendous power enslave them all to
carry out his will then stories of black
Wolf's armies attacking neighboring
countries came back he'll armed with
black magic but they would get bored or
sidetracked in the middle
i'm going to give up going home
[Music]
Fritz get up for God's sake get up to
kill strength that killed Fred
that's a lot of this stinking yellow
fairy a bullet choppy fell further
that's your lot of the lorders that
killed right they got maximum okay I'm
okay max just a screenshot to look at my
Robbie oh damn
there you go again stepping on my lines
raining on my parade costing me metals
oh damn Fritz Fritz get up for God's
sake it up Dave killed for its they've
just wax berries horrible the Japanese
palmyra they could easily have one but
they lack the motivation and inspiration
black wolf knew he needed more he said
his huge armies out to excavate ancient
ruins for links to the past
tails reach avatar at bits and pieces of
pre Holocaust technology for being dug
up and marched back to scorch one with
these ancient pieces he built a new war
machine still his generals needed more
to fight with this drove black wolf mad
with frustration
monday that frustration vanished i sent
my ELF spies to find out what was
happening
I'm sure he has found some great power
that will control his armies you mean
you sent out that elf envoy to
investigate based on a vague feeling of
you
[Music]
[Applause]
I failed you my wizard I've failed you
my president
[Music]
what news do you bring the lights
without the lights went out
199 have destroyed himself
it's done with the assassination of the
presidents of the free states comes for
and that of my mother it's done we have
four more light less for more time
important the main extermination
complete the remaining countries and our
rule by second rating confidence so
confused that even holistically the
killings on those within their own ranks
it's time Mike
I
[Music]
hey hey come on my bottom get up black
wolves Colin go eight black wolf calls
we go finally got out but what I heard
things anymore it's a bit like I'm
stupid to listen you don't be treat
burns butterfly everything got a right
to live you know what I mean everything
going to want to live anywhere black
gloves got a secret weapon and makes it
invincible we can lose weight quick
[Music]
it will never work people don't want war
it destroyed this planet its people and
all records the past civilization not
all records as you'll soon find out
attention run leaders of tomorrow's last
raid
[Music]
the time has come as i promised the time
when I reveal to you my loyal followers
they ancient secret of War the key to
creating hysteria fear
[Music]
[Applause]
black marks armies come again our cousin
ads are already in the trenches it's our
love Atlanta to open and fairyland
united we fly
[Music]
healthy do you those drums should you be
wittle I don't believe those books are
gonna try it again
I'm scared Wow
and don't be governor too young to
remember black wolf must have lost 1
million men here last time he tried to
invade and a black were stupid enough to
try it again he lose trace more they're
goblins and demons just look mean but
the ya got no cause to fight he always
give up and running with hours chasing
them all the way home
he's always been that way they will
always be the same had to choose buys
yeah
[Music]
ok
we are what they're always been doing
for four hours if he's looking for
answers from that assassin my father's
sword can get quicker than brain-eating
cool down cool down
I got and I ain't good
the key is a dream machine that inspires
on these what ancient war images and
must be destroyed it is in black Wolf's
castle in the land a Squatch when do we
need we are mainly you gotta be kidding
i'm too old for this sort of thing just
wake me up when a planet's destroy well
I'm not too old
I'll go myself very noble how we're
going I must avenge my father's death
ok no fairyland out the kid but alright
alright I was just testing
well well what
well what now
I don't know oh why don't you sit there
for a couple hours well I figure it out
okay
[Music]
avatar alright alright how do we find
this machine is creature i should call
him peace peace in the hopes that he
will bring it
he somehow wire to the Machine and the
only freedom will ever had from its
painful grip is in its destruction going
on both you and prepare for the journey
I'll reason when he wake of the dog
you're not that old
she's gotta be kidding and it looks like
my brother and I now begin out final
battle we Hawk spin tonight
sync by to his tribe asking them to
protect his family and to name a new
chief if he did not return
Eleanor said goodbye to her father and
then the other fairies of a kind she
told them she will return as Queen of
montego father's death revenged and
herself full-fledged very well I'll be
right down heroes
alright creep before I am tired i want
to tell you a couple things and I want
you to listen and listen carefully this
has been the biggest bummer of a trip
I've ever been on
you let me down i got my friends
especially abroad I got stuff planned
for you that will take 20 years to kill
you no pain and you'll be screaming from
mercy and at first five seconds peace
once loved 13 will help but just get it
you got it
don't be sad Eleanor I'll kill that
monster as soon as he shows us that
projected you kids ready this piece here
he knows everything towards scratch I
promised them life without pain life
without fear I still don't trust him
hey you know both forgetting you have
the protection of a powerful wizard
damn it get all the wood not much bolder
I wonder if I back my sketch and just a
song I don't want to but that's why we
brought you home
[Music]
we're really doing is guarding our home
there's been a war and this land is lost
why can't they find me because they have
weapons and technology we just have
loved it
and Louie what are we gonna do with the
prisoners
how do I know that finding out right now
hmm York was displayed some bowling its
religion manage your religion
yeah black wolf says the
responsibilities of the prisoners is up
to the priests inside now what we gotta
do
dumbo was recognized in a pre-season
find out bits and pieces of religion man
what's the matter with you all the
objects they say for millions of years
man who we looking for here so dumb
we're looking for please man priests
would I don't know I guess because you
need God and your side's stupid who's
good at stamp over them
oh listen you guys we interrupt you know
sorry
yeah but you see black wolf you know I
fewer wasn't our fault
sure we Blackwell got fewer and started
this war see we got all these prisoners
we want to feed them with something like
Piper we just can't type of war so we
were out I want to ask you guys can do
not move
yeah I'm asking you if you guys want to
take Carol it's okay with us right to ya
see you too
yeah okay Dumbo Luke my son's you say
you are the victors
uh-huh but there is only one 15 that's
him
AKA patients you must first observe
sundown and pray he's got a point here
are so loud here our petition not sure
but the Royal not created a dozen guns
for hands and I higher
running up to recognize that you can
build brown hair
[Music]
alright it's been five hours
time's up look okay Charlie it's no good
put planning to work about time
ok baby ain't gonna talk gimme plan B
what's plan B
a what
[Music]
the birthday soon very soon a lot you
are young to be queen but deliver me a
son you shall help you rule this planet
I don't want to rule this planet my lord
just our kingdom is enough enough enough
for mutants to stay in their place maybe
with radiation so our bodies crawl with
hell we will live in the good lands my
son will grow with tourism death and the
very bored as we drink here we breathe
wise men my son be human or mutant
mutant the chart say below the next one
won't be do not have me killed
[Music]
wait a minute avatar piece is taking us
towards the mountain fairies domain we
should go around avatar is peace tapping
very bad not good go around
hey come on mr. nice guy here those
fairies must be something else go on
that we lose time the very elves and
fairies of bad blood cousins and I'm not
in the mood for the pranks they may have
useful information
don't worry time has passed much a
rivalry between Terry and else has
subsided Syrians the whole candy
polychrome by my sword there is no way
to treat a lady hope Andy stop this
childish display why even else house
I've seen more sophisticated magic
alright alright you've had this is
avatar great you're fooling with avatar
console and and wizard of your
great-grandfather's consoles who was
turned into avatari old that's me a
makati old now I still got my powers and
you cross be my patients i call upon all
forces of darkness
Oh winds up mrs. howling through the
Stars many centuries
world and black gray and white
I calling
[Music]
increasing darkness shapeless and minus
beams corona and wrapped in your body
summon you
arrange time
right and please accept our apologies
for the behavior of some of our more
carefree brothers i'm sean meter of the
Knights of Stardust protectors of Dolan
king of the mountain fairies we have
prepared a feast to welcome you to our
humble domain
listen here you little wing it squirt
ideal realize the ground baby i'm a
baton now this year is Ellen we know
Martha god what brings you here
our on a quest to reach the land of
scorch you're heading for scorch afraid
you're in for trouble when you tell us
what you know
steady was with we leave alone unless we
sit with pools mitra worse piece allies
you fool
hey watch that assassin
[Music]
school and do lack Iraq oh that's one
thing I knew we should've killed him we
had the chance with my spine Eleanor the
fairies have taken her into the mountain
hey there's some time to waste
no one should have been two very
sanctuary before it's forbidden the war
drums begins
quickly now all is lost is a gallon 30
little fish at enough magical man run
[Music]
ok
very not good not good human technology
would it be proper against brother here
to only humans kill their own time she
loves technology and depth golden the
trade-off you pull release me straight
back for the Kings God's we kind of are
you there until the King rode over
Eleanor of months ago we
[Music]
avatar never told me i had full fairy
powers and I was ready you
I told you she's dangerous destroy what
is hi Howard you want to go and do that
for all of these are not controlling
those days relates me off
I Eleanor shall show oh you and
something
[Music]
you better stop him better if you
release mean we all ran
[Music]
[Applause]
always grown ellen has really gone and
that's all of his ass while Rome do
about it
you better hurry up miss have a time the
great coming
yeah you can kill me now i'm sure i've
given myself to I make no attempt to
save myself thank you sell save yourself
I can Alan are the only one who could
might be the King here my missional art
is to save the world from another
Holocaust Sean was killed not by us but
by my brother's assassin will been sent
to kill we are Allen peace and myself
before we reach Scotch for all I know
when fear we love is dead so might be
peace is for permission to take the girl
and myself to try to complete our
mission alone though it does seem doomed
now I will not allow you to hurt Eleanor
without a fight by myself
one that beat times getting short avatar
accretionary absolutely we have been
sent yet images and human each with a
different story something happening here
can you please I have always been very
good and can even be better sometimes
the only act has been real shofar is the
fact that avatar did not break his word
when the arrow struck e he did not write
back and from what we all heard about a
ménage power that surely the side
we will need our drawing nor Hinda not
help these two we will wait and see that
is audition
[Music]
wow we're out of their couch
oh thanks i forgot about that and me up
you know let me help
very pretty avatar
yeah well and it could be warmer we
might as well begin this is the way I
think scotch lie somewhere over these
mounds
[Music]
how to Marty cozy morning huh
Oh avatar attract is not a little hard
work won't yard
follow me Snow Queen
[Music]
so cold so cold so much father
Helen we've rested long enough we better
move on
I'll just a little while longer at the
time so tired
wow ok and I'll go over and see if I can
see a pass or for a path our house
[Music]
oh my god are all tracks
in that moment in circles
[Music]
and I'm not tell little do I not good at
the top-right run
assassin's come to finish the job right
they split up going to come at us from
each in time we really try didn't we
yeah and that's all anyone really could
have done study getting up
praxis relaxes traxxas Almighty God for
every piece we found him we find him
what took you so long quickly piece
quickly let's get about this glacier
question shave the night was spent in
the protection of the cane Eleanor and
we Hawk slept as avatar council with
piece on the quickest route to scorch
the journey took them past the ruins of
ancient civilizations strange beast
worked about the dangerous mutants that
live there were gone gone to black
Wolf's army all they left with their
wives hurling insults and rocks at the
party past
and finally together I feel
please do not attempt to draw your gun
avatar you come haha
[Music]
[Applause]
we've been camping in the death away
from prying I when you get the guns out
though God
well we got them from old black wolf
himself
you mean you join haha purple know we
ambushed a wolf patrol took everything
except their women and two days from now
we attack scorch one on a mean attack
the remaining elves of the free world
have joined under my bed that banner
will be carried to sports want join us
old wizard we desperately need
is this how you repay me turn back of
the car will not be touched in our world
was young so was mighty avatar
mr. moons ago he strode this planet like
a messiah curing radiation sickness from
man and bird cleaning the planet itself
it was avatar who fought alongside my
father against the first muted attack so
now we have our Messiah back again he's
going to destroy his brother for it with
what a woman child 1l and a moron
[Music]
what is it explains
you did you beat the demon what's
happened
well I suddenly felt very sorry for
peace so I went over to him and took his
hand when he tried to confidence pieces
and constant mental battle with no kind
words took his mind off the battle in a
lot of black his chance
what
[Music]
john pease job
retail development to the quest is
broken his heart there's nothing wrong
with it tomorrow morning attack begins
at the time we have to go now the cliff
scorch can be seen we have to go now to
complete our mission huh
we have to swim
[Music]
watch
remember by michelle wie scorch Rome
come we'll walk right up the road and
don't expect it like slaves
yeah the castle see it that's quite a
distance
[Music]
I was really
that must be the interest in the lower
cities are guards might be about come up
mm how hard we how widely in the leader
for news on college and how's it going
which were now I should've stayed with
hail of ammeter yeah just stay quiet huh
again around beard so many is for sale
precious over his get them i was still
hot
no more wash your pulls Wow Scott can be
beautiful to look real beautiful prairie
dog is out the whole trick from the room
its have a tough time general it's him
it's bad it's come to hurt the fewer
kill oh master kill it
what's it worth
man this are my father great haha that
is so then why I am I wore on Uncle haha
funny you should say that
[Music]
o master my god what have I done master
loves very master feed very what else is
good for avatar good-luck piece to show
us the way to the castle
I'm sorry we heart I'm just an old fool
you know the world owes you much good
even if we don't take another step
[Music]
ok
and
[Music]
[Applause]
ok
[Music]
God have a target down
I've seen him it can't be them is too
strong
avatar don't do it you may be right but
i gotta battle my brother you'll find an
entrance into the castle smash to
project until al anointed avatar will
die with her tonight even if we win how
you have aged full the world is mine
[Music]
what stop L blood on blood flowing
fathers and sons dying brothers and
lovers filling jorge and rivers of life
flowing away
who else think your sword is always
quick what else think we walk i couldn't
help when i touched piece in the desert
black will track my mind I'm not a
strongest piece it hurts have a Thomas
no trouble with you my brother that
you've always been too good
wow that maybe but I still think I look
more like modern you do in our lots of
character
I'm agent better brother
there is no need for me to destroy you
surrender surrender your world you
always did need an audience you SAP and
I tell you I practice much magic for a
long time I want to show you what trick
mother showed me when you weren't around
he was on special occasions like this
oh yeah one more thing I'm glad you
changed your last name you
son-of-a-bitch
[Music]
there's no train
the projector destroy the battle zone
shadow creatures rose in their tracks
some faded some crawled back to hell
mutants leaderless ran LOL swept the
beaches clear of the few remaining
mutants that still fought
hundreds of circling Blackford screened
at the carnage below there was some
rejoice
but mostly everyone wish to return home
quickly to tell their loved ones that
the war was won
Hitler was dead again and that they
could live once more in peace in the
land and love so God give hey char could
I cut don't Larry Larry serve piece of a
thousand scale
hey set it free
it's harmless without black wolf it's
not it's fall so be it
thank you thank you thank you master
we ride back to Monte guard we are you
right back to Monte Carlo avatar and i
will start a new Kingdom somehow you
will room on to guard their new king
free you whatever time married my queen
hey can take it easy huh did a good job
I don't get carried away you think
advertise to war to get married we have
how many years do is it lived in
thousand or more and i got at least a
thousand well you know what I mean
give me everything forgive me both of
you for Montague are forever
[Music]
well come on let's make it every time
you're getting older and much older
come on and let's make it out of here
sure you need time
when we
and watch
Oh
maybe
we bring
[Music]
to give