During the reign of Emperor Pu Y,
who called the epoch
prosperity and knowledge of the world,
I lived in the province of Fun gated
one man.
His name was H Thou,
and he was a great hunter.
He got in his craft
such heights
had no equal
throughout China.
He grasped all the nuances
and tricks of the case.
Any animal or bird could
catch in snares and traps.
5 times H Thou took part
in competitions
best hunters China. And never lost.
eleven 00: 00: 54.361 ->
00: 00: 57.360 "PECULIARITIES
OF THE NATIONAL HUNT IN WINTER"
He won
respect of all the famous catchers Empire
without losing modesty
nature and ease of communication.
He wrote treatises on art 8
catching animals and birds.
Pass on their knowledge to many people,
but no one could call
his disciple.
I got bored and he decided to find
worthy of his skill
and ability in other lands.
But anywhere, where would it
went, I could not meet that,
who could compare with him
in skill and knowledge of the case.
Not yet reached the end of the earth,
where all the space is covered with snow,
and winter lasted almost a year.
Residents of this icy country hunted
and fished so
strange ways,
that the shaken ideas and views
H Thou on the art of hunting.
He went into the cold forest,
and after a long wait
he managed to lure into their snares
just one little bird.
Then there were the people with strict
persons
and demanded his license for catching birds
and animals. thirty 00: 02: 09.861 ->
00: 02: 13,360 Curiously, just nothing you
again the structure of the East reached.
He described to the best of our,
domestic hunt.
Yes, we have the same no poetry,
one prose, and vulgar.
Materials, especially
at present,
even on a small tales
do not squeeze out.
Oh, it carries someone hard!
Reached! Wow, Mich!
- Good morning!
- Hello!
- Welcomes guests!
- Good evening!
And you, in fact, anyone?
Yes, actually, I ...
Kurt Yuri. Chief Chief of the
Department of hunting supervision
Ministry of Forestry.
- Actually, we checked.
- Really?
- With the unofficial?
- Naturally, informal.
Welcome!
- Clear. Bath to cook?
- By itself!
- Igor V. Cerenkov.
- Norsemen.
- Assistant Yuri Nikolayev.
- Very nice.
- Well, how do you do!
- Yes!
Good!
Well, there you bored?
Cold, poor fellow!
Well done! Home, home!
Good dog! What's your name?
Whistles!
Whistling?! Original name!
Do not name it!
Young else - he does not deserve the name.
And it is necessary to call up a whistle!
Igor park positivity!
- Mich, and you remember him?
- Who?
Well, this is who
with check arrived.
No, unless they remember them all!
Here they have visited many a season.
Sometimes it feels like
that you live in the city.
Oh, someone else has arrived!
It seems the 13th cordon.
The air is something which, as well!
- Oh, Mom!
- Who is first?
- I am the first!
- And for the first time is not terrible!
- Now, now, now!
- Come on, I'm with you!
Here, Yataro, learn!
Healthy lifestyle!
With a light steam, guys!
We are to you. With test
from the Ministry.
What?
- Good evening!
- That we from the Ministry.
We are from the Ministry of Ecology
and protection natural resources.
I - Measly, Head of Sector,
this is my assistant - Oleg Yataro.
- You - the huntsman?
- No, I'm not a ranger.
I - Head of Department
Ministry of Forestry.
- Do not you see it?
- Can not see. You - naturists?
Yes, we are out of the bath! Do you want to
join us, colleagues?
- Steam Mich canceled!
- Next time.
I'm sorry, I did not catch your
name and patronymic!
Olga V. Measly.
Measly.
Very nice. Yuri.
Sorry.
Olga V., in my opinion,
they are not naturists.
Something of their long gone. As if
polymerize not used to it.
Yes! This change in lifestyle can
a negative impact on their health.
ABOUT! What is it with you? Frozen?
They caught us with you, Igor!
Mich, put it all!
Do not understand! What for?
There's you, Mich
environmentalists arrived.
So what? To me the cordon
many come.
They long ago our Ministry
feuding.
So what to do now?
All! Check the full program.
Do you like with the beast?
- To run out there in the wild.
- That's right, run.
Unfed, I suppose. Without human
heat without a care. Wildly all.
- What happened?
- Environmentalists have come, I tell you!
Home at them - a woman.
I talked about it.
She used by the Ministry of
reclamation took place.
All men, cover holidays!
Yeah, and something very like it, nothing?
Yes, you did not raise such
not to hill.
Or, after the road so bathhouse
load off?
I opponent, and you do not advise.
All our troubles and suffering
But from this.
How could you have with nature, a ranger?
Normally, one might even say -
beautiful nature.
Yes, we have a wonderful nature!
Who to us nor come only:
prosecutors, generals
and all the other officials.
And, without exception, are
lost in admiration
from a modest and unassuming
our nature.
And destroy nature! Bonfires bundle
Trees felled.
- Yes Yes Yes!
- Beasts shoot.
And then wonder: no animals.
How else do you want to test
fat of the beast?
He is an animal, especially a wild,
so simple hands is not given,
so we can check it fat
layer, especially in the winter.
And this tobacco
you break the delicate balance
in our nature.
Tomorrow will begin to examine in detail
your possessions.
Oh please! Whatever you say.
And now to bed!
Rise early in the morning.
- Where is your convenience?
- What kind?
They are in the yard.
How to get out - just behind Apparatchik.
Well, what did I tell you ?!
Now, do not spit without permission.
How - ecological upsets.
You have something hearty like?
I suffer.
Do not worry. Now we fix that your
health. And take off stress.
Jams have something,
that the smell was not?
What insolent, got a skunk?
So now wallowing here!
Oh, Olga V.!
Oh, you snake! There are all sorts here!
Marta brazenly! The toilet has got me!
Olga V., what happened?
Are you okay?
What do you, the huntsman is going on?
The toilet is not possible to go!
Well, I have, of course, special
Comfort is not. But the exotic!
Exotic? It is you
exotic name, huh?
Marta all sorts of types, peep!
Who is it?
This I would like to know
Who is it!
Wow! What is it you?
Fist! In a brazen fist mug! That
not Donovan climb and spy!
- Mich, how is he?
- Breathe!
It is generally quiet,
Only very curious!
Yes. In time the den does not lay down,
That run hither.
And before you here, all of
Prosecutor General's Office arrived!
He have so much vodka throaty!
This is a hangover and suffering!
From this, and to do for you.
For compassion, maybe.
Who is it?
Bear seven years.
Six yet.
I've been watching him since birth.
Precocious and outgoing.
- What is it with you?
- Olga V.! Where are you going?
Olga V., how are you?
Drank!
Well, you, Olga V.!
As can be at work!
- What about him?
- With whom?
- With a bear.
- What will happen to him!
Avenue and will go further.
I checked. You did not crippled.
Thus, in a deep knockout sent.
Well, one came without
his wife and children.
Drink - lives in a frenzy to drown.
- Right, right, Olga V.!
- Exactly.
Oh, do not fuss, Yataro.
Who drinks, he does not understand life.
But she was right.
Well, that and will sit dry?
Norsemen, pour!
And what are you doing
sitting in the suburbs?
Yes, I can not! In the
morning I will suffer.
Oh, do not worry about it.
I've got this air
and the purity of the natural,
that as the baby wake up.
- Well, then as a second?
- I was then in a saucer.
For conspiracy.
Mich absolutely right.
And do not worry about the head,
It will not hurt.
- Well, how?
- Thank you, Olga V.. Excellent!
- Good morning!
- Everything is now all!
- We have work to do.
Just a minute, Yuri.
Please wait a little.
I quickly.
Good morning everybody!
I am in Japan, "rock garden"
Kyoto visited.
Honestly, I did not understand.
Whether it was hot, or we have lunch
warm sake was accepted. I fell asleep.
Yuri, free!
Yuri?
Yuri, and what are they?
A nonsense. Mind and meditation
the head can not be cured. Will not work!
You see here, Igor, find us some
schoolchild. Cabbage better.
- Cabbage?
- Yeah, better than cabbage. Our!
Following, following steps! Boggy swamp!
- Mich!
- A?
- And you can walk narrower?
- I can!
- Carefully, Olga V.!
- So why do you not step?
Boggy swamp! Here in the spring
Geologists have two tractors sucked!
Next in the trail to go. Over bumps.
Haste thee not. I am afraid
that by the night it’ll turn.
Lord. Drink no one, eh?
- On.
- Yeah.
Thank you. Well, let's go?
Why waste time to lose ?!
Why stand? Come on!
Follow me!
- Mich! Large field! - What did you say!
Three of Monaco will get!
- And what is there to grow?
- Sedge, lichen, moss! Swamp it!
A solid!
Oh, judging by the trail of the beast is.
And who's gone?
Vole ran.
And over there - weevil.
And who is this weevil?
Weevil - a small
local predators.
Maybe the fire dissolve, rotogravure?
Bonfires only destroy nature.
Yes, it would not hurt to get warm.
There's still something to drink?
What is it?
- Tea.
- Give!
- It is not tea.
- What?
- Cognac.
- Can not be!
- Come on, will soon begin to darken.
- Exactly!
- Mich!
- A?
But wait you! Where?
Where the road leads, in the end?
- Well, there - on a military
training ground. - So.
- And there - in my cordon.
- So.
A stone's throw!
12 kilometers left.
Ivan Susan in, we could here
by car to get there?
Of course, can! But you yourself
I want to see my land.
Here I have shown and their possessions.
Two of Luxembourg with a tail
almost will.
In my opinion, we all three passed.
Do not understand. And where...?
Mich, well, you ...
The original, great master!
I would say - only the original.
- Do not understand!
- Yes, what is there not to understand?
What the banana you shook us swamps
and snow?
I have all the legs, on the ears, erased!
You've got all of these?
Large? Originals?
No, I do not understand! You also had four!
Where is this - a little?
Yataro.
Dimes! Where are you?
Yataro, to me!
Oleg!
- His traces are still there!
- Where are you?
Dimes!
Oleg!
Grandiloquent us to contact them,
Yuri!
- Yataro!
- Where the predators are there?
There is. Vaughn, took a pair of wolves.
But it's still morning.
Dimes!
- I think his track.
- Oleg!
- Oh, gone!
- Yataro!
Quietly you be quiet!
- Well, there it?
- He slept.
What is it? Dimes! I lay down to sleep!
Snoring! Now I'll get you!
- Well, he was there, alive?
- A living, breathing!
Oleg! Climb!
Now I'm gonna get you!
Dimes, and Come on, get out!
Always with you nothing but trouble!
- In my opinion, he's not alone.
- Trouble.
- Get out. Get out immediately.
- And who is he?
Well, he was there, Olga V.?
There's a bear.
Yuri.
- Oleg. Yataro.
- Olga V..
- Get out slowly.
- Olga V.!
- Come on, come out! Faster!
- I have someone holding the leg!
- Do not Such you down! Not Jeri beast!
- Come on, come on!
- Who?
- Huntsman!
- Not Jeri it!
- Yes, can I help!
- I was someone's leg holds.
- Oleg!
Yes, I say, do not hit the bear
in the face!
- Bear ?!
- Do not hit in the face with a bear down!
- Yes, drag, drag me!
- Yuri! Keep up!
- Where are you going?
- Igor, one do not run away!
You get lost.
Olga V., run after me!
Why be afraid?
- He's home.
- Do not Eli beast!
- Faster, Olga V.!
- Keep a bear!
Do not hurt the animal!
Protect nature, Mich!
Stop! Freeze!
Well, and this is lost.
Good dog, beautiful.
F! F! F!
Get out!
Mikhail, in my opinion,
it's not cordon Mich.
Machinery, doggy some strange.
No, Mich cordon.
I've walked around - "rock garden"
in place.
Yes, with our uncertain
Russian life
anyone can build yourself
not only the "rock garden"
but whatever came.
I mean, unbridled imagination
people went.
Especially far from cultural centers.
This marginalized and alone all
Anything can take a notion in his head.
My professional experience
She suggests:
Mich 4 people at a party.
And one of them - a woman.
So that a shelter can go Mikhail.
Can, if only without women.
Oh I reached.
Hi, Mich!
- Health, Mich!
- Bath, bath, cook!
- I.E?
- We have a strong one frostbitten.
And maybe all four.
Oh, they should rub snow!
Wow, barely overlook!
Especially one - hard!
Who hard? What are you doing?
To shoot someone, huh?
Well no. These are my guests. Barely
through the forest they gathered.
Well, come on, come on! Help, help!
3:10 00: 23: 51.360 ->
00: 23: 54.360 Well, no need
to rub snow - will not help.
Why - the right remedy.
They need hot water.
Do you have suitable containers?
Well there is. Japanese bath, wood.
Furor called.
I have it as a gift from Japan sent.
The idea is that all will be included.
If no complexes.
There is one woman.
Well, not to the complex!
Mich, come quickly, there is still
one stirred.
- Now I go!
- I got warmed. You can stand it.
Where is it? Aha!
Hello? No, it's not Yataro.
He can not talk right now.
Call hassock through the pipe.
Maybe it departs. Aha! Till!
Hello, hello!
What are you doing? You what ?!
You what ?! You hand it to blossom?
I'll show you! I was with the men bare
in the tub to keep ?!
This is not a tub, and the present
Japanese furor!
- It furor.
- I as a gift from Japan sent.
I do not care,
where the tub, the audacity!
- Natural Japanese tree.
- Yes, we have them taken out!
Who knew ?! Oh sorry! Who knew
before you move away ?!
He has become a move!
I know that there they move!
From this and woke up!
- Me? With the naked man?
- Mikhail!
As you were!
You would have been in the heat, and
that in fact, and You can catch a cold.
Who are you?
Leo I am!
Olga V., you remind me
a lady,
I have served in the division
instructor in unarmed combat.
So ...
Yes, I'm sorry, I'll call back later.
On the hunt here?
Why, I dropped a couple of days off -
We decided to rest.
To shoot innocent animals?
Wow, innocent!
And who of the innocent bear I ran
through the forest, but the whole night?
It is another matter! We protect nature,
and you silhouette it for fun!
- Yes Yes Yes!
- Yes, we hunt! It's a sport.
Well, not necessarily
shoot the animals.
In fact, we do not do this.
- Yes.
- We appreciate the process.
- That's it.
- An introduction to the world of nature.
Here you can see for yourself.
Tomorrow, we invite you for a wild boar.
- On whom?
- Wild boar.
Here is the migration path
boars.
They cordon through my neighbors go.
We, too, let's go!
Can I go on migration
see Olga V.?
Black Raven,
what do you sheave
over my head?
- Mikhail, Holocene positivity?
- Yeah!
You production will not wait,
black raven, I'm not yours.
Stop!
Arrived! Hence the numbers stand!
I'm sorry, then I call back.
We have now just arrived
to track the migration of wild boars.
Okay, then explain.
Put the car into the bushes. The motor can
be do not turn off, that he is not afraid.
- But not to make noises!
- Good.
Yes? I can not talk right now.
I just stand on the issue.
Yes, I do not know on what.
I recognize - and then call back.
Sorry, Olga V..
Lou, how are you?
Quiet. Till.
- A Mikhail where?
- There.
- Where?
- I'm here Mich!
Well, whatever our guests?
Do not worry, I'll put them in the road.
They quietly. Kazan not walk.
- Well, no fluff you a pen!
- Yeah!
Just environmentalists.
Forgive me, Olga V..
I have weak lungs.
Should drink less! And do not climb
in snowdrifts the bears!
This accident. I do not understand,
How did it happen.
Well, quiet!
That shout - a wild boar is on the way.
- And where?
- Still far.
But hearing his amazing.
And the scent is not deprived.
This is a special ointment - sodium.
In order not to irritate the beast.
- It's getting dark.
- Yes.
Like them in the dark, you'll see?
How, how - the eyes red.
Clothes rubbing is not necessary,
Only open body.
He is not afraid of the smell.
Special ointment sodium.
The spirit of human discourage.
But the car you're so vain
close set.
Nothing was too late. You can scare,
you know.
What kind of ointment? Spruce smells!
Fir! But the main component -
their feces.
- Whose?
- Boars naturally.
- Olga V., you cold?
- And no.
Let's go to the car. From the living
room as well the road is clear and warm.
I feel empty, no animals.
Just nothing like shit plastered.
Sorry, Yuri.
In the cold ointment person he pulled.
The skin itches.
Organic any.
Olga V., want?
Yataro, look!
You see, over there?
Wisps of red?
Mich said that he had in the dark
eyes red.
Said.
Strange somehow glances at us,
like winks.
Squints. We spotted. What to do
we, Olga V.?
Only strange it all.
We have two-geek, normal
a man sitting here,
covered with the devil knows what, in
the car. In anticipation of a reptile.
But are you in vain, we're on the hunt.
Sorry, Yuri.
That is, they began to shoot?
Boar on the approach!
I went beast! Who shot?
Who scared of the beast?
Something wrong.
Kazan went. Handsomely!
Look heap. Exactly on the roof.
Judging by their appearance,
wheelbarrow end.
- Be careful!
- Caution!
- And then who?
- We!
Who are we? Environmentalists, too?
- Yes!
- I Yataro!
- You are safe?
- Intact, only lie uncomfortable!
What happened?
What happened, what happened!
Kazan migrated.
And in his way, not made
sonnet!
Reach us as quickly here!
- The cake! - Mich, I'm afraid,
to not dig up in the morning.
- Who shot?
We! We shot a wild boar!
In a wild boar? You've been in the car all
glass landed!
- Just have not ruined!
- Excuse me!
Olga V.,
You lie comfortably?
But how to pick out them out?
Come on, do something!
- Yeah, grandiloquent.
- Well, the same to us out of here!
Yes, I like Mich said, between the eyes
shot. They glowed in the dark.
What a wild boar? That's
what we smoked in the cabin!
Shooter damn! Have you
done something, eh?
Yes, we thought the boar is.
- Eyes of the world.
- That we were smoking!
Well, who is on the hunt smokes? Well?
- Well, quickly remove!
- Hey, what are you doing there?
We rested! Remove us of here
faster!
Yes, actually, and what
are you doing there?
What's that - a fall migration.
Hunters damn! Now I know,
What is your hunting!
You do not worry there are forces beware!
What shall we do, Mikhail?
- Come on, take it right! Right!
- Good for you, fit!
Come on! Forward!
Go to the place!
- You're not gauzy not gauzy!
- Yes, I'm kicking twist!
More, more, Mikhail, yet!
More more!
Brakes!
Stop!
- Le, I am now!
- Come on!
Quickly would be cold!
The whole body numb!
Thirteenth cordon. Mich.
The police come.
Sergeant Semen ova!
Well, do the something!
Faster remove!
- Good!
- We are here as sprats in the bank!
All you got! Now
We will free you!
Quickly would be cold!
The whole body numb!
We're suffocating from the stench!
Break you this car!
Lea, you still more careful
with a jeep!
This machine as a native!
And it may be, you can still fix it?
What do you think Lou?
You can, if only for a convertible.
O Lord, and it is your hunting, eh?
Well all Mikhail, phoned
to Norsemen.
Who will come to the special
rescuers.
Brazen, dirty, smelly creature!
I mean the wild boars, Comrade General!
Shoot them right!
Bastards - one word!
Well, let's be consistent,
Olga V..
They are intelligent animals.
They need to take care.
You yourself have in this convincing.
I admit my mistake.
Stop!
- Wow!
- Good morning, Alexis!
- Health, Norsemen!
- That's the best specialist, lifeguard.
Well, then who needs help?
Just quickly, and then I
ripped straight from the wedding.
Yes, that's stuck, you know.
But what stuck there?
- Slow down!
- Careful, we're almost deaf!
Oh, the signs of life are served!
- How many are there?
- Two.
We'll get. I'm in the last year 7 people
of "Zaporozhye" learned.
Gypsies. At some holiday
back, well, in a ravine and rolled.
You will not believe the car was like ...
Well, no more drums of diesel fuel.
- Where is their head?
- Who?
Well, who in the car.
Lenin reach.
- Who?
- Lenin.
- What is Lenin?
- In the name of Lenin, our lifeguard.
It is because of this submitted
does not love.
Because of his surname.
And married to change it.
The bathhouse was carried. They are there
as two stuck together pelmet were.
Norsemen, drip-key us
and then chilled, not chum feet.
- Well!
- Dripping. Dripping.
Well, for us! During the rescue!
Mich, and what are you as a non-native?
Olga V.,
Well, how are you feeling?
Whether there are any requests?
There is! Pour me a vodka-key!
- And me?
- And you too.
Good sit.
Tomorrow deer go.
Do not make the company? 5:20 00: 39: 14.361
-> 00: 39: 16.359 A license for the deer eat?
- Quiet, you!
- Of course, no.
- What is stopping you?
- We have nothing can stop.
I have a special craftsman
Horn presented. "The Call of the female."
The male on the roaring,
like mad, running.
Mich! Well, I understand,
He served in the Caucasus!
And you? You have something
where you know all this?
So sing as well!
To support the company!
Now we leave.
- Volgograd! You've got the wedding!
- I'm on the road. Do not worry. Save.
- Who?
- Everyone!
On.
Well, I feel better?
Yet?
- Good morning!
Hello? I am busy right now!
I'll call you later!
When we go to the deer?
So, let's start?
Maybe males are gone?
Come on, give me.
I was a child he played the trumpet.
Quiet. Responsible.
Male. Voice rough.
Something like roars. It
is seen wished. Come on.
Fired flute. There!
Exit male. What does he want ?!
Let us once more.
Or maybe this is not the
call of the females,
and more on the contrary
- the cry of the male?
Well, we call the male to a fight, and they
fear and go.
We are not gone! Come again!
There!
There! Forward!
You, above all, tea overlap.
He's from yesterday you quickly pull.
- A tea Mich excellent!
- Right!
This Chinese flower tea.
Which, incidentally, is
made from mouth-watering
inflorescence upper
leaves of the tea bush.
He always appreciated in Russia.
- Good morning.
- Who drank?
- Sit down.
- What happened to Olga V.?
- To the table.
- Some of my bed was a glass.
Good morning!
- Who drank it?
- I.
- Olga V., do not want tea?
- What?
The glass had my contact lenses.
You do not need help?
Don be upset. They had
dissolve rapidly in the stomach.
Nothing special.
Sit down.
- Wait, wait.
- Come on.
Spanking. Very close.
Brazen as a responsive, well!
I think it causes us to battle.
Left you have a horn!
Very correct my horn,
if it responds to the animal itself.
Now we will lay. Come on!
He is there. Forward!
Why are you the trumpet? My I never met?
- The dirty orange jacket!
- No, I have not seen!
4:00 left in the store,
no and no!
- A large male.
- I've already started to worry!
Something bothered me to hunt.
Black Raven,
what do you sheave
over my head?
- Yataro!
- Here!
- Home! Sleep!
- I'm coming!
- Yataro, fast home!
- I'm going, Olga V.!
- It's always wrong with you?
- How?
Oh, I was captain of the beast.
All that shouting, demanded.
I do it to the hunting of all Mich
a couple of days brought and all.
- With everything reformed?
- Out of left.
In the neighboring district forester
working. They say that was the normal guy.
No, my not so. Its so easy
not processed.
- Yataro home!
- I'm coming!
Well, I'm fast. She will lie - I to you.
Good sit. Beau, Olga V.!
That's right, all our troubles away.
That's where you're wrong.
Well, for real women, and they,
trust me,
and we, and all over the world
lots of!
Well, for women!
Throughout the year, or
even more, I spent H
Thou among the inhabitants
of the snowy country.
But he could not comprehend the meaning of and
their skill in catching birds and animals.
He learned about the most revered hunter
and I came to him with a desire
learn skills,
grasp all the nuances and peculiarities
hunting locals.
I want to be your disciple.
"How much time should be devoted
occupations
to reach your level? "-
Thou said H skillful hunter.
At least seven years,
no more than eight.
So long? Is there no more
shortcut?
Yes, but you will know only the outer
by scientists, but not its essence.
Even if you meditate in the yard
day and night in a pose of "cherry
on the snow-covered stone "
then it can take 6 years.
By itself, the meditation will not make
You master
but may return the tranquility
mind and body,
that is so necessary to any hunter.
Yes.
Yataro, where are you?
Dimes! Oleg!
Hey, Yataro! Get up,
you have weak lungs.
- What, it's time to hunt?
- No hunting!
Stop your hunts us.
Anything, but not hunting.
Here!
There is good depth. Even carp can
take. Or someone else.
Mich! And who is sitting there,
on the tree?
- Where?
- Lupercalia.
Oh, and the next one. And there still.
And we do not have guns!
He said the same: at least one gun
should always have with you.
Yes, they still can not take!
They are specifically from the top of the
sitting, to get close to them is not.
Unless the approach?
Approaching ?!
Norsemen!
Something I'm tired of fishing.
Come along with me as well.
Lou! Here I am found!
Wow! Will.
Lou! Are you quite sure?
The point is risky!
This method is still in the hunt benefits
Training will!
And it can, and will enter the annals.
- In memory.
- Come on.
For stories!
Wait, not so! Come on!
Norsemen, and I dreamed of since childhood
conquer the air element.
Finally!
Well, good luck!
Go!
Do not get them? How!
From Hitchhike’s
no one has ever left!
On every trick is a natural
savvy!
You're like, Le?
Oh, good picks!
More slack!
Yet? Stradivarius!
I say, the grass, but be careful!
Le, are you okay?
Lou is there?
We were born to make a fairy tale to ...
Norsemen!
- You Measure out?
- What?
How many meters measured?
30 meters, you understand?
30 meters counted?
Lou, speak louder!
I can not hear you!
I say 30 meters, no more!
- Got it?
- What? I do not understand!
- Norsemen!
- What?
You got me ... you above!
Above lift? I got it!
What's more podiatrist?
I can not hear!
- Above raised!
- Le, I'm letting go!
Idiot! I'll let you go!
I say, down, down to descend, you idiot!
You are welcome!
Hey, help me! O Lord,
what it is?
Higher? Lou, how is it? Handsomely?
- Help!
- Lea!
What do you mean ?! Let go!
Lou! Lou! For trees cling!
Do you hear?
Dimes, you bite, Oleg?
- A?
- Do you bite?
I do not know, Olga V..
It seems not.
Oh, and where a circle?
Oh, what is it? Someone caught!
Do not pull the stuck!
Mich, help!
This trout. Well then, the big fish.
Lucky.
How to pull it, Mich?
Oh, do not climb!
Oleg, you wait, do not wait!
Now I am well polyandrous.
Aha! Olga V., look -
I got big!
Most take at the edges!
Close caught!
Now.
Lou!
Lou! Shoot the probe -
you will drop! Do you hear?
Lou! If not enough, shoot down a second!
Le and I come from the organic
shot down!
I, too, Tsiolkovsky
fucking shooter!
Oh my God. Lord! How sickened.
- Le, do not be afraid!
- Norsemen ...
Do not you probe.
It is terrible, it is! Catch!
Then shoot myself!
Do not shoot! The cartridges were
the cordon! Help! I feel sick!
Lou, I'll run over to the cordon
for patrons! Hold on! Do you hear?
Hold on!
Idiot! How did he get these cartridges
deliver? Lord.
And I'll bring them to you, then?
You, please, be careful!
Fish do not hit my.
And it does not resist it?
You are mad, are not you?
No, the big one!
Maybe it was just curious?
Interestingly, when such attention
you has so many people.
- All right!
- Come on, be careful!
For gills for its gills
gently grab!
Hey, what?
- Cover it!
- Covers, cover him!
- People ... People ...
- What?
I told you over the gills should be enough
or reach.
- And where is my big fish?
- There, there.
Gone! I grabbed that arm
It turned up! You bastard!
As I waiting just pulled into the depths.
I almost dragged.
I'm surprised at you.
What are you doing there?
I watched a lot of fish there.
Well, how much?
Well, for the rescue!
Few leave me too.
Nerves are correct.
Yuri ...
Igor, well, give a mug!
Stuck.
Well, who of metal in the cold drink?
As small children!
Be careful, do not tear! It is
necessary to breath or saliva.
What are you looking at me? I am with my
subordinate kiss can not.
This is his fish. Let him answer,
and kisses him.
Yuri!
Yes, I am married! I can not his wife
to change, but still a man.
Now, if ...
Olga V.!
I? No way!
Or maybe try alcohol?
Well, that's, you know,
I emotion all traces of drinking.
How?
- I do not know how.
- What do you do something now?
Dimes! Deliver me, Yataro!
Olga V., do not worry,
free you!
Breath had warm mug,
and you, dear, lips climbed!
- Naturally, perimeter.
- I breathed on her ...
We'll have to see me to the cordon, to the
bathhouse, to drive, do not disengage.
Do not pull, Olga V..
- What do you have here is the wedding?
- Painfully.
- What wedding? What are you kidding?
- Then bitter!
- Norsemen, and where Lou?
- And Lea fall. On the armchair.
"Earth-3," says board
fifty-seven.
Observed an unidentified
flying object.
Ask what purpose,
fifty seven aboard.
SOS!
The man in the chair.
Flying on balloons.
SOS!
Repeat target characteristics,
fifty seven aboard.
Man flies in the chair. He waves his hand.
Welcome.
Your guidance, "Earth-3".
Hey! Shoot me!
- Just a little bit, Olga V..
- Oh, it hurts.
All! All Olga V.,
You are free.
For I have with you
I went to fish ...
Mirror forbid.
All men are your fun.
Slightly swollen lip, right?
Yes, normally, Olga V..
Almost imperceptibly.
In the coffin, I seen your
hunting and fishing.
So why do so, Olga V.?
Here we're going to hunt for a beaver.
Then next, Mich on the river, a flock
Beavers lives.
Would you like to see? I recommend.
Really curious.
We, too, will go.
Would you like to join?
Okay, persuaded.
Mikhail, to your phone,
border guards.
Something happened over there, I
I did not understand.
- What is it?
- Who will do.
Yes? General Involve listening.
Yes, I know Leo Hitchhike’s.
He departed in the afternoon from the
cordon. It is right on the chair.
Let the chair will return.
- What?
- Armchair let back!
Trying to cross the border?
Nonsense!
So. Ask him to call!
Why can not talk?
- Why can not talk?
- Why are not you talking?
- Voice cracked.
- The voice says, ripped off.
Voice broke, he said. Only whispers.
Can not speak.
- So warm and fed.
- There is warm and fed.
- Yes, there is, Comrade General.
- Warm ...
Yes knocked down in the fourth square. Flying
in the direction of the border. With weapon.
- Saved! I can speak! Mikhail!
- Sit!
Mikhail, let them explain to you!
Mikhail, explain!
Mikhail, do you explain to them,
I was not going to fade from home!
I am here for fun, at home! What I was
there, behind the hill, remember?
- Well, Mich?
- No, there's no beast.
Come on.
H Thou tried to penetrate into the
mysteries mastery hunter icy country.
And it was already seem
He grasped the mysterious
and obscure him peace
locals
how an event that,
Indigenous - no, dramatically
It changed everything.
He went once with hunters
on the red beast,
who was worshiped in the icy country
most notable for the trophy.
For three days they caught the beast,
forced his way through the jungle forests
getting stuck in deep snow, but
and could not get it.
H Thou distressed that they could not
catch the clever and cunning beast.
But he was more surprised behavior hunters.
Those were laughing and having fun.
Although tired and frozen, until chased
for tricky beast.
And he realized that it
is important not the
production, and the unity
of people and love ...
Again someone came.
- Good morning!
- Hello!
Good afternoon.
- On the spot! And you, in fact, anyone?
- From the Ministry of Forestry.
With the test to you. Doggie you
wonderful. As its name?
- Whistle.
- Originality.
By the end of the sixth year
H seemed to Joe,
that he penetrated into the essence
hunting skill.
For it is not production, and
the concept was his principal.
He told about the discovery the teacher.
He thought, looking at the student,
and then said:
"And now you have to grasp it,
that above this
and that is the foundation of our school. "
What do I need to do for this?
"Do a few more years
meditate in the yard? "-
H Thou little confused.
"You exhausted your soul
Search for hidden meaning, "-
the teacher smiled.
Try to get rid of it
and discovered his love for all,
that surrounds you.
Maybe you're looking for something
that is constantly It is in you,
and only need to feel it.
21.10.2003