Hey, I'm gonna go
to the bathroom real quick.
I want to look in the mirror
and make sure
I'm still dead in the eyes.
You think you can
handle my section?
Uh, yeah,
I think I can handle it.
Hey, Earl,
I don't know if you noticed,
but I'm running
the whole diner right now.
What, what?
The customer at table ten
appears to be choking,
and I would help,
but the last time I gave
a white woman the heimlich,
I did six months
in the Birmingham city jail.
Oh, my God, are you choking?
Oh, my God,
I feel like you're choking!
Is anyone here a doctor?
What am I saying?
I forgot where I am.
Has anyone here
ever seen Scrubs?
What do you do
when a girl is choking?
I just back up a few inches.
What do we do?
This woman is choking!
[Choking]
[Spits]
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
And feel free to tip me
what you think
your life's worth.
I feel 3 bucks coming my way.
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ♪
2x09
And The New Boss
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh ooh ♪
Sync & corrections by Alice
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
www.addic7ed.com
Here you go, guys.
I'm the only waitress.
Sorry you waited longer
for the burger
than you did for that
Cosby sweater to come back.
Max, look at my face.
I'm very upset.
Oh.
Is that what that means? I just
assumed you were constipated.
Caroline is late again.
And she better not use
your new cupcake shop
as an excuse this time,
'cause sister,
that crap ain't gonna fly.
First of all,
stop talking like you're
in a Tyler Perry movie.
And secondly,
Caroline's here;
She's in the kitchen.
Oh, really?
'Cause when I was in there,
you told me she was out here.
You play me, fool.
Stop talking like you're
in a Tyler Perry sequel.
And secondly--
I'll ask Earl.
Earl...
- Oop!
- Ow!
What happened?
Why did you scream?
I accidentally
sat on one of my boys!
Have you seen
Caroline tonight?
Of course I have, man.
I just saw her go down the hall
to the ladies room.
There. Happy?
You've solved the big mystery,
Shortlock Holmes.
Wait, she didn't
pick up any of her--
Caroline?
Can't talk now, Han.
And how many more times
do I have to ask you
to fix this damn pie carousel?
I mean, the temp
just isn't cool enough,
and those tapiocas
are gonna turn bad.
If you do want a lawsuit,
just keep ignoring me.
Max, can I see you
in the kitchen
where I was
just a couple minutes ago
after I got out
of the ladies room?
Yeah, get on that
temperature thing.
There's so much mold
growing in there
that cherry pie's
gonna need a pap smear.
That was some ballsy,
bold, in-your-face
awesome lying.
I learned it
by watching you, Dad.
Had to lie.
We need every minute
we can steal away from here
to get the cupcake shop ready.
We still have to do
the second coat of paint,
figure out
tables and chairs...
What?
Didn't have time for lunch.
Oh, I don't care.
I'm surprised
you're using a spoon.
I just stick my face in it.
So, my brilliant idea
of how we get this all done
is we should
get an intern to help.
What? No.
I can't be a person
that has an intern.
I can barely be a person
that doesn't have an intern.
Max, all businesses
use interns.
We just have to post an ad
online at NYU or Columbia,
and we'll have
20 applicants battling it out
to do our grunt work
for credit.
You make it sound like
The Hunger Games:
College Edition.
Sorry, I'm against getting
people to work for free.
I'm with you, Max.
My people were interns
for 436 years.
I am just getting used to the
idea of having my own business
and now you want me
to be someone's boss?
I am not the boss.
I'm the person who talks
behind the boss's back.
[Rings bell]
Pick up.
Thanks.
Isn't Han a tool?
- Total tool.
- Yeah, a tiny tool.
Like the kind you fix
your eyeglasses with.
See?
That's my wheelhouse.
Look, I don't want to ask
someone to work for free.
We can do it all ourselves.
You want to do it
all yourself? Great.
I'll write everything
you need to do on a to-do list.
Why don't you to-do that?
And I will to-tear it up.
What're we tearing up?
'Cause if it's that ass,
I already got that covered.
Hi, Andy.
That's so sweet and dirty.
Easy, easy. What are you,
shipping off to war?
Here. Take this giant bag of
skittles and look the other way.
[Scoffs]
I'm not that easy.
Ooh, new mystery flavors?
We getting together
after you get off work?
It'll be really late.
Max and I still have to go
to the cupcake shop
and tape up the windows so we
can start the trim tomorrow.
Okay, I'm not
very good at painting,
but I can do this
while you paint.
Yeah.
Yeah, roll that paint
on that wall.
Oh...
You are so freaking cute.
Ugh, white people.
Look, why don't you guys
just get an intern?
That's what I did
when I opened my shop.
You two are like evil warlords
mining the souls
of innocent zombies.
Oh, and keep your eyes peeled
at your store.
The janitor told me
he saw some rat droppings.
But all you gotta do
is set up some traps.
Oh, gross.
Who's gonna do that?
The intern?
So, Ruth,
you are a sophomore at NYU,
majoring in finance?
You know you're not
gonna get paid.
No money at all.
Yup, it's in internship.
I mean, it's all good, right?
It's all good
until you need money.
Well, we're a startup company,
and we're launching
our very first retail store,
so there's a lot of details
that you'll be responsible for.
There's a lot
of carrying things,
maybe some trapping things.
Oh, it's cool.
I have a car.
You have a car
and you want to be an intern?
How 'bout if we switch places?
I'll be the intern
with the car,
and you can sit
on a broken folding chair
next to Donna Trump over here.
Well, Max and I need to have
a little meeting right now,
so if you could go
over to the waiting room,
that'd be great.
Okay, Ruth?
I just wanna say
I know my name is weird,
but like it's too late, right?
Max, why are you
trying to convince her
to not be our intern?
Why are you not saying,
"You may get rabies and
bubonic plague from our rats?"
Don't mention the rats.
You're chasing them away.
And we do not have rats.
We have rat droppings.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
You're right,
the rats are probably
just coming in here
to use the bathroom.
Look, we need an intern.
Now, who do you like so far?
The one with the big boobs.
I knew it. All you big boob
people stick together.
Hi, girls.
Are you having
a beauty contest
and didn't invite me to give
the other girls a chance?
We're interviewing people
to be our intern.
Who doesn't get paid.
Well, this is for you.
You didn't have to do that.
You already gave us
the money for the shop.
I know, I'm too wonderful.
But it's for good luck,
and sounds like
you're gonna need it.
Oleg says that it's
rat central station around here.
Not rats, Sophie,
just rat droppings.
Oh, just rat droppings.
Oh, okay, no problem there.
[Laughs]
Are you out of breath
because you jogged here
all the way from 1974?
Sexy, huh?
You should see
his badunkadunk when he jogs.
Well, here they are.
60 rat traps.
Girls...
I don't want to interfere
with your business,
but what the hell
is goin' on here?
There's no fancy tables
or pretty chairs.
I mean, this place
is so unappealing,
even I don't look good here.
No worries.
We have some adorable old-school
ice cream tables and chairs
on hold at a kooky,
fun Staten Island junkyard.
Wow.
I can't believe you didn't
just shoot a blood clot
trying to make
dump furniture sound cute.
Okay, girls, well, call me
when you have a real business.
Yeah, and I'm--
I'm gonna take this,
you know, so that the rats
don't poop in it.
Come on, badunkadunk.
Oh, and, uh, Max...
Oh, she's good. Yes.
I knew it. All you big boob
people stick together.
Well?
Here we are.
The final three.
Well, you know the one I like.
I'll give you a clue.
One, two.
Standing in front of me
I see two beautiful,
qualified young women.
Is she really
going all Top Model right now?
If only. They pay.
I'm out, Tyra.
Ruth, congratulations.
You've been selected
to be our intern.
Max, will you get Ruth
started on something?
Yup, I got the internship.
Um...
You know what?
I got it.
It's not like
you're getting paid.
Big boob people
are so much easier.
As a kid, people told you
everything you did was amazing,
didn't they?
I was given a lot
of positive reinforcement.
I think it gave me
the confidence
that's gotten me
through this last year.
Well, it's time
you heard the truth.
You stink at stuff.
Like painting.
Fine.
And you stink at stuff too.
Like telling an intern
what to do.
Ruth had to go
to that concert.
She had the tickets for weeks.
It was Ashley D and Ashley B's
joint birthday. Duh.
And so the intern's
out having fun,
and here we are, the bosses,
painting the walls at 3:00 a.m.
Well, I'm painting.
You got a kind of
autistic ballerina thing
going on over there.
Can I ask you something?
I don't like Maroon 5.
No matter
how many times you ask,
the answer will always be no.
Not that.
Would it be okay if I told Andy
not to come over tonight
'cause I'm so exhausted,
or is it a little too early
in the relationship to be all,
"I don't think I can have my
legs up around my ears tonight"?
It's fine.
You don't think
he'd enjoy a night off
from constant Maroon 5
badgering? He would.
Feels awkward. Can't.
My legs can go up there.
They're fine.
I don't want to have that
conversation right now.
Hey, look, I get it.
There are conversations
you don't want to have.
Like, "hey, Ruth, here's $0.
Put down some rat traps."
We have a box right here
that's not touched.
Look, we're not talking
about your relationship anymore.
We're done.
Relax. It's probably not even
a rat, it's probably a mouse.
Not a big deal.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God,
I see it! There it is!
- The mouse?
- That is not a mouse!
That is a car
that a mouse drives!
Where did you see it?
It was in the middle, right?
- Shh!
- Why are you whispering?
I don't want him to hear me.
How do you know it's a he?
He looked at me kind of rapey.
There!
He just ran behind the thing!
- What thing?
- That thing!
This thing? Waah!
What? Did you see it?
I don't think so.
Oh, you'd know so.
It has a saddle.
[Gasps]
Oh, my God.
He just opened the door with
the strength of his whiskers.
He's gone.
He went into the kitchen.
Oh, what should we do?
Should we call the cops?
He doesn't have a gun.
Let's just get out of here.
We'll call an exterminator
in the morning.
[Gasps]
Too late, he's coming back!
- Aah! He's charging us!
- He's gonna bite me!
[Growls]
Waah!
You can stop now!
You painted him to death.
I just got a glimpse of you
at a Barneys sample sale.
What a mess.
Who's gonna clean that up?
The intern?
Oh, Andy...
I know.
I'm good at this.
[Moaning increases,
turns to cries]
What?
Is there another rat?
What are you doing?
I forgot Andy was here!
And your sex voice is the same
as your murder voice.
So are you just
gonna stand there?
Are you offering me
a three-way?
[Buzzer sounds]
Well, it looks like we're
about to be a full-blown orgy.
It's 2:00 a.m.
Who could this be?
It's Ruth.
- Ruth?
- Yes. I'm late, right?
Why is she here?
I texted her and said
you needed an enema.
Okay, now, this is some
industrial-strength girl talk.
I had to do something
to show her who was boss.
I learned it while interning
at Condé Nast.
We've all
gotten someone an enema
in the middle of the night,
it's a rite of passage.
For someone to get
their passage right?
Beat me to it.
[Knock on door]
There. Go open the door.
You know what has to happen.
Max has to put Ruth
in her place
so she can learn
how to be a boss.
Oh. That's all? Good.
'Cause I thought
from your tone
you were gonna force Max
to have an enema.
Sorry I'm late.
I had the tiniest pot cookie and
had to pull over to take a nap.
Anyway, here is your enema.
Enjoy.
They only had the triple pack.
Wait, Ruth?
Max has something
she wants to say to you.
Max, what did you
want to say to Ruth?
Um, thanks for the triple?
Three times the fun.
[Trap snaps]
You sure you don't want me
to help you with that?
Oh, no, it's okay.
You took the rat traps out
of the box, you need a break.
Plus, we couldn't afford
the game Mouse Trap
when I was a kid,
and this is the closest
I'm gonna get.
So, when do you
make the cupcakes?
Um...
I guess I could make them now.
Fun.
I'll go get the coffees, right?
Sure, of course.
Do whatever.
You got a life.
Who am I to tell you what to do?
Well, here's our
Martha Stewart blurb,
all blown up and ready to roll
out and paste up on that wall.
- Where's Ruth?
- She's in the kitchen.
- I was just in there.
- Then she's in the bathroom.
Oh, my God, you're Haning me!
She took a coffee break.
What? She didn't need a break.
She just started 20 minutes ago.
[Scoffs] Your rich
is really coming out,
and it is not pretty.
Forgot my phone.
I mean, get it together,
Ruth, right?
Watch and learn.
Ruth, can you put the rat traps
down, one in each corner,
and then you can get coffee
later after interning.
Thanks.
She's kind of a tool, right?
Max, were you
saying something?
Nope.
[Trap snaps]
Ouch!
Right?
Oh, look at this cage.
I think my mom
used to dance in it.
Here they are.
These are the ones
I had the guy hold for us.
Only $600 for all of them.
What do ya think, Daddy?
I like 'em, doll.
Wrap 'em up.
And can Daddy
get something he wants?
So cute.
Over the counter?
And that way when I'm
hungover and taking a nap,
people can still
find the cupcakes.
We could have Ruth clean it
and then paint
and reupholster these.
By the way, where is she?
She was supposed to
be here an hour ago.
Text her and find out
where she is.
Why are you so interested in
where she is, what she's doing?
Are you obsessed with her?
Max, I don't want to make
a purse out of her skin.
I just want her to do her job.
Never mind.
I'll just text her.
Well, be careful.
Don't delete any
of my penis with a hat pictures.
Even if I did,
it's not a big deal.
Oleg will always pose again.
Yeah, but I'll never get
that little pilgrim hat back.
"Where are you?
We needed you here yesterday."
All in caps,
'cause bosses talk in caps.
[Coughs]
Total tool.
[Phone chimes]
Look at that.
Texted right back,
'cause I'm the boss.
She says...
Yesterday was super hard
so she's not feeling great
and she can't come in today?
[Scoffs]
That's it. She's fired.
Here.
You have to fire her.
She said she was sick,
Condé Nasty.
She's not sick,
she's just taking advantage
'cause you're
too friendly with her.
She works for us.
Yeah, for free.
Why don't you just
hollow her out
and live inside of her,
you monster?
[Phone chimes]
Um, I don't think
we were supposed to get this.
"The dumb one wants me to pick
up all this crappy furniture.
"Right? As if.
I'll be at the bar in ten.
Order me a Bellini."
Oh, who's the monster now?
She just called you
the dumb one.
Uh, she called you
It's your phone,
you're the dumb one.
She knows I don't talk
in caps, so that's to you.
You're the dumb one.
- Fire her.
- No, you fire her.
No, you fire her.
No, you hired her,
you fire her.
I wanted to go
with Molly big boobs.
She'd be here right now
with four chairs on each boob.
Why can't you just fire her?
It's clear she called you
the dumb one.
All right, fine, I know
she called me the dumb one.
But I can't fire her.
I want to, but there is a block.
Right here.
It comes up, and then goes,
"nope!" It goes right back down.
I am not supposed to
fire someone.
I am the someone
who's supposed to be fired.
So I guess I'm the boss, then.
Sounds like a plan.
I'll be in my mom's cage.
[Scoffs]
All right, come on,
you lowly worker.
Help the boss
pull these chairs out.
Don't yell at me, boss.
I'm blocked.
Wish you had your enemas now,
don't you?
[Both screaming]
They followed us!
We walked into a trap!
It's a vendetta!
Ugh, I can't believe this!
Our intern's
out having cocktails
and I'm trapped
on top of rat mountain!
[Screams]
He's coming after me!
Whoa--whoa!
[Screams]
Oh, my God!
Max! Help!
No, you bastards!
Get off her!
Aah!
Get off!
My foot's caught
under this thing!
[Grunts]
Aah!
Max, that was amazing.
You just lifted that
giant thing up with one hand.
I know.
And now I'm gonna
fire that bitch!
Wow. You suck at this too.
Sorry I'm late.
I was having a dream
that I was sleeping in,
then I woke up, and I was.
Who's the boss?
Tony Danza?
No, Max, who's the boss?
I am.
Have a seat, Ruth.
Here?
Good call.
In addition to being a boss,
I am also a waitress.
But when I do my job,
I don't call people dumb.
All right, I do, but at least
it's to their face.
Oh, you're talking
about that thing?
I meant Caroline.
No, I know you meant me,
because I'm not dumb
and neither is Caroline.
And one thing I figured out
is that in business,
maybe I have to be
a little more ruthless.
Meaning no more Ruth.
You're fired.
So, I'm not
getting college credit?
I'll probably
get kicked out of school again,
but no worries, right?
I'm really proud of how
you stuck up for yourself.
You're fired.
Sorry, I can't stop.
Look, Max.
We're on our way.
Sync & corrections by Alice
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
www.addic7ed.com