Pick up!
Tables 12, 4, 11.
Got it.
Hey,
when you get a second,
stop looking at my boobs.
Excuse me.
Waitress?
Dude?
Hi, what can I get ya?
We need some...
Is that annoying?
Is that
obnoxious and rude?
Would you find it distracting
if someone did that to you
while you were working?
Oh, you don't have a job.
Sorry.
Damn, dude,
she burned you.
Oh.
No, hipster.
Do not think we're on the same
team. We have nothing in common.
I wear knit hats
when it's cold out.
You wear knit hats
'cause of coldplay.
You have tattoos
to piss off your dad.
My dad doesn't know
he's my dad.
You think...
This is the sound
that gets you service.
I think...
This is the sound
that dries up my vagina.
The other waitress
disappeared, the Russian one.
We need horseradish.
Please.
That, ladies,
is how you treat a waitress.
Paulina!
Oh, so... so good, oh...
Oh, sorry, I didn't realize
you were on break.
I just need
some horseradish.
- Here.
- Oh, cool.
Excuse me,
where's my waitress?
She's coming.
Earl.
Earl!
I made your favorite,
red velvet.
My little cupcake
brought me a cupcake.
Oh, no, no.
It's on the house.
It's your birthday.
How old are you gonna be?
75.
Oh, Earl, if you were just
three years younger.
Max, Max, big news.
The new boss fired
that Russian waitress, Paulina.
Turns out Chesty Kournikova
was Vladimir puttin' it out.
Hello today.
I have paycheck for you.
I need to talk to you.
You fired Paulina, Han?
I am no longer Han Lee.
I have new American name
to go with
changing neighborhood.
To go with
the changing neighborhood.
You need to remember this
for your immigration exam.
Correct. To go with
the changing neighborhood.
Bryce?
Your name is Bryce Lee?
Wait, wait,
um, um, um...
Don't hire a new waitress,
okay?
I've been doing
all the work anyway,
and I really could use
the extra money.
You need help.
- No, I don't.
- Everyone need help sometimes.
I don't. I've been waiting
my whole life, okay?
I've waited on tables,
I've waited in bars,
I've waited on
home pregnancy tests.
I already hire new waitress.
She work in all top restaurants
in Manhattan.
I gave her
Paulina's uniform.
Hi.
Mr. Lee,
not to complain,
but I think someone
wore this uniform before me,
like right before me.
Is it possible
that I could get another one?
Maybe one that's
a little less moist.
Also this mustard color doesn't
really go with my skin tone,
neither do
the mustard stains...
And these
various other stains,
and smells.
I hope that's clam chowder.
So...
I think it'd be better
for everyone,
including
my immune system,
if I just keep on wearing
what I'm wearing,
and not the apron,
'cause this is Chanel.
So thank you,
and let's waitress.
Whatever that is,
it does not belong
in this diner.
It belongs
in a show on Bravo.
But she blonde,
hair so shiny,
good for business.
Where do you even
find these people?
The Russian hooker, the one
before that was a meth addict.
You train her,
I am boss.
- Da boss.
- Oh.
Fine, but make her
wear the uniform.
Are you sure we can't get
the meth addict back?
She was really good
at cleaning.
But her teeth
fall out.
You are really judgmental,
you know that?
I'm only gonna say this once,
so pay attention.
I'm Caroline, by the way.
And you're Max?
Don't get attached.
This is the Williamsburg diner,
owned by Han Lee,
who just changed his name
to Bryce Lee,
because I guess he wants people
to take him even less seriously.
Eight months ago he bought it
from the Russian mob.
Clientele used to be
all eastern bloc criminals
and crack whores, but then
he took it over and ruined it.
Hey, sexy woman.
You look so pretty today.
You look so beautiful, I forgot
how bad your personality is.
Thanks, Oleg.
Hey, Barbie.
He will hit on you
aggressively and relentlessly.
He doesn't realize
he looks like that,
and I don't have the heart
to tell him.
Could we have some menus?
Oh, sure.
Don't smile.
'Cause it raises the bar,
and then I have to smile,
and I can't be doing that.
It's exhausting
and I have a bad back.
That's Earl,
we're in love.
Do not talk to him,
unless you want to feel whiter
than you already are.
Oh, and that stain?
Not clam chowder.
Go marry the ketchups.
Marry the ketchups.
I'm on it.
Okay.
Now divorce the ketchups.
Stop.
Just stop.
There's no such thing
as divorcing the ketchups.
You've never waitressed
a day in your life.
Yes, I have.
You expect me
to believe you
after watching that whole
Temple Grandin routine?
- I'm telling Lee.
- Okay, okay,
I may have enhanced
my resume.
Enhanced?
What, are we in Paris?
Please,
I really need this job, okay?
We lost all of our money.
My trust fund was taken
for legal fees.
My dad is in jail.
What? What are you,
Martin Channing's daughter?
Where's the paper?
Martin Channing?
The guy who ripped off
the entire city is your father.
He told us we were
having a good year.
You're
Caroline Channing.
You're like
a billionaire.
Was.
Was a billionaire.
They froze all our assets,
everything's gone.
I only have
what I could grab,
and I grabbed
all the wrong things.
- So do you know the president?
- I've met him.
- He's hot.
- He's the president.
- Have you been to Switzerland?
- Yes.
- Do you have a horse?
- Do you know Paris Hilton?
- No, she's a hundred.
Excuse me, uh,
two hot chocolate, please.
- Comin' up.
- It...
let me do that, please.
I'm a really
fast learner.
I went to
Wharton business school.
I got 2,300 on my SAT's
Can you make a hot chocolate,
or not?
Nailed it.
We split the tips.
Give me yours.
You did better
than I thought you would.
Listen, tonight
I thought of a way
we could make
some extra money.
They've totally
underestimated
the price point
on those red velvet cupcakes.
In Manhattan the asking price
is at least seven,
so we could sell them for seven,
and then pocket the difference.
Nothing about that
sounds wrong to you?
It's not our fault that
the idiot who makes the cupcakes
doesn't know their worth.
I'm the idiot
who makes the cupcakes.
New information.
That's stupid.
No one would pay $7
for one of my cupcakes.
Really?
'Cause...
Well, at least we know
you're not adopted.
So how'd you even
end up in Brooklyn?
Oh,
I went on monster.com.
Typed in
"place where nobody
from the Upper East Side
would ever go, ever,"
and this diner came up.
You can't wear
a fancy leather jacket
outside in this neighborhood.
You have to turn it
inside out.
Oh.
Fur. Cool.
Turn it back.
So where do you live?
Our townhouse was taken
and bolted up by the bank, so...
Is this where I'm supposed to
feel sorry for you?
I mean,
I don't want you to,
but just so you know,
a well-adjusted person would.
I'm dead inside.
You make that
pretty obvious.
Anyway, I'm just gonna stay
in the city with a friend.
I live a couple of blocks
that way.
I'd walk you to the subway,
it's just that I don't want to.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
Why is the music so loud?
Whoa!
It's 3:00
in the morning.
I'm sorry.
It's cool.
So what are you doin'?
The band's practicing.
But you're not
playing any instruments.
Yeah,
that's how we practice.
We, like,
listen to other good music
and play it in our head.
It's like The Secret.
Well, I have a secret
for you guys.
- Get out!
- Whoa!
- Uh, you guys better go.
- We should go.
Sorry, guys, I still
have to make the cupcakes.
Cupcakes? For why? You can
just buy 'em at the store.
You can do that in
the morning, babe, come to bed.
No, I can't. I have to
be in the city by 10:00.
Fine.
You can have three minutes.
Fine, you can have eight,
one for each ab.
Boom!
Stand clear
of the closing doors.
Well, I can cross that
off my bucket list.
Hey.
I have a taser!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
I didn't think it would hurt
so much. It's pink.
It didn't feel pink.
I didn't know it was you.
I thought I was being raped.
That's not
what rape feels like.
Did you...
did you
sleep on the subway?
I had nowhere else to go,
and I'm too afraid
to sleep outside on the street.
God, you're spoiled.
Next stop, greenpoint.
Ugh! Get your stuff. Come on,
I'll take you to my place,
but hurry.
'Cause I have to be
in the city in 30 minutes.
Call me.
Oh, my God,
you've been robbed!
This is
how it always looks.
Oh, my God,
totally cute!
All right,
I'll be back at 4:00,
and we can go to work together.
Bathroom, bedroom,
boyfriend sleeps till 4:00,
yard.
Oh, you have a yard.
Looks like a really nice place
to relax and do crack.
It is.
I gotta go, I'm gonna be late
for my other job in the city.
You have two jobs?
Yes, I babysit
for a Manhattan socialite diva.
Now I have a set.
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, thank God
you're here,
there is
a bridge and tunnel smell
over by the babies
that's stressing me out.
Their diapers
probably need to be changed.
Again? I swear,
the morning nanny just did that.
Motherhood is for reals.
Max, remind me,
what's my Twitter password?
Twitter password.
Yes!
Hi, Brad.
Hi, Angelina.
Max, I need to tell you
something because we're family.
Now get me room temperature
water and come over here.
We are victims
of the Channing Ponzi scheme.
Me, David,
and Brangelina.
How much money
did you lose?
Hold my hands.
Nothing.
But it really scared me.
Open that?
So do you know
Caroline Channing?
No,
but she lost everything.
She has no money.
Can you imagine
having no money?
I mean, you wouldn't even
have any money.
You should twit that.
And no one
will even talk to her.
I heard she went
to six different friends' houses
for a place to stay,
and they all had to pretend
they weren't home.
- That's not cool.
- Yeah.
- That's really sad.
- So sad.
Breaks my heart.
I guess motherhood has really
opened me up emotionally.
Max, I need to hold
one of the babies,
bring me one.
No, the other one.
That's not the good one.
Hello.
Oh, hi. Oh, I'm so sorry
if I woke you up.
Who are you?
I'm Max's friend.
Uh, don't tell her I said that.
I have a feeling if she heard me
call her my friend,
she'd stab me.
What are you doin'
over there?
Just washing my uniform,
trying to make it
a little more cute
and a little less crusty.
Oh, watch out!
Oh!
Sorry, oh, my...
- Do you have a towel or a rag?
- No, I... I got it.
Oh, okay.
I'm Robbie.
I'm uncomfortable.
You're getting me wet.
That's the point.
You're Max's boyfriend.
It's cool.
No, it's not.
Back up, Jersey shore.
You're pathetic,
and that's coming from someone
who's homeless
and wearing white
after labor day.
And I've seen better.
No, you haven't.
Hey.
Why didn't you wait for me?
I thought we were
coming over together.
Oh. Um, I wanted to get here
early to marry the ketchups.
Listen,
I heard something
really upsetting
about you today.
What did he say,
that I came on to him?
Him who?
Nothing.
Him, Robbie?
It's none of my business,
but you deserve better
than that guy.
Yeah,
it is none of your business.
Ooh, I was just starting
to feel sorry for you.
I'm just saying,
you're worth more than that.
What, I'm supposed to
believe you about this?
The person who lied
on their resume,
and lied about the cupcakes...
you're a liar.
- I'm just trying to help.
- You know what?
Since you seem to know
so much about everything,
why don't you
take your Wharton degree,
and your ridiculous coat, and
figure this all out yourself.
Max.
- Max, wait.
- Oh, look,
the arcade fire concert
just let out across the street,
good luck with that.
She's coming back,
right?
She's not gonna
leave me here alone
with a restaurant
full of people?
Let me put it to you
this way.
You might as well be
a night maid
at the Schwarzenegger house.
You got screwed.
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
That feels so good.
Now put your tambourine
around it.
Hi, honey, I'm home.
I want you gone
by the time I get back.
Babe!
Babe, I can explain.
You weren't
supposed to be home.
People say
I deserve better than you.
Who?
That blonde girl? She doesn't
know what she's talkin' about.
She went to Wharton
and Switzerland.
Yo, yo.
Look at that.
That girl is
workin' harder
than Stephen Hawking tryin'
to put in a pair of cufflinks.
Here, let me help you
with that.
I don't need any help.
Everyone needs help
sometimes.
This isn't
what I ordered.
This is Caroline.
She may have gotten
your order wrong,
but she does
get some things right.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
What'd you see in that guy,
anyway?
He had these
muscle thingies.
- Oh, those things?
- Yeah.
I don't know
what those are called,
but they make smart girls
stupid.
Max!
I thought your tight ass
wasn't coming in tonight,
and my heart
broke in half.
You know what, Oleg?
I needed that.
So, um...
I need a roommate,
if you want to crash.
Hmm.
Not gonna lie, the subway's
cleaner than your couch.
Wow.
I just felt myself
starting to like you.
Really? Because I really feel
like we could...
I knew that wouldn't last.
Come on.
Tomorrow we can
go into the city
and get
the rest of your stuff.
Everything's locked up.
What, you have nothing that
you care about that we can get?
Well,
there is one thing.
The weirdest thing
is that nobody stopped us.
I'm gonna save
a fortune,
keeping him here
instead of in the stables.
When did you put this whole
horse-in-my-yard thing together?
I can't help it.
I see an opportunity,
and I make it happen,
like with your cupcakes.
Like what
with my cupcakes?
Ready?
To open a bake shop,
all we need is
250 grand start-up money,
for the real estate,
and the basic equipment...
Yeah. Oh.
- 250 grand, that's all?
- Yeah.
Did freakin' Chestnut here
kick you in the head
while I was in Starbucks?
Hear me out.
If we both worked two jobs
and made $2,000 a week,
we could open a cupcake business
in a little over a year.
In the past two days,
we've made $387,
and that's a good start.
We can make extra money
at other jobs,
like publicists,
advertising executives...
Janitors, drug mules.
We really need to
work on your self-esteem.
So...
You, cupcakes,
me, business background,
us, success.
What do you think?
I think
you have a horse.
I think we have a horse.
Don't get attached.