Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 43
I'm off then.
What brings you out here again?
Just got curious so I came by.
You said you were busy.
Ignore him and just go.
I'll go after seeing you off first.
Get inside quickly.
Alright...
The sibling relationship looks good.
What do you mean, sibling? What are you talking about?
Well,
I wonder what it could mean.
I'm just saying that you seem friendly and cozy like siblings.
Don't mind me.
Stop talking nonsense and go already.
Come to think of it, you two seem to resemble each other too.
No, I think that's overstating it.
What are you trying to do now?
Heaven helps the one who helps himself or something? My sincerity has reached the heavens, should I say?
I think even the heaven have been moved by my one-woman loving determination, don't you think?
I'm getting a mixed feeling about this and the tip of my nose is twinging (making me emotional - about to cry).
Ai this man...without returning home as you planned and why are you back again?
Ah yes, well I was about to return home but I felt so elated so..
So I came by.
Don't reveal the secret of nature! (you promised to not say anything)
If you easily open your mouth, you can get zapped by the thunderbolt &amp; lightening.
Shut your mouth, please.
Yes, yes, yes. I was about to leave
I'll be going.
Let's see you again~
I'm off.
I'll go ahead first
Uh, ok.
Take care.
Aunt
Huh?
Wha-what?
A moment ago with that man (Cheol Gyu)
what were you talking about?
Uh, just, um,
I haven't seen him in a while so
just asked about his well-being.
It's nothing.
Mommy, mommy mommy, mommy,
Aigoo, aigoo, why the sudden flippancy?
No matter how I look at it, I think Chae Won and I are about to get a happy ending.
Without a doubt, the heaven was on my side.
What is that you're saying?
I can't say because I'm not supposed to reveal the secrets of the nature,
but just know that in short time, my Chae Won is going to return to us, so
mom, you need to be well prepared.
I mean, are you saying that Chae Won, that thing, is planning on coming to you?
Um-hm. It's predicted that she'll be back to me.
It's become impossible for her not to be back to me.
It's become impossible not to return...ai, say it so I can understand!
Mom, if you know too much, you could get hurt. Today, let's just stop it here.
Kim Cheol Gyoo, hooray!
Chairman Bang, double hooray!
Aigoo, why are you doing this?
It's great.
What the heck...?
What is this?
I think you should take this medicine, instead of me.
Why does your face look so tired?
Is there something that's bothering you?
No.
What's there to bother me about...
By the way, father-in-law,
this time, I think you should admit yourself into the hospital.
I think I can withstand the pain still.
Which is why I'm bringing it up,
let's set the date for Chae Won's wedding quickly.
What?
I don't think I have very much time left.
Before I die,
I would like to pair Chae Won up with her partner.
I hear you and the in-law have a special relationship. So, discuss amongst yourselves, and set the date.
I'm home.
Are you coming back from dropping Chae Won off at home?
Yes.
Then, did you also see Chae Won's mom?
Nope.
We said our goodbyes in front of her house because I had some work left to do.
Ah, I see.
Then, I'm going to my room to rest.
Oh, mom. By the way,
Do you know per chance,
What about?
Whereabouts of Chae Won mom's son?
Wha-what are you talking about?
I heard two of you gave birth at the same time at a maternity clinic, 30 years ago.
I say, from whom did you hear that?
Last time I had dinner with Chae Won's mom, I heard it from her.
It seemed that Chae Won had no idea.
I wondered how that could be?
Choon Hee sister-in-law's son died as soon as he was born.
He died?
Yes.
After her husband died of car accident,
shortly after, the baby died too, which caused Sister-in-law Choon Hee to lose her mind.
I didn't think it possible for her to get a grip of herself and re-establish another household like that.
I couldn't imagine.
She seems always so bright and fun so I didn't suspect mother-in-law could have such a tale.
Oh, by the way, I think I better lie down.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, Oppa.
Why did you get a divorce?
That human being..
Ah no..My ex-husband couldn't make a living very well,
our personalities didn't mesh very well either, so we divorced.
I see.
You are...disappointed, right?
It's because my heart aches at the thought of my Sook suffering.
It's not that I'm disappointed.
"How can every word he utters be so classy and of good quality?"
"It's the kind of words that would move a king's heart"
I didn't know your in-laws operate a noodle factory.
I thought your dad ran a barbershop.
A barbershop?
We did. Then
we became bankrupt and then took over the management of the noodle factory that our grandfather was running.
Is that right?
Oppa,
why don't you go?
No, I'm going to see you off before I go.
No,
Oppa go ahead first.
How about we play rock, paper, scissors, and the losing person leaves first?
Oh, gosh..
Oppa, how can we, like children...
Let it be then.
Rock, paper, scissors! Whoo~
Yayyy! I won!
Now, you can go first.
Should I do that then?
I have to take the step I don't want to take then.
My Sook, sleep well.
What are you doing here?
Oh my god you scared me!
Ewww, seriously!
This darn woman!
Where have you been all day long and come in this late? Do you do this knowing what time it is?
Look here, Mr. Uhm Ki Choon.
My name isn't "darn wife", but it's Gong Kang Sook.
Why do you leave a perfectly good name and call me a darn wife?
And,
how am I your wife?
We have already been divorced since last winter.
I wonder what belief makes you talk big?
Wait a minute,
you got all dressed up too.
Are you having
are you cheating on me?
Do you think you can really say whatever you want?
So, what if I'm having an affair?
It's true,
who in the right mind would pick up a used good like you?
Since it's me, I'm living with you.
What did you say?
Come inside immediately!
How can someone be so undignified and overflowing with low class?
There's no comparison to Oppa.
Aiyoo...
During the day, Se Yoon's mother wasn't feeling well.
At night, Mom isn't feeling well.
I don't know what is causing them to take turns being sick.
Instead of suffering like this,
just do as what I'm telling you to.
If you tell me where he's living, I'll immediately go and bring him here.
Bring who, Dad?
Huh?
Ah...
Well... To you, he would be your oppa.
Oppa?
Ah... Well...
Please...
Please stop.
What's wrong? Eventually Chae Won will know anyway.
The truth is, your Mother...
Please, just stop it already.
Alright.
♫ Break away... Break away...
♫ Break away... Break away... Break away...
♫ Break away from my suffocating life.
♫ I'll take charge. I'll just run towards my future.
♫ I'll break away from my suffocating life.
You did well. My husband is doing really well.
Thank you honey.
Here.
Let's stop for today. If your voice gets damaged by practicing too much, it will affect your recording.
No. Let's go at it one last time.
You're a practice addict.
This time, no matter what, I'll make a big hit. I'll provide well for my honey.
I'll make sure you will hear, "Our last son-in-law is the best".
Even if you don't achieve success, you're still the best husband to me.
I want that good impression of me to remain with you for the rest of your life.
I'll do my best, okay?
Since you have made such a great impression on me,
it will never leave me. So, don't worry, Honey.
Should I eat one more?
Have one more!
Mother!
Mother, mother.
Mother~ Mother~
Aigoo... Seriously, why are you all fired up?
Bam! An oath.
What is this?
I'm going to send Chae Won a video, so take an oath with your right hand.
And take that off! You look like a ghost.
Why you!
Seriously, what is this out of the blue, in the middle of the night? Why an oath?
What is this?!
One. I, Bang Young Ja, will allow Min Chae Won to be my daughter-in-law again
and never make her do household chores.
Two. I, Bang Young Ja, will allow Min Chae Won and my son to move out of my house,
but in turn have them to visit me once a month.
I will never ask them for money.
Hey, what do you think you're doing with this?
If you make sure that you would never do the things you did in the past, then Chae Won would come back to me!
So you're making me take an oath?
Right now is a crucial juncture. If I can't get Chae Won to change her mind at this point,
then it'll be difficult forever.
What kind of juncture is the current juncture?
I can't tell you yet.
Just cooperate, Mom.
Aiyoo, this is so disgusting and petty, seriously.
So, this old mom of yours...
Do you have to make me take an oath for you to get a wife?
If you don't want your only son to grow old alone, then...
Please help me, Mom!
Aiyoo, I'm sick of this. I'm so sick of this! Then, what do I have to do?
Raise your right hand,
and read everything honestly and sincerely.
Raise my right hand.
Then,
we will be taking the video!
Ready?
Action!
Hey,
they say no parent can defeat their children.
Anyway...
Whether it's day or night, whether he's asleep or awake,
whether he's sitting or standing, all he does is think about you.
I'm confirming Cheol Gyoo's devotion to you.
But, you're really something! At this point, you should listen to Cheol Gyu and come.
How long are you going to keep being stubborn like that? Are you going to make me to do something like this, right now?
C-c-cut! Mother!!
Chae Won! My mom has something to tell you. Listen well!
Hello, Chae Won.
Oath.
One.
I, Bang Young Ja,
upon having Min Chae Won as my daughter-in-law again,
also upon moving out, I'll never make her do
household chores.
Two.
I, Bang Young Ja, upon allowing Min Chae Won (and my son) to move out of my house,
once a month,
I request that they visit me without fail.
Financially, I will never...
What now?
Oh, Honey.
What do you think you're doing?
What do you mean what am I doing? I've prepared a lot to perform this show for you.
Look here!
The video recording I sent you, it took a lot for my mom to do that.
This time, for sure, my mother has intentions of becoming the best mother-in-law in all of Korea!
Do you have any pride?
How long are you going to do this to a person who doesn't like it?
There isn't much left anymore.
Because Lee Se Yoon, that bastard, and you can't be together no matter what.
What are you talking about?
What I'm saying is,
it's not very attractive for a man to talk too easily.
Just wait a little longer.
Do you know
some secret that I don't know?
I can't say anything more. We're finished for today. That's it. Sleep well, Honey!
Hello, hello?!
What on earth is happening?
Why is she out here and not sleeping?
Really...
We spent 4 billion won on advertisement, and now you want to pump another 1 billion won?
If we make a good first impression, and raise the image of the product, we'll profit from this business.
You can't even make payments on the noodle factory, and you have to give promissory notes. Aren't you being too risky?
How could you speak like that when you look at the sales? Our noodle is a huge hit.
Of course, that's right. But, you're asking for a lot more than I expected.
Without doing a major restructuring, we can't catch up with Sunbae's company by just advertising in the noodle market.
We came this far, we can't back out now.
Alright.
I'll ask the financial advisor to look into getting a bank loan.
After we stole their new product, they are in chaos.
I'm going to crush Sunbae with this chance.
You said there was something urgent. What is it?
I was wondering if you can establish a technology partnership.
A technology partnership?
Yes.
I want to make Chae Won's noodle that won first place at the competition a premium product.
The noodles that I made?
Yes.
Since Chae Won's factory is small,
there is no way they can make the products we need.
So I hope to establish a technology partnership.
What's that?
If we establish this partnership, our company can produce noodles at other factories using Chae Won's technology.
In return, you'll be paid royalties from the sales of noodles made using Chae Won's technology.
This is like hitting the lottery.
Isn't it?
You're right.
I couldn't imagine us coming this far.
Let's sign.
Uh,
Madam your friend is here.
Should I open the door or not?
Which friend?
Open it.
Yes Madam.
Without calling first
what are you doing here?
I came because I had something to say to you.
Ajumma. Ajumma.
Yes Madam
Please go to the market.
Ah, yes.
I understand.
Have a seat Choon Hee.
Over the past days,
your face has gotten worse.
Think of me not getting crazy
and being fine in front of you as lucky.
I'm sorry.
If you found out the truth
I thought you would tell it to Se Yoon.
I thought that.
So you're thankful I kept my mouth shut.
Don't fool yourself.
I have no intention of keeping this to myself.
For whose benefit, do you think I should keep mouth closed?
When the blood in your entire body dries up
and your liver shrivels, I'll let it all out. I'm forcing myself to wait until then.
You should have felt the same thing to that extent.
It's no fun if you reveal everything so easily.
You
are really cruel.
Cruel?
Did you say I'm cruel?
You taking my child
and making my whole life a lie. Did you just say that I'm cruel?
Are you in the right mind?
Hello, Ahjummunim.
Ah, yes. Welcome.
Is mother...?
She's inside.
I'll be going to the market.
Yes. Have a safe trip.
Instead,
I tell everything to Se Yoon.
I don't think I can live like this any longer.
I lived like that for 30 years.
But, since you've been bothered over these couple of days,
you're complaining to me?
Choon Hee!
I'm going to tell my son.
So Unnie you just keep your mouth shut.
If there is reason that you two really can't be together
would you be able to give up on Seyoon?
Of course, it's not like I don't know your heart.
If it's really for Se Yoon,
isn't it best to just skip over this?
What?!
If Se Yoon finds out that you're his real mother,
then Se Yoon and Chae Won wouldn't be able to get married.
If it becomes like this,
it'll become a scar on each of them.
Even though Se Yoon is still your son,
Chae Won is still your daughter.
Anyways,
no one can follow your head.
You're saying that I should keep this a secret in front of Chae Won?
That's not what I meant, Choon Hee!
Don't get mad and listen to what I'm going to say.
I'm not saying to keep this a secret from your daughter.
This is my decision after thinking about it over the days.
This is your final decision that you've been thinking?!
Se Yoon being your son
is revealed, what exactly do you want returned to you?
Is there any more to this than giving your children scars?
You really have no shame.
So, what you're saying is,
I should let my innocent child that was taken away from me
call you mother for the rest of his life?
Look here.
If you don't like me being around Se Yoon, then I'll secretly go to America.
I'll go to America.
You can just live with Se Yoon, Choon Hee!
Stop saying this like that!
Don't get mad!
Don't get mad, Choon Hee, and talk reasonably.
Think about it reasonably!
Stop saying such nonsense!
No matter what it takes, I'll get my son!
So,
stop having such unnecessary hope!
Chae Won...
When did you get here?
I'm sorry. I'll be leaving first.
Chae Won... Chae Won
Now...
Now it's all over.
It's all over now!
Chae Won! Chae Won!
Chae Won!
Talk with me for a moment.
You've been really surprised, right?
Are you alright?
Towards Mom,
I was thinking what was wrong.
Ah, how can this be.
How can this happen?
I'm sorry.
Since I was stupid,
something like this happened.
I... I can't believe this.
This is impossible!
Chae Won!
Chae Won...
Chae Won, wait a minute.
I'm here!
This person, really!
How can you just walk in by yourself?
I called you, but you didn't pick up,
so I came.
I must have not heard it because the machine was on.
But, what are you doing here?
Did someone stop by?
Yes.
A courier is here, Mother-in-law.
You can't keep on coming here like this!
If Seul Hong's dad and Bo Reum's dad find out, you won't have intact bones.
If they find out the whole truth, they will be on my side anyway.
It's an absolute secret.
Shh..
By the way, Mother-in-law hasn't said anything yet?
What kind of words?
What do you mean what kind of words?
She should declare, "Lee Se Yoon is my son".
What if others hear you?
Be careful with your mouth, please!
Yes... Yes.
But,
Seriously!
When the time comes, there will one or two huge commotions.
You just have to wait a little.
Why are you being so impatient?
I think it's because I feeling a little impatient.
I'm ready to get back with Chae Won anytime.
I only trust you.
Why do you keep on doing this?
I feel burdened.
The only person on my side from this household
is you, Aunty.
Ah... This mouth...
brings me awful luck.
I don't know why I told you. I'm being tormented by you, seriously.
Look...
The fact that Chae Won's mom is Se Yoon's biological mother, you absolutely cannot
tell anyone, huh?
Okay.
Please don't worry. Even though I look like this,
I can really keep my mouth shut.
I heard the news of your marriage and I cried for 3 days and 2 nights straight.
After I got dumped by you,
I gritted my teeth and tried my best.
I succeeded.
It's clear he hasn't been able to forget me until this day.
If he didn't have other motives towards me,
there's no reason why he would've treated me to the steak and wine dinner.
He even escorted me home at night,
Eeek, you surprised me.
Don't you know how to knock?
Is there a moron who'd knock on his own door?
What's this?
What did you do that makes you fall back from a surprise?
You're
hiding something from me aren't you?
Wha... Wha.. What could I be hiding?
Without my knowledge,
did you hide some emergency fund?
I'd say your class is...
If not, never mind.
It's been a while
since I dressed in suit for work, I felt so stifled.
I'm coming back from contracting re technical collaboration with Se Yoon's company.
Um hm.
Every time a noodle that's been made from our company gets sold,
we're going to receive a royalty.
What is this darn wife thinking about?
Bo Reum's Mom
Huh?
What?!
Nothing.
filled with a note~ (musical note)
if I close both eyes~ (singing to himself)
♫ I came into this world with nothing, and I'll leave with nothing.
♫ I have nothing to lose.
♫ Break away...Break away...
♫Break away... Break away... Break away.
♫ I'll break away from my suffocating life.
♫ I'll take charge. I'll just run towards my future.
Wait a moment!
Why is the condition of your voice like this?
I told you not to sing at the club until the recording was over.
He didn't go to the club.
What 's wrong with his voice?
He must have over did while practicing last night.
Can we start over again after I feed him a raw egg?
That's fine.
Let's take a little break.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Would you like another?
You two have such a harmonious relationship.
How did you meet?
I am her first love.
Ahhhh...
first love
My first love is your sister in law.
My sister in law?
Yes, Gong Kang Sook .
When I was in high school, she was my first love.
Who is Gong Kang Sook?
That's Bo Reum's mom.
Bo Reum's mom..? Ha!
Hah!
President.
You have a unique preference.
How can you like that bulldog like...ooof
I had a date with her yesterday.
We had dinner and
a glass of wine.
You had a date with her?!
Aigoo,
how can you taking up space on the floor when the weather is so nice?
Perhaps you can go to the senior center and play chess or
have a drink with friends or
Aren't you bored stuck in the room all day?
Never mind.
To mind not,
I don't think we can leave it like this anymore. Let's go to the hospital tomorrow.
Why the hospital?
Aigoo, each day your condition seems to worsen
I have a feeling that something may be wrong.
I'm perfectly fine so you need not concern yourself
but what are you going to do about our last daughter?
Ai, don't even bring up Ki Ok's story.
She fell over heels over that old gigolo and dropped her mother, father,
and siblings like old shoes, a world's most wicked wench.
They've even registered their marriage already,
there's nothing we can do about it now.
What what? You were bouncing off the wall with anger over it but suddenly got a weaker resolve?
Since it's impossible to put back spilled milk and,
we should consider it all her fate.
What can we do at this juncture?
I can't do that even if the dirt covers my eyes (=die)
I cannot accept an old gigolo as my son-in-law.
Does dad not know yet?
Yes.
He just knows that I have a son,
The fact that Se Yoon is my son
he does not know yet.
I see.
Chae Won,
If
If mom,
I reveal that Se Yoon's my son,
If mom does that,
Chae Won you and Se Yoon would be
Is that the
only way left for you, mom?
Is that the only way?
I'm so scared.
Chae Won,
But
Se Yoon is to you, mom, the only blood relation,
I'm sorry Chae Won.
Mom is in this way,
was about to block your future...that I didn't know.
I'm really sorry, Chae Won.
I'm sorry.
Se Yoon calling
Is it Se Yoon?
Pick up quickly.
Yes, hello.
Where are you?
I'm taking a walk with mom, why?
I think we have to go to the factory together.
Since you Chae Won are the one who's developed the noodle,
I would like you to check the noodle yourself.
Right now?
Get in.
This here is the person who developed the Premium Noodle, Min Chae Won.
How are you?
We used the ingredients you sent and produced the first proto-type sample.
Good work. Let's go then.
What are you thinking so hard about?
Chae Won!
What?
You've been close-mouthed since our trip back from the factory,
why are you so quiet?
Is something the matter?
No, ah...
Nothing's the matter.
Se Yoon
Mom...
likes you Se Yoon very much.
I know.
When your mom looks at me, many heart shapes (like emoji heart = affection) come through her eyes.
Ai, what's this expression? You're making the person who was joking embarrassed.
Ah, by the way,
your mother's son that I mentioned about before,
Mom's
son?
I heard he went to heaven as soon as he was born at the maternity clinic.
So, I heard your mom had a very difficult time.
Your mother said that?
No,
my father told me that.
He was born at the same maternity clinic with me
on the same date,
so every time your mom sees me,
it looked as though she was reminded of her son.
If I marry Chae Won, then I'm going to act her son's role as well.
I promise.
I'm here, Mother.
Welcome.
I came here from the factory, so I didn't have anything to eat.
Please feed me, Mother.
Oh.
Of course.
I'll feed you. Just wait a little, ok?
You came?
Yes.
I came over to eat dinner.
You're really reducing the amount of rice we have.
You need to buy and bring us a sack of rice.
Okay, I'll do that.
First, I'll greet Grandpa and Grandma.
Grandpa and Grandma, I came!
Chae Won, are you sick?
Excuse me?
What's wrong with your face?
It's nothing.
I'll be back after I get changed upstairs.
I came this far with much difficulty.
What do I do now?
It's soybean paste stew again?
I'm sorry.
I only know how to make soybean paste stew.
Ah, it's alright.
It's really good for you.
It's sweet pickled radish.
We ran out of Kimchi.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Since it's been a while, I'm happy to have sweet pickled radish.
Let's hurry and eat.
Is it salty?
It's alright.
We just have to add more water.
Uh!
It's perfectly seasoned now.
Here... You too.
Ah!
It's more delicious because my honey fed me.
You guys are having fun.
Oh... You didn't even call.
What brings you...
Why don't you come over here and join us?
Okay?
What are these side dishes?
Ah, why do we need side dishes?
I look at my wife's face once, and then, I eat a spoonful rice.
I eat a spoonful of rice, and then, if I look at my wife's face, I'm full.
You're stupid... stupid... totally stupid.
How could you talk like that in this situation?
Our father and mother are ill, and they're in bed.
I didn't think through.
I'm sorry.
Seriously.
Why did you come here again?
Why are you tormenting him?
We didn't come here to torment him.
We brought some dry side dishes and kimchi.
Here.
Ah, it's radish kimchi!
How long has it been?
Ah! Seriously!
Do you think we got all these ready and came here in the middle of the night to feed you, Rootop?
We brought these here because we were worried that our miss will suffer from malnutrition.
You, Rooftop, don't touch any of these side dishes.
Are you going to be petty like that with food, seriously?
It's alright, Honey.
It's alright.
Honey, you enjoy, ok?
That word, "Honey"... Ah!
It gives me the creeps.
If you are going to be like this, I can get aggressive.
What do you mean, aggressive?
Kang Bong Soo of Sugar Entertainment.
Who is that person?
That person is...
uh...
The company that I got the recording contract with...
He's the president of the company.
Please chew slowly and eat a lot.
This side dish too.
Chae Won doesn't feel like eating because her stomach doesn't feel well.
Her stomach doesn't feel well?
How come?
I think she got motion sickness.
The whole time we were coming home from the factory, she seemed to be suffering.
By any chance,
did anything happen earlier?
What thing...?
The soup is getting cold. Hurry and eat.
Okay. I'll enjoy it, Mother.
Eh...
Since you're staring at me like that, it's too embarrassing for me to eat.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
You feel like you're full just watching your son-in-law eat, right, Mother-in-law?
Right. That's right.
The side dishes suit your taste?
I'm sorry, Mother.
Since I lost my sense of taste, I honestly don't know how they taste.
I know you prepared them diligently.
I'm sorry.
Why are you being like that, Mother?
Sorry.
It's alright.
How did you...
How did you lose your sense of taste?
What was so difficult?
At that time, the shock I got was too much for me.
After meeting Chae Won, I have recovered a lot from my emotional wounds.
The awful memories I thought I would never forget,
I was able to forget them.
They said if I become emotionally stable, then my sense of taste will return naturally.
So, you don't need to worry.
Chae Won is helping me a lot by my side also.
Does your stomach feel a little better now?
Yes.
It's alright.
When we are married, let's have as many children as possible, ok?
Since my mom grew up alone, she always wanted a lot of grand kids.
Mother would feel the same way, right?
You must be tired from walking around the factory all day.
Have a good rest.
I'll get going.
♫ I can't love you?
♫ I can't get closer to you?
♫ Do we grow apart if I love you?
♫ I can't get one step closer to you.
♫ I can't forget you.
♫ I'm stopped at the same place.
If Mom reveals the fact that Se Yoon is my son,
then you and Se Yoon...
♫ How did I come to love you?
♫ My longing for you becomes more unbearable.
♫ I can't bear to forget you.
♫ I still only love you.
♫ I'll love you as long as I live.
I'm back.
Are you coming back from
Chae Won's house?
Yes.
Mother made dinner for me.
Alright.
That was good.
I was running around all day long to endorse the new product, so I'm very tired.
Go to sleep, Mom.
Se Yoon.
Mom...
Can you give me a hug?
There is nothing going on, right Mom?
What could be going on?
I just want to be hugged by my son for once.
I think you're losing weight, more and more.
You're smaller than before, Mom.
Mom...
loves you. You know that, right Son?
Of course.
Later on,
no matter how much you hate me,
the fact that
I loved you,
don't ever forget that.
Why would I hate you?
That will never happen.
If they find out you are Se Yoon's biological mother,
Se Yoon &amp; Chae Won's wedding will become naught,
then
that will inevitably hurt the kids,
as Se Yoon is your son isn't Chae Won also your daughter?
I'm very scared.
But
Se Yoon is the only blood relative to mom.
How did you come to lose your sense of taste? Just what was so stressful?
I was back then so psychologically shocked.
Since I met Chae Won, the wound in my heart has healed a lot.
I've come to forget terrible memories which I didn't think possible to ever forget.
Why is it always
Why
I am the only one who has to have everything taken away from me?
I don't like it. I don't want to have things taken away from me.
But,
if I alone make the sacrifice, then my son and daughter will both be happy.
If I'm the mom,
If I'm really my son's mom...
So pretty, my daughter.
Why don't you say anything?
Could it be that you don't like it?
What do you say at a time like this, mother?
I don't think plain "pretty" reflects even a 100th of my feelings.
I don't know what to say.
You look beautiful, Chae Won.
Among all the brides this mom has seen, you're the most beautiful.
Now, let's take a commemorative photo with a cell phone.
Look this way.
Right,
One, two, three...
What is it?
Se Yoon has
sent the photo so I saw.
Chae Won's wedding dress look so good on her.
I think you're mistaken about something
I don't feel at ease enough to converse with you on the phone.
I know.
I just couldn't stand to see the blood tears flowing from my kids,
so I figure that it'd all be over if I could just shut my one mouth,
so I decided to bury everything, but
I cannot forgive you until I die.
I know.
Why wouldn't I know that?
Really,
thank you, Choon Hee.
I didn't do this to get your gratitude so shove it.
What's this?
Come in!
Wow, what brings you here, aunt-in-law?
Uh, right. I had something really urgent to discuss with you.
If you have something to say, all you had to do is call. And I'd have driven to you at the speed of a bullet.
Why don't you sit down anyway, please?
Here, take a seat over here, please.
Oh, right.
What would you like to drink? Refreshing green iced tea or juice or water?
Oh, no, no, no. I just came by to return something so as soon as I return it I'll be on my way.
Why is this, once again...?
I think it's really all over so
Let me return it to you.
All over? What is?
Our Chae Won just set the date to marry Se Yoon.
WH-A-A-T?
What are you saying?
I had a lot of work to do lately so I couldn't pay closer attention to this. Has something happened in that short time?
How can those two get married?
Chae Won's mom decided to bury everything.
For Chae Won and Se Yoon's happiness, she decided to "I'll sacrifice myself", Baek Uyi Jong Goon (general as commoner).
What kind of rule is this? It can't be this!
Now the bus has left (=missed the opportunity), so Kim hubby you too should give up on our Chae Won and
meet a nice woman and start anew.
I can't never do that.
I can't do that!
Aiyoo, look at all this flour dust.
It's almost time the guests will be arriving so go and freshen up and return soon.
I'm sorry, mom.
I feel so brazen and sorry so
I can't even thank you.
What nonsense are you talking about?
If you both are happy then I'm happy too.
I don't have any further desire.
I'm sorry.
Aiyoo, Ajumma! Bring me some headache medicine.
Aiyoo, all day at work, I labored over annoying company trouble, I feel as though my head will explode!
Yes, Chairman.
Aigoo, no way!
Aigoo, aigoo, aigoo.
It's been lapsed for a while so I was curious. Why did you swill again?
In the world,
How in the world, can something like this happen, mom?
What is it again?
Yi Se Yoon that bastard you know
finally is going to marry our Chae Won. They have set the date.
They set the date?
I just cannot understand it.
Ai, what's there to understand? The two like each other and would like to marry.
Hey hey Chul Gyu, you too switch off your concern!
I mean, how can SIBLINGS
can marry each other?
Siblings get married? Who?
That bastard, Lee Se Yoon's biological mother is
Chae Won's mom.
What? What did you say?!
You must had a difficult time making such a long journey.
Not really. Thank you for inviting us.
You've been well, right?
Of course.
You have been well too, right?
Yes. Thanks to you.
Now...
Let's start eating since you must be hungry.
There's not much, but please enjoy.
This is a feast, Elder. We'll enjoy.
Madam, you enjoy too.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, Chae Won's mom!
Yes... did you call me?
You eat with us.
What are you doing?
Yes. Join us, Mom.
Oh, I... have some work to do in the kitchen.
Please enjoy, Brother-in-law.
Thank you, Sister-in-law.
Aunty!
That... that...
Is this guy crazy?
Who are you to barge in like this?!
I'm sorry for ruining such a good atmosphere.
Uhuh! Won't you get out immediately?!
I'll send him away.
No, you stay put.
-Hey, Ki Choon.
-Hyung. Let's go out.
-Please just let go of me!
-This man...
Omo! This guy must be crazy!
Let's go out. First, let's go out and talk, Son-in-law Kim. Let's go out!
This marriage...
absolutely cannot happen!
Even though they don't share a drop of blood,
they are still siblings.
How can they marry?
♫ Living like this is not living.
♫ How did I come to love you?
♫ My longing becomes unbearable.
♫ I can't bear to forget you.
♫ I still only love you.
♫ I can't forget you even for a moment.