Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 44
Even though they don't share a drop of blood,
they are still siblings!
How can they marry?
You keep on saying that we're siblings.
What do you mean by that?!
He's drunk. Why are you concerned?
What are you doing?
Why aren't you taking him outside? Hurry!
Okay.
Let's go out, jerk!
Aunty, you definitely told me...!
That Lee Se Yoon's mom switched her dead son with Mother-in-law's son!
Is he really crazy?!
He's drunk...
Why are you being like this, seriously?
Aiyoo!
If you drank, you should recover quietly somewhere. How dare you come here and become argumentative?
Won't you get out of this house immediately?!
Wait a moment, Sister-in-law.
You...
Can you take responsibility for what you just said?
Of course I can.
Even though my speech is a little slurred from alcohol,
my mind is clear.
Stop it, please!
The mother who gave birth to Lee Se Yoon is no one other than
Mother-in-law
here.
What is this jerk saying right now?!
Omo! Son-in-law Kim!
Son-in-law Kim!
Omo!
Mom,
what he just said...
I...
I.. I'll...
excuse myself first.
Mother!
Seriously!
Sister-in-law, Choon Hee, why don't you speak?
What on earth is going on?
Something... is wrong, right, Mom?
How can something like this...?
Something like this can never happen, right?
I think it would be most accurate to hear from Sister-in-law. Speak, hurry.
What happened?
Please go home.
If you hear directly from Unni,
it would be better.
Mother!
I'll take you home.
No, it's alright.
I can go home alone.
Ah... I'm really alright.
I'll be going.
Se Yoon!
You knew about it all along, but
didn't say anything to me?
How could you do that?
Mother-in-law and Mom...
were afraid that you might get hurt.
I can't believe it.
Is there some misunderstanding...?
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Ok...
Please be careful going home.
You're really shocked, aren't you?
Are you okay?
Are you saying everything Son-in-law Kim said is true?
Yes, Mother.
What in the world...?
How can a person do something like that?
I know.
You really don't know the inside of people.
Such an elegant and perfect looking madam stole someone else's child...
What kind of talk is that?
I still can't believe it.
By the way,
how did that bastard, Son-in-law Kim, find out the truth?
How do you think he found out?
Probably Hyungnim couldn't keep her mouth closed.
Anyway, that mouth of yours is the problem.
Why did you say useless things to Son-in-law Kim, and cause all this trouble?
Oh... I...
I felt sorry for Son-in-law Kim as a human being.
Why do you feel sorry for this jerk?!
Do you know what he has done to our Chae Won?!
Honestly, Son-in-law Kim was really devoted to our Chae won.
Son-in-law Kim's mom was the one who treated her awfully.
The alligator bag who've been carrying around lately, Son-in-law Kim gave it to you, right?
Alligator bag?
Oh...
I returned everything to him earlier.
If you say "everything", that means there were more things besides the alligator bag.
You're screwed up inside.
How come you don't have any principles?
No matter how much you wanted the alligator bag,
still, Chae Won despised Son-in-law Kim so much.
And, you sided with him?
I'm not being like this because of the alligator bag.
I was just moved by Son-in-law Kim's pure love and devotion to Chae Won.
And in the end, it became difficult for her to marry Se Yoon anyway.
What can we do about it?
I was really counting on Se Yoon to be my granddaughter's husband. What do I do since he's too good to give up?
You say something too!
Don't just sit there like that.
I feel sleepy.
Hurry up and lay down the blanket.
Hey.
Your father
looks very disappointed.
Aiyoo, what do we do?
Eh...
Aigoo... Aigoo.
The more I think about it, the more confused I get.
I can't object to the marriage or support it.
So...
By the way, that bastard, does he think this is his bedroom?
Hey, get up.
Won't you hurry up and go home?!
Hey!
If something like that happened, you should have discussed it with me.
How could you not tell me and keep it to yourself?
Am I really your husband?
I thought if I just kept quiet,
it would be easier on everyone else.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Then,
you're weren't ever going to tell Se Yoon?
Even though Se Yoon is my son,
Chae Won is also my daughter.
Finding my son
would make my daughter cry tears of blood
What else could I do?
I had no idea.
And I kept on talking about bringing your son back.
How...
How can we handle this situation...
I have no idea.
I was going to keep it a secret for the kids' sake.
I have no idea how things happened like this.
Se Yoon looked so shocked.
I wonder if he's ok.
Exactly what this is about,
tell us in detail.
What that person said earlier, is it true?
Did you...
Did you really...
Yes.
That's right.
I did that.
Honey?
Mom?
It sounds like an excuse,
but at that time, I didn't have a choice.
The son I gave birth to, after four miscarriages,
died as soon as he was born.
Would I be in the right mental state?
And having an orphan as a daughter-in-law,
your mom was unhappy about everything.
If I didn't carry on the bloodline,
she threatened to do it outside our marriage.
I had no other choice.
As soon as you were born, Choon Hee went to the hospital because the bleeding didn't stop.
Instead of feeding my crying baby,
I fed you my breast milk first.
While you were being breastfed,
I looked at you as you were watching my eyes,
even though I didn't give birth to you,
I felt that you were my child.
This is the truth, Se Yoon.
Those words are not enough justification, Mom.
I have no intentions to justify.
My feelings at that time,
that's what I'm conveying.
Even up to now, never once
did I think that you're not born out of my body.
Even in my dreams,
I never thought that.
You kept this completely secret from me.
How could you do that?
It might seem brazen,
but if I were to go back 30 years,
I probably
would make the same choice.
For me,
I really like being your mother.
You, being my son,
I really like it.
Even if I were to die,
even in the afterlife,
and in the afterlife after that as well.
Se Yoon.
I definitely
will be
your mother.
You seem to really care about your mother.
Compared to what my mom does for me,
this is nothing.
Mom is completely clueless when it comes to me.
She thinks I'm the greatest and wonderful son in the world.
Is that right?
Ehh~
Because you're staring at me that way, I'm too embarrassed to eat, Mother.
Oh.
Aiyoo...
I'm sorry.
You're really shocked, aren't you?
The person you're calling is not answering
Please leave a message after the beep
He has his cell phone turned off.
Where is he, and what is he doing?
Aigoo...
You haven't gone to bed yet?
How could I sleep when you left like that?
What were you doing all this time?
I went to the in-law's.
Which in-law? Chae Won's?
Yes.
Lee Se Yoon's family was the invited guest for dinner, so I went and sprayed cold water on their party.
Sprayed cold water?
That's jerk Se Yoon
his birth mother is Chae Won's stepmom.
Wait,
Are you sure you didn't misunderstand?
That jerk's birthmom is really Chae Won's stepmom?
I'm telling you it's true!
That's jerks mom took her dead baby,
and switched him with Se Yoon.
Oh my God!
How could someone be so awful?
Aigoo, externally,
She acts so high and mighty all the time.
She's not even worth a penny.
What are you guys still doing awake?
Hey hey hey~
The heavens have helped you and Se Yoon out.
What do you mean all of a sudden?
That Se Yoon, the truth is
Chae Won's stepmom's son.
What are you talking about?
You're just now home.
You didn't answer your phone so I was worried.
I want to be alone.
Please get out.
Se Yoon.
I said please!
I don't want to hear another word
or say anything.
Ok,
I understand.
Go ahead and rest.
Se Yoon
just came home.
Where...
Are you going?
For now,
I'm going to sleep in the other room.
I could have prepared breakfast,
Why are you awake already?
I'm sorry for yesterday.
I had no idea son-in-law Kim would have done that.
The cold wind is really blowing.
It's not a cold wind, but the wind of a swipe of a knife.
I don't care how much you like alligator bags.
How could you?
I told you,
I didn't do it for the alligator bag,
but because I felt sorry for him!
Yeah right!
Did you sleep well Sook Ah?
I've been recording all night, and having some ramyun now.
Drinking the refreshing ramyun broth made me think of you.
So I'm texting you.
Who's texting you so early?
It's a spam text.
The person you are calling is not available.
Please leave a message after the beep
Can I come inside?
Yes, Mother.
Were you able to call Se Yoon?
Not yet.
Surely,
there wouldn't be a problem, right?
I'll go to the company later.
Even if it was hard,
I was planning to keep everything a secret.
How could this happen?
You were let down a lot, right?
Are you already leaving for work? What about breakfast?
I'm fine.
Aigoo. But anyway,
The sales were going up steadily, but how come we're always losing money? Huh?
Why do we have to extend ourselves to private loan?
Loosely wait about a month. I'll be responsible for putting us in the black.
Can I trust that?
During launch period, there were many 1+1 sale (buy1 get1 free) &amp; rebate events, and ad fee expenditure was heavy too.
Now that consumers brand awareness is up, we're going to carry out a regular marketing strategy.
Aigoo.
But, was what Oppa said yesterday true?
It's true!
How could someone who thinks so highly of themself
be such a thief?
We were about to be in-laws with that person!
How can a human act that way?
I can't even imagine!
I'll be leaving before I'm late.
Ok. Work hard.
Aigoo aigoo aigoo aigoo aigoo~
Your sister couldn't even have breakfast because of work,
and you come down like this?
I'm just a front man, president in name only, anyway.
Aigoo, must be nice!
What do you mean must be nice?
I can't sleep because I'm thinking of Chae Won.
She can't marry that guy anyway so isn't it a shoe in?
Don't just assume, but go and talk to Chae Won for me.
Aigoo...
As we're at the juncture where Joo Ri and that jerk are over, why on earth do I need to visit that household?
Don't you want to have grandchildren?
What?!
If I don't marry Chae Won, then I won't ever marry.
So if you don't want grandkids, then do whatever you want.
Do you have to be like this?
No matter how much I tell her you changed
she doesn't believe me.
So you go to her and show her you changed.
Aigoo drat, aigoo drat, aigoo drat!
MOM!
What the... You scared the crap out of me!
Just once~
Aigoo~ Aigoo Aigoo Aigoo.
AIGOO!
I'm here...
Se Yoon.
Oh...
When did you get here?
Just now.
Have a seat.
I was worried because I couldn't reach you.
Are you alright?
I'm trying
to be alright
the best I can.
It's hard.
Mom is really worried too.
You didn't have breakfast, did you?
Mom made this.
I made
the heart.
For mom's heart.
How...
Is she doing?
She's...
Doing her best.
It must have been difficult.
How long has she known?
I don't think it's been long.
When the head nun past,
She sent a secret diary to mom.
Nothing should change.
Even if my birth mom is your step mom.
Nothing,
should change between us.
Later...
Let's talk about us later.
Since the end of 1 + 1 promotion (buy one get one free), the sales has been declining significantly.
Our competitor has launched a new product as well.
We got a new product?
Try our new noodles
Enjoy our new noodles.
Welcome.
It's been a long time.
You're even doing this?
You didn't have enough work at the factory
so you picked up a part-time job?
If you're not going to try it then leave.
I'll try it.
I'm curious about the new product.
Thank you.
Oh...
Congratulations.
You must be happy to
have a big brother like Se Yoon.
Again, congrats!
Welcome. Try our new noodles.
Put Kim Yong Gun on the phone, please.
You are aware of our competitor's new product launch?
I just tasted it, and it's completely different than the typical prepared noodles. Find out how they produced it!
Thank you
Welcome. Try our noodles.
Here you go.
Try this, our new noodles.
What brings you hear without a word?
I've brought young radish Kimchi because you said you were eating rameon noodles after an all-nighter.
I didn't ask you to bring me lunch.
With our relationship you didn't have to tell me anything, oppa.
I just wanted to bring some for you
so just enjoy.
You made this kimchi yourself?
Of course, oppa!
I'm so touched!
Having Sook Ah's hand made kimchi,
Is this a dream or reality... I'm unsure.
Pinch me.
Ouch.
Since you're here come and have a tour.
Oh, your sister-in-law's husband is here.
Her husband?
He started recording.
No it's ok. I already have plans.
You're leaving after you came all this way?
Just today.
Also, please don't tell
my brother-in-law that you saw me.
Don't tell him about the kimchi either.
How come?
Because he's such an odd bird.
He doesn't have a good relationship with my in-laws either.
Ok. Don't worry.
You must have had a guest, President?
Someone I know came to see me.
I mixed this for you,
So enjoy!
Wow
Thank you.
Have it with this kimchi.
Ok.
This is a familiar taste.
Pardon?
Oh, nothing.
That's kimchi is totally the same as the in-laws.
Album hot of the press.
Is it to your liking?
Why are you acting like this??
Boss, you're my savior.
I'll become #1 with "Teu Teu Roo"
and repay you 10, no 100 times back.
For certain, without a fail,
I'm gonna become a Psy of teuroteu!
Yes, yes!
That's great to know, now let go.
I won't ever let you down!
I'll do my best.
I can do it!
Yes, yes, you can stop this now
Boss, I'll be the best singer in Korea.
I understand just...
That's okay!
In my life,
you're the best!
Stop this now!! Enough!
My noodles are soggy now.
I hate soggy, puffy noodles more than anything.
You eat this.
I got too excited.
It's alright.
Father-in-law! Are you okay?!
Father-in-law!!
Father-in-law, father-in-law!!
What's wrong? Are you okay??
Take me home.
You don't look good, shouldn't you go to the hospital??
No, it's okay, I just need to go home
I understand! Let me carry you
What on earth happened??
He was just sitting there
at the neighbor pharmacy so I carried him here.
Then you should have taken him to the hospital? What can we do here at home?
There's no need, I'm fine
You're not okay, father
It could be a huge problem!
I did it to test Kang son-in-law.
I did it on purpose so don't worry.
Father-in-law..I
am son-in-law
Is that right?
Judging by the way you ran with me as a piggy-backer,
I think you can live about 50 more years.
There won't be a problem with you a Gi Ook.
So what you're saying,
is that you're acknowledging me as your youngest son-in-law.
Can I take it like that, Father-in-law?
Thank you!
Father-in-law
Thank you so much!
Actually, today, my album came out for the new song.
So I'm so happy.
Father-in-law.
You even called me Son-in-law Kang.
Even if I were to die right now, I have no regrets.
Hey,
How can you leave my daughter and die?
I'm just saying, that's all.
What's going on here?
Mother-in-law, you're here?
What are you doing here, Rooftop?
Just now, father-in-law
called me Son-in-law Kang.
Mother-in-law too, please don't call me Rooftop anymore.
Please call me Son-in-law Kang, Mother-in-law.
Thus, what dog-eating-grass kind of nonsense are you talking about?
Have you gone senile?
How could you call him son-in-law?
Do you have dementia?
Please stop it, mother
Sul Joo Unni
What do you have to say?
I shouldn't say these words to you, but
my heart.
is at peace.
All these years, not for one day,
I was able to sleep
without anxiety.
I always suffer from nightmares.
I'm anxious and apprehensive.
From the very moment I've stolen your son away,
I was locked up by the jail of conscience,
for 30 years,
I couldn't live breathing freely.
I thought it was the rightly receivable
punishment.
You should.
After ruining someone's life completely,
if you were able to sleep in peace, then would you be a human being?
What...
Can I do to make things right?
Even though I can't
erase your heartache
How can I
compensate you, at least a little bit,
for your ruined life.
Even now,
if I were to be judged by the law receive my punishment,
would your heartache ease?
If not,
should I disappear from your eyes?
To far away,
Should I go abroad?
If that won't do, our Se Yoon...
I mean,
your son...
Put him on your family registry
and you guys live together
Then, would you be more at ease.
I'll do everything you tell me to.
I really will, Choon Hee.
I'll think about it.
I...
really missed you.
Even though I insisted that you to go back to the States,
when I saw you after 30 years,
deep down I was happy to see you.
I wanted to just tell you everything.
I wondered if I should beg for forgiveness.
I kept on having such weak thoughts.
Because I didn't want to waver anymore,
I became
more harsh towards you,
and treated you awfully.
We...
The way we were 30 years ago...
Is it possible to go back the way we were, Choon Hee?
You are very brazen.
How can you, with the current situation,
want to return to the way we were 30 years ago?
I,
cannot forgive you until you die.
No.
Even when I die and become a ghost, I cannot forgive you!
Ai, you rascal, why do you keep making me repeat myself?
Ok, I got it!
Today, I will get a definite answer when I get back, no matter what. So,
just CHILL OUT!
Hello in-law.
How have you been?
It couldn't have been good because that thief.
You must have went through a lot.
Why are you here?
I heard the story from Chul Gyoo and thought about you, in-law.
How you must have been so heart-broken, so I came by as fast I could to console you.
How could she appear after we were talking about her?
How can you call yourself a human being?
Aigoo, in public, you totally
act cultured and refined but in reality you were lying. How can you steal someone else's priceless son?
I've seen all kinds of thieves at my age,
but this is the first time I have ever seen a baby thief.
These kind of people should have
a huge advertisement posted about how they're human trash.
That's enough.
Aigoo...
You're so kindhearted.
If someone did that to my Chul Gyoo...
I wouldn't be satisfied even with them locked up.
Aigoo, she's acting haughty until the end. Distasteful.
Aigoo, nauseating.
If you're done, then please leave.
What do you mean done?
I'm just starting.
I told you we have nothing to talk about.
Why do you even come inside the house?
Aigoo,
How can you not even offer your guest some water?
and repudiate me before I even start?
Hah! Please.
Boss, I'll be outside.
Okay!
In-laws, I'm here.
First your son, and now you.
Ah.. Why are you here again?
What do you mean?
We promised to forge an alliance, reneging now would be a slight.
Who's here?
Have you been well elder?
What the heck are you doing here?
I had a cause to come and discuss with you, Elder, so I came by.
So what I'm saying is
We should get the kids back together.
Back together?
Since she can't marry Se Yoon,
let's go back to square one, and have Cheol Gyoo and Chae Won
get remarried.
That's what I mean.
You think marriage is a joke?
How could you say that?
That makes no sense.
How can we trust you to send
Chae Won back to THAT house?
THAT house?
Don't you think you're being rude?
What do you mean rude?
Just thinking of how much Chae Won suffered, it still makes me shiver.
This... in-law...
Why have you been so quiet all this time?
You should say something to help me out during times like these?
What should I say?
Why are you talking like that?
Earlier,
I sent a video to my ex daughter-in law.
If she remarries my Cheol Gyu, then as of that day,
I'll let them have a separate household,
and only once a month,
I'll see them, I vowed.
As they said, a previous governor is the best governor,
After time passed, honestly, there's no other daughter-in-law like Chae Won,
in the world. I've realized that thoroughly.
So,
Despite my shame,
that's why I'm here.
To ask for your permission.
Please
let's get Chul Gyoo
and Chae Won back together.
We have no thoughts to do that.
I,
never thought of anyone but
Se Yoon for my granddaughter.
What do you mean?
How can you say something that is so obscene?
Se Yoon's mom is Chae Won's step mom.
Even so,
you will approve of their marriage?
That's all.
"How ill bred is this family?"
Yes?
What are you doing here Father in law?
You must be busy. I don't know if I'm bothering you.
No you're not.
Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
No that's alright.
It's been rough, huh?
I know it's hard.
I...
Wish that you could be
understanding of your two mothers.
For thirty years
Chaewon's mother who thought her son was dead and
the mother that raised you
for thirty years
the both of them are your mothers.
At this point, whom would you choose, and whom would you get rid of ?
Your birth mom, or the mom that raised you.
They both brought you to this point.
Even though it may be difficult,
I hope
that you will be understanding of both of them.
Also,
the issue of your marriage to Chaewon
take some time and think about it.
Father in law
I can't ever break up with Chaewon.
That problem;
later,
let's discuss it later.
Aigoo!
Aiyoo!
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy!!!
Mommy, Mommy!
Aiyoo. Your mom won't die, so stop calling me.
What did in-laws say?
Aigoo...
I can't believe it.
What?
Chae Won's grandfather!
What about grandfather?
For his grandson-in-law
Se Yoon is his only choice.
It's not like he's senile, seriously.
That's strange. There's no way. He loved me!
Aigoo~ You're so confused.
Not even one person in that house hold was on your side.
Stop drinking the kimchi juice and get to your senses!
Then are you saying I should give up on Chaewon?
I can't ever do that!
I don't care if you give up or not. I've done all I can so you're on your own now.
There's a big problem.
What happened?
I just received a word from the borough office that
from our noodle
twice the standard allowance of
heavy metal has been found.
What are you saying?
How could they find heavy metal from a perfectly fine noodle?
I believe it must be due to the main ingredient
mugwort.
What are you talking about? When you received mugwort delivery, didn't you check the quality assurance certificate?
We checked,
however,
because we received the delivery of cheap priced murgwort,
there was a problem.
A-ah, tell Kim Joo Ri director to return quickly, to the office, quickly!
Honey
Are you sick?
No I'm not.
I was sleepy so I laid down.
I'm not sick.
Ta Da!
Omona! Your album is out.
What do you think?
That's awesome!
Your picture is very handsome.
You know I'm truly photogenic!
You're better in person!
Oh~
I have to celebrate cutting my album (CD). Gotta throw the celebration party!
I bought pig feet and makeolli.
What...
What's wrong honey?
The pig's feet seems rotten it smells funny.
It's fine.
It's not rotten.
It must have been something I ate at lunch.
Anyway, I can't eat this so you enjoy it by yourself.
Then makeolli,
have a cup.
This is rotten too.
No it's not.
I think you're wrong.
Did you plan to ruin this company as well?
How can heavy metal be discovered in the noodle, huh?
Something must have went wrong.
That cannot be!
This is impossible!
Hey!
What happened?
It looks like we'll have to recall all the noodles distributed in the market.
What?
How can we do that after so much money has been poured over it to distribute it?!
It's already all over the internet.
You may have to prepare for production suspension or operation suspension,
even an administrative measure.
What?
Ahh~
AHHHHHHH~
Mom!
MOOOOM!
Oh...!
Are you ok Mom?
OOOOHHHH~
Mr. Kim Cheol Gyu's mother was here?
She asked if you could
get back together with Kim son-in-law.
Do you still have some feeling for him?
That's nonsense Dad.
In any case with Seyoon...
Even if I don't get married to him,
There's no way I would be with Mr. Cheol Gyu again.
Goodnight
I met with Se Yoon earlier.
I went to see how he was doing.
Thank you.
He must be going through a lot.
If you want
to live with Seyoon do so.
Don't pay attention to what others think.
Just do what you think best.
I'll follow your decision.
Where did you drink so much?
I have to drink so I'll be able to sleep.
So I had a drink.
Seyoon...
I thought my mom was the warmest and
best person in the world
I did, but...
now that I look
Mom you're a really scary person.
How could you do something like that
And for 30 years,
Act like nothing happened?
When I think of that I get goose bumps all over and get frightened so
I can't look at your face.
I'm sorry.
That's alright.
I can go up myself.
Hello?
Chae Won
What?
There's...
Nothing different between us.
Like planned,
Let's get married next month.
Why aren't you answering?
Who cares who's son I am?
I love you
and you love me
Isn't that what's important?
Since you're drunk just sleep
and we'll talk tomorrow.
Chae Won,
You're mine.
You belong to Se Yoon.
From your head to your toes
I won't let anyone take you from me.
Se Yoon...
We worked so hard...
to break up?
Even if I die,
I can't do that.
I can't do that!
Se Yoon
Se Yoon?
Did you fall asleep?
Living, isn't living
Why did I fall in love with you?
longing for you just expands
I can't bear to forget you.
I still
only love you.
Let's talk for a moment.
I've been thinking for awhile.
Let's pretend
like the wedding plans never happened.
Father.
After finding out the truth,
there's no way you can marry each other.
Honey...
If,
You decide to marry her,
I won't be your father anymore.
Honey! How can you say that?
Stay out of it!
I don't care who your birth mother is,
You're my son.
That's how it was in the past, and that won't change.
But,
if you insist on marrying that girl til the end,
I will take it as your decision to cut our father-son ties
that's how I will take it.
Father?
Also,
Since the person responsible for that is your mom
We will separate.
Father?
In other news
Green Noodle produced by Joong Yong Gp, launched last June, was found to contain lead, cadmium like heavy metal
therefore the Green Noodle currently in distribution is in a state of total recall.
Green Noodles already sold within the market place amounts to 390 ton,
in that time, noodle...
What is this saying?
Isn't that Kim son-in-laws company?
Yea, isn't it?
We put the entire first half of the year's budget into noodle launch,
and in addition, we borrowed from the private loaner
you say Total Recall! I mean...
What are you going to do about this?
How can you deal with such improperly run company?
I was trying to reduce the operating budget so we looked for a cheap provider
I'm sorry.
Haven't you heard penny-wise and pound-foolish?
How can you be so clueless?
Ayyy..
Who are you?
What..what is this?
Geum Yong Food is
charged with production, distribution, and sales of heavy metal to the market place
hence the court issued a search and seizure warrant.
Eh, what?
From now on, we're going to start search and seizure.
No, no
no, what is this?
Who are you to touch my things?
What is this?!
Seriously~
For the charge of production, distribution, and sale of heavy metal containing noodle,
the court issued an arrest warrant for Ms. Bang Young Ja.
As an accused, you have a right to select a lawyer, you have a right to remain silent
you have a right to refuse answers that may be against you.
Aiii..Aigoo, hey!
Mom!!
-Ah!
-Mom!
Aigoo, I mean what did I...?
What did I do wrong that I have to--
What is this?
My mom hasn't done anything wrong!
We were cheated!
Hey take me instead!
Don't cuff my mom!
What is this?
Hey hey hurry and call the lawyer
Let's go to the police station first.
Ai-ya!
Hey! Hey! Hurry, let's go to the police station.
Mom!
Oh my mom hasn't done anything wrong!!
Ah this
why are they taking pictures? Go away!
Get away!!
Mom..MOM!!