Final Episode 50
You said you would make sure I never get my hands in water loudly.
Making me even shave you.
Lee Se Yoon sshi
Isn't this joke a little too harsh?
Look at you just lying still and not even responding.
You can fool the doctors and everyone else, but
you can't fool my eyes.
Se Yoon, I know you are listening to everything I am saying.
The patient's present condition is not just unconscious, but
it looks like he will progress into a vegetative state.
Vegetative state?
If the patient remains unconscious for more than one month,
it will be difficult to regain consciousness.
It is for certain.
They said Se Yoon was in a vegetative state...
That can't be true.
When I say it
The eyes that always looked at me
were always sparkling.
So, hurry up and get up.
All the times you gave me a hard time,
you have to repay it.
Let's see.
Hundred Year Inheritance
After shaving, you became more handsome.
Here drink this medicine, it is good for you.
I made it, so
Get up, and
drink it all up.
I am fine.
What do you mean you are fine?
At times like this you are supposed to keep your eyes straight.
And take care of your body.
If Chae Won's mom gets sick to, then it will be a big problem.
So, get up.
Drink it all up.
Get up.
My own child is like that,
How can I drink this as a mother.
Why are you saying nonsense.
Because you haven't collapsed is why the kids are doing their best.
Don't say anything, and
drink it up.
Hurry.
Even if it doesn't go down, force it down.
Don't even leave a drop.
Good, Drink it all up.
Aigoo...
One's mind can be so tricky.
Not long ago, Sister,
you took Se Yoon away from me.
I wanted to kill you with my hate.
Since, Se Yoon turned out like that
I think I can connect with you.
Sister, you are also in torture as well, like me.
Sister, like me,
you must be hurting.
We both are
Se Yoon's mother.
You thinking like that,
I am thankful.
Sister, as you said,
If I raised Se Yoon,
I would have probably placed him far away,
or sent him to an orphanage.
Like Se Yoon right now.
I wouldn't have raised him that well.
You did well.
For you to
make me feel embarrassed.
It is not to make you feel embarrassed.
Unni,
come to Seoul with me.
Don't you miss Se Yoon?
It may seem belittle of me, but
I will remain here.
I want to repent.
I'm a person that doesn't have the courage to be next to Se Yoon.
From here,
I will volunteer and pray
for Se Yoon's full recovery.
For Se Yoon,
protect Se Yoon.
Promise me.
Sister.
After coming from the hospital, you became totally mute.
Are you in shock?
You don't need to think of it as serious.
Every time I went alone,
I felt lonely, and
All the wives with their husbands,
That is why I took you along.
If you don't like it, I will go alone from now on.
I knew you were a strong person.
It is really amazing.
A child without its daddy is hard to do.
Why did I do that?
A child that looks like you,
I want one.
Ma Hong Joo.
A Mamma boy,
I don't know why I like you either.
That's just what I want to do.
That is all.
Se Yoon sshi!
Please wake up.
What is wrong?
Why are you like this?
Please get yourself together.
He was just fine a bit ago, but then it's strange.
Se Yoon shhi!
Hey look, get yourself together.
Nurse! Nurse!
Se Yoon sshi!
I will call the doctor here in a moment. Please lay him down to the side.
We have to keep his airway clear.
To the side. To the side.
Wait just a little bit.
The doctor will be here, so it should be fine.
The patient is fine.
Why is he like this all of a sudden?
It is something that can happen after the surgery.
Everything is fine and stable.
After a little bit more treatment in the ICU,
we will move him back.
Yes, thank you.
It is nothing too severe. So, don't worry.
Thank you for today.
Are you okay?
Yes, I am fine.
There is no problem.
You look very courageous.
For me at the beginning it was uneasy and hard, but
when I think about it,
the fact that I can even wait for him,
I think it's a great blessing.
We are breathing the same air.
That is true.
When I see you, I have the thought of having more courage.
Lately,
there's been another life that I'm waiting for.
Hong Joo is pregnant.
Congratulations.
Do I have any traits to be a father? It made me want to run away.
When I see you,
I have the thought of having more courage.
Aiyoo... You're very tired, aren't you?
Congratulations, Mom.
What... What are you saying out of the blue?
What should I be congratulated for?
That... What is that...?
Isn't that an ultrasound picture of a baby?
Whose is it?
What do you mean "whose"?
It's mine.
What do you mean it's yours?
Congratulations, Mom.
It looks like you are going to have a grandchild in a few months.
You... Did you have a mishap?
Hong Joo...
Hong Joo... is pregnant.
What... What happened to her?
Hello?
Hey, do you think my son is a pushover?
It's been a long time, Mother.
Have you been well?
Ah... That's enough!
Didn't you take every penny that you could for your alimony?
Now, you're saying the baby you're carrying is Cheol Gyoo's?
You're framing him?
What do you mean by that?
To say it bluntly,
how can you guarantee the baby you're carrying is Cheol Gyoo's?
How would I know you didn't get pregnant by fooling around with others?!
Mother, you're still the same.
You... I want to...!
I'll make it short.
Just pay back my money.
Money? What do you mean?
You only lived with him for a few months, and
you took away all our assets. Does it make any sense?
Are you that worthy?
Mother.
Ah! Mother or Father...That's enough!
I'm in a very difficult situation right now.
I really need that money.
Let's meet first thing tomorrow.
We'll talk when we meet.
If I meet with you, I don't think it will help with my pregnancy.
So, I'm sorry, but I have to refuse.
Then...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey... don't hang up!
Hey! I'm not done talking yet!
HEY!!
This wench...
Her rude behavior hasn't changed at all.
Do I look at it this way or that way?
Damn it!
What's the matter, Mom?
Hey, read this. Aigoo... Aigoo...
The merger of Tae San Group and Geum Ryung Foods...
The CEO is Ma...
Chairman Ma Hong Cheol's only daughter, Ms. Ma Hong Joo?
Hey, hey, when she met with you, did she say she got married or
anything like that?
No. She didn't say anything like that.
You have to get back with Hong Joo again!
What's this? You were so upset yesterday!
She's pregnant. We can't just ignore that!
A man should be responsible.
It's your baby. We have to take care of it together.
You came?
Se Yoon...?
He was transferred to the ICU last night.
Why? Did he turn for worse?
He had convulsions all of a sudden.
You should have called if something like that happened.
Did his condition deteriorate?
They said it is common among patients who had neurosurgery.
In a little while, they said he will be moved to a regular floor, so
don't worry too much.
Aigoo... What would happen if the days just go by?
Your insides must be turning into ash.
You came?
Aigoo...Whoosha...
It looks like a lot more than before.
Right?
I'm back.
Oh, Chae Won...
Are you just coming back from the hospital?
Yes.
Se Yoon... Se Yoon hasn't made any progress yet?
Did they deliver the salt?
A little while ago, we received ten sacks of refined salt.
Are you changing out the salt?
Yes. Starting this month, I want to change to refined salt.
Okay.
Here...
By the way, you re-registered your marriage with Bo Reum's mom, didn't you?
No, we didn't do it yet.
If you just put it off like that, not only her first love...
What would happen if her second love shows up?
Hyungnim!
Did I say something incorrect?
So, let's just go to town hall and do it!
How many times do I have to tell you? I absolutely cannot re-register until I get a formal proposal from you!
I stopped by the bank on the way back from the hospital.
Bank?
Yes. We have to share the profit as I promised before.
You worked hard all this time.
-Thank you.-Thank you.
Oh my goodness!
It's this much?!
Let me see. Let me see.
This is definitely a jackpot!
This wife...
We were supposed to split it precisely in halves.
If father were to see this, he would have been happy.
I feel that way.
How pretty!
By the way...
You can't say two different things with one mouth.
You said you would buy everything I want.
Honey, you definitely promised, ok?
I got it.
Gangnam's madam must have had a hard time working at the factory and living with in-laws.
I am so proud that if it were up to me, I would buy the whole store for you.
Only you know the hardship I had.
Pick anything you want.
Ok.
Let's get out of here.
Why? You don't like anything?
Come on.
Why did you come out empty-handed?
Oh, if I were to buy that purse...
How many boxes of our factory noodles do we have to sell?
I... really can't buy it because it makes me too nervous.
In the past, you were able to easily buy more expensive things than that.
That was then.
As the eldest daughter-in-law of a noodle factory, it doesn't suit me.
Let's go.
I will show you what's romantic!
You would never have imagined this.
Bo Reum's Mom. Bo Reum's Mom.
Mother.
Wait.
What's that?
It's sparkling a lot.
Isn't it a diamond ring?
It's a diamond!
But why is this here?
Just what "surprise" are you going to show me?
Come here. Come here.
Wait a moment.
What is Son-in-Law Kang holding in his fist?
There's nothing.
The other hand.
In that short time you touched other people's things!
Give it to me.
Give it to me now!I can't do that for free, brother-in-law.
Give it. Give it!
Give it.
Spit it out! Give it to me!
I didn't put it in my mouth.
What is it, Bo Reum's Dad?
The diamond ring that I was about hold while proposing to you was swallowed by him!
What?
You're really doing everything!
Stop playing around, spit it out.
Give it! Give it! Give it!
How can you swallow the ring?!!?
Chae Won.
-Did you run here?  -Yes.
I thought I may not make it to the visiting hour.
Is Se Yoon's guardian here?
-Yes -Yes, I'm here.
The patient has woken up.
What?
Se Yoon?
Se Yoon, are you regaining your senses?
Do you know who I am, Se Yoon?
Mom...
Chae Won...
Yes, yes. It's Mom.
It's mom, Se Yoon.
Thank you.
Thank you, Se Yoon.
For waking up like this, I thank you, my son.
You've worked hard throughout this time, Se Yoon.
Thank you.
Hello?
It's Chae Won, Mom.
Se Yoon...
Did something happen?
Se Yoon woke up.
Really?
Yes, he woke up awhile ago.
Ah...really!
Thank you, thank you.
You and your mom worked hard during this, Chae Won.
Thank you.
Thank you, Chae Won. Thank you very much.
What? Aigoo, is this a dream or is it real?
Is it true Se Yoon has regained consciousness? He can recognize people too?
Yes, yea. I'm on my way now.
Aigoo.
Our Se Yoon, woke up?
Yes, Mother-in-law. Just awhile ago,
Yes, he recognizes everyone and he's mentally unscathed.
That's great. It's great.
Now the big sister-in-law and Chae Won can rest easy.
I couldn't stand to watch the mother and daughter during this. I'm so glad.
Your father is smiling from heaven right now.
Ah yes. Father-in-law helped us from up above.
Shouldn't we slaughter a pig and put on a feast for the village, mom?
Let's do it. What could possibly stop us?!
Let's do it!
Ah...so glad...
Mom!
I heard you became a total popper?
This woman is just...
Do we really have to live together with your mother?
Can't it just be you and me?
Korea's biggest Mamma boy.
I understand.
My mom changed so much.
She is not the old Bang Yong Ja chairman anymore. That person doesn't exist anymore.
She's swearing to become the best mother-in-law
of the Republic of Korea, and is burning with desire so
Just trust me for the last time.
She always has only the burning desire, pah!
Aigoo, Aigoo.
Sit down.
Aigoo, it's not like you're carrying just yourself. What deep bow should be necessary?
Aiyoo between us two, what formality should be observed, Ms. daughter-in-law?
Have you been well all this time?
Ah, by the way,
I totally forgot.
Aigoo, our daughter-in-law is looking so fine.
What fine? My shoulder's laden with burden due to the unexpected responsibility for the company.
By the way, how did you become the CEO?
Cheol Gyu gave me whole bunch of Geum Ryong shares when we divorced, so I became the majority share owner instantly.
I've heard that you've treated badly on the account of you being the child born on the wrong side of the blanket,
but in reality
it doesn't seem that's true.
I have a good relationship with my oldest brother since we are half siblings.
Ah...I see.
Now that I get a chance to say it, after making you leave like that
my heart ached so much.
I bet you were upset, huh?
It's all passed now.
That's right. It's all in the past. Let's brush off all things in the past and
let's start anew with new attitude.
From now on, I'm going to consider you my real daughter not a daughter-in-law.
If you do that I'll appreciate it.
By the way, you're not saying you'd like to live here together, right?
What to do?
Daughter-in-law must have heard the rumor and is aware,
that we got caught by the evil conman so
we've become penniless.
Even though this house is small and uncomfortable,
let's think on our situation and
I hope you can understand us.
Then come to our house.
Where is your house?
-Your last house. -Our house?
Yes.
You...you mean you bought the house I used to live in?
If sister-in-law doesn't have any suitable job lined up, start working in our company starting next week.
I'll find a post for you in the business planning department.
Really?
You are my chief secretary?
Why aren't you answering? You don't like it?
Aigoo, what do you mean "not like it". He's like this because he does like it.
Aigoo, he likes it!
Aiyoo, you have become our family's savior!
A savior, I say.
You've revived the nearly collapsed husband's family...
You are the most devoted daughter-in-law among the daughters-in-law!
Aigoo.
Aigoo, you good luck charm.
Chae Won worked hard throughout this time.
Every morning she brushed your teeth and shaved your face.
Even though she's my daughter,
I was really touched.
I only did the things that are normal to be done.
That's why I'm saying this,
what do you think about quickly getting them married?
What do you think,
Chae Won's father?
Then,
do you give your blessing for the kids' marriage?
I'm very sorry for everything.
If I just hadn't objected,
the kids wouldn't have had to go through this much trouble.
I'm sorry.
Sister-in-law,
Thanks, Honey.
Congratulations, Se Yoon.
Thank you.
It's time for Se Yoon to take his medicine.
Congratulations, How do you feel?
Good.
But, Doctor.
I have no feeling in my hands and it's hard picking up a cup.
I also have no feeling in my legs.
My condition won't continue like this, right?
In your case,
though there isn't any specific nerve damage in your limbs
there is a slight possibility that you may have disability
due to undetected neurological nerve damage.
What you just said,
does it mean that I might not be able to walk?
Right now there is nothing that I can confirm.
You must have patience
and do your best rehabilitating yourself.
There is no other way.
Surely,
it's not like Se Yoon won't be able to walk, right?
It's not it.
That won't happen.
Don't worry about anything.
It should be like that.
There shouldn't be any problem.
Don't worry,
Calm your heart.
I thought you would've thrown out that ring with anger.
I'm thankful that you still had it.
Truthfully that day,
I got a plane ticket from your mom and went to the airport.
I was planning on giving up on everything and following you.
So don't be angry anymore, okay?
How can I get mad at you?
You're the person that has been with me all this time protecting me.
Se Yoon.
Thanks.
I owe you a life-long debt of gratitude.
I'll give you a chance to repay me.
Since father-in-law gave us his permission to marry, so let's
I'm sorry.
I can't even walk...
In this situation,
how am I supposed to propose to you?
Se Yoon...
I'm sorry.
Be careful, careful.
Carefully.
Over there.
-Yes. -Yes.
You came, Mother.
Aigoo, I feel so relieved to be home
and away from living amongst those ignorant and inelegant women!
Aigoo, there's no other heaven!
Aigoo, where did Mrs. Park go?
I sent Mrs. Park away.
Oh.
So there is another worker besides Mrs. Park coming?
With Mom here, why would we need another worker?
What?
Wait.
You mean, then are you telling me to be responsible for the kitchen duty too?
So am I supposed to do it?
No,
Well...
This is my room.
Why is this your room?
This naturally is my...
It's the biggest room in this house,
and you want to use it all by yourself?
What?
If you want to be living off of a daughter-in-law,
be sensible, okay?
Living off of daughter-in-law?
Ai, hey,
Mother-in-law says because I'm pregnant I should use the master bedroom.
Seems like Mom changed alot.
Right? Didn't I tell you.
I told you that she became Korea's best mother-in-law.
Thanks, Mom.
I heard you turned down when Chae Won asked you to propose to her?
Just in case I can't walk due to a side effect of the accident,
or other disabilities
I couldn't decide to marry with ease.
Se Yoon...
I don't want to laden Chae Won with that sort of burden.
I can't do that.
Why are you only thinking about the bad?
Let's think more positively, shall we?
I can't even walk...
I can't propose to you, Chae Won.
Aiyoo.
Ah...
what brings you here?
I'm a person in charge of the banquet
for the International Conference of Asian Arts &amp; Culture
named Bahg Gyu Sik.
Operation Center of Cheong Hwa Dae (Blue House = US's White House)?"Chef Bagh Gyu Sik"
I'm a chef.
What?
But why did you come-
Your noodles have excellent reputation.
Thank you.
My job is to make dishes at the Blue House,
at this time, I've come to be responsible for the banquet
during the International Conference for the Asian Arts &amp; Culture,
I came in hope of offering your noodles during the banquet.
Our noodles?
Yes.
I also wanted to watch how the unique tasting Son-Gook-Soo (hand made noodle)
was being made, exactly.
Oh, yes.
Come this way.
I'll give you a guided tour.
Yes, thank you.
Bo Reum's Mom. Mom!
We will start with the easiest step first.
♫  I can’t love you.  ♫
♫  I can’t approach you.  ♫
♫  Why do you get farther away when I love you?  ♫
Even among the patients who are diagnosed as paraplegic
some are known to walk again if they focus on rehabilitation process.
So, don't give up.
♫  Although I’m standing in that spot, crying as I wait.  ♫
♫  Living doesn’t feel like living. ♫
♫  Why did I come to love you?  ♫
♫  My longing keeps growing bigger,
♫  I can’t bear to forget you.  ♫
♫  So I still only love you.  ♫
Se Yoon.
Are you not here?
Did Lee Se Yoon go somewhere?
He told the doctor that he would go on a trip for a few days.
A trip?
Where did he go?
I'm not sure.
"The telephone of the person you're trying to reach is turned off..."
Just where did he go when he's not completely healed?
Fox, a fox. There isn't more cunning fox amongst all the foxes, doctor.
Aigoo, when my son's around, she pretends to be so nice
but as soon as he's gone
right away her true nature comes out!
Aigoo, she is beyond wicked!
Since the subject came up,
she checks the housekeeping ledger and checks even the receipt...
Man, oh man. She's so cheap and nasty, I can't stand it!
I mean, doesn't she know I've earned as much as money as she does back in my hay day?
She is such a know-it-all and a showy of her wealth that
I just can't stand it.
In a word, a turn-off!
I'm bet you were upset.
For sure I'm upset.
I feel like inside here is all charred completely black and
is only left with ashes.
I see.
I mean, what kind of a person treats her mother-in-law
less than the dog she has?
I mean...
A dog, you say?
Yes.
To her dog,
she does all kinds of pampering for the dog giving snacks on time
but she never ask her mother-in-law whether she ate or has skipped a meal
not even in passing.
In a word, she's inhuman.
So the major source of your frustration is your daughter-in-law.
Yes.
I would like to live in a world without a daughter-in-law.
I feel each day
is beyond suffering.
We are in a war without a gun sound.
I can't stand it because it's so repulsive!
I feel so much better now that I've poured my heart out.
Who is that over there?
Isn't that Chae Won?
Hey, our baby.
It's been awhile.
How did you come-
I came to get treatment in the mental health department.
Mental health department?
Aihoo, I'm mentally struggling a little these days.
Is something wrong?
No, it's just...
Just laugh, laugh.
Just laugh.
You have all the fun you can have with another man, do all things you should or shouldn't do with him
and deny all by saying "I can't remember any of it"
and return to the way things were before?
I will ask for forgiveness after confessing the truth.
You are going to live as if nothing happened, is that right?
Wow! You really live the world as you wish.
I'll return Cheol Gyoo to you, Mother.
I will unconditionally get a divorce.
So, please leave my father alone.
I understand your feelings now.
What?
These days,
I suffer unfair treatment from my daughter-in-law,
I'm saying that I now understand what you were feeling.
It is said there's no person above another nor below
and there should be no mother-in-law above daughter-in-law and vice-versa,
as I keep on suffering,
I feel as though I have come to understand you.
Why are you saying this so suddenly?
I'm being punished right now.
All the things I did to you are being returned to me exactly.
I'm being punished by the daughter-in-law right now.
I didn't know it back then,
but I have come to understand your feelings a bit.
Throughout that time,
I was too harsh.
Forgive me.
If I don't apologize to you now,
for the rest of my life,
as I live or die, go left or right,
I'll remain exactly as I am now
being treated less than a dog.
So, I'm sorry.
What's with your face?
Since you're caring for the sick, you have to eat better, don't you know?
Buy something to eat and put some products on your face.
It's fine.
It's my sincere effort so just take it.
This is all I have right now.
Mom, where are you right now?
Uh, I came out to run an errand.
I informed you that today was Coco's vaccination day. Did you go to the vet?
Hey! Hey, your mother-in-law is about to die of anger!
Do you think you should care about a mere dog, right now?!
Mom!
I understand. I'm going.
I'll see you.
I'm back.
Is there no one home?
Where did they all go?
Mom? Aunt?
Grandmother isn't here either.
Se Yoon was like that too.
Where did everyone go without a word?
Hello?
Chae Won, There's a problem.
Why? What happened?
Right now, all the noodles we supplied to Arts & Culture conference are spoiled.
We have a mess on our hands with food-poisoning.
The noodle was spoiled?
There's no way that could happen.
I'll go over there right now.
Today you can't cry like the last time, okay?
Ok, am I an idiot?
Don't make a mistake,
just do as you always have.
If you do that then first place will be yours.
Maybe it's because this is live broadcasting? I'm so nervous.
Even my heart feels like it's clanking.
Our "Blessing" is going to criticize
that daddy is a coward.
So, fighting!
"Blessing"!
Daddy will have glorious victory on the stage! Fighting!
-Fighting!  -Fighting!
Awesome!
Next contestant is this contest's Teuroteu genre's favored candidate
Ddool Uh's Gang Jin!
We'll announce.
This week's Teuroteu genre's honored
1st plaaaaaaaaace is...
Kang Jin's, Dooruh.
Yes!
Honey!?
Uh?Hur!
Why is he fainting after singing so well?
I say he does all kinds of craziness.
Call them and check whether they should go to the hospital.
There's no reason to. He just fainted from loss of nerves.
Never mind, mom. Don't worry about a thing.
I think uncle-in-law will be up on YouTube again!
It's admirable though.
1st place is 1st place, no?
That's what I'm saying. When you go out in public, that song is played constantly!
Gang hubby is definitely an outstanding person.
Hey, can anyone take the 1st place?
Chae Won came.
Oh!
Let's go.
Excuse me!
How do I get to the International Conference center?
By any chance, are you Min Chae Won?
Yes.
Please follow me.
There's no way the noodles are spoiled.
Please let me meet with the person in charge of food preparation.
First, follow me.
Mom!
Mother-in-Law!
What's going on?
First of all,
let's change your cloth into this.
Just what is going on?
Throughout this time,
Because of us things have been hard. It's a present.
What?
We've decided to have a small wedding ceremony just with the family.
You'll marry Se Yoon, right?
I want to do that but,
Se Yoon hasn't-
Don't worry.
Of course the bridegroom has agreed so we could hold the ceremony, Ms. Bride.
Se Yoon
agreed?
Where in the world is there a man that wouldn't like a beautiful bride like you?
A big thanks to all our faithful viewers.
Chae Won!
Aiyoo!
My daughter is really very beautiful.
The celestial fairy has descended from the heaven!
Dad.
Throughout this time,
I'm sorry for upsetting you all this time.
If we talk about feeling guilty, I should be more sorry.
Don't cry.
Your make-up will get messed up.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Groom, enter.
♫  I won’t ever cry again,
♫  I'll show you a smiling me.  ♫
♫  I don’t want to stop, I want to keep going.  ♫
Bride, enter.
♫  a little more, dear heart.Because I have you, who is looking at me,
♫  I can withstand this.  ♫
♫  I have you who holds my hands, and
♫  and looks at me with your eyes.  ♫
After their wedding ceremony ends, should we take a photo since we're all dressed up like this?
I've never seen a human being that asks to recycle a wedding ceremony.
Still, the diamond ring isn't recycled.
I'm wearing considering that it's your sincere effort.
I feel all grossed out when I think how the ring was in Roof-top's belly!
No matter how hard try I just can't like that guy.
♫  I'll show you smiling me.  ♫
♫  I don’t want to stop, I want to keep going. Just a little more,  ♫
♫  My heart. Because I have you, who is looking at me,
♫  I can withstand this.  ♫
♫  I have you who holds my hands, and
♫  and looks at me with your eyes.  ♫
-Se Yoon!  -Se Yoon!
What happened?
I want to surprise you.
so I put unbelievable amount of effort in physical therapy!
This is all thanks to you, Chae Won.
For holding my hand,
until the end,
and not giving up on me.
Thank you.
What did I say.
Chae Won's Grandfather is helping from heaven.
Thanks, Choon Hee.
For giving birth to such an amazing son.
Thanks Sister, for raising him to be such an amazing person.
"Olden day Noodles. 101 year anniversary"
Thanks for the delicious noodles.
Yes, thank you.
Glad you came.
Even though the world has become a place that believing its prosperity gave right to look down upon noodles
the noodles during hardship
is a thankful food that filled the hungry bellies
and economic and readily available food eaten during the wedding or ancestral rites ceremony
and is a warm food that melted the coldness in hearts.
I hope that you who have come to continue the 4th generation family business
also will not extinguish
that warm embers.
"COULD YOU KNOW THE TASTE OF NOODLE?"