Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 47
Se Yoon!
Mom left home.
What did you say?
She turned off her phone so there is no way of reaching her.
I was wondering if she had contacted you.
If she does call me, I'll have my secretary call you.
What?
Besides meeting for work, I hope we don't meet for personal reasons.
I'm sorry.
I knew you would get hurt, but...
I had no other choice.
After knowing very well that Mother went to the emergency room in an ambulance,
I couldn't insist on our marriage.
Though, it's not that I don't understand your feelings.
I'm too tired to go on now.
I was sure that I'd stay by your side
for a long time until the end.
I guess I overestimated myself.
If mom calls me, I'll contact you.
The customer's phone is powered off... Please leave a message...
Do you think our company is your playground?
Didn't you just submit your resignation and run away?
Now you have decided to come back to work on your own?
I clearly told you,
That if you marry Chae Won our relationship would end along
with your position in the company...
I didn't get married.
Mom went to the ER in an ambulance yesterday.
The emergency room? Why?
They said she overdosed on the anti-anxiety medication.
Keeping it secret from the family,
she has been getting psychiatric treatments all this time.
What?
If I decide to go to the branch in the U.S., will you reconcile with Mom?
If you promise me that you will, I can leave as soon as next week.
She is cold and cruel.
Without saying a word, how could she
just toss us the divorce paper and leave home?
We never even had an argument.
Did she really not say anything about it to you?
She didn't.
It's not like she has any family. And since she lived abroad for so long, she doesn't have friends in Korea.
Just where could she have gone?
She wouldn't go back to america, would she?
Then there is really no way of finding her.
I'm really disappointed.
What are you disappointed about...?
If you really thought of Chae Won as your daughter,
then, you wouldn't be like this.
Even if Se Yoon is your Son, Chae Won is your daughter.
As if nothing is wrong,
how could you say, "Let's let them get married."?
How can you say that?
Until now I have thought of Chae Won as my daughter.
I was wrong Choon Hee.
I shouldn't have said those words to you.
Since I apologized please come back.
Choon Hee.
Where are you right now?
You must have been very suprised...
I'm sorry.
Where are you right now? I'll pick you up right away...
Just tell me where you are.
If I didn't end it now, there would have been no way to end it later.
This could all end by sacrificing only myself.
Please honor my wish.
Then what about me?
If you leave like this,
haven't you thought about how I... would be?
Do you not care whether I live or die?
I know that you're having a hard time,
For our children's future, we have no choice.
We have to make the sacrifice.
I can't do that. I won't do that.
I can't live away from you one minute or one second!
If I'm not there, then Se Yoon and Chae Won can get married.
There won't be any problems.
Seriously, how are you understanding what I said?
Do you only care about the kids,
am I nothing to you?
If you leave like this...
I...
Do you think I can live without going crazy?
Honey.
Don't torment me anymore.
Tell me where you are. First lets just meet and talk.
If you leave me like this,
the only choice I have is to bite down on my tongue and kill myself.
I'm sorry.
How can you do this to me?
How can you hurt me like this?
I'm sorry Honey.
If you know you're sorry, then stop doing things that will make you say that.
Hurry up and come home, immediately.
Even though it wasn't that long...
Meeting you made me quite happy.
I spent all my life being lonely as an orphan.With Father and Mother,
I was fortunate to live in an extended family.
and I got to have a pretty daughter like Chae Won.
Having met you,
I got to live like a person.
Honey.
Even at our age, parting is so difficult.
I cannot let our children suffer like this.
Let's just end it here, please?
I'll give you a call when you're over me.
Don't hang up Honey.
Honey? Honey?
The customer's phone is powered off...
Geum Yoon Food has been focused on contributing in dietary life of people
with foods that are mass-marketed but nutritious.
However, recently,
due to management's lack of knowledge
and sub-standard food production
we were not able to meet the customers' expectation for which we deeply apologize.
Yes
In order to change the image to
forward thinking Geum Ryong Food,
from CEO and president to
entire executive board members
will be resigning.
You've worked very hard mom.
Here, it's Cheongsimhwan (pill for calming one's nerves).
Please take this and chew carefully.
The company I gave my entire life to establish
is now in the hands of undeserving wretches! What...
I'm sorry Mother.
It's because of me..
I should have came to my senses a long time ago.
This is all my fault.
You often called me awful and ignorant,
we live in a world where if you close your eyes they'd steal your nose off your face.
Look at this.
I sweated blood all my life to build my company.
With eyes wide open, it was taken away.
The world is a very scary place.
Because I was brought up like a hot-house plant, I didn't know the way of the world very well.
Going through this ordeal, I have realized a lot of things.
You've realized more things?
How come you have so many things to realize about? Huh? Why didn't you realize a little earlier?
What's it about, after the soup has been spilled and the bowl has been broken, huh?
Aigoo.
Why can't I see even a nose booger of Lawyer Hong's?
Fetch Lawyer Hong.
Yes, President.
But, Mom, what's going to happen to us now?
We have to sail with the wind direction, and
we have to follow where the water spills.
President?
What?
His phone number must have changed, It says that number is unreachable.
His number changed... What are you saying?! Did you push the numbers correctly?
Last night I...I.. I called him last night. What are you talking about.
The number you've dialed is not in service. Please try...
What happened?
What is it Mother?
I have a weird feeling.
Weird feeling?
Wait mom.
What?
What is going on?
Mother!
Why?
Why won't this open?
It must be his day off, Mom.
No, but, It's not even the weekend, why would the doors be closed?
Excuse me.
We came to find out something. But here, the lawyer's door is locked?
The sign is still left there.
This office shut down.
Aye,
why did an upstanding business close?
The Lawyer said he had to move overseas urgently
they were going to close up the office, I heard.
He went overseas?
Mother, Mother.
Be careful.
No. No. When did the doors close?
It's been 3 or 4 days.
This rotten
we even spoke yesterday but he didn't say a word about this.
How much did you give Lawyer Hong?
I said, HOW MUCH DID YOU GIVE HIM?
All of it?
All of it, I gave all of it.
Real estate and savings and etc., all of it...all of it...I put all of it under his care.
Oh my god, even Chae Neung (?) account is also under Hong attorney's...
Aye, no way, no way.
There is no way this is happening. This isn't possible. He wouldn't betray me
How could he betray me?
That rascal. Mom we have to report this to police.
What will we do?
Aigoo.
What are we supposed to do?
My blood money.
Aye, my blood money, taken right in front of healthy eyes.
What to do?
Mom, Mom! Are you okay? Come to your senses!
Mom!
Ow.
This won't do. Mom, get on my back.
Mom, Mom.
Common let's go up.
What is it?
I was worried about how you were doing.
Are you feeling better?
Bringing me to the hospital,
I understand you had a hard time.
Thank you.
Up to that, is that hard for a friend?
I brought porridge.
Take a bite.
let's go sit on the bed.
Since I hurt inside, I still can't eat.
I'm sorry, Sul Joo.
Truthfully,
I was very
jealous of you.
Not only you have a capable husband, you have a great son as well.
You didn't have one thing missing or lacked anything.
Watching your perfect life,
I...
I envied you to death.
And,
since your husband is the owner of the company our Seul Hong's daddy worked for,
I wanted to appease you
and always felt timid
so I kept trying to read your intent and please you.
I'm sorry
No,
No. I'm not saying this to get an apology from you.
I'm confessing to you right now, Seol Joo.
I had such an inferiority complex towards you
I thought a lot of bad things.
When I found out that you were not Se Yoon's biological mother,
I sang a celebratory song in my head.
Finally, that haughty and overproud Baek Sul Joo
would be taken down without mercy.
I'm bad right?
You have the right.
I've been pretty fussy and
over sensitive.
While driving over to the emergency room in the ambulance,
I thought about it.
When you're better,
I must ask for forgiveness.
What forgiveness...non sense.
Thank you, Do Hee.
aigoo... stop crying.
You're going to ruin your beautiful face.
So,
How is Choon Hee faring?
Oh, Chae Won's mother
left home this morning.
She...left...
home? What does that...
What are you saying?
Welcome...
Who is this?
I've come, Unni
One and only Choon Hee
Oh my world!
Have you been well?
Without any warning, what brings you here huh?
I came to be a burden to you, Unni.
Please promise me,
This shroud..
You have to wear it 20 years after, okay
Father, promise me.
I promise.
You leaving like this. Is that why you brought me this present?
Se Yoon's mom.
I will be leaving on a long journey.
You should see me off.
This is so frustrating.
Why did these good teeth get so sensitive?
Why...what's wrong?
I'm sick and tired.
Because of Chae Won's mom,
These teeth are causing suffering, suffering.
Are you have a toothache?
Last night's dream was a bit on the wild side...ow ow.
Say "ah".
What would you know.
I said say "ah".
Wow, your molar is black and rotten.
You just left it until it became like this?
You should have gotten treatment at the dentists.
I went a while ago, and the doctor said
I needed have a new tooth put in.
It sounded like it would cost a lot of money.
Stand up.
Let's go to the dentist together.
To fix my teeth?
It will cost a lot.
Come on, get up.
What's going on?
That miser old man is giving a large amount of money without a complaint.
Since you came,
ask the dentist to fix whatever needs fixing too.
I'm fine.
Fine, really?
Because of your teeth you can't even drink cold water.
I'm fine, so just worry about yourself.
Ms. Kim Kkeut Soon.
Right here.
Please come with me.
I'm scared. I have a bad feeling.
Are you a kid, to be afraid?
Go in there with me and hold my hand.
Aigoo, that exaggeration...
The relationship between you two must be very good. It's really nice to see, Elder.
She has many worries,
so please go easy on her so that it doesn't hurt.
Yes, Elder.
Grandmother, please say "ah".
-Ah. -Yes, that is very nice.
What brings you here?
Aye, yes, we're interior remodelers.
The madam who'd be moving into this house next month has asked us to renovate.
Re..no...va...
Renovation?
Ah, yes.
You have to move out by the beginning of next week so that we can start the construction.
You sold the house too??
And that money too, [went to] Lawyer Hong?
Uhh, uhh. (yes)
Aiyoo, I was going to go house-hunting when the company problem ended.
What are we going to do?
Cheer up, you'd be great.
All you have to do is just answer only the question being asked.
No need to be nervous.
I know. There's no problem.
When you were in concert, you performed in bigger venues, honey.
I said I'm not shaking so it doesn't matter.
Kang Jin, get ready.
Yes.
Honey, fighting!
Ba-sha (fighting!)!
Today after 10 years, we're here with trot singer, Kang Jin.
Yes.
Please greet the fans.
Hello
I am a comeback kid with a new song, Gang Joon.
Yes, nice to meet you.
The album is coming out after 10 years,
and I'm wondering if there is a specific reason for that.
Yes, after a long time waiting for this album overcome with emotions,
he can't speak. Is what I'm saying correct, Kang Joon?
Ah, well, yes, because of radio format
I'm sure all the viewers would know but
I believe Mr. Gang Joon is reminded of the hardship experience while he was an unknown.
It must have been very hard.
It appears that we cannot continue...
Should we take a listen to the song now?
Yes, here is Kang Jin's live performance of Dooruh.
Thank you very much!
♫ Even though life is hard, I shouldn't get stressed out.
♫ Love makes me cry.♫ Money makes me feel bad about myself.
My apologies to everyone.
I kept on thinking about sad and difficult times of my life.
I'm sorry. I'll try to sing well.
♫ Break away... Break away...♫ Break away... Break away... Break away...
♫ I'll break away from my suffocating life.
♫ I'll take charge. I'll just run towards...
Yes, oppa.
Did you hear the broadcasting?
I was listening and thought it so absurd that
I bet you're kind of unhappy, Oppa?
This was a hard earned interview opportunity. I'm so mad.
I feel a little stressed. Do you want to have dinner with me?
Do you have time?
Of course! I have time.
Yes.
Then I'll see you there.
What do I wear today?
What are doing over there?
Nothing.
She really is cheating. My feeling was right
♫ Love is that not anyone ♫
♫ not something that everyone can know ♫
♫ I came to know it only today ♫
These people are acting without fear in the middle of the day?!&gt;
Whichever bastard this is, just you come home, wife.
I'm going to teach him a big lesson
♫ Did you love me? ♫
♫ If it's that, do say that to me ♫
♫ Should I go back? ♫
♫ There's nothing I can do ♫
Encore! Encore!
She must have gone crazy. What are you doing?
Now.
A guy that looks as slippery as the Yin Jeol Mi (rice cake) that has a coat of sesame oil
He's a total gigolo even at one look.
Why did you already come? You should sing a few more.
I was feeling so off put that I sang a song.
This is a place where singers who signed with the company performs occasionally.
Yah, after seeing your face
my frustration has completely gone away.
"My Sook i"? "That, that, that courtesan's brother like gigolo!"
Actually, there is somewhere that I want to take you.
With me? Where?
Oh my god, this is a luxury brand retailer that I've only heard about.
Gang Sook do you like luxury brand?
How can I on my situation?
What luxury brand would you need when you yourself is a luxury brand?
Oh my my, that's non-sense. How could I be...
You came, President.
Bring out the ones that I picked and show it to her.
Ok.
which one do you like?
"The fact that he hasn't been able to date shows clearly."
How can you ask a girl to pick out the proposal ring.
Is there nothing that you like? Should I tell her to bring more?
No, no.
This one seems to be the prettiest.
As I thought, my Sook, you have a discerning eyes.
That's the one I picked too.
Yes.
Get this ready. When will I be able to get it?
In a week.
Ok, a week.
Lets go.
So we're done?
Why? Is there anything else that you like?
I'll buy it for you, so tell me. Do you want a necklace? or a bracelet?
Just the ring on it's own is very expensive. How could I ask for a necklace or bracelet too.
No, that's fine.
Then lets go eat.
What kind of ring did those people, that just left, look at?
You mean this?
How much is this?
Fifty million won.
Fifty million won??
Honey, I am taking another look at you.
I thought you were a miser who would shiver at the thought of spending even a penny,
but you charge a huge amount on a credit card so that your wife can get her teeth fixed, and
I didn't realize what a big spender Mr. Um Paeng Dal was in the past.
It's not cause your pretty that I did this.
No?
If you can't chew properly, it might lead to other issues.
Later it might give the children a difficult time.
I'm doing the prep work ahead of time.
If I get dementia, you're going to pass me off on the kids?
If I get dementia, for certain, you have to feed me and change my poopy diaper.
Why are you making your children do the hard work?
Talk about your meanness.
What's wrong? Are you sick somewhere?
No. Nothing's wrong.
What do you mean no when you're sweating so much?
Let's rest for a bit.
Yes, I understand
Ahhhhhhhh! Honey! Honey!
Ki Moon's Father!
A person has collapsed over here! Please save him!
Honey you can't loose consciousness.
Please save this person!
Grandfather are you okay? Come to your senses.
Can you please take him to the hospital?
Honey! Honey! You can't loose consciousness.
Honey you have to stay conscious
Yes. Hello
Mom?
Mom, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Mom is crying? Why?
Emergency room?
Dad fainted?
Mom?
You came?
Just what happened?
Why would he suddenly faint?
How could this happen?
Why mom?
Your father...Your father...
What about father?
Did the doctor say something was bad?
They said it's cancer.
What?
I didn't know at all, your dad kept it hidden until now.
Aigoo, what are we supposed to about this? What do we do about this?
Dad?
You didn't hear wrong, right mom?
What misunderstanding? The doctor told me just a while ago.
Grandfather..
told me to keep it a secret.
You knew?
Yes.
He fainted before in the factory.
So we brought him to the hospital.
If something like that happened you should've told me.
why would you keep your mouth shut?
Chae Won has no fault.
I wouldn't let her.
Honey.
Dad.
Help me up. I'm going home.
What do you mean go home?
You have to stay in the hospital and get treatment.
I know my illness the best.
If I rest at home I'll be okay.
Stay quietly put.
Grandfather.
Subtitles brought to you by the Inheritance team @Viki
You...
What are you doing here.
I heard it from Se Yoon.
How are you doing?
The doctor said
I can be discharged tomorrow.
Then when you get discharged, I'll also return home.
Se Yoon decided to go back to America.
What did you say?
Even if it's a little difficult right now,
he'll come to understand including about the wedding.
Then..
What about Chae Won?
Se Yoon can't leave,
until he marries Chae Won.
What are you saying right now?
Are you in the right state of mind?
Of course I'm not, that's why I ate pills
Honey.
Choon Hee left home.
She left, so there would be no problem with them getting married.
But how could you hold on to your greed until the end?
Greed?
Does this look like greed in your eyes?
Please stop.
Calm down.
I told him it was my wish to go to America.
If this is because of me, do something else.
Me unto you, I'm destroying your house.
I'm sorry Se Yoon.
Coming and going is part of life.
No need to make this serious.
When you are young,
death felt heavier than a high mountain.
now that I've become this age
lighter than the bird feather.
In addition,
I worried that what if the 3rd generational family business ends on my generation.
I was most worried but
luckily, you guys inherited, so
I don't have anything else to wish for since the company is now growing well.
Why do you keep talking weakly?
Go to the hospital and get another examination Dad.
Yes Father in law
I haven't even done anything for you yet.
I can't send you off like this.
You made a promise to me.
50 years.
If you come even one day before 50 years,
I will wait for you at heaven's door.
and punish you. Understand that.
Yes father in law, I'll be sure to keep that promise.
It's possible that the doctor could have misdiagnosed!
Let's go to another hospital and get a second opinion.
I've already done all of that. Nothing's going to change.
Father, go to the hospital for treatment anyway, father.
That way you can live a bit longer.
Let's go to the hospital today father.
I'm a noodle fool.
A noodle fool must die smelling flour.
would you rather I die smelling the disinfectant instead?
Why do you keep talking about dying?
I can't let you go dad.
Father. Father. Father.
Dad.
Son in law Min...
Yes Father in law
Send a message to Chaewon's mom
Tell her before I die
that I must see her on more time.
Tell her to come.
Yes. I'll do that.
Your father hasn't died yet.
I can't just go without giving you a hard time first.
that that mean grumpy old man, eww.
Subtitles brought to you by the Inheritance team @Viki
It's new voice mail."
Mom, it's me.
Se Yoon..
I heard everything from Chae Won awhile ago.
You've suffered from heartache all your life so
I cannot hurt you again.
Our marriage born of your suffering
that you can't be happy.
We will break up.
So return to your family mom.
I can't do that.
I'm a mother who hasn't done anything for you your whole life.
Even if you do this...
The only thing I can do for you is to protect your happiness.
You've worked hard all this time Ajumma.
No. It's okay.
It's not much.
Because I'm giving it, please accept it.
Thank you.
Mom,
we've cleared out everything so we should also leave.
How can I leave my house?
I've established our business hearing a loan-shark from people,
not eating what I wanted and not wear what I wanted, like living like dead...aigoo
Aiyoo, I'm too aggrieved to take it as is and return.
I can't go back now.
Within 3 years I will get us this house back mom,
so just believe in me.
If I find that Hong attorney or that weasel, I'm going to
scratch his eyes out.
What are you still doing here?
Hey!
If you didn't make those noodles or whatever this...
this wouldn't have happened.
There's no enemy like you.
In any case it's already in the past.
Please stop Mom.
What? It's already in the pass so I should stop.
Yah!
You blow away my entire life's worth of assets in one moment
and honestly can talk like that?
Then what do you want me to do?
Should I should just die in front of you?
How can you be so rude?
What kind of behavior is this towards your mom?
What did you do well that you are making such a fuss.
I'm really going insane!
Since this already happened don't pay attention to her.
Ai, I'm so upset and aggrieved...
I already told you...
your son will earn money in 3 years
and get back this house and also get back the company.
For today let's get out of here.
Aigoo let's go. Hurry!
Let's go
Just go
Is this where we're going to live?
The 3 of us are supposed to live in this place?
Well, it's a good place.
Aigoo...
I leave my perfectly nice house and what am I doing?
The rich takes 3 years to lose its wealth,
how can we be so completely broke suddenly?
This is embarrassing. What's wrong with you?
People are staring at us.
What's embarrassing when we all just became poppers?
Can you be of sound mind in a time like this?
This is so humiliating.
Get up
Aigoo, my mom does a one heck of a moving notice!
Hello
We are the people moving into 102.
We put ourselves in your care from now on.
Aigoo.
I don't think you can fit even 1/10th of your belongings we moved here.
If you make monthly payment
there's a place that keep your belongings in a storage container.
Keep your stuff there for the time being and
How can I shove my life's furnishing that I toiled for in a storage place?
I can't.
I can't do that.
No matter how we try, in this house you can only fit less than 1/10th.
Look here, madam.
one false move, you're going to end up living with your furnishings on your head.
Whether I live with my furnishing or wear them on my back, why are you talking so much?
If you came to move our stuff, focus on that, why do you have so much to say?
Ai, see here old lady. Where do you get off shoving fingers in my face?
Unlucky!What?
What?
Grandmother?
Unlucky?
Did you do anything for me when I became a Hal Mo Ni (grandma)?
Did you help me at all?
Mom! Mom!Let go!
Did you help me?Aigoo
Mom! Please stop this!
Aye, that's enough. Stop it now.
AigooCOMMON!
Quickly go to work.
Come in, Chae Won.
Hello.
You must have a production meeting in a conference room?
Yes.
Then.
Min Chae Won you also will come to the farewell party, right?
A farewell party?
The director is leaving to go to America next week.
I have another appointment, so I'll be leaving first.
Did you really not know?
You didn't hear anything from the director?
I've already completed your discharge paperwork so
you can just go straight home.
Why did you come?
I could have gone on my own.
This type of service
is only for a few days more.
Your mom...
hasn't contacted you yet?
Not yet.
I called Sister a little bit ago.
but she didn't go there either.
I can't think of where she might have gone.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I don't know if your busy or not.
It's me.
No I'm not Grandfather.
Because I lack strength
I'll get right to the point.
I, for my granddaughter,
have never thought of another person besides you for her.
Next to Chae Won -
you need to be there.
Grandfather.
I'll ask you for the last time.
Our Chae Won,
you have to take responsibility for her.
That way,
I will be able to close my eyes.
Father-in-law is very ill.
He wants to see your face for the last time.
Come home when you receive this request.
Stop causing people to bleed out with pain
and obey his words, Choon Hee.
If you just lay around, what can you do?
Go and serve your father
and be by his side at least.
When I was a child
I caused a lot of grief.
When I was going to school
I didn't study
I hung out with bad kids
so I gave so much trouble to him
I refused to take on the family business
take off this way and that
there isn't a single son as bad as me
anywhere in the whole world.
Still in the end, you straightened up and did factory work diligently so
your father was satisfied.
Even still,
good that's come of this bad situation is
The fact that dad
doesn't have to know,
that we got a divorce.
is a relief.
Thanks, Kang Suk.
Wa-wha
For what?
For not saying anything to him.
I will decide in near future.
Wha-
What do you mean?
Boy he sure talks as if he's on to me.
Brother-in-law.
Are you going somewhere?
Father in law want to see he whole family.
He want's to take a family picture.
Family picture?
Yes,
I'll call the photographer.
Call Sister in law and tell her to come here with Son in law Kang.
Suddenly why are we taking family picture?
Making me nervous.
We don't have time, quickly do it.
Chae Won,
Where are you right now?
Yes,
Work just ended and I'm on my way home.
Then grab a taxi and come quickly.
Why?
Is Grandfather getting worse?
No,
He wants to gather the family and take a family picture.
Family picture?
Ok.
I will come right away.
Chae Won.
If you say "don't go", I won't leave.
If you tell me not to go to the American branch,
I won't go.
Should
I not go?
♪ Crying as i wait ♪
♪  Living ♪
♪ doesn't feel like living♪
I'm sorry.
♪ Why did I come to love you♪
♪ My longing keeps growing bigger♪
♪ I can’t bear to forget you ♪
♪ So I still ♪
♪ only love you  ♪
Grandfather's expression is very good.
Ai, Hal Mo Ni and the children's facial expression is rather dark,
Happily smile please.
Kimchi,
Cheese,
Smile.
Ey, you are too stiff!
Please smile brightly.
Smiling pig's head (used for festivals etc.) fetches higher price, they say!
Don't scrunch your faces and
Just smile.
Yes elder your expression is very good.
One,
Two,
Three.
Wait.
Min son-in-law
Yes, elder.
Come sit next to me.
Come here.
Yes.
Thanks for everything.
you
aren't my son-in-law,
but my son.
Yes.
Thank you,
father.
Then I'm taking the picture now.
Everybody smile together.
One,
two,
three.
Subtitles brought to you by The Inheritance Team @Viki.
Extracted by rispana2.blogspot.com
Even though I've said this before,
noodles are for cold days
It's comfort food.
Before I die, this is my last request.
On the day of my funeral
make seriously delicious noodles
and serve it.
Chae Won.
Why did you...
Even though our relationship isn't good
since grandfather passed away I had to come.
Give your greetings and leave.
Chae Won.
This may be shameless but
can you comfort me.
To be honest,
I'm very scared.
The company is completely ruined and
we got kicked out of our home.
We moved to a place like mole's underground dwelling...
In front of Joori and my Mom I pretend that it's nothing but
truthfully several times a day I feel thiis way.
I sometimes feel like I'm being punished by the heaven for all the ill deeds mom and I have done against you in the past
Everyday is like living in hell.
But if you give me some encouragement
I will draw up some strength this time.
Chul Gyo.
You are a strong person.
You can start again.
Thanks, Chae Won.
I missed your one word like that until I went crazy.
Because you cheered me on,
I truly
will be brave!
Stop it now.