Episode 48
Because you've cheered me on,
I truly
will be brave.
Stop it now.
Subtitles brought to you by the Inheritance Team@Viki.
Did you guys have a fight?
Since you're here, you should pay your respect to Grandfather, and
have some noodle before you go.
The mood between the two seems very cold.
Father, Se Yoon is here.
Aigoo.
He always said there is no one else except Se Yoon for grandson-in-law.
That's how much he liked you.
I am sorry for coming so late.
Thank you for coming when you're very busy.
Grandfather
went to a good place, a peaceful place.
Aigoo, Grandfather.
Why are you over there?
Husband Kim is here.
The one who only gave you worries,
Cheol Gyoo, the miscreant who can't even behave properly as a person.
Husband Kim is here, Grandfather.
Aigoo.
This brat!
Why is he like this?
Ki Choon, Ki Choon.
Let him be. Let him be.
I didn't know you were this ill, not even in my dream.
If I knew you were, before you passed away,
I would have brought you
sweet red bean jelly that you liked so much.
Aigoo, Grandfather.
Please forgive your undutiful child... Grandpa.
This brat, he's making me cry.
I know.
He still has sentimental attachments.
You...
Let's have a chat.
Yes.
Grandfather...
How is your mother?
She have recovered a lot.
You should stay by her and give her strength.
I've told you before,
the one who gave birth to you is your mother,
and the one who raised you is also your mother.
Yes.
By the way,
mother has yet...
Yes,
I haven't heard from her.
I sent a letter telling her that Chae Won's grandfather has passed away.
Will she come now,
or will she come later,
I've been waiting like that...
By the look of it,
I guess she isn't coming.
I...
Father.
Truthfully, I am
leaving this Friday for United States.
I've been assigned to a branch in the U.S.
Does Chae Won know about this?
Yes.
I was hoping that she would tell me not to go.
But she didn't even move a muscle.
Thank you for coming.
Please eat and let me know, if there is anything lacking.
I'll be going.
Yes.
Go safely.
Before I leave for the American branch,
we might not see each other again,
so I'll say my good bye in advance.
Take care of your health
and be well.
You too,
be healthy and be well.
Of course.
I must do that.
Take care.
♫ I don't know why I started loving you.
♫ My longing for you becomes unbearable.
♫ I can't forget you.
♫ I still
♫ only love you.
I ate well. I'll be going.
Goodbye.
Lee Se Yoon, that jerk,
is going to America.
You must have been distressed during this period.
Don't be concerned with other people's business.
Just take care of yourself.
I am not the old Kim Cheol Gyoo.
Wait and see, with my name, I'll make an awesome comeback,
and I will definitely appear and stand before you.
These are not empty words.
Soon I will definitely show you the changed me.
They say if old people's eyes are not clear,
you're at heaven's doorstep.
Do you think you'll live long?
Of course, I will.I'll live 20 years longer than you.
Are you senile?
To this rude bastard and thief, you call him "Son-in-law Kang.
Are you demented?
Please stop mom.
Without a clue,
he, who's ill...
I tormented him.
I'm sorry.
Aigoo, I was wrong, husband.
If you have any disappointments, please let it all out before leaving.
I'll be following you shortly.
Please calm down, Grandmother.
Your grandfather,
when the thought of how much he must've been lonely and sad,
my insides are burning.
Even if no one else, at least,
I should have known, since we slept under the same blanket and ate together.
I was too unconcerned.
I did wrong... Honey...
Father-in-law left with full understanding.
You shouldn't torment your heart.
That's right.
Father...
probably thought all those things were charming.
I am sorry.
I'll accept all the punishment for my sins, later when I get to heaven.
Is it because you are of lesser quality?
Your class is totally low,
way down low.
How can such an elegant and precious person...
What's in this neighborhood
for a person like you to come?
Look at this fishwife, who are you sassing with dripping sarcasm?
Forget it.
Call for a person tomorrow
and ask for maintenance. Got it?
They said the one who's thirsty should dig the well
you buy the material and paste it!
Is this woman crazy?
Why should I ask for maintenance because of you?
Why on earth should I pay out of my pocket when the problem comes from the old house?
Then, the water falling from our living room ceiling
has nothing to do with you?
I have nothing to do with it, of course!
You... This iron masked (thick face) wench!
Oh my!
Let go!
Hey!
Aigoo, why are you like this?
Calm down Mom!
What in the world...?I'm speechless.
Aigoo...aigoo. These low class people...
Wait a minute. If water leaked from their bathroom
which dripped downstairs
and it caused damage
then naturally, with certainty,
they should repair. How dare she put out a duck pad (pretend innocence)?
Stop Mom,
You're going to be registered as the fighter within days of moving to this neighborhood, my mom!
Aigoo, aigoo! Hey!
What does it matter, as soon as we catch that con man,
we will be leaving this place without looking back!
Wait a minute, that household!
Aigoo. Aigoo. Mom.
Hold back. Hold back.
Aigoo, so not in the same class!
Aigoo, aigoo.
Subtitles brought to you by the Inheritance Team@Viki
You've been in your room this entire time, what have you been doing?
Come out and talk with mom.
I don't want to be bothered.
Lee Se Yoon is leaving for the American branch.
American branch?
Yeah.
He's leaving this week.
With "Zero"?
Why would my Chae Won go with him?
He's going by himself.
If I knew it was going to be like this,
I should have stayed by Sunbae's side quietly.
About now, since the situation changed,
we could have talked about marriage.
What's the point in talking about the past?
If you and "Zero" didn't get divorced,
there wouldn't have been a chance for "Zero" and Sunbae to meet.
Then I wouldn't have ruined the noodle project.
Then,
the company wouldn't get ruined.
Did you meet with your mom?
No.
Does she not know...
that Grandfather passed away?
Father said that he left a voice message for her.
Just where is she? Why doesn't she call?
How is your body doing?
It's doing better.
What about Chae Won?
Did you see her?
I'm
going to go up and rest.
Oh... Ok.
Did you not hear that Father-in-law passed away?
He worried about you and missed you
to the last moment he passed away.
The burial is tomorrow.
Come quickly.
Bid your final farewell.
I'll wait.
I'm sorry, Father.
I can't see you while you're leaving far away.
I've failed in my filial duty.
Oh my word, Father!
Father, forgive me.
Father.
This factory is the place
where you, Father, dedicated your entire life.
Please look around for the last time.
Aigoo.
If there wasn't this factory that was passed down for a 100 years,
there wouldn't be a chance for all of you to be here.
Please buy some noodles.
Subtitles brought to you by The Inheritance Team @Viki
I...
think that you
should inherit this factory.
Thank you.
You've accomplished a big feat.
We've won at the contest,
because of our noodle's superior taste.
In reality, it's your cooking skill that saved our family business.
Father,
we'll take good care of you.
Don't worry about a thing.
Father-in-law.
The weather today is also very good.
Then.
Let's start leaving.
Take me with you, too! "Uh-hah, uh-hah (chant in funeral process)
(colorful flags usually contained guarding the deceased)Uh-ha~ (mourning song &amp; chant)
Aigoo! Aigoo! Let me go, too!
Aiyoo. This place is cold.
How could I leave you in there by yourself?
Let me go with you.
Stay with me.
I'll stay by your side.
Mom, if you're like this...
Father won't be able to...
He won't be able to leave!
Mother.
Please let Father leave comfortably.
I can't let him go like this.
I can't let your father go like this.
Mother.
Grandmother.
Mom!
Ok.
Ok, calm down.
Shovel up some dirt,
and put it over your father.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
This is,
Grandfather's favorite kind of noodles.
I want to send this before he leaves.
Aigoo.
This noodle...I'm sick to death to this.
Isn't it enough that you've seen it all your life that
now you would take it even to your death!
My thought is
father-in-law will
even in after-life
make noodles
to feed the hungry.
What I'm thinking is right, Father-in-Law?
Of course!
I could see my father doing just that.
Father,
we'll work hard at the factory,
and Mom will eat well.
Don't worry about anything here.
Please leave well, Father.
Yes, dad.
I, too,
will get my act together and
live well.
It would have been good if you left after you saw the baby in my stomach.
I'm thankful...
The promise I made with you to meet in 50 years
I'll absolutely keep it.
Grandfather, I love you.
Grandfather, I miss you.
Grandfather,
you were my life's best teacher.
Thank you, Grandfather.
Bro...Brother in law! Brother in law!
What's wrong?
That... That...
I came, Unni.
You came early.
Were there a lot of customers?
Was it because of the hot weather? It seemed like only flies came in.
Did the funeral go well?
Yeah..
I guess.
Welcome.
Hyo Dong.
Drink this.
How can a person do that?
You knew my feelings very well...
How could you be so harsh, cruel, and
end it like that?
Weren't you worried about me at all?
Why wouldn't I worry?
I worried a lot.
A worried person
would just give a call that the divorce paper is ready and needs to be stamped?
And don't keep in touch at all?
I had no other choice.
Please understand me.
If I happened to seen you at the funeral,
for a lifetime,
were you planning on not contacting me ever again?
Then what was I supposed to do?
If I could only sacrifice myself, then my children would be happy.
Since I became a mother,
should I take care of my greediness
and ignore my children?
Who said to ignore them?
I just said to give it time and think about it.
My kids are crying blood, how can I look the other way?
Anyways,
since we met like this, I won't go back alone.
Just so you know, no matter what happens, you will be returning home with me.
What are you doing right now?
Come back home with me.
Choon Hee.
When I left home, leaving you and my family behind,
I made up all of my mind.
I'm being sincere.
So, just go back.
In order to let the children marry,
Choon Hee said she signed the divorce papers and left.
She signed divorce papers?
If she wasn't Chae Won's mom,
then the wedding between Se Yoon and Chae Won has no problem.
She said she would sacrifice herself.
If I killed Choon Hee 30 years ago, then
this time, you're the one doing it.
The kids are not even related by blood. There are no legal problems.
You just have to give your consent.
Don't lecture me.
It's against my values and ways of life.
Because of your principle oriented personality,
Choon Hee is forcing herself to part from Chae Won's father.
And, you're making the children
break up in the end?
You're saying it's all my fault?
Because of who, do you think this happened?
Again, you're talking about the problem's origin.
I understand.
Subtitles brought to you by The Inheritance Team @ Viki
Yes?
Why are you...?
I heard that you were going to America.
I wanted to see you once before you left, so that I could apologize.
I know you probably won't be able to forgive me with this one word.
I took the researchers from your company, and
using bad intentions and cheating with my factory.
I'm really sorry.
I was wrong.
Because I was betrayed by you,
I resorted to anything, and only thought to get revenge on you.
In the end, I received this punishment.
I'm sorry.
I hurt you also.
Let's forget everything that happened and just start anew.
We should do that.
What about work?
I'm looking into it but it's not too easy.
But...
I heard you're transferring to the American branch.
It turned out that way.
If you leave this time, when will you be returning?
Who knows!
Whenever my heart becomes clear,
I'll be there until then.
The name is Hong Jong Goo.
He previously worked as a lawyer.
That person stole all of my property!
If you can only find that rotten person, I will pay you well for the service.
Huh?
The undertaking fee is 5,000,000 Won?
Aigoo... No... The undertaking fee is 5 million won...
Then, instead of doing that, when you find that person,
I'll give you 1/100th of all of the things that he stole from me.
Aigoo, if you change the worth of it to money,
its value is very big!
Then, I'll generously give you 1/50th of my stolen assets.
Hello?
H-Hello?!
Oh no.
He is a genuine thief, just without a knife.
To just find one person, he's demanding so much money.
We already gave so much money to the detective agency. Stop here, Mom.
Aigoo.
What have you been doing since before?
I was writing my resume.
If I pass this out and beg every sunbae or hoobae I'm acquainted with,
I'm sure we'll hear some good news.
Aigoo.
You boasting that you'll get your old house back was such a lie.
If you go work under someone, when would you get our house back?
You can't get satisfied with just one try. Please wait a little more, President Bang.
Aigoo aigoo.
Seems like someone came.
Is it Joo Ri?
Joo Ri?
This lady, what brings you here again?
This... This trash is yours, right?
It's not like it has a name on it. How do you know if it's ours?
Ahjumma,
Your name is Bang Young Ja, right?
How do you know my name?
Inside the trash bag,
the moving company's contract was discovered.
So, don't think about denying.
Why is that in there?
You came?
Oh. You were here too.
Since this is your first time I'll let it slide, but
if there's more food trash or any regular trash,
I'll report to the organization and get 10 dollars from you each time.
Be careful from now on.
Yes! Yes, we'll be careful.
Aigoo, seriously. Hey, hey!
Here, 10 dollars! Use it to eat and leave.
What a rude and ill-mannered wench you are!
What? Rude and ill-mannered wench?
-Right!-You... You don't see...!
Aigoo! Aigoo!
Aiyoo!
-Let go of me! - Please stop!
Hey! Seriously!
Don't fight.
Don't interrupt! Hey!
Hey! I'm...
Why is this person like this?! Aiyoo!
You've worked hard.
Here...a sweet Popsicle.
Here...
Eat this, it's refreshing.
Relax my President Bang Young Ja.
Why?
Is it too cold to your teeth?
What should I do?
Should I heat it up a little to melt and feed you?
No.
Since we already moved,
you should try to get along with the neighbors
You fight all the time like a fighting rooster.
What will we do, Mom?
I just...
get angry.
Moving to this kind of neighborhood makes me angry.
Talking to those women makes me angry also.
Joo Ri who acted rashly to make noodles
which put us in this position...that makes me angry.
I'm burning up inside with anger.
I understand your feelings very well Mom.
But what can we do?
We have to accept this.
In my head I understand but
not in my heart
How did Geum Ryong Food's Ban Young Ja Chairman
become this inconsequential person?
I still feel as if I'm dreaming.
It doesn't feel like reality.
I'm sorry, Mom.
It's because I'm useless.
I want to go to our house.
I don't like mixing with low quality people like that in this kind of neighborhood.
I want to go home.
Mom, just a little more,
Lets endure it a little more.
Mom, don't cry.
Why the raw egg?
He has an event tomorrow so we're caring for his voice.
Hyung-nim do you want one ?
I'm fine.
But Oppa,
Umh. (Yea)
Pay more attention. Pay more attention to Unnie.
It's because I can't just stand by and watch.
What do you mean by that?
No more how i look at it,
it seems like Unni is cheating with the President.
They are each other's first loves.
Then,
You mean that guy who looks sleek like an In Jeol Mi (a kind of rice cake) brushed with sesame oil,
that's your agency's president?
It seems like you've met our President.
I did see him from far away once,
and he looked like a total gangster.
What do you mean a gangster?
He's totally pure!
He's got a humanity you can't find in this industry.
He looked like he loves to brag about his wealth...
he's just posturing, right? It's always the empty cart that's the loudest.
What empty cart...
Every song he releases hits it big
so he's famed to have the hand of music industry's Midas.
His private mansion is also
on highest point in Gang Nam (equivalent to Beverly Hills or Park Ave).
Subtitles brought to you by the Inheritance Team@Viki
What are thinking about so hard?
Just this and that,
and Father.
You really
are a good woman
Honestly,
When her ex-husband's father passes away
how many women would actually work so hard to help out
and share the heartache?
You're sounding mature for once.
During this time
you have done all you could so
I'll comfortably let you go.
You can go when you please.
Wh-
What do you mean by that?
If it were up to me, I would like to re-register our marriage
and live with you
But unlike someone
I don't have a lot of money.
nor do I have the capacity to succeed.
It's just my greed.
Lik-
Like who?
Is there something you know about me?
You-
Is there something your hiding from me?
No way!
Hiding? What could I be hiding?
If not, then never mind.
By the way, what was THAT?
What about?
I mean, if you are being broadcasted,
you should do some self promotion and
sing the song wonderfully...from the beginning to the end all you did was cry like a baby the whole time.
It was because I was so moved.
It was my first broadcasting in 10 years. When I think about all the hardship I faced,
how could I not be filled with emotion?
Like I'm saying,
what good is filling your heart with emotion?
when you bombed the broadcasting.
Despite that uncle-in-law's video is
a main topic on-line.
His video is getting a lot of hit on YouTube too.
What do you mean by that Seul Hong?
Yes, it's Ddul Uh's Gang Jin.
Yes, President.
Huh?
You scheduled me for another radio broadcast?
Another radio broadcast?
Uh, uh. Yes.
Yes, which date?
All of my uncles will help me.
We'll all do our best so
Don't worry.
Rest peacefully Grandfather.
I have a request.
The fact that I'm here,
keep it a secret for the time being.
Because you insisted til the end,
I might be going back alone today,
but that doesn't mean I've given up on you, Choon Hee.
Hyo Dong.
I'll be coming tomorrow and the day after and everyday after that to look for you.
Where do you think Paju is that you can come looking for me everyday.
It's my choice so don't worry about it.
Hyo Dong.
Be careful on your way.
Also,
Don't come again.
It's my choice!
So what you're saying is
you're selling all of this to me?
I don't want to
ask you for this favor but
If I were to catch the bastard who skipped town with my money, I have to pay
retainer to the detective agency.
Are you saying
that you don't have enough money to pay the detective agency
so you would like to sell the purses and jewels
is that what you are saying?
Oh my world, Oh my world.
Geum Ryong Food Bang Young Ja Chairman is selling purses and jewels
because she has no money?
I guess you just can't tell what tomorrow brings.
Ahhhh! Nevermind that!
Will you buy it or not?
What is this?
It's not a big amount but use it as a spending money.
What?
No matter how much I think about it, there's no one around me
who would buy a used luxury goods...
Is your pride hurt?
What's there to hurt my pride?
Aiyoo, cham.
Not knowing that I've been had with a fraudulent marriage
If I had sued you I would have gotten a big settlement.
Aigoo this person
has a conscience.
I'll use it well.
Conscience? Chairman
I agree.
But,
have you stayed in contact with your old Daughter-in-law, President?
old Daughter-in-law? Who?
What do you mean who,
Tae San Group's youngest daughter...
That's enough.
Ai...tasteless...why bring out the story of that thing?
A while ago I went to Paris.
By chance I saw someone that looks like your former daughter in law.
Her stomach was...
Since we're done talking leave now.
Just listen to what I'm telling you.
You're so annoying! -Her stomach...
Aren't you leaving?!
Go!No, I mean, Chairman.Go!
Go!No what I mean is...
If you're done with your business so it's all good. No, I mean her belly was...
Listen to what I'm saying President.
Aigoo! Get out now! President just listen to what I have to say.
So, I can start working from today on right?
Yes, of course.
Download the substitute driver app on your mobile phone
and don't forget to deposit gas-refill money into the virtual account.
Ah yes, Of course.
But, President
When one takes the substitute driver's job,
what's the approximate income?
If you have many calls then about 100,000 Won a day.
A beginner may even make about 5,000 Won.
100,000 Won...
5,000 Won you say?
Gim Cheol Gyu style is cramped quite a lot.
I have to do this kind of work just to earn 100,000 Won or 5,000 Won.
Cheol Gyoo
You have a strong side.
You can surmount this.
That's right,
since my Chae Won Cheered me on, I should do my best.
It's just temporary until I get a regular employment anyway.
Yes, is that the call center?
This is Gim Cheol Gyu substitute driver who started today.
The telephone of this client is turned off. The message will go to the voice mail after this announcement.
There will be a call charge after the voice mail starts.
Mom, It's me.
I'm departing on the evening flight, tonight.
I wanted to see you once more before I left.
Please contact me.
This time when I leave for America,
I don't have any thoughts of coming back soon.
So, make sure to contact me.
He is going on a plane today?
A guest came.
Guest?
The light has been flickering for a while and though I meant to change it I kept forgetting to do it.
But your husband is taking care of it all.
Why did you come here again?
I already told you,
That I'll be coming everyday.
I'm off to make a delivery.
Work hard.
Yes. Go on and back.
I...
have a question.
I heard that Se Yoon is being transferred to the American branch,
does that mean that Chae Won is leaving too?
No.
No?
I was afraid that you'd feel dissapointed, so I didn't say anything.
Se Yoon is asking to leave together
but I guess Chae Won isn't budging.
Se Yoon's father's objection is strong too.
Choon Hee, It's me.
I don't think you should be acting like this.
Se Yoon,
is being transferred to the American branch.
I try to stop him but
your brother-in-law is holding fast.
Also Se Yoon...
Then you should also let Chae Won go with him. Why are you letting him leave alone?
That...
Se Yoon and Chae Won broke up...
it's on that condition that he's going to the States,
Then what am I?
I divorced my husband so that Chae Won and Se Yoon could get together,
Just what is this?
Where are you?
First lets meet and talk.
There's no need to meet.
Se Yoon is leaving today,
Chae Won has to go with him.
Choon Hee..
Call Brother-in-law.
Tell him, that if he doesn't do as I say...
I'll be reclaiming Se Yoon as my son.
That is what brother-in-law fears the most.
Choon Hee.
Don't make me say it again.
Chae Won and Se Yoon must leave for the States together today.
If not, I may turn really crazy!
Was that Choon Hee?
Choon Hee said that,
if Chae Won and Se Yoon don't go to the States together,
She will...
Reclaim Se Yoon.
Is she threatening us right now?
Choon Hee got a divorce for the sake of the kids,
However, Se Yoon and Chae Won is
about to be ripped apart from each other
do you think she'll stay mum, knowing that?
I,
agree with Choon Hee.
you,
If you oppose until the end,
I will go to the police office,
and set straight,
what I did 30 years ago.
Then I'm sure it will become a sensational special story on mass media and
to a person like you who puts honor and pride before all else
and that will be fatal to you.
This person!
So please,
Honey, let's both end it right here.
Subtitles brought by The Inheritance Team @ Viki
Mom, please drink this.
Please get up Miss Kim KKeut Soon.
What is that?
Gang seo bang picked up a herbal medicine prescription.
Kang son-in-law?
Yes. I had it made from a renown medicine center so it should be quite effective.
Drink it all up then shake it off and recover, mother-in-law.
Are you guys in the right state of mind or not?
How can I bury your father in a cold ground and audaciously take the herbal medicine?
Gosh, Mother-in-law
how is father-in-law in a cold ground?
He's probably settled in the best seat in heaven
and in the midst of cranking out noodles.
Wow, since the noodle is being produced by our company's 1st, 2nd, 3rd, and 4th generation presidents
I bet the taste must be unbelievable.
Just for the sake of Gang seo bang's effort
drink up, mom.
Aye, common mother-in-law.
Here you go, mom.
Aigoo.
Way to drink it, my mom.
Here's a candy Mother-in-law.
Aigoo.
Yes, Oppa.
Do you have time today?
Why, Oppa?
Today is a very important day for me,
I would really like it if you could be with me.
Are you busy?
No, I'm not that busy.
Then meet in a hour at,
The Cafe we were at last time.
Ok,
I'll be at the Cafe we met at last time in a hour.
If it's the best event of his life then
I guess he's about to formally propose to me?
Also, since you've done as much as you should,
I'll let you go without a fuss.
Do what your heart dictates.
It feels like Bo Reum's daddy is also
becoming enlightened as of late.
You scared me.
Why are you so jumpy?
Are you hiding something?
Hiding? Hiding what?
I'm going to go out for a bit.
Where?
I'm going to go see some friends.
Ok, I understand.
Honey,
Uh, that
orange color dress, you know?
That seems to suit you the best.
Wear that when you go out.
Does he know something or not?
That Oppa is singing again.
It really looks like he is going to propose to me.
What should I do?
I'll ask him to give me some time for now.
I need to listen to Bo Reum's opinion.
Now that I am thinking of parting, I'm feeling sentimental.
He has a good personality and is well mannered.
Actually, there are not that many men around like Bo Reum's dad.
How did you like my song?
It's always nice.
Really?
Oppa!
Over here.
Who is she?
I told you on the phone earlier.
I said the biggest event of my life will happen today.
She's my girlfriend. I'll propose to her today.
With the ring you picked out earlier, I'll propose to her.
Ah, why don't you say hello?
She's my first love from high school, MS. Gong Kang Sook.
I've heard a lot about you, Unni.
Yes...
Over here, she is my first love when I was in my 30's, Kim Ma Ri.
I happened to meet her again recently.
Seriously, how many first loves do you have?
I didn't tell you?
That all love is first love.
So...
You were going to propose to your first love from your 30's...
That's why you took me to look at the rings.
You sang in front of me to practice. Is that what happened?
Thanks, Kang Sook.
You helped a lot.
What kind of jerk are you?!
Did you just play around with my wife?!
Bo Reum's dad!
Are you leaving already?
Yes. I'm supposed to meet Hyung Seuk Joo at the airport.
You have a lot of time.
You should have dinner before you go.
I can eat something at the airport.
I... will just get going.
Ah... wait a minute, Se Yoon.
I'll be right back after I get changed.Let's go together.
I called for a taxi.
When I get to the airport,
I'll give you a call.
Are you really going to send away Se Yoon like this?
Be healthy and come back safely.
I...
will get going.
Don't worry about me.
Spend time well with Father.
And take care of your health.
Please take me to Incheon International Airport.
Ok, Customer.
Hello.
Where are you right now?
I'm heading to the airport.
Before you leave,
shouldn't you visit your mom?
Where is Mom?!
Ok, ok.
I understand.
Driver, I'm sorry, but
please take me to Chun Ahn.
Didn't you tell me you had a flight to catch?
It's a 940 PM flight.
If we can go there quickly, I think it will be alright.
All the way to Chun Ahn, we are tight on time.
I'll pay you well for the service, so please try.
Then, let's take a shortcut.
You don't have much time.
Pack up immediately and go to the airport.
Mother!
Chae Won, this is your last chance.
Still...
Leave everything else to me.
I'll take care of everything.
So, you just close your eyes and leave quickly.
Hurry!
Driver, could you speed up a little bit?
I'm already driving fast.
I think we're going to be a bit tight with time for my flight.
This is your last chance, Chae Won.
We are almost there.
Okay, Driver.
The pt was involved in a motor vehicle accident.
He's unconscious, and sustained severe trauma to his head and chest.
Call and tell the neurology service to come quickly.
And notify the patient's guardian.
Okay.
Defibrillate, hurry!
-Defibrillator!-Ok, Doctor.
Shock!
It's me, Se Yoon.
I can't get in touch with you.
I... am at the airport right now.
Give me a call as soon as you get this message.
Shock.