Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 42 ~
Sorry.
What?
I'm really sorry, but
with our Se Yoon,
I think you'll have to break up.
I was going to give up all my greed, and accept you as my daughter-in-law, but
I don't think it will work.
You and Se Yoon..
are not meant to be together.
I... really don't understand what you're saying.
Did I do something wrong?
Then mother-in-law, you should tell me.
You didn't hear anything from your mom?
Hear what?
You haven't made any mistakes.
It is true that I looked at you negatively in the beginning.
Once I decided to accepted you as my daughter-in-law, from that point on,
your kind, gentle and beautiful disposition
were very pleasing for me to see.
I have no ill feelings towards you.
Then, why all of a sudden, did you say Se Yoon and I have to break up?
Later...
you'll find out later.
Maybe,
you might find out real soon.
I don't understand.
Just...
let's just think that I'm being fickle,
then would you be able to understand?
Mother!
What I said today,
Keep it a secret for now.
When an opportunity comes up,
I will tell
Se Yoon.
Mother..
Mother, mother!
Mother.
I'm sorry but..
I can't break up with Se Yoon.
And, the reason you told me to break up with him...
I truly can't understand.
Please just think it over, mother..
I know I'm far from being perfect, but
since I'm going to put in my absolute best effort, so
please give us some leeway, Mother!
The matter between you two
has already left my hands.
There's nothing that I can do about this anymore.
What do you mean there's nothing you can do?
credits
Mother..
Mother!
I'm sorry, but I don't think I will be able to do that.
Please forgive me mother!!
Yes, mother.
I'm..
Am I calling at the wrong time?
No, it's okay.
I was going to call you anyways.
Yesterday, I heard that you had a date with my mother.
Huh?
Yes..
You should have let me come with too,
Well, I thought that you were busy with work at the company.
Perhaps,
Will you be able to spare time for me?
I...
want to buy you a meal.
Yes, that sounds good.
Then I'll come with Chae Won..
No.
For today, let's meet just the two of us.
I have something to say to you.
Yes, Son. What's up?
Tonight, you will have to eat with dad alone.
Do you have a business appointment?
No.
Chae Won's mother wanted to eat together.
Chae Won's mother?
Yes.
She said she had something to tell me.
I might be late, so you don't have to wait up for me.
I'm hanging up.
What now?
Today,
are you meeting with Se Yoon?
He's my son,
do I need to tell you?!
What are you going to say when you meet him?!?
You don't know!?!
Choon Hee, please.
Living 30 years in deceit is killing me with indignation.
Every minute and every second is urgent for me.
This is not something that should be handled emotionally.
Let's talk.
Let meet, huh?
There's no need.
I'm gonna meet Se Yoon and tell him everything.
Things that should be made right, will be made right.
Do you have to do this?
If I dont,
30 years ago, under my perfectly fine two eyes,
my son was stolen and the unfairness of that has me exploding in anger,
and you want me to pretend like nothing happened?
Why should I?
The shock Se Yoon is going to receive,
have you thought about it?
A person who thinks like that
is able to steal another's child?
Your words don't make any sense. Stop it!
Choon Hee!
Choon Hee, please..
Were you talking to Chae Won's mother on the phone?
Huh?!
Why are you so shocked?
Why did you get in here without making a sound?
Ah... Without making a sound?
Ahjumma opened to door for me.
What is it now?
Because of the package. I was worried that you would be searching all day.
Did you find the package?
Huh? Yeah.
Of course I found it.
That's a relief.
It's not like the package had feet.
So I was worried, where I could have run off to?
But?
What did you talk about with Chae Won's mother?
Did you talk about the kids' marriage?
Marriage?
You're acting like it's a new story.
I'm talking about Se Yoon and Chae Won.
I don't feel so well
I think I better go lie down.
You came over because you were worried about me...
I'm really sorry..
I smell something suspicious.
There is definitely something going on.
Between the two,
It's certain that there was a situation in the past they can't talk about.
What do you think you're doing right now?
Yes..
I was cleaning.
You must be coming from an outing.
Are you really going to come out like this?
I already told you.
I'll become your Daddy Long Legs.
I think you must have misunderstood something.
If you keep on doing this to someone who doesn't want it, then you're being a stalker, Mr. Kim Cheol Gyoo.
Ahh, honey.
Don't be so sharp.
You're making me feel embarrassed.
Here.
What is this?!
When I saw you you last time, your face seemed
so rough with a lot of dark spots.
I brought some Hanyak (korean herbal medicine).
You know it too right, that mom's favorite Korean Medicine Clinic?
The doctor from that clinic prescribed it so it'll be effective.
Are you now giving me the illness and the medicine?
No matter how much I show you how I've changed,
your distrust, I think it's natural.
Because I know I and my mother together
acted so unreasonably to you.
But, until you feel touched,
if I deligently put in my heart-filled efforts for you,
You'll probably acknowledge my sincerity.
I told you already,
that that isn't going to happen!
I decided to think positively.
I'm so tired of exchanging negative words with you.
Get out now!
Drink this.
You must be very tired working in the factory.
If you drink this, your body will feel great,
Here, drink it.
Really, why are you doing this?
Aiyoo..
This waste, now that it's all spilled, what will we do now?
Stop bothering me and get out now! Please?!
Don't mind me and go on with what you were doing. I'll just finish cleaning and take my leave.
Do you not hear what I'm saying?
Hey!
This jerk!
What is it now?!
Aiyoo.
How have you been?
I came because I had something to say to Chae Won.
What would you have to say to Chae Won?
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey. Let go and talk.
Do it with words.
I think I already told you.
If you come here to talk to Chae Won again, that it won't be fun for you!!
I'm not the old Kim Cheol Gyoo.
I've graduated completely from being a mama's boy, Uncle.
Why am I your uncle?
Why don't you leave!!
Before you cause a huge commotion, just leave now.
Today, I'll be going.
Chae Won, I'm leaving!
Why did that guy come again?
What do you mean 'Why did that guy come again'.
He just wanted to get back together with Chae-Won and was fooling around.
Hey?!
My niece is with Lee Se-Yoon so,
don't interfere!
Let's take care of this.
All day you were gone from your post. Where were you wandering around?
Huh?
Aigoo, what is that stain?
Ahh,
I spilled some herbal medicine while I was feeding it to Chae-Won.
Feed her herbal medicine?
She's looking haggard from all the strenuous factory work.
I went to your favorite Korean Medicine Clinic and got a prescription.
While you went all the way over there getting prescription, did you not think of this old mother of yours?
All you have to do is make a phone call and it gets delivered, pshoong!
Eyi you rascal without prospect!
Aigoo, what now?
I've worked until my finger nails were worn out to raise you,
but this old mom doesn't even enter your thought,
and all you can think to get a prescription for is your ex-wife whom you divorced? You unbelievably ungrateful wretch!
Mom, it'll be troublesome, if you keep comparing yourself with Chae Won and being jealous of her.
If Chae Won and I get back together, you must show a different side, 180 degrees from the you of the past.
Aigoo Tsk. You're counting the chicken before they hatch.
Hey, your Chae Won and that Se Yoon seem to be having a lot of fun right now.
Wake up and smell the coffee instead of wasting money feeding Bo Yack (Herbal Medicine).
My Chae Won will return to me!
Look at this. Making big promise without any plan.
The noodle samples have arrived.
Oh my goodness. So Fast?!
In July or August is project completion. What do you mean, "already"?
It was made with mugwort which is green, hence green noodles.
It's the advertisement plan.
Do we have to spent this much on advertisement?
For an unknown company like ours, we must first attract consumers' interest via focusing all our efforts in marketing.
If we take out the production cost and others, it's 4 billion won for marketing. Isn't that too steep?
4 billion won?
Kim Joo Ri, you've become ballsy.
If we compare it to the inheritance you gave away, it's a price of a gum.
What is this?!
Don't concern yourself with the company's business, just focus on your romance business.
Do you have any progress with Ddang (Chae Won)?
You shocked me, you wench. Did you swallow a funnel!
I'm sure you have the hwabyung because of Gi Ok.
(Hwabyung is a disorder due to repressed anger.)
Aigoo...
If she was to be crazy, why can't she be gently crazed. Are there not enough men, that she has to be with that old...
Aiyoo. Mother-in-law!
We came.
My, that beastly being, where does he think this is to show his face again?
Who are you to come into our house?
Mother.
Who is this Ahjumma calling me mother?
Why are you doing this? Making me upset.
This person,
she cried all night, and didn't sleep at all.
Do you think anybody slept?
Because of Gi Ok, your father has the hwabyung
and is under the covers laying down. And I
can't even swallow water, you horrible child!
Father are you really ill?
What are you two doing here?
Once a day
we promised each other that we'll see you and father-in-law to ask for forgiveness.
Are you giving me a disease and then giving me medicine afterwards right now?
We're sorry we've made you worry.
Please stop being angry.
It's too noisy. Close the door.
Father.
I told you to close the door!
Get out of here you two before your father's blood pressure rises!
Please don't get mad like that,
and listen to what I am about to say, Mother-in-Law.
Stop saying mother-in-law nonsense! Why am I your mother-in-law?
My legs hurt so much!
Just endure it, Honey.
You're having fun!
The next time you step into my house again, I won't hold back the salt, so hurry and leave!
Don't you thing this is too much, mother?
Even though you don't like him, he's still your son-in-law! A son-in-law is considered as a guest for 100 years!
This person is not a hundred year's guest, he is a hundred year's enemy!
Did you know that?
How can you treat people like this? Don't you think this is too much?
Are you ok?
I'm okay, so
calm down, Honey.
I'm okay.
I'm back.
You came, Hyungnim?
What?
Yes.
Aigoo.
Don't hurt so much over this, Cheotjjae (last born).
When time passes, Mother-in-law and Father-in-Law will calm down about this.
Honey.
Aigoo.
I feel so bad for them I can't watch it any more. Tsk.
Aiyoo.
Have a date with me, Mother. I'll hold the grocery basket. Let's see the market together.
Aigoo.
Why?
What about this one?
How does it look?
The best.
I'm here.
Honey.
What were you thinking about so deeply that you didn't even know a person came?
Outside,
you didn't know that Rooftop and Cheotjjae (last born) was here?
-Oh, really? I didn't know.
-They just left.
Oh, yes.
Is there something wrong?
You're like a half absent person.
What's the matter?
Honey.
Yes?
Um.
I have a dinner appointment today, so I'll go and come back.
Dinner appointment? With who?
I'll tell you when I come back.
Honey. H..H..H..H..H..Honey.
Why is that person like that?
What in the world is the problem?
Se Yoon?
He has a dinner appointment.
By the way,
you should arrange a date in place of that meal we couldn't have the other day.
You mean the face to face meeting?
Gather all the relatives and have a meal.
And arrange a marriage date.
Aren't we rushing into this?
It was your idea to rush this.
Call Choon Hee,
and arrange the date.
The world is small.
Choon Hee's daughter will become our daughter-in-law.
Why are you here, Mother Superior?
Return it to it's rightful place, right now.
Return it to it's rightful place?
What?
What do you mean what?
This child.
What are you saying right now?
You can fool everyone in the world, but
You can't fool God.
Why don't you know that?
I don't understand anything Mother
Superior is saying right now.
Did you think I wouldn't know that you switched your dead child with Choon Hee's?
What do you mean by that?
For Sul Joo, born in February,
I made your baby a purple anklet in the form of a violet.
And for Choon Hee, born in April,
I made her baby a pink anklet in the form of a rhododendron flower.
We made these anklets specifically for the two.
For sure, on your child's ankle,
there was a purple anklet in the shape of a violet.
Right now, you're lying about Choon Hee's child being yours.
You must be mistaken Mother Superior.
Let's go to the hospital and get a blood test, and reveal who's words are telling truth.
Let's go to the hospital, right now.
Soo Cheol died so
she wanted to abort the baby within. But the person who convinced her otherwise was me and
the first person to nurse him was also me.
If it wasn't for me,
this child wouldn't be in this world.
Anyways, Choon Hee can't raise this child.
She would have sent him to an orphanage or for an adoption.
Those are all excuses.
Tell Choon Hee that you did wrong.
Return this child.
Choon Hee left for America.
America?
She left for America, but I don't have her address, and she has not been in contact.
Even if I wanted to return the child, there is no way to.
Is that true?
If you don't believe me, Mother Superior go try and find Choon Hee?
Please save me.
If the truth comes out, I'll get kicked out.
And this child will be abandoned at the orphanage.
We don't even know where Choon Hee is.
If you pretend that you don't know,
There won't be any problems.
Please. Please save my life, Mother Superior.
Please. Save Me.
Please.
Help me Mother Superior.
What are you thinking of that's causing you to stare off into space, Honey?
Honey?
Honey?!
What?
Did you call me?
While eating, what are you thinking about so deeply?
N..No...N.. N..Nothing.
Do you have anything special you want to tell me, mother?
Going on a date with Mother made me nervous.
Perhaps, are you going to scold me without Chae-Won knowing?
No, there's nothing like that.
Just with Se Yoon,
I wanted to eat something delicious together.
That's why we met up.
So, I can eat without burden, right?
Of course.
Eat a lot.
I'll eat well.
Please wrap the sushi for me.
My mom really loves sushi.
Is that so?
Ah, wrap the fried shrimp for me please.
Yes.
To take to your mother?
If she hears about fried shrimp, she would wake up immediately even though she's sleeping.
Your mother is really lucky to have you.
Compared to what my mother does for me,
this is nothing.
She is a complete dummy when it pertains to her son.
She thinks I'm the greatest and best looking son.
Even if I do something stupid or say something wrong,
she always is on my side.
Really?
Oh,
I'm not sure if I had any points taken off for being a mama's boy.
Have I got many points off, Mother?
No.
It's nice to see.
When I get married to Chae Won,
I'll be a devoted son to you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Eat.
You too.
This is my first time doing this and it is really embarrassing.
To be thoughtful, I wanted to write a letter,
but as you know my writing skill is a mess.
So, before you go to sleep, I'm going to send you a video message each day.
Today as a celebration of the 1st ever video message
with the idea of recharging my sweetheart who's fatigued due to producing noodle all day
I'll send you the love serenade.
"bato bato bato" "na na na na"
"every lonely night"
"don't want to send you away"
"underneath the fluorescent light"
"my image seem shabby"
"don't like it" "cozily chirping those birds"
"playing with my heart"
"yeah!" "ba ba ba bam"
"ba ba ba bam ba ba"
Hey, hey!
"say..."
I mean...
Wah!
Hey you
I mean, it's not like you're performing an exorcism in the middle of the night
What are you doing right now?
What are you doing, you rascal?
Ay, I was mid-immersion. How come you're messing up my work?
Huh?
You didn't even drink alcohol, so why are you doing this?
Ah,
why are you like this, Cheol Gyoo? Get your head straight!
Mom.
I'm sending a video message to Chae Won!
W-what?
She was working in the factory all day, so to give her strength,
I'm singing to her!
Aigoo, 1/7th, 1/2, 1/3 a penny's worth! (you fool)
You're doing anything! Aigoo.
Mom.
You too, say something.
Hurry!
Aiyoo, I'm fine!
What do you mean you're fine?
Say that I want to see her.
Say that I want to see her! Hurry!
Aiyoo! Aiyoo, aiyoo!
Aiyoo, this fate is worse than a dog's.
Cheol Gyoo says he wants to see you!
He says he wants you to come back.
Why is this person like this?
Oppa, are you married yet?
Well, I haven't met a woman like Gang Sook, so
I am still a bachelor.
Really, Oppa?
That scared me!
You're so messy, I can't stand it!
If you're going to trim your toe nails, go to the corner and cut them!
It's getting everywhere!
It's nothing important, so why are you getting so mad.
Seriously! You're so messy, I can't live!
Can't you do that outside and then come in?
Suddenly it's not like we're dating again, what's the big deal?
What kind of man could have no manners?
Where would you find any manners in our relationship?
What kind of relationship is ours?
Two people that divorced and will get soon back together kind of relationship.
You must dream a lot.
Who said I would marry you again?
Aiyoo, you're so dirty.
Why is she getting so mad?
Why is she like that?
When I coincidentally heard your "Ddool Uh" at the cabaret, it felt like my ears just popped open.
Lyrics is good, melodie is easily understandable, the song just was so easy on the ears.
Thank you.
Why don't you sign with our Sugar Entertainment?
I've heard that President Kang Bo Ju has the midas touch in Teuroteu.
How can such a famous person be...
The first moment I saw you, I got the feeling.
If only you'd trust and let me guide you, I'll make you the Psy of Teuroteu genre.
Psy of Teuroteu genre?
Yes!
I'll make you the nuclear missile of the music world!
I'll transfer the signing bonus to your account tomorrow.
Ah, yes.
Then I'll be going.
Yes.
Your sister's name is Kong Kang Sook isn't it?
How do you know my sister?
We are acquaintances from the past.
Can you give me her number?
What?
Okay
Put in the number right.
Yes.
If you're tired take a rest. I will wake you when we arrive at your house.
It's been such a long time since we had a date. Do you think I can sleep?
As I thought, the saying "Son-in-law's love is the mother-in-law" must be correct.
Hey.
Yes, Mother.
To tell you the truth,
I wanted to meet up to tell you something.
What is it that you want to tell me?
Your mom and I,
were from the same orphanage and
lived like really close sisters.
Yes, I heard from my mother.
So...
your mother and I both gave birth to a son
at the same orphanage on the same day...
Did you hear from your mother?
No, this is the first time I'm hearing this.
You had a son.
I think I heard Chae Won say that you came into the family by yourself.
Then, where is your son?
My son...
Mother, your phone is ringing.
Huh?
Ohh.
Hello?
It's me. Tell me what time the bus will arrive.
Alright.
I was wondering who she went out on a date without me knowing. It seems that it was you.
If she went on a date without you knowing, then we should have stayed out later.
You two talk. We'll be inside.
Yes.
Have a good night.
Mother?
I enjoyed today's date.
Okay.
Drive safely SeYoon.
Let's go.
What did you talk about with my mom?
It's a secret.
What is this?
Not much happened.
We just had dinner and drank tea...
Ah, by the way,
Does your mother have a son?
No. It's the first time I'm hearing this.
My mom has a son?
It's not certain but,
that's what I heard at first.
It seems like you've heard her wrong. She was living on her own at first and then married my dad.
Your mother didn't say anything to you?
What do you mean?
Never mind, it's nothing.
Did Choon Hee...
tell him the truth?
If that happened,
what would my Se Yoon think of me?
Would he still consider me as his mother?
Or
Would he think I'm the world's
worst thief?
You're not sleeping yet?
Oh. You hadn't returned yet how could I go to sleep?
Did dinner with Chae Won's mother go well?
Yes
Did you ask why she wanted to see you?
I think she just wanted to have a meal with me.
Is that right.
Ta-Da
What...is this?
While I was eating dinner, there was a package that made me think of you. It's your favorite sushi and fried shrimp.
You bought this for me to eat?
Try one mom.
Why are you crying mom?
Because I'm thankful.
And I'm happy.
Ah, my mom's becoming old too. She's shedding lot of tears.
How can you be so moved by fried shrimp?
Thank you, Son.
Calm down or you'll get indigestion Mom.
I think I heard Chae Won say that you came into the family by yourself.
Then, where is your son?
Finally, our factory's noodle is being sold throughout the country.
That right. You've all worked very hard.
Chae Won, you've worked hard.
It's nothing. Uncles and Aunts have been working hard, too.
You've all worked hard.
The work that I couldn't do you guys have done in my place
if I die now I'll have no regrets.
We're gonna earn all the money in Korea by selling noodles.You should see your offspring become Chae Beol before you die
Father, if I earn $100,000,000, I'll buy the Mil Ban 10,000 Pyong (like Korean acres) in your name.
Always bounced check!
How's that bounced check?
Father, please live long long time.
From now on, us offspring who's inherited the family business will conduct business with all our might.
If this man fell in the water, his mouth would float.
I doubt he'd surface because he'd be too busy talking with the fish.
Ha ha ha
That's not true!
Of course it's true.
I'm serious!
Hello Se Yoon
My Mom is not feeling well. I want to make her some porridge but I don't know how so I called you.
How did you come to be here...
I came after receiving Se Yoon's phone call.
I made some vegetable soup so have a little, mother-in-law.
What happened to what I told you yesterday and...
I'm sorry mother-in-law but,
If you were to be in my place,
and were told to split up with Se Yoon without any specific reason
would you be able to give up on Se Yoon?
I cannot do that, mother-in-law.
Then...
What if there were a reason why you should never be together?
then can you give up on Se Yoon?
What does that mean?
Does that mean that there's something between us?
Does the taste suit you, mom?
Why did you call &amp; bother Chae Won?
It's no bother at all for me, mother-in-law.
Naturally. This is an excellent opportunity to make some bonus points with you, do you think Chae Won would miss it?
Aigoo. You've ran out of things to do so now do you have to provide a singing and dancing service too?
What are you talking about?
When I went upstairs yesterday,
he had a necktie around his head and toilet paper wrapped around his body and
was shaking a tambourine and... It was a spectacle!
I can do even more spectacular things only if Chae Won's heart would come back.
Totally lame.
What did you say, you wench?
Aigoo. Why are you shouting at the dining table?
So,
Did you receive a thank-you message from Chae Won?
Aigoo. Aigoo. Tsk.
Everyday you act a fool with the excuses of doing a good deed.
Hello!
Is that you Gang Suk? It's Bong Su.
Oh...
Oppa!
Oppa?
Right now?
After breakfast, I was drinking Cafe Americano while listening to some music.
By the way, how did you get my number, Oppa?
I asked your younger sister.
My little sis?
Yes, singer Mr. Gang Jin's...
wife?
Ah, ah yes.
If you don't have any plans for lunch, would you like to join me?
No worries if you have a plan.
I don't have any!
I don't have any plans.
Older sister-in-law.
Did she step out?
I'll borrow her clothes for just a second and return it.
Eeeek! Oh mommy!
You shocked me!
Why are you come into an empty room without the owner's permission and opening the wardrobe, hmmm?
Aiyoo. I was planning on meeting a high school classmate I haven't seen in a while but
I didn't have any suitable clothes to wear so I was going to borrow hers.
Your high school classmate who?
You gotta be kidding. Do you know who it is if I told you?
Naturally. She has so many clothes based on her trade (vocation).
Uh, what's that?
Isn't that the parcel I delivered to Sul Joo?
Uh, why is that here?
Did you get your parcel?
Uh, um, of course. I got it.
That wench lied to me.
What do you have on your hands?
Shhh..
Just what is that she's reacting like that?
Aigoo!
Who is this?
It looks like they're Sul Joo and Chae Won's mom.
Look here, Ms. Yang Choon Hee.
We ARE a married couple, right?
Why do you ask something like that suddenly?
Married couple is of one mind and body, of one thought, right?
However,
these days, I don't feel as though I'm of one mind with you, Choon Hee.
Lately, your face is filled with worries and
last night, you woke in the middle of the night and cried.
Did you see it?
Yes.
I thought about asking you what's the matter but
you cried so sadly that I couldn't approach you.
Just what is it about?
We are
a married couple.
A little while ago,
I gave you a quick story.
On the year I graduated from high school,
I fell in love and set up house with a man who's also an orphan like me
but he died in 3 months in a car accident.
Yes.
Actually,
between us
there was a baby.
What?
I wasn't intentionally trying to hide it from you, Kyo Dong.
I, myself
had such a hard time bringing up that memory
so I didn't say anything.
I gave birth to a baby boy in a maternity clinic,
they couldn't stop my hemorrhaging, so
while I went to get treated at the hospital
the baby was dead due to oxygen deprivation.
Oh dear.
Sending the baby's father and the baby to heaven
was unbearable.
On top of that
when I was pregnant with the baby
I didn't have enough courage to raise him by myself so
I thought many bad things too, you know.
The thought of me
being the cause of the baby's death, drove me insane.
But,
But, honey.
The boy who I thought dead,
in reality,
alive all along.
Wha..what?
What does this mean?
That means,
Sul Joo took her own baby and Chae Won's mom's baby
and switched...them.
What does that mean then?
Se yoon is, in fact,
Chae Won's mom's son then? Ooooh!
Oh my gooooooood!
Aigoo. How can this be?!
Oh my, you shocked me! You shocked me!
What are you doing in my room, right now?
Um, I, um, didn't see anything.
I..don't know anything.
The diary,
you stole a peek, didn't you?
(nodding)
I didn't intend to steal a peek but
I saw the parcel Sul Joo asked about, accidentally, so..
I got curious and meaninglessly...
I wondered why a parcel that was addressed to me was delivered to that house...
It's because there was a spy in our house.
What spy? Nonsense.
Sul Joo called and said that a parcel that she should have received was addressed wrongly and came to our house instead
and asked to bring it to her, so I just
did an errand, that's all.
The content of the diary,
to whom did you reveal it?
I didn't say it to anyone.
I just finished reading and was bringing it back.
This story
you cannot reveal it to anyone.
If per chance this gets out
then you and I are going to both die. Understand?
They say the sense closest to the taste, is the sense of smell.
Therefore, using the sense of smell alone could make salivary gland react.
Is there salivation?
Yep.
Then it's half way successful.
Then just imagine and...
I think I'm feeling it.
Those two are so in love,
I'm sorry, Se Yoon.
What should be the karma for me, has gone to you.
What can we do about this?
credits
It's one of the top music companies in the country, and
when the President heard me sing,
because he liked it so much
that he made me an offer right away.
Here,
the contract amount,
W50,000,000 so
we changed the Rooftop apartment from monthly rent to annual lease.
What's the big deal about a lease at that age, please.
Aiyoo, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Mom!
I'm still lacking but
when "Ddool Uh" (song title = "break through") becomes a hit,
in a year,
I'll definitely buy her a building.
Only the mouth is alive saying blah, blah, blah!
By the way,
is the title of the song "Ddool Uh"?
Yes.
"Ddool Uh, Ddool Uh,"Ddool Uh!"
"Ddool Uh, Ddool Uh, Ddool Uh,"
"break through all the blockage in my life"
"face it head on and breakthrough", "just run looking only ahead",
"breakthrough all the blockage in my life"
Shut it!
Your noise is breaking my inner peace so shut it.
Son!
Daddy will open the lids for you.
By the way, Bo Reum,
where did Mom go that we don't even see a glimpse of her?
This wife of mine, she even turned off her cell phone. Where is she, and what is she up to?
When we are sitting like this, it makes me think of the first time we met at the eatery.
I know.
You bought me all the dumplings and dokboki I wanted.
I don't spend money on just anyone.
The first time I met you, I thought you might be the woman for me, so I spent some money.
Of course, how can any man not have a crush on you?
Is that true?
How was my first impression?
Well...
Should I say you seemed like a single blossom of magnolia?
You were warm, yet cold.
You seemed open and bright, yet under a shade of darkness.
I felt you seemed somewhat unorthodox?
Everything he says sounds so elegant.
I must have been crazy.
Why did I ignore this king card, and end up with someone like Uhm Ki Choon?
After I heard you got married, I cried for 2 nights and 3 days.
He said he didn't get married because he couldn't find someone like me.
I think he meant it.
credits
Just a second!
You should have my personal wine glass.
Ah... I'm sorry.
Please wait just a minute, President.
Oppa, you must be really successful.
The company that was on your business card, I looked up on the internet.
It's a really big recording company, I found out.
After I got dumped by you,
I gritted my teeth and worked really hard,
and became successful.
It seems like he was really hurt by me.
Here...
To our time together,
Cheers!
Omo! Omo!
Hello.
Aigoo... This person...
Why did you come here again?
I came to see Chae Won, but she wasn't at the factory. I was waiting for her.
It seems like she went somewhere.
Ah...
Chae Won went to Se Yoon's house.
Why did she go to that bastard's house?
Se Yoon's mom is sick, so she went to make some porridge for her.
Now, she completely became their daughter-in-law!
Aiyoo!
Aiyoo... Calm down.
Aiyoo, you can get hurt.
Anyway, it's like talking to a wall.
No matter what I do, what kind of show I put on,
she doesn't even blink an eye.
If it doesn't work with all my efforts, then I don't think it's meant to work.
That's not it.
I won't do anymore crazy things.
I think I'll give up on everything.
What do you mean you will give up?
Why do you want to give up when you're almost there?
Pardon?
Ah...
You're almost there now, so close eyes tightly, and
wait a little more. Huh?
What do you mean I'm almost there?
They treat me like an insect.
Aiyoo...
You're skipping lunch, and waiting for our Chae Won?
Is that for real, Aunty?
Sh...
This must remain an absolute secret.
Sh!
I was going to keep my mouth shut.
Others don't need to know about it, but I thought you definitely should know. That's why I told you.
You must have suffered a lot all this time because of Chae Won.
Anyway, our Chae Won will have no choice, but come back to you.
So don't be too anxious, okay?
Then, Lee Se Yoon's biological mom is
Chae Won's mom, right?!
Sh...
Lower your voice a bit.
How can something like this happen in the world?
So,
things like this can happen in life.
Chae Won's mom has her eyes set on getting Se Yoon back, and got a blood test.
If that happens, then Chae Won and Se Yoon will
become siblings.
Right.
Their marriage plan
will be over.
Heavens helped you, Son-in-law Kim.
Oh... Oh...
Thank you, Aunty.
I'll never forget my indebtedness to you.
Ah...
You don't need to say like that.
Since you desperately want Chae Won,
I felt bad for you.
If I...
get back together with Chae Won,
I'll really treat you big, Aunty!
Look at you.
I'm not doing this because I have an ulterior motive.
Oh my god!
Yes!
The fact that Se Yoon is
my son...
Why did you tell me now?
Rather...
It would have been better for me not to know, Mother Superior.
I think I have to go today without visiting the elders.
I need to go to the company.
Okay.
Then, hurry up and go.
Thank you for today.
Mom looked like she was very thankful.
Se Yoon,
perhaps,
something didn't happen that I don't know about, right?
What are you talking about?
It's good, if there is nothing.
For some reason, Mother
didn't look good.
Mom says she's like that because of her menopause.
I really think she should get a thorough check up.
She's sick often lately.
I'll be going.
What are you doing here again?
I came by because I was just curious.
You said you were busy.
Just ignore him and go.
I'll see you going in first, then I'll leave.
Hurry up and go in.
Alright.
You guys look good together, as brothers and sisters.