Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 41
Hello?
I came with the package, but there's no one here.
You brought a package?
Is it from Sangroksoo Orphanage (Evergreens Orphanage) for sure?
What's this?
Why is the package here, when it's addressed to me?
This was sent from the orphanage.
But, why is this here?
Who brought it here?
Oh, taxi!!
Did the ahjumma already take it?
Ahjumma!!
Yes, madam!
Ahjumma! Did you get the package from the mailbox?
No.
The postal package that was for me,
did you not take it out of the mailbox?
Today, I haven't opened the mailbox.
Oh my,
How did this photo...
Francesca
It looks like Mother Superior's diary.
Why did she sent this to me?
But why was this at Sul Joo's house?
What are you trying to say?
I'm pretty sure I left it there.
It's not there. Not there at all.
No matter how much times I check the mailbox,
it's not there.
It's not like the package has feet,
what do you mean it's not there?
Are you sure?
Did you possibly put it in someone else's mailbox, and got it confused with ours?
I don't have dementia.
I've been to your house for so many years. Would I get confused, and put it in someone else's mailbox?
Where did it disappear to, then?
A ghost is toying with me, seriously.
I specifically placed the package there.
Exactly where did it disappear too?
Okay.
I got it.
Up to where did I read?
Oh. It starts from here.
January 5, 1983.
Sul Joo and Choon Hee came to say hello at the orphanage.
Sister.
You didn't even call.
Girls, what brings you here?
We came to say Happy New Years.
Have you been well, Mother Superior?
When you two were at the orphanage, you two used to stick together like twins.
And now you are even pregnant together
Choon Hee, you have a little more time before the due date, right?
Fifteen more days left.
In a little while, I was going to send you a message anyway.
You don't have anyone to help you postpartum. Why don't you deliver your baby here?
I've already notified the maternity ward members.
Is it really alright?
I wanted to tell her to come to my house, but because of my mother-in-law, I didn't say it.
It's turned out well, Choon Hee!
I... I can't manage this.
How can I raise a child who doesn't have a father?
I... I want to leave this world, and be with Soo Chae.
How can you say those things? The baby in your belly is going to hear you.
Is the baby the problem here?
I feel like I'll go crazy!
God is cruel.
Why was he in such a hurry to take the baby's dad away?
At that time,
only if you didn't stop me...
I have no confidence to raise a child!
Don't think about anything else, and for the meantime give birth to your child.
Then, I'll figure out everything else.
Sul Joo, you seem like your baby has been in your stomach longer than expected.
The baby is 10 days overdue. It must have no intention of coming out.
The three of you, please stand side by side. I'll take a picture of you.
My tummy looking like this, why get a picture taken?
All this will be a memory.
Here.
Choon Hee! Smile, okay?
1, 2, 3!
Ah!
My stomach, my stomach is in a lot of pain!
Your water broke!
What should we do?
Wait! Delivery room!
Let's hurry up and take her to the delivery room!
Aiyoo.
Is your stomach also hurting?
Sul Joo! What's wrong?
I think my baby is coming out!
Ah!
Your mom will be coming home from the hospital shortly.
Let's eat and wait for her, ok?
You're so cute!
What about Choon Hee?
The director called a little while ago.
Fortunately, the bleeding stopped.
She will be released shortly.
Thank goodness.
They said your mom is fine.
We don't have to worry about her, ok?
You're working hard, Sul Joo, instead of Choon Hee.
It's a relief that I can produce a lot of breast milk.
Aiyoo, why is our prince crying?
Should I change his diaper?
woo-ssha-ri (Korean sound made when lifting heavy objects)
Let's see.
His diaper is fine. I wonder why he's crying?
He must be hungry.
Go over there, ok?
Woo-Ssha.
Tst-tst (clucking tongue to a baby)
Baby, shall we go to the other room?
Have your diaper changed and then sleep?
Don't leave any seaweed soup.
You have to eat all of it, ok?
Yes, Sister.
Aiyoo, how beautiful.
You must be really hungry.
Aigoo, let's eat!
What is wrong with you?
Baby...baby!!!
Baby?
Baby!
Is no one outside?
Sister! Sister!
Is no one outside?!
Baby!!
Sister!
I'm angry that I have an orphan as my daughter-in-law.
If you end our bloodline on top of that,
I can no longer accept you as my daughter-in-law.
I have no choice, but tell Dong Gyu to have a baby with someone else.
I'm sorry, Baby!
I have no other way.
Hey, baby...
It's not there, Ahjumma?
Yes.
I searched everywhere.
It's not there.
Where on earth did it end up then?
By any chance,
Was there a visitor?
Visitor?
Ah! Your friend that visited you a while ago.
Friend?
That person who you yelled at to get out of the house.
Choon Hee!
Choon Hee..
was here?!?
Sul Joo Unni
There's been a terrible situation, Sister!
Why?
Choon Hee's baby has been...
What's wrong with my baby?
The baby has...
Choon Hee! Are you okay?
Ah!
For sure,
I put a purple bracelet around the ankle of Sul Joo's child,
and for Choon Hee's child,
I put a pink bracelet around the ankle.
I put the bracelet around their ankles,
but one day, the bracelets have suddenly switched.
While Choon Hee and I stepped away,
Sul Joo switched her dead son with Choon Hee's son and took him away.
I am sure of it.
Dear God,
what should I do about this situation?
My son...
My son was switched by Sul Joo unni?
Then, Se Yoon..
Se Yoon is my son?
Aigoo, aigoo, aigoo...
Mom, are you going out?
Aiyoo, why is your mom acting like that?
Lost half her wits
Yeah.
Her complexion didn't look so good either.
Did something happen?
Aiyoo, this person has been calling me all day!
What is so important about that package that's causing her to act like this?
A package?
What kind of package?
What?
Oh, it's just something.
What now?!
Chae Won's mom?
She just went out a while ago.
Why?
What do you mean they won't sign the contract?
What's happened that made them cancel the contract so suddenly?
Ah, that is...
Is there a certain circumstance?
As Kim Joo Ri was leaving the company,
she went into partnership with our researchers.
They are under a contract with Keum Reung Foods.
She went into partnership with our employees?
Is that true?
Yes, Director.
What about releasing our new product?
I believe it'll be delayed.
They were the team members who were getting the new product ready.
We took away all their researchers related to getting the new product ready.
And we took over the factory.
That bastard, Se Yoon,
must be having a real hard time.
Wait and see.
In the not too distant future, I will gobble up Sunbae's entire company.
Aigoo! Our Joo Ri is like her mother so much, her business skills are excellent.
Aigoo, even though I made Cheol Gyoo the president,
he's not good at business.
Ah
Lee Se Yoon has come to see you.
Who?
How are you?
Aigoo... facing the release of your new product, you must be
having a tremendously difficult time since you ran all the way here.
I have come to confirm the truth.
You partnering with our researchers...
You could have just called.
Why did you spend your energy coming here?
It's right that I have done it.
How can you scheme something like this?
What do you mean?!
In a free, democratic country, if you have the capacity, of course you can scout and compete too
How dare you come here to argue over such triviality?
Mom, please!!
I didn't come to pick a fight.
It's because I feel sad for you.
If you start your first step like this,
for the rest of your business life, you will never be able to escape from your temptation of
only walking comfortable and easy path.
What kind of nonsense are you giving as an advice?
We'll live with our own method!
So forget about this and focus on yourself!
President!
Ah! That's enough!
We have nothing to be ashamed of, so
don't talk too much. Hurry up and leave.
Get out! Hurry up!
We've heard enough, so you should leave.
Who may this be?
What business do you have here?
I finished what I have to do, so I should be going.
I'm not sure if you heard from Chae Won.
Not long ago, I got a divorce.
Not sure if you'd be aware of the term "Donl-Sing" (returned to being single)
I didn't say it, so you can make fun of me.
I'm saying this to worry you.
You are not a person that is able to make me worry.
This bastard, it seems like he thinks that words are enough!
We'll find out how things turn out, so don't get overly confident.
According to the information I got, your mother-in-law and your mom,
their relationship is very bad, I heard.
So be on your guard. I'm not dead yet.
Relationship between my mom and Chae Won's mom is not good?
Lee Se Yoon, that bastard, why was he here?
You didn't even come to the directors' meeting. Where have you been all day? And, you just came.
What's the use of having a puppet president around?
You have Joo Ri.
Aigoo, aigoo, aigoo.
You, by the way...
Is having the company getting taken away from your younger sister not having any effect on you?
Even without the company matters, I have a lot on my mind.
Aigoo! Aigoo... You're are talking about her again.
Listen carefully!
You're scaring me with your stare.
I'm going to crush Lee Se Yoon with business.
Oppa, you have to take away "Zero", I mean,
Sister-in-law from Lee Se Yoon.
You must! No matter what you have to do, got it?!
Of course.
They say if a woman harbors resentment, it'll snow in May...Scary.
You're scary!
Bo Reum daddy!
You didn't hear from Ki Ok that wench, did you?
Why ask me?
The person who went to fetch her should know.
Just coming back from a fruitless visit.
I knew it.
It's like find a needle in a haystack. How can you catch someone who planned to disappear?
Oh my, goodness..
Uh.
Uhm Ki Ok.
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
Have you no shame?
Father and Mother are inside, right?
And if they are inside?
I will formally introduce them to this person.
Let's go in, Honey.
Honey!?!
These people, really!
Even if you love each other dearly,
are you this dense in understanding your situation?
The moment this old gigolo steps over the front door, mother and father will go to hades in fear!
Why are you thinking so extreme, Hyungnim?
Hyungnim?
Why am I your hyungnim?
This fox-like person!!
Let go. Aren't you gonna let go?
Hyungnim, Ahjoomunim! Come out here!
There's been a problem!
Oh my! Oh my! Honey!
You! You!
Let go!
Honey!
What are you doing right now wearing Hangbok (korean traditional clothes)?
They came out here to say hello to Father and Mother.
No way!
Never, definently not!!
Why not!?!
If Father and Mother faint, are you going to take responsibility?!
It's not a kind of problem we can sweep under the rug?
HYUNGNIM!?!
He definitely has a nerve of steel.
Calls any old person Hyung Nim, Hyung Nim.
Aiyoo, this won't do.
If Father and Mother see them, it would be bad!
For now, let's split them up.
Let go!
Aiyoo, what are you doing? Let go!
Th-those people! Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Where do you think...
Let go of me! Are you not going to let go?
What should we do about this old gigolo?
Since he comes at us like a bulldozer, I'm hard pressed to come up with countermeasure.
Aigoo, what brings Teacher Kang here?
Mom.
You even wore Hangbok!
For all these times, hello, Moth-
Come inside!
Aiyoo, I said come inside!
Ah, seriously.
Auntie!
Are you not embarrassed to look at your niece?
Chae Won! Do you think your aunt is embarrassing?
No.
Aghassi, aren't you crazy?
I mean, without permission from parents and siblings, you register marriage and honeymoon
can you act without a care like this?
Then what should I do!
If I were to wait, there's no guarantee it'd be in 1000 or 10,000 years
If you leave without visiting after having come all this way, I'd be sad.
You should at least drink up a cup of cool mixed-nut-powder-tea.
Oh?
When did you come, Ki Ok?
Mom
No wait,
why are you wearing a hanbok?
Why are both of you wearing a hanbok?
Hey, Uhm Ki Ok!
You better get up!
Aiyoo, why are you yelling so loudly?
Be quiet!
Wh-why are they acting like this?
For what reason are these two kneeling?
I'm sorry mom..
We...got married.
Mar... What do you mean you got married?
Who married whom?
Even though I lack,
please accept me as your youngest Son-in-Law, Mother.
What do you mean, Mother-in-law?
Why am I your mother-in-law?!
We are back from registering our marriage.
We even had our honeymoon.
Mom! Mom!
Get back to your senses! Mom!
Get the Chu...chu...chu...Chung Shim Hwan (relaxant)! Chung Shim Hwan!
Quickly, quickly!
Mom!
Get back to your senses, Mom!
Water!
Chae Won!
Hey, bring it quickly, quickly!,
Mom! Hyung Nim, more!
Aiyoo.
Aiyoo!
I'm sorry.
Mom and Dad.
Mother-in-law and Father-in-law, we've committed a deadly sin.
What should we do with this person?
You frightful man!
Please calm down, Mother!
Let her be, Jun Bot Tae (utility pole).
Please hit me until you get out all of your anger out, Mother!
What precious daughter Ki Ok is to me, huh?
How dare your meager self can covet her, huh?
You worst thief, you!
Aigoo
This wench, this insane wench!
You couldn't find a man that you fall for a total old man!
Let's see.
To have you fall for a total old man did I send you to college in our tight budget?
Brought you up treasured?
Instead, let's you and I, in dishwater
put our noses in and die, DIE!
I'm sorry, mom.
Aigoo..
I'm really sorry.
Aiyoo.
I should die to avoid this and that mess.
Aiyoo, Father! Mother!
Please take me with you!
Please take Kkeut Soon!
Aiyoo, Mom! Please stop it.
Let go!
Your younger sibling, your sister-in-law, is
walking down the wrong path, you all are sitting there &amp; watching it like it's someone else's problem.
You irresponsible beings, you!
We've done plenty to discourage and stop, mother-in-law.
That's right.
Me and Sister-in-law have barged in to the rooftop apartment, and caused as much trouble as possible.
Hyung (Older brother) and I also,
did plenty of grabbing and forcing them to stop but
they were unresponsive.
Ai, just die.
Oh, mother-in-law!
When has your mind slipped?
Mother.
Like a ghost that ate a cow,
Why are you staying still?
Are you saying that you approve this marriage?
Is that it?
Leave my house right now.
Father.
Doing this without your parent's consent.
Isn't doing this saying that you no longer want to live with your parents?
Take this person and leave.
Father-in-Law.
Who are you to call me father-in-law?
I don't have a son-in-law like you.
Son-in-Law Min!
Yes, Father.
Drag those two out immediately.
Right now!!
Dad!
Father!
Leave it alone.
It's best if you stop here today.
Hurry and stand up!
That's right.
Listen to him.
Mom...oh my god what do we do?
Why aren't you picking up the phone?
After you listen to this message, call me.
I have something to confirm.
Please, Choon Hee!
The diary...
Would Choon Hee have taken it?
No! No! No!
Thank you young man.
Ahjumma..
I'm Chae Won's mom.
Aiyoo, this is my favorite flower.
For some reason, I thought that these flowers would suit Mother the best.
Go on a date with me, Mother.
A date?
I will go to the market with you, so let's go market-seeing.
How is it?
It's the best!
How could this have happened?
He's my son that came out of me.
He was right in front of me.
Like a stupid person,
how could I not have recognized him at all like that?
Can you still be a mother?
They say blood is thicker than water.
How could I not see it with my own eyes, stupid?
Fool!
What?!
Do you,
by any chance-
Have the diary?
How...
do you have that?
I was wondering why you were running away from me!
Chun Hee,
let's meet.
Let's meet and talk.
Enough!!
I don't need to meet with you.
I'm going to meet with my son and tell him the truth.
I'm going to take my son with me!
Choon Hee, don't hang up the phone!
Let's meet for now.
Let's meet,
I will tell you from the beginning.
Choon Hee! No! You can't take Se Yoon!
Choon Hee! Se Yoon...no!
You can't.
The Director has gone out out and is on his way here.
What kind of tea shall I give you?
It's fine. I'm fine.
Don't worry, so go back to your work.
Yes.
The son that I thought died...
To a total stranger with no blood tie,
he called them mom and dad, for 30 long years.
What should I do?
How do I handle this fury and resentment?
Mom!
Oh, Se Yoon.
Do you and dad have an engagement?
Yeah..
I had an errand to run in the area,
and to see your face too.
To kill the two birds with one stone.
I'm glad you came.
Right now, Chae Won's mother is in my office.
Chae Won's mother...
Why did she come?
Director! I came to talk about the contract.
Madam, you've come.
Then why don't you discuss work? I'll go up first.
Yes, Mom.
Let's go.
First,
let's go out and talk.
You!
You didn't only steal Se Yoon,
but you also stole my life!
Did you not know that Mother Superior
had dementia?
Naively,
the things in the diary...
Are you believing everything right now?
You're denying it to the end.
Unfortunately for you,
That diary was written way before Mother Superior has gotten dementia!
What should we do since it was written 30 years before?
If you keep saying these things,
I can have a gene test.
Let's speak
in a quiet place.
Here,
Employees are around.
It's our company.
I told you!
I didn't come to meet you,
but I came to meet my son!
Please. Please calm down.
Listen to what I say first.
You can meet Se Yoon and speak with him anytime!
Please. Please.
To me, too.
For the last time,
give me a chance to explain, Choon Hee.
For the past 30 years,
I haven't slept in peace for even one day,
I haven't laughed freely.
Because every time I see Se Yoon,
I remember your face, Choon Hee.
I wanted to die.
After stealing all of
someone else's life,
you thought you wouldn't even suffer that much?
How could you wear a human mask,
and do such a thing?
You're not even human!
After the doctor's prognosis that I could not get pregnant,
he was a child that I gave birth to with great difficulty.
My mother-in-law was pressuring my husband
to birth a son outside of our marriage.
If they knew that
something went wrong with the child,
I thought that things might return to the awful past,
and in a moment I committed a sin
that could not be taken back.
After sending the child's father and the child to heaven,
you saw me wander around like a crazy woman without her mind,
and yet, how could you do that to me?
So that's why you sent me to America!
To separate me from my son!
To separate me from the Head Nun!
Ah, stupid idiot!
I didn't even know that, and was thinking you were my life's benefactor.
You were not in your right mind at the time!
You were not capable of raising a child then!
You had depression,
and it was hard to take care of even yourself.
How could you raise a child?
And,
when you went to the hospital to abort the child in your stomach,
it was me that dragged you home.
If it wasn't for me,
my Sae Yoon would not have come into this world.
Even if I hadn't brought Se Yoon then,
you would have given him up for adoption.
At that time, you had no will to raise a child.
So,
for raising him instead of giving him up for adoption,
I should be thankful?
Isn't that too shameless?
I'm sorry Choon Hee.
My whole life, until I die,
I'll live with a mind of atonement.
I don't need any of it.
I'm going to go immediately to get my son!
Choon Hee!
He doesn't know anything,
and he's doing well,
so let's not make him confused.
Keep my two eyes open, and lose my child?
My Sae Yoon...
lost his sense of taste.
He became like that three years ago after losing his girlfriend in a car accident,
if we say that he has a birth mother...
its so terrible I don't even want to imagine that!
I'm not asking you
to do that for me.
For the sake of my Sae Yoon..
for my Sae Yoon..
Don't make me laugh!
I'm going to whatever it takes,
to bring back my son.
Choon Hee!!!!
Don't call my name with that dirty mouth!
You thief!
Choon Hee!
Choon Hee... Choon Hee...!
Se Yoon... You can't, Choon Hee!
No..
Our Se Yoon..
This is a noodle that just came out recently,
try it out and please tell everyone about it!
Yes..
Thank you..
Come again!!
Goodbye!
Yah,
the whole day its bustling with customers!
Today's sales are going to be high!
Bro, let's go!
Okay~!
Ah, welcome!
Welcome!
Did you come to buy noodles?
Just give me 10 packages.
A whole 10 packages?!
I was told to buy 10 packages.
Oh, alright!
There's regular noodles, and noodles that have been stretched by hand, which one would you like?
I was told just to buy the most expensive one!
By who?
The bachelor in front of here told me to.
Ah yeah, thank you for your work.
When the next woman comes back, you can go in, okay?
Got it.
And, you have to act naturally, like you really came to buy noodles.
You must not make it obvious that you're being paid to do this.
I understand, don't worry.
Okay okay~!
It's the first time in my life making money so easily!
It's the first time spending money so easily myself!
What is this?
The next time you need to hire people, call me.
I'll bring a whole group with me.
Oh, okay okay I got it!
Hmm..
Oh she's back!
Noodles! Hand me the noodles.
Where are the noodles?
Look here, Kim Cheol Gyoo!!
Are you joking right now?!
A joke? If you don't acknowledge my sincerity, I'll be very upset, honey.
Didn't I tell you to stop calling me that?!
I'm sorry, honey.
Honey is stuck to my mouth.
Why are you doing this?
Why? Why?
You're working so passionately at the factory,
so I was looking for ways to be of help to you.
In a phrase, I'm like your Daddy-Long-Legs.
You must have nothing to do.
Do you not even work at your own company?
Yes!
I completely gave up working there.
Joo Ri quit working at Lee Se Yoon's company, and came to our company to work.
And she's getting along great with our Mom, so she does most of the work now.
And as for me, I'm there for looks.
You lost your work to your younger sister,
and aren't you even embarassed of yourself?
You know too, that I don't care much for company work.
All I care about, whether I'm sitting or standing, is you.
All I think about is, what can I do to make you forgive me and accept me again.
Nothing like that will ever happen,
so go help out your mom and sister at your company.
And if you come back again to play jokes again,
I'm going to tell my uncles about you,
don't even come near the factory.
Honey, aren't you being too harsh?
If I tried this hard, even a stone Buddha statue would give in.
How could you be so cold towards me?
I told you before!
I love Se Yoon.
Honey, I've changed!
I'm a completely new person! No longer the mama-boy I used to be.
I rebel against my mom all the time now!
I don't want to hear about this.
Just you wait, you are going to come back to me.
I'm going to make you.
Ah~
what is all this?
Can't you tell, its noodles.
Yes I know, but why did you buy so many noodles by the box?
Oh, I was buying up some of Chae Won's noodles.
Whew, oh my gosh,
you're so busy going around spending money, aren't you CEO Cheol Gyu?
I have to help her, since she gave up working at the company and started work at the noodle factory.
And you know, I like noodles.
If you like noodles that much, you should be eating our company's noodles, not some other company's.
Our company makes noodles?
Whew, jeez.
Even if you are just around for show, isn't this too much?
I've never heard about it before though.
Joo Ri brought all the researchers and subcontractors from Se Yoon's company to our company.
Isn't that being a company spy?
Spy? Watch what you're saying.
If you're not, then never mind. And, it hasn't even been that long since we launched our new product.
We're producing noodles now?
Mom, aren't we straining the company?
Ah, you just wait around and reap the rewards.
Not too far ahead, Geum Yong Foods
will take over the noodle market.
She said she'd be in the office, but when I came, she wasn't here.
She isn't even answering her phone.
Was there any contact from her?
No.
Then, did she leave with my mom ?
With your mom?
My mom actually came by earlier too.
Okay, anyways I got it, talk to you later.
How did things go?
I think that we need to give up the new noodles we were about to launch,
and plan for a new product asap.
Why did mother go to Se Yoon's company?
How is grandma?
She seems better after taking some medicine,
but I'm really worried about her.
But, where has your mother been the whole day?
Mom! Are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
I'm going in to rest a while.
Where have you been all day long?
There was a huge commotion today.
A commotion?
Rooftop and my sister-in-law came back from their honeymoon,
and mother-in-law lost her mind,
father-in-law told them to leave this house immediately,
it was a huge commotion.
Yes...
I'm going to lie down because I feel tired...
Do you feel sick?
It seems like you have a fever...
It's nothing.
There was something I needed to take care of today, that's all.
Dad, mom, I'm going inside.
Yes,
Drink this, its cool.
If it's discovered that Se Yoon is actually my son,
my Chae Won...what will happen to her?
Do you have something to say to Chae Won?
No, I don't have anything to say.
A little while ago, I got a phone call from Se Yoon.
Why? Why did Se Yoon call?
He said you were going to wait for him in his office, but when he came you weren't there.
That's why he called.
Why did you go there?
I was in the area, and stopped by to maybe have some tea.
It was nothing.
I'm so enraged I can't live!
I'm so furious I can't stand it!
Ah!!!!!!!
I have to go immediately to get Ki Ok!
It's no use to sit around doing nothing.
Leave her alone.
Leave her alone? Then what?
Are we just going to watch that 60-year-old gigolo live with our daughter?
Like watching a fire from across a lake?
Didn't I say, it will be just as though we never had her as our child.
How can we act like she's not our child?
I can't do that!
Calm down mother-in-law, please.
Does it look like I can calm down now?
I have to go break at least one of that old gigolo's legs.
Only that way, will I be able to feel better.
Mother-in-law!!!!
Hurry!
Is this the place
that the old gigolo sings?
There it is, on that huge poster.
That... that... that bastard... that creep is like an old gigolo.
He's not just an old gigolo, but he's a wolf with 99 tails!!!
I'm going to go and cut off each and every one of those 99 tails tonight!
Let's get going!
Oh!
Grandma, what business do you have here?
What business?
I came to dance at the cabaret!
Do you think I came to buy taffy?
It's going to be trouble if you hurt your back dancing at that age!
Go home and watch your grandkids!
You can't discriminate people like that!
What are you doing right now?
You two, don't you even have a mother and father!?
ARGH!
No, you can't go in!
AGH!!
AHHHH!
Mother, please go home.
Why all this noise?
What are you!@!#@#
-You're interfering with business. Please leave!
-Won't you let go?! Won't you let go?!
You need to filter these kind of people out.
Watch it!
Oh my gosh!!!
♫ No matter how hard and desperate it gets...
♫ I came into this world with nothing, and I'll leave with nothing.
♫ I have nothing to lose.
♫ Break away... Break away...
♫ Break away... Break away...Break away...
♫ I'll break away from my suffocating life.
♫... I'll just run towards my future.
The singer who's singing right now...
Mr. Kang Jin?
Tell him to see me after he's done singing.
Ok, I got it.
You crazy thief! Bastard!
Mother-in-law!
Mother-in-law? Who's your mother-in-law?!
You wrecked my daughter's bright future, you enemy bastard!
You bastard... You bastard...
Mother! You can't do this!
Let go of this, and then talk.
Hey, you guys...
My daughter's future is totally wrecked!
Is his singing important?
Let go.
Watch out, watch out!!
Hey! Let go of her!
Let go!
Don't you have your parents?
Hey!
If you even touch me...!
I ate honey too!
You guys are dead if I lose a strand of my hair, got it?!
Kang Sook!
Bong Soo oppa!
It's you, Kang Sook!
Due to a personal problem, I sincerely apologize for not finishing my performance.
I'll come back shortly to give a great performance.
What the heck!
Why are they being like this?
Ah...
Kang Sook...
I'll say this again.
Even if I were to die and come back alive 100 times,
I have no intention of having you as my son-in-law.
Go nullify your marriage registration immediately, and return our Ki Ok.
How can I nullify our marriage registration, Mother-in-law? It's already done with.
It wouldn't have been enough even if you begged and said, " I committed an unspeakable crime, and I was wrong, Elder".
What good thing have you done that you're talking back like that?
Aiyoo... Mother-in-law, let's go home and talk about it.
We got away by begging them not to turn us over to the police for interfering with their business.
By the way, where did Bo Reum's mom go?
Sugar Entertainment
Kang Bong Soo
Oh my god!
It seems like you're really successful, Oppa.
Not really. It's like having a small store.
Wow! You haven't changed at all, Kang Sook!
No way.
Oppa.
Did you get married?
Not yet
You haven't gotten married yet?
Since I can't find anyone like you, I'm remaining a bachelor.
You can joke easily.
My Kang Sook, you're married of course, right?
We got divorced.
Then, those women I saw earlier...
They are my in-laws.
Your in-laws, I see.
I have a younger sister-in-law. The old gigolo who sang earlier, I mean,
the singer... She hitched up with him.
Then, the woman who came up to the stage
is your mother-in-law, right?
Ah, yes. That's correct.
What are you doing here?
Aiyoo, Mother-in-law is waiting.
Who is that?
Oppa, I think I have to go.
You must call me.
Yes, Oppa.
Oppa?
Aish..
Please take them home safely.
Mother-in-law, Seul Hong's mom, Bo Reum's mom, have a safe trip.
Aiyoo.
You're Kang Jin, who sang "Break Away", right?
Pardon?
I'm Kang Bong Soo from Sugar Entertainment.
Would you like to draw up a contract with me?
Contract?
No matter what I have to do, I'll get my son back!
Hey, Choon Hee...!
Don't call my name with your filthy mouth!
You're a thief.
Mother.
Oh!
You got off work late.
I had some work to finish up.
Were you crying?
No, I wasn't crying.
When I went up to the office earlier, you and Chae Won's mom weren't there. Did you go somewhere together?
Huh?
Oh... you seemed busy.
We parted after having a cup of tea together.
According to the information I got, it's seems like your mother-in-law and your mom have a very bad relationship.
Hey, Mom.
Uh... Why?
I'll take care of the laundry, so why don't you go to bed, Mom? You look tired.
Ok... You must be tired too. Go rest.
Se Yoon...
Our son...
let me hug you once.
Is there something wrong Mother?
Do you hug only if something's wrong?
Mom's hugging you because I want to.
Before I get married, I'll do as you say, so hug me as much as you want.
I'm sorry my son...
Your mom couldn't recognize you.
I'm sorry.
Have you been waiting long, Mother-in-law?
No, I just got here.
I see...
Did you run here?
Yes.
Since you told me you had something urgent to say, I rushed here.
Is something going on, Mother-in-law?
I'm sorry.
Pardon?
I'm really sorry.
But with our Se Yoon...
I think you have to part from him.
Pardon?!