Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 45
Under the charge of producing, distributing, and selling the heavy metal containing noodles
Ms. Bang Yong Ja is under arrest.
Mom!
Mom...
Excuse, look here. My mom didn't do anything wrong! Please let her go!
Ayish, this darn...
Why the heck are you coming as a flock to take pictures?
Get away. Get AWAY!
Mom, Mo-m!
Uh, we didn't commit any crime...
Don't cow down. No reason to cow down. Don't cry! Don't cry!!
We Geum Yoong Food is
an honest company that even received an excellence award from the minister of commerce.
We were taken by the horrid supplier and cheated. We are the victims here.
In short time, we will be filing for a damage compensation and
we will recover the lost integrity of Geum Yoong Foods.
Now, we will reveal details after the investigation,
Please move aside. Move aside, please!
U-huh, common.
What do I do if you just take her blindly?
Mom!
Ai, Mister, where are you going right now, huh?
Mom, MOM!
Don't worry too much, as we will resolve this issue after negotiating with the lawyers well.
I understand, I understand. Don't cry, ok? Don't cry!
It's all going to work out!
Yes.
Just wait a little, mom.
It's alright. Our guilt will be removed!
Mom, MOM!
Mom, Mom, MOM!
Stop taking pictures!
Hey, Kim Joo Ri!
Snap out of it!
All this is because of me...
What do I do?
What do we do about our mom?
She'll be alright.
Mom will be released shortly.
Is this how our family declines?
What do you mean decline? What bad luck!
It's not like we did this on purpose...
When we are clearly the victim, do you think anything would happen to us?
Don't worry about it. Your brother will take care of everything.
See? You did do it.
Get over here!
I don't have...
Ms. Bang Young Ja!
Yes.
The mugwort that was supplied to you,
Did you really not know that they were imported through illegal distribution channel?
Ai, cham.
If we've known it, why would we have received the shipment???
How many times do I have to tell you?
We're also the victim!
In order to get a supply of ldow price mugwort
didn't you ignore the problem even though you were aware?
Wait a minute, listen to this man.
How many times did I tell you?
I told you that we received the certification that proved the quality of...Ach!
Never mind. I didn't commit any crime so hurry up &amp; investigate!
Hurry up and investigate and let me out quickly.
I am incredibly busy laden with company work!
Right now, I'm not an idle person who can stay put here. Seriously!
Investigate!
It's known that the entire noodle quantity currently in distribution in the market place
will be recalled then destroyed.
Then, could they receive a criminal penalty as well?
That is yet to be known.
Good work.
Yes, director.
Yes.
Wedding invitation has arrived.
Wedding invitation you say?
Yes. It's so pretty, director.
If you insist on marrying her til the end,
I'm going to assume you want to sever our father-son relationship.
And I'll separate from your mom.
What is this?
Se Yoon's infant clothing and
the anklet that Abbess has made for him.
And photo album and video that contains memory from Se Yoon's childhood.
They're all things that I've temporarily kept
so I should return them to you.
Your brother-in-law said to Se Yoon
if he marries Chae Won then he'll sever his father-son ties and divorce me as well.
What?
All these happenings are due to me
I'm preparing for the worst.
I'm going to follow Se Yoon and your decision
unconditionally.
So you two should discuss what you're going to do
and tell me.
Are you ill somewhere?
You look like you're having a very hard time.
Se Yoon said I
make him shiver
and am creepy and scary.
I know I deserve to hear words like those 100 no 1000 times
but when I actually hear it
it breaks my heart.
In the past 30 years
I feel as though my life has become wind-blown sand.
Cruel and pathetic
This is what I'm like.
How audaciously can I say "I'm having a hard time" in front of you?!
I'm sorry...Choon Hee.
I'm going to go first.
Choon Hee
His childhood pictures are all placed in the photo album so I don't have a single one at home.
I forgot to take one out before you came,
do you think it's possible for you to give just one photo of him to me?
I'm sorry, Choon Hee.
Please just give me one picture.
This one is my Se Yoon's 100 day baby picture!
Thank you, Choon Hee.
Truly, thank you.
Common, step, step, step
Sweetheart,
you release your hold and let Se Yoon walk alone.
Don't you think it'd be overdoing it a little?
It's past his 1st birthday, let's give it a try!
Hey Se Yoon, try walking without mommy holding you, ok?
Here you go.
Step, step...Oh.
Oh, Se Yoon. Are you okay? Oh.
My baby, does it hurt?
That boy. Who do you take after to be such a crybaby?! Hah hah.
Did he say "crybaby" to our prince?
We don't like you daddy. Ddatchi (soft slap, pretend smack)
Oh ho. Bad daddy.
Ai such a good boy. You stopped crying so quickly.
Isn't he a good boy?
Se Yoon!
Wah...
Chae Won! Chae Won!
I don't think things are going well.
What is?
That rascal Son-in-Law Kim's company.
They keep coming on the news
saying that the police took away the President.
What?
Open the door!
Open it! Open the door!
Hey! Do you even know who you put in here?
I'm Keum Ryeong Food's President
Bang Young Ja!
Hey!
Aiyoo.
If you keep being rowdy it won't go well for you.
I-I
am not able to breathe so I'm getting sick.
Let me out.
I'm not ashamed to face the heaven. I'm an innocent person!
We have more to investigate still so wait quietly, please.
What are you people doing locking up an innocent person here, huh?
I'm not an idle person who can just stay put here.
Me getting out of here is the only way I can work through all the backlog at my company!
Oh, hey!
How can you just leave?
Hey! Open the door!
You're so loud!
Ah, seriously.
Please look at you rotten...
What are you people saying?
What?
What do you think you're saying? I'm saying let's get some sleep!
You want a piece of me?
Be quiet!
Even if our non-involvement with the supplier is proven
it'll be difficult to avoid the administrative action from managerial negligence.
If you're saying administrative action, what type of things are you talking about, Counsel?
According to the Food Sanitation Regulations, you can receive 1 month production halt
destruction of all involved products
and have no choice but to receive 1 month of operation suspension.
Yes!
There's a big problem.
What is it this time?
Amongst the Green Noodle consumers, anti-Geum Yoong Food activism has started and
stock market also
This seems to be serious.
What?
Welcome.
Um.
Please give me a pregnancy test.
A pregnancy test?
My daughter
has gotten married not long ago.
It seems like she's pregnant so she asked me to buy her a pregnancy test.
Yes, just a moment.
Please give me medicine for headache and stress-relief.
What brings you here at the pharmacy?
Yeah.
Should be in full honeymoon phase, what business would he have in the pharmacy?
Here is the pregnancy test.
Ah, yes.
A pregnancy test?
It's not confirmed,
so we have to take the pregnancy test.
Oh my god!
Get back to your senses, Hyungnim!
What should we do?
Even though the pregnancy test has directions on it, two lines means that she is pregnant.
Please tell your daughter so she is not confused.
Yes.
Daughter?
Aigoo, man.
Honey.
You bought it?
Here.
What brings you two here?
Aiyoo.
You're going at the speed of light.
It hasn't been long since you've left and you're using those.
That's right.
Is this a honeymoon baby or something like that sister-in-law?
Why did you bring them?
I met them at the pharmacy, so don't worry.
Let's go.
Aiyoo, hey!
Where do you think you're going with her?
My mind's in a hurry and I'm curious-
My my. Know your place.
Just wait out here!
You're senseless. Senseless!
Why are you clucking your tongue?
You should have been careful before!
How could you do this without thinking?
Without thought?
Aigoo. When you marry, aren't you supposed to have a baby?
Oh my goodness, you're too greedy!
This is really unbelievable!
Don't you know how old you are? Where do you get off thinking you're going to get an off-spring?
What are you going to do now?
Ah, really.
Aren't you two overreacting right now?
Overreacting?!
Even though we are family,
you shouldn't be putting your nose in every single private matter of a married couple.
Mind your own business! What's the matter with you?
Ah, really.
Did the results come out?
About being pregnant...
I am.
What?
It had two lines?
Look. It's two lines!
You worked hard!
You really worked hard, Honey!
You've worked harder!
Aiyoo.
Two lines!
It's total fast lane for them...
Yeah.
They're really going at it at top speed!
Hey, at the pharmacy,
they said if it's two lines,
it's confirmed!
You've worked hard.
Pregnant?
Does that mean you have a baby?
Mother-in-Law.
We've gone to the hospital
and confirmed it on our way here.
Aigoo, my head! Aigoo, my head!
Please take a tranquilizer for right now, Mother.
To be prepared for an emergency I bought this at the pharmacy earlier.
aiyoo, aiyoo.
Aigoo, aigoo.
Here you go.
I have to say that you are talented.
You're putting the final nails on it so this family has no where to run.
You...99 tailed,
old WEASEL!
I should have cut off the tails on that butt first.
O-ho.
What o-ho?
How old is that old gigolo that he is producing a baby?
I guess he can wear Depends when the child enters college.
Such problem children that always cause problems without ever having any backup plan.
Aigoo.
Where are you going mid-conversation?
I'm going to have to go lie down.
My head feels like it's exploding just with Chae Won's issue but Gi Ok that wench is adding to it
I feel like my head is going to "Boom" explode!
Aigoo Mother-in-law!
Aigoo, Aigoo.
Aigoo, aigoo. Let me die!
What about Chae Won?
Did something happen to Chae Won?
Oh, I'm hungry. Get the meal ready.
You said you didn't have any appetite earlier.
Since my blood pressure rises quickly, a sudden hunger strikes me.
Hurry.
Uh, okay.
Aiyoo, hungry.
What's the matter?
Oh I forgot.
I said I'd contact the collaborators and I forgot.
Everyone's leaving me out. Isn't this a little harsh?
Congratulations.
Thank you, Father-in-law.
I'll do my best and
raise him to be the best.
Now that you're not caring just for yourself,
you need to be careful of mind and body.
Yes, father.
Now you've got one more mouth to feed,
you need to take better care of your health.
I still have another 50 years without a problem, father-in-law!
Mom,
Uh, Chae Won.
What are you thinking about so seriously?
I called you out several times.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was thinking about something.
You mean, thoughts about Se Yoon?
I saw you watching the video earlier.
It looked like Se Yoon's childhood...
I met Seol Joo during the day.
Then did mother-in-law give you those?
I'm not sure what she was thinking
but she gave me Se Yoon's childhood photo album and video tape.
I see.
You're quite upset, right?
In the end, I feel I've become an obstacle in your path to the future,
so I can't face you or your dad from guilty thoughts.
That's nonsense.
How can you say "obstacle"?
It the end, it's come to that.
If only I didn't marry your dad,
you two wouldn't have had any problems.
Also, if I didn't appear in front of Se Yoon,
he also wouldn't have suffered heartaches.
Come to think of it now,
I shouldn't have returned home.
Why do you say things like that?
If dad heard you he'd be so sad.
What would be an optimum situation for you two is what this mom is
agonizing over right now.
So just wait a little longer for me.
Se Yoon calling
It's Se Yoon.
Go ahead and take it.
Hello?
It's me.
Uh. Right.
Can you make some time for me this evening?
Today?
You're home now Hone...
Where is Seyoon?
He must of had an appointment.
He sent text saying he'd be a little late.
I met with Choon Hee
I met her and handed over all Se Yoon's childhood things.
Album, video, and
What's your intent in handing all those things to Choon Hee sister-in-law?
Let's just let Se Yoon go comfortably.
You just do everything the way you want alone!
In your eyes do I look laughable to you.
Honey...
If you bring home a stolen child, I act the fool and become it's daddy,
if you say let's release Se Yoon then I have to act the fool once again and say go with peace,
wave goodbye is all I have to do?
That's not what I meant.
I cannot give up on Seyoon.
Whether it be 30 years ago or now
he's the one to lead our group and continue our family to next generation.
Therefore, meet with Choon Hee sister-in-law and make it clear.
What are you saying that I need to
make clear?
Make sure she promises that she will not get involved in legal matters.
You... Aren't you being too harsh?!
How could you say those things to Choon Hee?
Do you think you have the right to say that kind of words to me?
Honey!
It's an unfortunate thing for Sister-in-law Choon Hee, but I have no choice.
It's a problem you have started, so you end it.
That 's
like killing Choon Hee a second time.
I'd rather die than
do that.
You waited for long, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
There was some traffic due to rush-hour.
You waited for long, huh?
Mother, you waited 30 years.
I had a mother who waited for me for 30 years,
how could I not wait 30 minutes.
Seyoon
Thank you
What a foolish mom who's lost her son,
what a stupid mom... I was worried that you'd curse and blame me.
As a mom I couldn't even recognize the son she bore herself...
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It wasn't your fault.
It's not your fault so please don't feel guilty.
My father, what kind of person was he?
He was a warm person.
He was so bright that he got accepted and was studying in a law school of an Ivy-League college
he had brilliant mind as well.
Then...
how did you two then...?
Your father and I were both orphans
his economic situation was difficult.
Because he didn't have the tuition, he took a leave of absence from school
and he worked part-time at the printing company I was working for.
Because we had so little money,
we couldn't get married properly,
but we set up a little house together and were so happy.
Your father was
so attentive and tender that
When I saw how you were with Chaewon
Honestly, I often thought of your father.
Truthfully Seyoon,
I don't know whether I should,
appear in front of you so rightfully
I feel guilty.
After your dad passed from car accident,
I didn't have confidence in living as a single mom at young age,
I tried to abort while I was pregnant with you,
even visiting a hospital
and taking some pills
I'm
I don't have the right to hear you say birth-mother.
If it was such a situation,
you couldn't have done things any differently.
Mom
it's not your fault.
Se yoon
Hearing you say "mom", my goodness,
all the hardened shards piled in my heart for the past 30 years
are at last all melting away, it feels.
Thank you.
For saying "mom" to a person like me who's not qualified to hear it.
Truly, thank you, Se Yoon.
Why do you say things like that?
No matter what anyone says,
the person who bore me was you, Mom.
Se Yoon
When did you come?
A little while ago.
You should say you came, when you come,
why are you staying like that?
If I say I came, I thought you may shoo me away.
Today, I want to look at your face for a long time, Chae Won.
Did you talk with mom alright?
She cried a lot.
Of course,
if one wants to vent one's 30 year long regrets,
I think she'll be crying for much longer still.
No matter what I'm going to get married on the date we planned.
You know it's not a matter that can be resolved by insist like that.
Se Yoon and mom's relationship has become known to the world,
how can we get married?
There's nothing that would be a problem.
Our wedding will happen as planned.
Don't be unreasonable.
Then treat wedding ceremony as non-existent?
I can never do that.
The wedding will happen as we planned.
Se Yoon, Se Yoon!
Next on the news
Geum Yoon Food's Green Noodle had a total recall as large quantity of lead and cadimum etc. heavy metal were detected
The police started the seize and search on Geum Yoong.
Investigation shows Geum Yoong Co used low priced supplier to cut cost
What's that? Kim hubby's captured on camera!
this...has been discovered.
Right. Big problem's happening.
It was decided that all noodles distributed to the marketplace will be recalled.
Consumer's anti-purchase activism started and stock price dropped.
Isn't Kim hubby's company failing at this rate?
Chaewon ,Chaewon
come over here and take a look at the news.
In-law mother and Kim hubby's faces are on TV as big as a door!
Hurry!
Please move away! Move away!
Mom. Mom. Mom.
Son-in-law Kim, that rascal, what's he going to do? A mama's boy who can't do a thing without his mommy?
Like you said. He looks like he lost half his senses.
These people who play with consumable food should get punished!
Aiyoo, that mama boy, tsk..
Aiyoo, aigoo, I can't be staying here with both my hands idle, aiyoo.
Aiyoo, my innards are gonna burst. I'm going to go mad!
Aigoo, what in the world are Counsel Hong, Cheol Gyoo, and Joo Ri doing anyway?
Aigoo.
You really are getting on my nerves!
All day long what are you so busy with? I can't even sleep!
Aigoo, this rotten cabbage, you wench, how can you be bitching about sleep all day?
Did you come to jail to sleep? Is this a motel room?
I'm pissed off as is and how dare you start a fight with me, you fishwife?
This...this.. Have you considered who I might be before you start with me?
What do I care who you are?
This... this...did you only eat trashy food, where do you get off talking disrespectfully to me?
this...this how in the world...
Miss Bang Young Ja
Uh uh... mme me me
Mom you must have suffered. It was a hard day wasn't it?
Well for me who's suffered through this that and every possible thing, this is nothing.
I'm sorry Mom, It's all my fault.
At this stage, nit picking over who was wrong, has no point.
What about the stock price?
It's almost at the bottom.
This...
It's not only the noodle products, but
the dairy products and processed food product sales have also sharply declined.
and also
and also what else?
A message came from the bank.
From the bank ?
They said they can't postpone the date for the loan payment.
They think we're going out of business.
This is wrong. If they're like this, it will be difficult.
Lawyer Hong
Come with me to the office and we'll discuss this.
Ah...
You and Joo Ri go home. I have something to discuss with Lawyer Hong.
Does she have a secret with Lawyer Hong.
I'm angry. I'm so angry that I want to die.
What is it now?
I really meant to revenge on Sunbae Se Yoon. How do we look now?!
Is that the issue at hand? The company's about to blow.
When are you going to come to your senses?
Don't bother me!
Okay
You're late
Yes
Good night
Chae Won's mom...
You met with her?
I saw your text.
I thought you were coming home after having dinner with Chae Won's mom.
Right.
Mom...
I met her, and we had dinner and talked.
Ok... Ok.
Now... She's not just Chae... Won's mom.
You have to call her mom.
I'm sorry. I was not thinking.
Go to sleep please.
♫ You're becoming more distant from me.
♫ Your love is becoming more distant.Mom is probably having a hard time just like me.
♫ We still have a lot to say to each other.I don't why I only say cruel things to her.
♫ I should hate you
♫ because you left me.
♫ I shouldn't think about you because we have parted ways.
The whole world knows about the relationship between you and your mom. How can we marry?
Then, are you saying we should pretend that marriage plans never occurred?
I'm making this very clear to you.
I will never be able to do that.
♫ In your eyes... ♫ I'm right here.♫ If I could only go back into
♫ your heart again...
Why are you coming back so late when you only out to urinate?
I thought you fell and got hurt in the restroom, so I was about go out to check.
Honey.
They say life is a pilgrimage from birth to death.
We become food for frogs in the water.
They say we're dew on the grass.
What is this Confucius and Mencius in the middle of the night?
There is nothing much to life.
Leave Chae Won and Ki Ok to do whatever they want to do.
You became a living buddha.
Don't just bicker.
Se Won's biological mom is Chae Won's stepmom, do you still want them to get married?
Even though they don't share a drop of blood, they are still siblings.
If others were to find out, what would they say?
There is no use of paying attention to what others say.
Then, do you want to applaud the old man who is almost 60 years old and Ki Ok who's living with him?
She's even pregnant, what can we do?
Because you have a good heart, everything might be okay for you.
I'm not so nice, so I can't ever do that.
Her view of the world...
Hello, Father-in-law.
Long time no see, Brothers-in-law.
You, old gigolo, how did you get here?
What do you want to gain?!
Why are you getting mad so early in the morning, Hyungnim?
Father-in-law called me early in the morning. I slept very little, and rushed over here.
Father, did you call him?
Alright. This morning, the Uhm men will have a rally to strengthen our unity.
Let's have refreshing baths, and part after having a bowl of pollack soup.
Father-in-law, let's get going please.
That... that... gigolo...
I don't want to soak in the same public bathtub with him.
You're being childish. Let's just go in.
Let's go in.
Thinking on it, I feel we have a good thing
The three generations being able to soak together in this bath.
I'm grateful.
These days, people don't want to be burdened by their old parents.
Thanks to my children who came back to carry on the family business.
The last years of my life...
I couldn't be any happier.
I owe you a big debt that I can't even pay back from heaven.
Why do you talk like that, Father-in-law?
Yeah... The factory is running well. We even get royalties from a large company.
Now, you only have things that will make you happy.
Of course. When I see Father naked, he looks like a sixty year old. It's believable.
When I look at his good posture and build, he looks the same as 20 years ago. He didn't age a bit.
Aye
don't talk nonsense.
Nonsense? I'm saying it's true!
Yes, it's true.
Look here son in law.
Yes, father in law.
Don't get too upset by Chae Won's matter. You should take care of it the way it's meant to be.
Yes, that's what I should do.
My oldest son, Uhm Ki Moon...
Yes Father?
Don't be too greedy for money.
Starting from a long time ago, noodles have been meant to satisfy hungry stomachs. It a food to be thankful for.
You have to make them without greed, just with warm heart and hands.
Yes.
I will keep that in mind.
My youngest son, Uhm Ki Choon...
Yes, sir!
Don't treat your brother-in-law badly.
Pass the time together well.
Father!
If General Uhm acknowledged him, you, Private, should just follow me without a word.
Son in law Kang
Yes Father in law
You made a promise together with me, that you have another fifty years ahead of you.
Yes, don't have a single concern.
I have the confidence to do it.
Yes, then that will do.
Who will scrub Grandpa's back?
-I will.
- I will.
Ah now...
Because of my two grandkids, I'm being well taken care of.
Let's go.
Make it refreshing.
Today, there's something strange about Father-in-law.
If it weren't for me,
the kids' wedding would have
happened tomorrow just as planned.
It seems like Miss is suffering a lot from morning sickness.
Shouldn't you go check on her Mother in law,
No, it doesn't matter. She's doesn't care about her mother and father at all.
Really, what's the beauty in that? Leave it be.
Hello, did you sleep well?
Didn't you get any sleep? Your face is getting haggard more each day.
I had to do a lot of work concerning the factory.
Where's Grandfather?
Grandfather along with all the Uhm men went to the bathhouse,
and will return after eating pollack soup. This morning, let's just the women eat.
I don't have an appetite.
I'm going to the factory.
If you don't have the inclination, what's with that ? Hey, Chae Won dear.
Leave her alone Mother in law.
If we didn't have that problem, tomorrow would have been her wedding day. She must be upset.
Even if she eats, will her food sit well?
Oh my, I should have died before seeing these things happen.
Aigoo.
For having the wrong parent,
the kids will suffer for the rest of their lives.
Aigoo.
Did he leave for work already?
"Please celebrate our love with us" Groom: Yi Se Yoon, Bride: Min Chae Won, Date, Time, Location...
How did it go?
I met with the president of the bank. I begged him to postpone the loan payment date just once.
I couldn't persuade him.
Oh, the rottenness
Come in.
The promissory note we have to cover today is W50 billion.
What?
If we cannot cover the promissory note today that's preliminary bankruptcy, Chairman.
Let's sell our shares that should prevent for now Mom.
Stop talking nonsense!
How can we sell the shares and cover the promissory note when the value of our company share has become tissue long ago?
Then, maybe the cash we have...
Ah!
That's enough.
Take leave.
Yes, Chairman.
Don't we have plenty of cash and gold bullion in our home vault? Why not just take those to the bank and...
Please. Please Please.
Just keep your mouth shut.
Even though we should try our best to cover the notes, don't we have to find a way to survive too?
The way for us to survive is to request the walk out (defaulting on the loan possibly) and
If that occurs, you and I will be thrown out first. Understand? Got it? Knowing that, you're still babbling now?
No. I'll never give up on our company.
Aigoo aigoo aigoo.
Aigoo, that reckless simpleton who doesn't know a thing about the way of the world!
Aigoo aigoo.
Where's Lawyer Hong?
We just parted company.
Firstly, he said he'd sell everything in our name and turn it into cash
Ok.
Savings, you told him to withdraw it all, right?
Of course.
By the way,
What are you doing here?
Hello.
You're Kang Sook's Unnie (older sister), right?
Unnie?
I saw you that time at the cabaret. Don't you remember me?
You have a visitor outside.
Who is the guest?
The man we meet at the cabaret.
Hey! What's this about?!
I'm going out for a while, don't tell Boreum's father anything.
Something smells fishy.
What are you talking about, smell? He's just an oppa I used to know from school
Is that all?
And if it's not all?
The why are you telling me not to tell Boreum's father?
It's not even a big deal. I'm just afraid he will misunderstand.
With Chae Won's case also. Hyungnim, that...
that mouth of yours is your flaw, you know that, right?
I'll only be gone for 30 minutes.
Something really smells (fishy).
Where did that person go?
Uh...someone came by to visit her.
A guest?
Yes.
Oppa.
I'm not bothering a busy person am I?
No. What are you doing here without calling first Oppa?
I didn't have that much to do today. I thought we might have lunch together. Also to return this kimchi container.
Yes.
My Kang Sook, not only you're pretty, but you're good with your hands.
I was really moved.
Oppa, for something like this...
Boreum's Mom.
Kang Sook!
What's going on?
Shhhhhhhh
Boreum's Mom
Kang Sook!
Boreum's Mom?
I had a son with my ex husband.
His name is Bo Reum.
Oh
Then who is that guy?
He's my brother.
Then why are you hiding?
My family is kind of strict.
If they find out a man visited...
things will get complicated.
Aaaahhhh
Kang Sook!
I brought you some strawberries.
I washed them out in the yard. Get up and eat one, hurry, Honey.
Thanks.
Here, here, ahh.
What's wrong again?
Ug, the smell of the strawberry is making me nauseous.
Is there anything spicy?
I want to eat Soon Dae soup, Honey.
Soon Dae soup?
Oppa, you know how to eat this too?
Of course!
I really enjoy Soon Dae soup.
How can even his taste in food could be so easy going?
Doesn't even make smacks his mouth as he eats, like somebody I know.
a genuine gentleman, he is.
Boerum's mom. Older sister.
What are you happen to be doing here?
This person all of a sudden wanted to eat soon dae soup.
President, what are you doing in this neighborhood?
I came by to share lunch with Gang Sook.
By the way, does that make Gang Sook Mr. Gang Jin's Cheu Hyung (wife's elder sister)?
Cheo Hyung?
Of course.
That's correct.
But,
the sisters don't look alike at all.
Hey there, there is something I've been curious about.
why aren't you married?
From the past having broken up, I'm now meeting again my first love.
Your first love?
I only trust you, Attorney Hong.
So I hope you take good care of the problem.
My family's survival depends on you, Attorney Hong.
You got it?!
Yes, okay, okay.
I understand. We'll connect again tomorrow.
Mom
Mom, mom.
Yes.
How did it go?
How do you think?
Who am I?
Quit the smack talk.
What has happened?
I submitted the extension to the bank so
it won't become a preliminary bankruptcy until tomorrow 10AM.
Is that so?
You worked hard.
I shouldn't have just left it up to Mom and Joo Ri.
I should have gotten involved with the company affairs a long time ago.
Then, something like this wouldn't have happened.
You'll be assigned to a branch in the U.S.
Be there next month.
Father!
You have to give all you've got for the factory.
If you want to get over things fast, I think you should go to the U.S.
I've never told you I would get over Chae Won.
If you don't...
As planned,
we'll get married tomorrow.
If you do that, this company...
I can't leave it in your hands.
[Resignation]
You...
What are you doing right now?
I submitted my resignation.
And, I
will leave home.
Se Yoon!
As planned, I will marry Chae Won tomorrow.
You must...
You must do this?
No matter how much I think about it, I have no other choice.
Alright.
Go.
Since you will be happy,
I don't want to hold you back anymore.
I shouldn't hold you back.
To Chae Won...
tell her that I congratulate you on your wedding.
I am sorry.
Grandfather!
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
I came here to kidnap Chae Won right now.
Please give me your permission.
You're going to kidnap her?
No matter what, I can't give up on Chae Won.
Because of the elders' past, we can't give up on our future.
We'll go down to the countryside. We'll come back after we get married, just the two of us.
Please give us your permission.
Please give us your permission, Grandfather!
Take her.
I give you my permission.
You can kidnap our Chae Won.
Thank you, Grandfather.
What brings you here tonight?
I came to kidnap you.
Also, I just got permission from Grandfather.
What are you talking about right now?
You have to go somewhere with me.
Where?
Have you ever heard a kidnapper telling his destination?
Don't ask anything.
just follow me.
What are you doing?
Where are we going?
Where are you going right now?
You'll find out when we get there.
Are we going far?
Yes, we're traveling really far.
Where is that place?
It's a place where we can become one with each other.
What are you thinking right now?
Perhaps...
You're right.
Why are you acting childish?
This is wrong. You shouldn't do this.
Think about the family members who might get hurt because of us.
From now on, I won't think about anything else.
I will only think about you and me.
What is this place?
It's the place where we will get married.
Se Yoon!