Hundred Year Inheritance
Episode 46
Where is this place?
This is the place where we'll get married.
Se Yoon!
If we don't do it like this, maybe we'll be finished forever.
This could be our last chance.
But, if someone gets hurt because of us...
In life,
because of me, someone could get hurt from one thing or another.
That person is our mom.
Why aren't you looking out for your own interests?
You're so bothered when others are in pain.
Do you really not care about your own sufferings?
And what about me?
If I'm in pain,
and if I get wounded,
you don't care?
Se Yoon.
Do you have the confidence that you can call me Oppa?
I don't have the confidence to accept it.
When I see you, I want to kiss you, hold your hands, and hug you.
I don't want to live rest of my life hearing "Oppa" from you.
I will prepare and take care of everything.
You just have to stay by my side.
Please have courage.
Don't be a coward anymore.
Got it?
What are you doing right now?
Can't you see?
I'm drinking alcohol.
This person... seriously!
Se Yoon
left home.
What?!
He said just by themselves...
they will have a wedding ceremony.
Are you in your right mind?!
You should have stopped him!
Did you just watch him go?!
Of course that's what I did.
What right do I have to stop him?
I didn't even give birth to him.
I'm the mom who stole him.
What can I do?!
So, you too
leave.
If Se Yoon
marries Chae Won,
you said you will divorce me.
I'll let you divorce me!
You leave me too.
This person...
Anyway,
I'm always alone.
You can all leave me.
I'll be alright.
What did you do that is good?
Why are you having a drunken tantrum?
Only if you
didn't drive him to the edge,
our Se Yoon
would not have made such a desperate choice.
So...
Are you blaming me, right now?
You should have just let them get married!
Then, Se Yoon wouldn't have left home!
You took
our son away from me!
Give me back my son.
Go get our Se Yoon!
You have the audacity to accuse me, when you're the one who's done wrong!
You're not salvageable!
What...?
Unsalvageable?
Fine.
If that's what you want,
I'll leave.
Alright.
Leave!
There is nothing to be afraid of.
I AM IMPENETRABLE!
I'm alright.
Are you in there, Chae Won?
Is she still at the factory?
Chae Won is not in bed.
She's not here.
What are you talking about, Father-in-law?
Se Yoon came to me, and asked me if he could kidnap Chae Won.
I told him he could.
Pardon?
It seemed like the two will have a wedding ceremony.
Ah...
What are you talking about, Father-in-law?
What do mean wedding ceremony?
Who is marrying whom?
Who do you think? It's Chae Won and Se Yoon.
Father-in-law!
What did I tell you?
You should let things work out the way they are meant to be.
Even so!
Without parents' permission,
how could they elope?
This won't do!
It doesn't matter.
They love each other.
Chae Won lost her mind.
Hiding from her parents,
how could she think of eloping?
Leave it.
It's already done with.
Let's just watch over them.
I'm really disappointed!
What are you disappointed about...?
If you thought of Chae Won as your own daughter,
you wouldn't be like this.
If Se Yoon is your son, Chae Won is your daughter too.
As if nothing is wrong,
you say you want to get them married.
How could you talk like that?
I lived all this time regarding Chae Won as my own daughter.
Why is it so noisy?
What's going on?
You never yelled at each other before.
Why are you so loud?
What's the matter?
I'm really disappointed!
Did you fight over Chae Won's marriage?
Sorry for being so loud, Mother.
According to Hyung, Seok Joon, this is the best bed and breakfast place in the neighborhood.
Let's spend the night here. After our wedding, let's go somewhere nice for our honeymoon.
You know Hyung, Seok Joon, don't you?
You met him once a long time ago.
He was working as a doctor in Namhae hospital.
Of course.
I contacted him a couple of times afterwards.
He is supposed to come to our wedding tomorrow.
He will be an important witness for our wedding.
And,
our wedding will be officiated by Seok Joon's brother-in-law.
He's the pastor for the church we visited earlier.
When did you prepare all this?
I'm a very capable man.
Ah, what's this?
I said the joke so you can laugh. So serious.
You're right.
You are
too good for me.
Even though I got you in the car, drove down,
honestly, I was worried that you might insist on going back to Seoul.
Since you're acknowledging me like this, I feel relaxed.
I barely got the postponement until 10 AM tomorrow.
Will we get the money before then?
Both Kim executive director and the head of the operations
They are
trying their best, so we have to trust them.
I'm sorry, Mom.
If I came to my senses a little earlier,
the company would not be this messed up.
I was too unconcerned before.
Aigoo...
Even though it's a little late,
it seems like you came to your senses.
I feel good about it.
I can't live with my pride having been stepped on like this.
I'm too angry to end it like this!
This wench, Joo Ri, why is she being like this?
Hey, Kim Joo Ri! Are you drinking?!
Aiyoo...
After one of them came to their senses,
the other one turns me inside out.
Aigoo... my life, even a dog wouldn't bite me.
She's crazy.. You must've really gone crazy. You're not even afraid.
You're having a drunken tantrum again.
Let go of it!! After I drink this,
I'll just die.
Hey... hey... hey... You made all this mess. How dare do you whine?
How could you talk irresponsibly right now that you want to die?
Joo Ri is saying those words out of frustration, so don't get too upset.
Aigoo... Why should I blame anyone?
I'm the dumb one who went along with you.
I spent all that money to educate you abroad.
Stupidly, you get played by a piddly supplier
with those people, this company...
you messed it up like this. You idiot!
Did I know things would turn out this way?
I wanted to succeed, and
deliver a blow to Sunbae.
The only crime is that I tried my best.
You're talking about him again. Aigoo... I'm sick of it. I'm sick of it!
Anyway, he's the public enemy.
Being around Chae Won isn't enough, now, he made our company like this...
Why?
You're done eating?
Since you wanted to eat it, I went to Jangchundo to buy it.
It doesn't have the taste it used to have.
What?
My younger sister-in-laws' pig's feet have no smell, and they are chewy.
These don't have the same taste.
They don't smell.
I want to eat Bo Reum family pig's feet.
How can you eat their pig's feet right now?
Really, I have to eat them.
Boss, why aren't you marrying?
My long lost first love,
I found her again.
Who else could it be?
Definitely it's me, Gong Gang Sook.
Oh my, that scared me!
What does she want again..?
Agasshi, why'd you call?
I wanted to eat your pigs feet, that's why I called.
The store's been long gone.
How can you request that?
I want to eat your's specifically
You must be craving pig feet because of your morning sickness,
ask your husband to go buy you some.
No, I have to eat your homemade pig feet specifically.
What is this crow-drops-lower-jaw-while-yawning kind of talk?
So what your saying is that you want me to make you pig's feet right now? Is that it?
During pregnancy, they say if you don't eat what you crave, the baby will be small.
Ah, hmph, no manners,
What time is it right now that you want me to make you pig's feet?
And furthermore, when it comes to pig feet, I'm personally disgusted by it.
I'm sorry but go just buy some.
I didn't want to have to resort to cheap rhetoric but
It looks like I'll have to call oppa.
Your brother only knows how to deliver pig's feet. Your brother knows nothing about how to make pig's feet.
Not that oppa..
Sugar Entertainments President Kang Bong Soo!
Bong- Bong Soo oppa?!
For your sake I wanted to keep my mouth shut
I guess, to you, a friendship with me is nothing special.
So if my brother is nearby, hand him the phone.
There should be some in the fridge.
It shouldn't take long to prepare.
So just hold on a bit, Agasshi.
Why pig's feet this late?
Agasshi wanted to eat it and asked me to deliver it.
She has a lot of nerve.
Who's she to ask for pig's feet this time of night?
What are you doing right now?!
How is being pregnant something special like earning a government post,
I'm going to call and scold her.
It's fine,
Mother hasn't even looked in her once,
at least I should look after her a bit.
And since it's due to pregnancy cravings,
I should do this.
What's with that look?
Honey, you're trying to score some points with me.
What?
If it was old you, you would have used all kinds of curse words and grumbled
you're boiling pig feet at midnight without any complaint.
Here!
Come be held by this broad chest.
I'll hug you til your ribs crumble.
Get out of here before your ribs crumble to bits by getting beaten by the pig feet.
She's pretending to fuss while she likes it.
To-night...
We're gonna do it!
Earlier, I was too harsh.
Even if i was mad,
I shouldn't have said that.
I just felt very frustrated,
so don't think much of it.
I...'ve done what I could do
Not once did I feel that Chae Won is
another's daughter.
But it seems it looked that way in your eyes.
Honey..
If I just wasn't here,
wouldn't our kids,
be able to get married?
What are you saying right now?
I..
even though it's true that Se Yoon is my child,
if I'm not Chae Won's mom..
Let's stop for now.
Honey, Choon Hee.
That person,
what is she thinking right now?
You must be tired, so rest.
I'll be in the next room,
So don't worry right now.
Sleep well.
Should I just sleep next to you tonight?
What?
It may be scary sleeping alone.
Let me sleep here.
Right over there, I'll do nothing but sleep.
Are you joking again?
I'm not joking.
I'm saying this because I'm really scared.
No way..
Just sleep in your room.
I know..
I was just joking.
Mom.
It's mom.
Don't answer.
Father also called several times.
They'll be worried.
let's turn off our phones until the end of our wedding tomorrow.
Until the wedding tomorrow,
I don't want to be in contact with anyone.
The phone you have called is turned off at the moment. Please leave a message after the beep.
I heard from Grandfather.
Me, your wedding
I'll be happy about.
Have a beautiful wedding
and return home.
And to Se Yoon too,
tell him that I said congratulation.
I really wanted..
to see the wedding of you both.
I love you daughter,
and also son.
I feel weird..
Chae Won and I,
will get married tomorrow as planned.
Hurry and go.
I hope you are happy together.
I don't have any thoughts of holding onto you.
I'm sorry Mom.
What are you saying?!
Oh no, right now Chae Won is eloping without his parent's knowing? Is that what your saying?
What do you mean thief wedding (eloping)? I gave them permission.
Wait so everyone sitting here doesn't count and you are the only human here?
Are you saying if Mr. Um Pang Dal allows it, it's okay to go through the marriage ceremony?
Wow, total score! Chae Won noo-na (older sis) caused a big problem!
Hey, tsk.
But,
Does Se Yoon's family know this?
I bet Seol Joo was foaming at the mouth and fell backwards.
Is thief-wedding (eloping) in style these days? Gi Ok that wench and now Chae Won too...why are they acting like this?
The Uhm women, this won't do. We have to smack them back to their senses.
I didn't think Se Yoon would act this way. Disappointing.
Why?
Then now, how are we related to each other?
To the big-sis-in-law, is Se Yoon a son or son-in-law? It's really confusing.
Why do YOU need to worry about something like that?
Aren't you worried then?
I will leave first.
You barely ate last night's dinner too.
I have no appetite.
I will be back.
Aigoo.
Of course at this juncture would any food go down his throat?
Aigoo, how nicely this family situation is becoming.
Aigoo.
My wife, I'm finding out that she's a sleepyhead.
I already did my morning exercise and washed my face.
I was tossing and turning all night because I couldn't fall asleep. I think I finally fell asleep at dawn.
Did you sleep well Se Yoon?
Of course, as soon as I laid my head on the floor, I fell asleep soundly.
I saved some warm water for you to wash up. I'll help you.
Wait one moment.
For today, I'll give you a full service.
Full service?
I'll wash your face.
That's alright.
What's alright?
Only if you marry me, I won't let you get a drop of water on your hands.
Cleaning, doing laundry, washing dishes...
I'll do everything.
you're lying.
What do you mean I'm lying?
You just have to trust me.
That's alright.
I'll do it.
Ah... You really don't listen to me well.
Even before marrying, you don't listen to your husband very well. After marrying, won't you just nag and torment me?
What?
So please listen to your husband, my dear wife.
It's me, Ahjumma.
Seul Hong's mom.
I think Sul Joo has turned off her cell phone, that's why I'm calling her at home.
Can I talk to Sul Joo?
Madam is not awake yet.
What time is it now...?
She drank late into the night.
I understand Ahjumma.
Please tell her that she must call me when she wakes up.
Did you call Unni, Sul Joo?
I think she's sleeping in after drinking late into the night.
Figures.
If the wind blows wouldn't it blow away, if grabbed wouldn't it break, (cared for as if one was fragile)
how much she devoted herself to Se Yoon.
To say it in a word, it's a sitting duck
Just in case, please don't misunderstand me, ok?
You know I'm a witness who's watched them for 30 years.
Seol Joo really did devote all to Se Yoon.
Things that Seol Joo did for Se Yoon... I couldn't do 1/100th or 1/1000th of that for my Soo Rung.
But,
I don't mean
to say that Sul Joo did a good thing..
I know.
I won't misunderstand, so don't worry.
♫ I can't love you?♫ I can't get closer to you?
Where are we?♫ Do we grow apart if I love you?
We don't have much time left until the wedding ceremony. We have to get ready fast.
Get ready for what?
Are you going to get married like that?
♫ I'm crying and waiting.
♫ Living like this isn't living.
This would look good on you.
♫ My longing for you becomes unbearable.♫ I can't bear to forget you.
♫ I still only
Do you like it?♫ love you.
♫ I'll love you as long as I live.
I can't think!
Sit down, please.
My blood feels like it's getting dried up. How can I just sit around?
What about Joo Ri?
I don't know. She didn't even come to work?
That... rotten...
She gulped down the company with one swallow. Now, she's not even coming to work?
Not long ago, I was a puppet president. You applauded Joo Ri that she is taking care of everything for the company.
Aren't you disliking her too much?
They say even the king of Hades closes one eye in front of money.
She almost ruined the company that was running well, do you think I'd look at her kindly?
How did it go?
I'm sorry President.
LK Investment Firm also refused to lend the capital
just now
we've received a notification that the company is in preliminary bankruptcy.
What...rotten...h
Please notify the creditors immediately. We have to avoid the final bankruptcy.
In this kind of situation, there will be unreasonable demands from the creditors side.
We can't idly sit by and watch when the entire Geum Yoong company's employees might lose their jobs in a split moment.
The restructuring are debt-redemption plans have been readied, right?
Yes.
But...
the stockholders seem to be very nervous.
I'll give my life not to get delisted, so tell them not to worry.
Our Geum Young food will not die this easily.
Ok, I will catch a taxi now so just wait a bit.
Aigoo, where are you going?
I'm going to take a ride to Seong Gook Dong.
Why? Did something happen to Sul Joo?
I got a call form the ajumma there, and it feels weird.
What is weird?
She locked the door and there's been no sound from within it
somehow feels like a bad omen.
Ah...then
I'm worried so if anything happened call me.
Ok.
I'm sure nothing bad will happen.
right about now...
would the ceremony for the kids have begun?
Congratulations on getting married Chae Won.
You must be busy, thank you for coming.
Days like today is when we play hooky.
You look very beautiful.
Doesn't she?
Oh boy. Your condition is more serious then I thought (more deeply in love with her so brags about her).
What about my brother-in-law?
He went inside the church.
I'll be going inside.
Thank you.
For trusting me and being courageous..
I'll make it, so that it'll be easy to say "I'm glad I listened to him."
The Minister wants to start the ring exchange. I'll be right back.
Is it still...ajumma?
Yes.
Sul Joo, I came.
Are you still sleeping?
Open the door Sul Joo!
Something doesn't seem right.
You have a key right?
Yes.
Sul Joo?
Sul Joo? Sul Joo?
Why is she like this?
What is that?
What kind of medicine is that?
That is... It looks like anti-anxiety medication that madam always takes.
It looks like she took them while drinking.
Sul Joo? Wake up. Sul Joo?
Sul Joo. Come to your senses! Sul Joo!
Hey! Come to your senses!
You should call your mother before the wedding starts.
She must be very worried. Call her.
I'll call her when it ends.
Ok.
Are you guys all prepared?
Yes, Pastor.
I heard from Grandfather.
I will accept the decision you've both made.
Have a beautiful and nice,
wedding ceremony and come back, alright?
Also, tell Se Yoon,
that mom sends her congratulation.
I really wanted to see the wedding between you two.
I love you, my daughter.
and also son.
Chae Won!
Come Quickly, we're starting.
Ok, I'm coming.
We'll now start the wedding ceremony for the groom, Lee Se Yoon, and the bride, Min Chae Won.
Groom, enter.
Wow, looking cool.
Next, the bride will enter.
Bride, enter.
The bride will enter.
Bride come in.
I'll go outside and check.
I don't see the bride.
Chae Won! Chae Won!
Where are you?
The wedding started.
Just where are you?
Answer me!
Hello?
Chae Won?
Where are you right now?
I'm asking where you are.
Se Yoon.
Mom went to the emergency room in an ambulance.
They said she's in critical condition.
What did you say?
My aunt just called me and your mom...
They said she took some medication.
Hurry up and go back to Seoul.
Chae Won.
She must have been having such a hard time.
How can I go through with this wedding?
Do you think we'll be happy if we get married?
I can't.
Where are you?
First lets meet and talk.
I'm going to Seoul right now,
so you should see your mom, hurry.
Chae Won? Chae Won?
Chae Won?
♫ In your eyes...
♫ If I could see you...
♫ Me, who's in your eyes...
♫ If I could see myself again...
♫ In your mind...
♫ I'm right here.
♫ If I could only go back
♫ into your heart again...
♫ In your eyes...
Chae Won's mom.
What about Sul Joo?
She's still in there.
How is the patient, doctor?
If she had come later then we would have had a big problem.
When she arrived at the hospital, her breathing was about to stop.
So, she's alright right now?
She's over the hump, but she needs complete rest.
The patient has been misusing her medicine.
If she wants to stop using medicine, she needs to be treated in the hospital for a while.
Yes, you've worked really hard doctor. Thank you.
Sul Joo?
The housekeeper said that Se Yoon's father also left the house yesterday.
What?
The luckiest wife in all of Korea...
How could this have happened?
Is anyone home?
What brings you here?
Is Gong Kang Sook here?
I'm Gong Kang Sook.
I came to deliver a pot of flowers.
What is this about?
Who sent it?
By any chance, Kang Bong Soo?
Ok,
That's fine.
Ok then, I'll be leaving.
Bye.
Maybe because he's a successful man, his scale is different.
Instead of a few roses, he gives me a huge pot of flowers.
There's even a card.
He's very attentive.
I happened to go by a flower shop. I thought the bright flowers look like you, so
I'm sending them to you.
They are azaleas.
Azaleas symbolize first love.
First love.
This man! Why is he making me moved like this?
What is the occasion for the flowers?
When I saw those bright flowers as I passed by the flower shop, I thought of your wife.
Congratulations on the pregnancy.
Thank you.
But,
What kind of flower is this?
They are azaleas.
Azaleas symbolize first love.
First love?
A writer said this...
All love is first love.
The fact that you met the person and fell in love...
Definitely, that love happened for the first time in this life.
Ah... I thought I was the only romantic here.
My boss is one too!
Thank you.
Even though I may be a little awkward, there is a romantic side to me also.
Did you come all the way to my house to deliver the flowers?
Ah, I almost forgot.
Kang Jin,
I got your schedule to go on the air.
Broadcasting schedule?
Honey.
Bo Reum's mom.
Did mom go out?
No, she's watering the flowering plant.
Flowering plant?
What flowering plant?
She got it as a present from her friend.
Oh.
Tell your mom that I'm back and want her to come out.
Ok.
Wow, it's hot.
Dad says to come quickly and help him wash up.
Wash his back? What non-sense!
Tell him to take a shower.
if your heart goes that way...
without thinking...
I don't know how long it's been since I've received a present of flowers.
Thank you, Oppa.
And I didn't quite realize how Azalea blossom could be this stunning in the past.
Oppa your sincerity is
being conveyed...
Did this wife of mine get affected by heat?
what's all this fuss sending a text to a wrong person?
Oppa's sincerity is
What?
Oppa?
Isn't this cheating?
I bet my feeling has been conveyed with that text?
Oppa.
Ah, if you review the financial analysis report you will see that this situation is
not a bankruptcy in the red, but in the black.
Since it's a momentary cashflow shortage,
you the creditors could either provide the investment
or...ah...
ah...if you could extend the repayment period then
ah...I'll turn this crisis and
make into an opportunity.
There are two things our side wants.
Resignation of the entire current board of management team and,
the biggest share holder and the highest board member Ms. Bang Yong Ja will
by using privately owned assets contribution
take responsibility for the poor management.
Private assets contribution, did you say?
I understand.
If we can save the company, we will do anything.
Ah, that's enough.
President Kim Chul Kyu, step out of it.
I already transferred the shares and gave up my control so that should be enough
What do you mean, contributing privately owned assets?
Don't you think that's a bit too much.
I knew they would emerge like that.
If it wasn't for the alternative plan we've made,
with one misstep,
we could have become penny-less beggars and gotten out on the street.
What do you mean you've worked on an alternative ahead of time?
You remember she directed Hong attorney to exchange all real-estate property and the bank savings into cash.
That means we can't keep the promise we made to the creditors, isn't it?
Aigoo, aigoo, that simpleton.
Are you saying that we should give up our total assets and go out on the street?
I know what you're saying is true but...
After siphoning everything down to the last penny
and then I'm going to tell them to go take a hike.
What are they gonna do when I say I've got not a penny?!
If you think our Chae Won as a real daughter,
you won't be acting like this.
If Se Yoon is your son then of course Chae Won is also your daughter,
how can you, as if unaffected,
say "let the two marry"?
What kind of relatives does that make us?
But really to Sister in law, is Se Yoon a son or a son in law?
What good comes from revealing the fact that Se Yoon is your son?
Eventually, isn't wounding the kids the only result?
Why here?
Father, I want to go ahead and buy you clothes at least once.
I'm an old man who's headed for the Hades shortly,
clothes, what for?
Let's go inside, Father.
This one is handmade cloth.
It is the premium quality.
And this is a little lower priced Nam Huay burlap,
Chung Yang burlap, Moo Joo burlap
We also have Myung Joo and In Gyun.
Take your time looking,
and picking with the help of your daughter in law.
Father,
They say if one prepares the shroud ahead of time, one
will live for a long, long time.
Which is why we're buying them now,
instead of right now,
you're going to wear this after 20 years from now, okay?
Unexpectedly,
there are quite a variety.
Which one do you like?
This precious thing...can I receive it so shamelessly?
It's my desire, so please accept.
My thinking,
this one is good, Father.
Fabric is good and
stitches are neat, too.
That's fine.
It's all for naught when the flesh rots
There's no need to spend money on this.
Just get the least expensive.
I
have a lot of money squirreled away without Hyo Dong knowing.
Don't worry about anything.
Let's just take this one, Father.
There's no point spending money on useless things.
It's because this is the first present I am able to give you.
I want to give you the best I can.
Father,
make a promise with me.
This shroud
you have to wear it after 20 years have passed, okay?
You must.
Father, promise me.
I promise.
Who told you you can go in there?
Dad.
In your eyes, do you not see your grandfather, grandmother, mother and father?
What kind of worst behavior is this?
Is this what I taught you?
I'm sorry.
You did as you please and cause all this havoc, and you think it'll end by you just saying "I'm sorry"?
Where is Se Yoon? Why are you here alone?
We...
We didn't get married.
What?
I'm here.
Mom, I'm here.
Se Yoon is here.
Mom, you really are a scary person.
Even after you've committed such wrong,
how can you, for 30 years, hold up a front as if nothing was wrong?
Whenever I think about it, it gives me the creeps and I'm horrified.
Honestly, I can't handle seeing your face.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
For giving you a heartache,
I am really sorry.
I warmed it up, so drink some.
Thank you.
She drank alcohol with valium, so
she's gone into a shock.
Her stomach was pumped and is receiving an emergency care,
so no need to worry too much.
Not having the wedding because the bride disappeared..
Se Yoon must have been really surprised.
I'm..
an idiot, aren't I?
I was really just going to close my eyes,
and think only about me and Se Yoon.
But I couldn't.
I must really be an idiot.
It's not because your an idiot.
My daughter's heart is just,
really soft and kind.
That's why.
Se Yoon.
Must have been really hurt and disappointed.
When I think about it,
My chest hurts so much I feel like I'll die.
I know what you mean.
Our Se Yoon.
Se Yoon must really be suffering and hurting.
I'm sorry, Chae Won. I'm sorry.
Mom is really sorry.
Are you feeling better?
You...
How did you get here?
What about the wedding?
Did it go well?
What about Chae Won?
Where..
is Chae Won?
The wedding,
Didn't happen.
What?
Aah.
Are you ok, mom?
Here, drink this medicine.
Chae Won! Chae Won!
There's a big problem.
What's going on so early in the morning.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Why, What's wrong?
What's wrong Hyung?
Dad what's wrong? What happened?
Your mom...Your mom..
What about Chae Won's mom?
She left home.
What?!?!
Dad, what do you mean she left home?
She left divorce papers and left without a word.
What is this?
Your right. These are Divorce papers.
Why would she divorce you so suddenly?
Dad? Dad?
She appeared to be normal last night. Why the divorce all of a sudden?
What on earth is this?
Mom? Mom?
Se Yoon!
Mom...
Mom has left home.
What did you say?
She turned off her phone so there is no way to contact her.
I was wondering if she had contacted you.
If she calls me, I'll have my secretary to call you.
What?
Besides meeting for work,
I hope there won't be any meetings for personal reasons.