Miko...
Miko, please protect this child.
Miyu.
Has your sister come back yet?
I had a bad dream last night.
I felt paralyzed when I
first woke up this morning.
Miyu may have been killed...
Don't say such things.
It was just a dream.
I hope so.
I will make sure tonight.
Making sure means you will do...
...what, exactly?
Please, Shizuka.
Why are you laughing?
I'm relieved.
Finally, Miko is back
to her old self again.
I can't use Ninjutsu, but
I always want to help you.
We are friends.
Thats right.
I may look unreliable, but
I will do my best for Miko.
Finally, it will be born.
I've looked forward to this moment.
Come here...
Whats that?
This way...
...come here.
Thats right, go up.
This way...
Yes, this way.
Come here.
I will make you happy...
...come here.
Rape the woman...
Now.
Miyu, why?
What are you doing here?
Where are you from?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
This child is...
...cursed by birth.
Who are you?
One of the Miroku Clan...
...Hiro.
The Miroku Clan? Don't lie.
Miyu and I are the only survivors.
The Miroku Clan has
scattered nationwide...
...in order to prepare for the
final battle with the Sex Fiends.
Why did you try to kill her?
Miyu sent a telepathic
message when she died.
She told me to kill her.
Stab me.
My mission is only to kill her...
...but I can't do it right now.
Because I'm not sure
why I have to kill her.
Whats your name?
Miyabi.
I'm Miko.
Miko?
You aren't strong
enough to win, Miroku Clan.
Increase the number of your friends.
Make the girl awaken
and open the way for us.
That girl, Miyabi, is the key
to connect our world with yours.
If the two worlds connect, I
will give you limitless power.
It is a power that can't
be had in your world.
Go!
Run, or we'll be late.
Hurry up.
What happened to your sister?
I think she was killed.
Oh, God...
This is our destiny.
So...
I don't like it.
Thank you.
I'll definitely protect Miko.
So, please don't die.
Bido, its a strange name.
Hello, home delivery service.
Shit, isn't anyone around?
Hello, I'm from a home delivery service.
Good afternoon,
I'm from Smile Delivery.
Can I get your stamp?
I need your stamp here.
If you don't have
one, a signature is fine.
Good old Bido!
You are from the Bido family, the
strongest family in the Miroku Clan.
Who are you?
My name is Yaku,
one of the Miroku Clan.
For me, babies stop crying, old men get
hard, and young boys come five times.
Nice to meet you.
You don't trust me.
Why not look at my family emblem?
Yoo hoo!
Suiton magic.
I heard that you use
Suiton magic in the water.
No, no, no, the Amateur
Clan doesn't know anything.
In the context of Sexual Magic...
...the man inserts.
The woman's moaning
makes him even harder.
No, no, no, stop!
Finally, the man reaches the
point of no return and almost comes.
At that moment...
...you suck his semen and at
the same time inject a lethal curse.
Sounds horrific.
Suck and kill, we call it Suiton Magic.
Are you serious?
Yaku, when you
came, was anyone here?
No, I thought I was just lucky
because the front door was open.
The girl was kidnapped.
Oh!
Miko, ask me
anything If you need me.
Me too.
Thank you.
Hey, Yaku...
...please teach me how
to use Sexual Magic sometime.
If you learn it, you will enjoy
making love repeatedly, without tiering.
See you.
Shall I see you home?
No thank you, I'm fine.
Its good for you that Yaku came.
Right?
She will help you to
forget your sadness.
She's just so boisterous.
See you.
I'll take off.
Good bye.
What are you doing?
I have to find the
girl I was talking about.
I have a feeling that she has
something to do with the Sex Fiends.
Is that so?
What do you have in your hand?
Nothing special.
Don't get on my nerves.
Did you notice?
This is a great chance!
What do you think about this?
Its impossible to find them by praying.
Can you find them?
You haven't changed.
Yaku, you haven't told her anything...
...have you?
Because you were
talking about a camp-fire...
...l'm in the mood to roast
potatoes and marshmallows.
Do you know her?
She's a bitch.
She has a short
temper and is very bossy.
Seems that she is better than you.
Tell me...
How many Miroku families are there?
Three.
We will locate her with this.
Is your purpose to find and kill her?
Don't move.
If you move, they will eat your eyeballs.
Don't make a noise.
Looks like they like you.
Why don't you enjoy it?
You can enjoy sex you
have never before experienced.
You are dripping all over.
Are you feeling good?
The time has come to finish.
If she dies, it all comes to nothing.
I will feel your body all over.
Miyu and I are
cousins, and the same age.
We grew up like sisters...
...before you were born.
I haven't seen her
since I left the Miroku village.
She was kind, but also
stubborn and she never cried.
Miko, you should
cry when you feel pain.
This will be tough...
...but we have to
win the battle for Miyu.
You are easily defeated.
Are you really a match for me?
I feel very good right now.
My body is filled with power.
I feel that I could do anything.
So you say, but it seems like
you can't fight without hiding.
Why don't you come out
and fight fair and square?
Its a shame that such a legendary
clan can't strike back, isn't it?
Miko Bido...
I can take care of you by myself.
Miko, leave it to me and go ahead.
Yaku, lets go.
Yes.
I am your opponent.
Misaki, Shizuka!
You fell for my trick.
What?
You are ambitious.
Let me see how
delicious a Miroku woman is.
Misaki...
How do you feel?
Soon, the snake's poison will stimulate
you all over, and you will lose control.
Let them enjoy you for a while...
...until you lose your mind.
This girl will awake soon.
If the girl wakes up
and becomes a Sex Fiend...
...the door to the Realm
of the Sex Fiends will open.
She will be the strongest Sex
Fiend, descended from your family.
Misaki!
No!
...almost coming.
Once you start moaning,
you can't stop, can you?
The ecstasy they
give you will be limitless.
Its a wonderfully muscular vagina.
Good old Miroku Clan!
Miroku Sex Magic, Hydrochloric Hell!
When I go into
ecstasy, I secrete a strong acid.
You used a dirty trick!
You melted my
most important member!
Lmportant member?
You have no right to say that
because you didn't make me come.
Wait, come back.
You must not go to such a place.
I'm not your enemy.
Please come back.
You are a human being.
You shouldn't become a sex fiend.
You have the same blood as we have.
Wait...
Don't take the girl.
Hiro!
Miko.
Please protect the girl.
The door is opened.
It means we can enter anywhere.
Miroku Clan, get ready to
put your lives on the line.
I will finish you.
I will give these two
our power in our world.
Then, your end will come.
Look forward to the next time we meet.
Hiro.
Hiro...
Miko...
Miko, you are right.
That girl has the blood
of the Miroku Clan in her.
She won't become a Sex Fiend easily.
Hiro, don't die, Hiro.
The special board I gave
you, gather our comrades by it...
...with the girl.
Now what?
I have no idea.
Even though its not your strong point...
Use your head.
The girl is...
...here.
I will go see Miyu first.
Hiro!
Hiro, don't die, Hiro.
Hiro.